<root>
    <component name="TCPU" version="请自行修改"></component>
    <default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
    <language code="2052" name="zh-cn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新主要针对系统进行了优化，推荐您进行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="辅助功能">
             <feature>•  新增敲击背部两次启动指定快捷功能，帮您快速开启 Google 助理、录音机、计时器等应用。操作路径：设置 > 辅助功能 > 快捷启动及手势 > 敲击背部两次</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="相机">
             <feature>•  优化部分场景相机拍摄效果</feature>
             <feature>•  提升部分场景相机使用稳定性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="稳定性">
             <feature>•  提升系统稳定性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="性能">
             <feature>•  优化系统性能</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安全补丁">
             <feature>•  合入安卓 2025 年 10 月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="更新注意事项" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份
2. 更多精彩功能介绍，请访问“玩机技巧”应用
3. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="en-us">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Dear user, this update mainly enhances the system performance. Update to enjoy the improvements</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Accessibility features">
             <feature>• Double-tap the back to launch a specific shortcut, enabling quick access to Google Assistant, Recorder, Timer, and other apps. Try it out by going to: Settings > Accessibility features > Shortcuts &amp; gestures > Double back-tap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Camera">
             <feature>• Optimizes the shooting effect of Camera in some scenarios</feature>
             <feature>• Enhances the stability of Camera in some scenarios</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stability">
             <feature>• Improves the system stability</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Performance">
             <feature>• Improves the system performance</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Security patch">
             <feature>• Android security patch (Oct 2025) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about Honor Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating
2. Discover more information on product features in Tips
3. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling Honor service hotline or visiting Honor customer service center</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1118" name="am-ET">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ ይህ ዝማኔ በዋነኛነት የስርዓቱን አፈጻጸም ያሻሽላል። በማሻሻያዎቹ ለመደሰት ያዘምኑ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="የተደራሽነት ባህሪያት">
             <feature>• የተወሰነ አቋራጭ ለማስጀመር ጀርባውን ሁለቴ መታ ያድርጉት፣ በዚህም የGoogle ረዳት፣ የድምጽ መቅጃ፣ የሰዓት ቆጣሪ እና የሌሎች መተግበሪያዎች ፈጣን መዳረሻን ስራ ያስጀምራሉ። ወደዚህ በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > የተደራሽነት ባህሪያት > አቋራጮች እና የጣት ምልክቶች > ጀርባን ሁለቴ መታ ማድረግ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ካሜራ">
             <feature>• በአንዳንድ ሁኔታዎች ላይ የካሜራ ማንሳት ተጽዕኖውን ያተባል</feature>
             <feature>• በአንዳንድ ሁኔታዎች የካሜራ መረጋጋትን ያሻሽላል</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="መረጋጋት">
             <feature>• የስርዓቱን እርጋታ ያሻሽላል</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="አፈጻጸም">
             <feature>• የስርዓቱን አፈጻጸም ያሻሽላል</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="የደህንነት መጠገኛ">
             <feature>• የአንድሮይድ የደህንነት መጠገኛ (ኦክቶበር 2025) ለስርዓት ደህንነት ተካትቷል። ስለHonor ደህንነት ዝማኔዎች ተጨማሪ መረጃ ለማግኘት እባክዎ የእኛን ድረ-ገጽ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10 ይጎብኙ</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ማስታወሻዎች" type="end">
             <feature>1. ይህን ዝማኔ መጫን በእርስዎ የግል ውሂብ ላይ ተጽዕኖ አያሳርፍም፣ ነገር ግን አሁንም ከማዘመንዎ በፊት የውሂብዎን መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ ይመከራል
2. በጠቃሚ ምክሮች ውስጥ ስለምርት ባህሪያት ተጨማሪ መረጃ ያግኙ
3. በዝማኔው ወቅት ምንም አይነት ችግር ካጋጠምዎት ወደ የHonor አገልግሎት ቀጥታ መስመር በመደወል ወይም የHonor የደንበኛ የአገልግሎት ማዕከልን በመጎብኘት የእኛን እርዳታ ማግኘት ይችላሉ።</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="3073" name="ar-eg">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، يحسّن هذا التحديث أداء النظام بشكل أساسي. للاستمتاع بالتحسينات، ما عليك سوى التحديث</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ميزات إمكانية الوصول">
             <feature>• اضغط مرتين على الجزء الخلفي لتشغيل اختصار معين، مما يتيح الوصول السريع إلى مساعد جوجل ومسجل الصوت والمؤقت بالإضافة إلى تطبيقات أخرى. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > ميزات إمكانية الوصول > الاختصارات والإيماءات > الضغط مرتين على الجزء الخلفي</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="الكاميرا">
             <feature>• يحسّن تأثير التصوير بالكاميرا في بعض السيناريوهات</feature>
             <feature>• يحسّن استقرار الكاميرا في بعض السيناريوهات</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="الاستقرار">
             <feature>• يحسّن استقرار النظام</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="الأداء">
             <feature>• يحسّن أداء النظام</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="تصحيح الأمان">
             <feature>• تم تضمين تصحيح أمان أندرويد (أكتوبر 2025) لأمان النظام. لمزيد من المعلومات حول تحديثات الأمان في Honor، يرجى زيارة موقعنا على الويب https://www.honor.com/ae-ar/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ملاحظات" type="end">
             <feature>1. لن يؤثر تثبيت هذا التحديث على بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن لا يزال من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية لبياناتك قبل التحديث
2. اكتشف المزيد من المعلومات حول ميزات المنتج في تطبيق التلميحات
3. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيمكنك الحصول على مساعدتنا عن طريق الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة عملاء Honor أو زيارة مركز خدمة عملاء Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1101" name="as-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই আপডেটটোৱে মূলতঃ ছিষ্টেমৰ কাৰ্যদক্ষতা উন্নত কৰে। উন্নতিসমূহৰ আনন্দ ল'বলৈ আপডেট কৰক</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="প্ৰৱেশযোগ্যতা ফিচাৰসমূহ">
             <feature>• এটা নিৰ্দিষ্ট চমুপথ প্ৰাৰম্ভ কৰিবলৈ পিছফালে দুবাৰ-টিপক, যিয়ে Google Assistant, ৰেকৰ্ডাৰ, টাইমাৰ আৰু অন্য এপ্প্‌সমূহলৈ দ্ৰুত প্ৰৱেশ সক্ষম কৰে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াক ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ছেটিংছ > প্ৰৱেশযোগ্যতা ফিচাৰসমূহ > চমুপথ আৰু ভঙ্গিমাসমূহ > পিছফালে দুবাৰ টিপক</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="কেমেৰা">
             <feature>• কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত কেমেৰাৰ শ্বুটিঙৰ প্ৰভাৱ অনুকূলন কৰে</feature>
             <feature>• কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত কেমেৰাৰ স্থিৰতা উন্নত কৰে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="স্থিৰতা">
             <feature>• ছিষ্টেমৰ স্থিৰতা উন্নত কৰে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="কাৰ্যদক্ষতা">
             <feature>• ছিষ্টেমৰ কাৰ্যদক্ষতা উন্নত কৰে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ">
             <feature>• ছিষ্টেমৰ নিৰাপত্তাৰ বাবে Android নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ (অক্টোবৰ 2025) অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হৈছে। Honor নিৰাপত্তা আপডেটৰ বিষয়ে অধিক তথ্যৰ বাবে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি আমাৰ ৱেবছাইট দৰ্শন কৰক: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="টোকাসমূহ" type="end">
             <feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটাত প্ৰভাৱ নপৰিব, কিন্তু আপডেট কৰাৰ পূৰ্বে আপোনাৰ ডাটাৰ বেক আপ ল'বলৈ এতিয়াও পৰামৰ্শ দিয়া হয়
2. আভাসত প্ৰ'ডাক্টৰ ফিচাৰসমূহৰ ওপৰত অধিক তথ্য অনুসন্ধান কৰক
3. আপুনি আপডেটৰ সময়ত কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হ'লে, আপুনি Honor সেৱা হটলাইনত কল কৰি বা Honor গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ গৈ সহায় লাভ কৰিব পাৰে।</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1068" name="az-az">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, bu yeniləmə əsasən sistemin performansını artırır. Təkmilləşdirmələrdən yararlanmaq üçün yeniləyin</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Xüsusi imkanlar xüsusiyyətləri">
             <feature>• Google Yardımçı, Səsyazan, Saniyəölçən və digər proqramlara sürətli giriş təmin etmək məqsədilə xüsusi qısayolu aktivləşdirmək üçün arxa tərəfə iki dəfə toxunun. Buraya keçərək sınayın: Parametrlər > Xüsusi imkanlar xüsusiyyətləri > Qısayollar və jestlər > Arxa tərəfə iki dəfə toxunun</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Bəzi ssenarilərdə Kameranın çəkiliş effektini optimallaşdırır</feature>
             <feature>• Bəzi ssenarilərdə Kameranın sabitliyini artırır</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabillik">
             <feature>• Sistemin sabitliyini yaxşılaşdırır</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Məhsuldarlıq">
             <feature>• Sistemin performansını yaxşılaşdırır</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Təhlükəsizlik paketi">
             <feature>• Sistem təhlükəsizliyi üçün Android təhlükəsizlik paketi (oktyabr 2025-ci il) daxil edilib. Honor Təhlükəsizlik yeniləmələri haqqında ətraflı məlumat üçün veb-saytımıza daxil olun: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Qeydlər" type="end">
             <feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınıza təsir etməyəcək, lakin yenə də yeniləməmişdən əvvəl verilənlərin ehtiyat nüsxəsini çıxarmaq tövsiyə olunur
2. İpuclarında məhsul xüsusiyyətləri haqqında daha çox məlumat əldə edin
3. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlə qarşılaşsanız, Honor xidməti qaynar xəttinə zəng edərək və ya Honor Müştəriyə Xidmət Mərkəzinə gedərək yardım ala bilərsiniz.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="jv-id">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran iki utamane ningkatake kinerja sistem. Anyarake kanggo ngrasakake pangapikane</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fitur aksesibilitas">
             <feature>• Tutul kaping pindho bagean mburi kanggo ngluncurake trabasan tertamtu, sing ngaktifake akses cepet menyang Asisten Google, Perekam, Timer, lan apl liyane. Coba kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Fitur aksesibilitas > Trabasan &amp; obahan > Tutul kaping pindho bagean mburi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Ngoptimalake efek ngrekam Kamera ing sawetara skenario</feature>
             <feature>• Ningkatake stabilitas Kamera ing sawetara skenario</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitas">
             <feature>• Ngapikake stabilitas sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kinerja">
             <feature>• Ngapikake kinerja sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch keamanan">
             <feature>• Patch Keamanan Android (Okt 2025) wis digabungake kanggo keamanan sistem. Kanggo mangerteni informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan panganyaran Keamanan Honor, bukak situs web kita https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Cathetan" type="end">
             <feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mengaruhi data pribadi sampeyan, nanging nggawe serep data dhisik tetep disaranake sadurunge nganyarake
2. Temokake informasi liyane babagan fitur prodhuk ing Tips
3. Yen ana masalah sajrone panganyaran, sampeyan bisa entuk bantuan kita kanthi nelpon hotline layanan Honor utawa nekani Pusat Layanan Pelanggan Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2074" name="sr-rs">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se unapređuju performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u unapređenjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkcije pristupačnosti">
             <feature>• Dvaput dodirnite poleđinu da biste pokrenuli određenu prečicu, omogućavajući brzi pristup Google pomoćniku, Snimaču zvuka, Tajmeru i drugim aplikacijama. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići u opciju: Podešavanja > Funkcije pristupačnosti > Prečice i pokreti > Dvostruki dodir zadnjeg dela uređaja</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Optimizuje učinak snimanja Kamere u pojedinim situacijama</feature>
             <feature>• Povećava stabilnost Kamere u nekim situacijama</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Poboljšava stabilnost sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Učinak">
             <feature>• Poboljšava performanse sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezbednosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (oktobar 2025.) radi bezbednosti sistema. Za još informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima kompanije Honor, posetite naš veb-sajt https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zabeleške" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka pre ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o karakteristikama proizvoda u odeljku Saveti
3. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, možete da dobijete našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati dežurnu liniju Honor servisa ili posetiti Centar za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1059" name="be-by">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта абнаўленне ў асноўным паляпшае прадукцыйнасць сістэмы. Каб палепшыць уражанні ад выкарыстання, устанавіце абнаўленне</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Функцыі спецыяльных магчымасцей">
             <feature>• Двойчы краніце заднюю панэль для запуску канкрэтнага ярлыка, які падтрымлівае хуткі доступ да Памочніка Google, Дыктафона, Таймера і іншых праграм. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню: Налады > Функцыі спецыяльных магчымасцей > Ярлыкі і жэсты > Двайны дотык да задняй панэлі</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Камера">
             <feature>• Аптымізаваны эфект здымкі Камерай у некаторых сцэнарыях</feature>
             <feature>• Палепшана стабільнасць Камеры ў некаторых сцэнарыях</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Устойлівасць">
             <feature>• Павышана стабільнасць сістэмы</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Прадукцыйнасць">
             <feature>• Павышана прадукцыйнасць сістэмы</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Выпраўленне сістэмы бяспекі">
             <feature>• Для павышэння бяспекі сістэмы ўключана выпраўленне функцый бяспекі Android (кастрычнік 2025 г.). Больш інфармацыі аб абнаўленні сістэмы бяспекі Honor можна знайсці на нашым афіцыйным вэб-сайце: https://www.honor.com/by/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Нататкі" type="end">
             <feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не закране вашы асабістыя даныя. Тым не менш рэкамендуецца стварыць рэзервовую копію даных перад абнаўленнем
2. Больш падрабязная інфармацыя аб характарыстыках прадукту даступная ў Падказках
3. Пры ўзнікненні праблем падчас абнаўлення вы можаце атрымаць нашу дапамогу, патэлефанаваўшы на гарачую лінію службы падтрымкі кліентаў Honor або наведаўшы цэнтр абслугоўвання кліентаў Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1026" name="bg-bg">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Уважаеми потребители, тази актуализация подобрява основно ефективността на системата. Актуализирайте, за да се насладите на подобренията</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Функции за достъпност">
             <feature>• Докоснете двукратно, за да стартирате конкретен пряк път, който позволява бърз достъп до Google Асистент, Звукозапис, Таймер и други приложения. Изпробвайте го, като отидете на: Настройки > Функции за достъпност > Преки пътища и жестове > Двукратно докосване отзад</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Камера">
             <feature>• Оптимизира ефекта на заснемане на „Камера“ в някои ситуации</feature>
             <feature>• Подобрява стабилността на „Камера“ в някои ситуации</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Стабилност">
             <feature>• Подобрява стабилността на системата</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ефективност">
             <feature>• Подобрява ефективността на системата</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Корекция за сигурност">
             <feature>• Корекцията за сигурност на Android (октомври 2025 г.) е включена за защита на системата. За още информация относно актуализациите за сигурност на Honor посетете нашия уебсайт https://www.honor.com/bg/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Бележки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да се отрази на вашите лични данни, но все пак е препоръчително да архивирате данните си преди актуализиране
2. Открийте повече информация за характеристиките на продукта в „Съвети“
3. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализацията, можете да получите нашата помощ, като се обадите на горещата линия за обслужване на Honor или посетите сервизния център за клиенти на Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2117" name="bn-bd">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই আপডেটটি মূলত সিস্টেমের কর্মক্ষমতা বাড়ায়। উন্নতি উপভোগ করতে আপডেট করুন</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="প্রবেশযোগ্যতার বৈশিষ্ট্যগুলি">
             <feature>• একটি নির্দিষ্ট শর্টকাট চালু করতে পিছনে দুবার ট্যাপ করুন, যা Google অ্যাসিস্ট্যান্ট, রেকর্ডার, টাইমার এবং অন্যান্য অ্যাপে কুইক অ্যাক্সেস দেয়। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > প্রবেশযোগ্যতার বৈশিষ্ট্যগুলি > শর্টকার্ট ও জেশ্চারগুলি > পিছনে দুবার ট্যাপ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ক্যামেরা">
             <feature>• কিছু পরিস্থিতিতে ক্যামেরার শুটিং এফেক্ট অপ্টিমাইজ করে</feature>
             <feature>• কিছু পরিস্থিতিতে ক্যামেরার স্থিতিশীলতা বাড়ায়</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="স্থিতিশীলতা">
             <feature>• সিস্টেমের স্থিতিশীলতা উন্নত করে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="পারফরম্যান্স">
             <feature>• সিস্টেমের কর্মক্ষমতা উন্নত করে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ">
             <feature>• সিস্টেমের নিরাপত্তার জন্য Android নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ (অক্টোবর 2025) অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে। Honor-এর নিরাপত্তা আপডেটগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্যের জন্য, আমাদের ওয়েবসাইট দেখুন https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="নোট" type="end">
             <feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে তা আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটাকে প্রভাবিত করবে না, তবুও আপডেট করার আগে আপনার ডেটা ব্যাক আপ করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়
2. পরামর্শ-এ পণ্যের ফিচাতগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্য জানুন
3. আপডেট হওয়ার সময় আপনি কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে Honor সেবা হটলাইনে কল করে বা Honor গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে গিয়ে আমাদের সহায়তা পেতে পারেন।</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1105" name="bo-cn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནི་གཙོ་བོ་རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ལ་དམིགས་ནས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུའི་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="རམ་འདེགས་ཀྱི་རྩོལ་ནུས་">
             <feature>• རྒྱབ་ཁུལ་ལ་ཐེངས་གཉིས་བརྡབས་ནས་ངེས་གཏན་གྱི་མྱུར་བདེའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་འགོ་སློང་བ་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་ Google ལག་རོགས་དང་སྒྲ་ཕབ་འཕྲུལ་ཆས། དུས་བརྩི་ཆས་སོགས་ཀྱི་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་མགྱོགས་མྱུར་གྱིས་འགོ་སློང་བར་རོགས་རམ་བྱེད། བཀོལ་སྤྱོད་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་རམ་འདེགས་ཀྱི་རྩོལ་ནུས། དེ་ནས་མྱུར་ཐབས་ཁ་འབྱེད་པ་དང་ལག་བརྡ། དེ་ནས་རྒྱབ་ཁུལ་ལ་ཐེངས་གཉིས་རྡེབ་པ།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="པར་ཆས།">
             <feature>• བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་པར་ཆས་ཀྱི་བརྙན་ལེན་ཁྱད་ནུས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
             <feature>• བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་པར་ཆས་བེད་སྤྱོད་པའི་བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་ཡོད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན།">
             <feature>• རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་ཡོད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="གཤིས་ནུས།">
             <feature>• རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་གཤིས་ནུས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ།">
             <feature>• ཨན་སྒྲོའི་ 2025 ལོའི་ཟླ་བ་ 10 བའི་བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདྲེས་འཇུག་བྱས་ཏེ། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་སྟོབས་སྒྱུར་གཏོང་། རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉེན་ཆས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནང་དོན་སྐོར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ། རུང་ཡོའོ་གཞུང་ཕྱོགས་དྲ་ཚིགས་ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/10 ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
             <feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གཞི་གྲངས་སུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་སྔོན་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. དེ་ལས་མང་བའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་ལེགས་པོའི་ངོ་སྤྲོད་ཐད་ཁ་པར་རྩེ་བའི་ལག་རྩལ་གྱི་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱ་རོགས།
3. གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་པའི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད་དུ། གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ། ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་མཁོ་མཁན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་ཕེབས་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་འཚོལ་རོགས།</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="5146" name="bs-ba">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo ažuriranje uglavnom poboljšava performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da uživate u poboljšanjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkcije za pristupačnost">
             <feature>• Dvaput dodirnite zadnju stranu da pokrenete određenu prečicu i omogućite brz pristup Google pomoćniku, Snimaču zvuka, Tajmeru i drugim aplikacijama. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u opciju: Postavke > Funkcije za pristupačnost > Kratice i geste > Dvostruki dodir stražnjeg dijela uređaja</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fotoaparat">
             <feature>• Optimizira efekat snimanja Fotoaparata u određenim scenarijima</feature>
             <feature>• Poboljšava stabilnost Fotoaparata u nekim scenarijima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Poboljšava stabilnost sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Performanse">
             <feature>• Poboljšava performanse sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sigurnosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Ugrađena je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (oktobar 2025.) radi sigurnosti sistema. Više informacija o Honor sigurnosnim ažuriranjima potražite na našoj web lokaciji https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Bilješke" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja ne utiče na lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o funkcijama proizvoda u Savjetima
3. Ako otkrijete bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete dobiti našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati dežurnu liniju usluge Honor ili posjetiti Centar za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1027" name="ca-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització millora principalment el rendiment del sistema. Actualitzeu-la per gaudir de les millores</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funcions d'accessibilitat">
             <feature>• Feu un doble toc al darrere per iniciar una drecera específica, fet que habilita accés ràpid a Google Assistant, Gravadora, Temporitzador i altres aplicacions. Per provar-ho, aneu a Configuració > Funcions d'accessibilitat > Dreceres i gestos > Fer doble toc al darrere</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Càmera">
             <feature>• Optimitza l'efecte de captura de la Càmera en determinades situacions</feature>
             <feature>• Millora l'estabilitat de la Càmera en determinades situacions</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilitat">
             <feature>• Millora l'estabilitat del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Rendiment">
             <feature>• Millora el rendiment del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pedaç de seguretat">
             <feature>S'ha incorporat el pedaç de seguretat d'Android (octubre del 2025) per garantir la seguretat del sistema. Per obtenir més informació sobre les actualitzacions de seguretat d'Honor, consulteu el nostre lloc web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. El fet d'instal·lar aquesta actualització no afectarà les vostres dades personals, però es recomana fer una còpia de seguretat de les dades abans d'iniciar l'actualització
2. Descobriu més informació sobre les funcions del producte a Suggeriments
3. Si teniu algun problema durant l'actualització, truqueu a la línia directa de servei d'Honor o visiteu el Centre de serveis del client Honor per obtenir ajuda.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1029" name="cs-cz">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Vážený uživateli, tato aktualizace především zvyšuje výkon systému. Aktualizujte, abyste si mohli užít vylepšení</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkce usnadnění">
             <feature>• Dvojitým klepnutím na zadní stranu spustíte konkrétního zástupce, který umožní rychlý přístup k aplikaci Google Assistant, Diktafonu, Časovači a dalším aplikacím. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce Nastavení > Funkce usnadnění > Zkratky a gesta > Dvojité klepnutí na zadní stranu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fotoaparát">
             <feature>• Optimalizuje fotografování pomocí Fotoaparátu v některých situacích.</feature>
             <feature>• Zlepšuje stabilitu Fotoaparátu v některých situacích.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilita">
             <feature>• Vylepšuje stabilitu systému.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Výkon">
             <feature>• Vylepšuje výkon systému.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Oprava zabezpečení">
             <feature>• Do systému byla začleněna bezpečnostní oprava (říjen 2025) pro systém Android pro zajištění bezpečnosti systému. Více informací o bezpečnostních aktualizacích Honor najdete na našem webu https://www.honor.com/cz/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Poznámky" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalace této aktualizace neovlivní vaše osobní data, ale přesto doporučujeme před aktualizací zálohovat data.
2. Další informace o funkcích produktu najdete v aplikaci Tipy.
3. Pokud během aktualizace narazíte na nějaké problémy, zavolejte na informační linku Honor nebo navštivte Centrum služeb zákazníkům Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1030" name="da-dk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Kære bruger. Denne opdatering forbedrer hovedsageligt systemets ydeevne. Opdater for at drage nytte af forbedringerne</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tilgængelighedsfunktioner">
             <feature>• Dobbelttryk på bagsiden for at starte en bestemt genvej, så du hurtigt kan få adgang til Google Assistent, Lydoptager, Timer og andre apps. Prøv det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Tilgængelighedsfunktioner > Genveje og gestus > Dobbelttryk på tilbage-knap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Optimerer kameraets optagelseseffekt i visse scenarier</feature>
             <feature>• Forbedrer kameraets stabilitet i visse scenarier</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitet">
             <feature>• Forbedrer systemstabiliteten</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Præstation">
             <feature>• Forbedrer systemets ydeevne</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sikkerhedspatch">
             <feature>• Android sikkerhedspatch (okt 2025) er blevet inkluderet for øget systemsikkerhed. Du kan få flere oplysninger om Honor-sikkerhedsopdateringer på vores websted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Noter" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering påvirker ikke dine personlige data, men vi anbefaler alligevel, at du sikkerhedskopierer dine data inden opdateringen
2. Få flere oplysninger om produktfunktioner i Tips
3. Hvis du oplever problemer under opdateringen, kan du få hjælp ved at ringe til Honors servicehotline eller gå til Honors kundeservicecenter.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1031" name="de-de">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung verbessert hauptsächlich die Systemleistung. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bedienungshilfen">
             <feature>• Tippen Sie doppelt auf die Rückseite, um eine bestimmte Verknüpfung zu starten, die Schnellzugriff auf Google Assistant, Rekorder, Timer und andere Apps ermöglicht. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Bedienungshilfen > Verknüpfungen und Gesten > Doppeltes Tippen auf die Rückseite</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Optimiert den Aufnahmeeffekt der Kamera in einigen Szenarien</feature>
             <feature>• Verbessert die Stabilität der Kamera in einigen Szenarien</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilität">
             <feature>• Verbessert die Systemstabilität</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Leistung">
             <feature>• Verbessert die Systemleistung</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sicherheitspatch">
             <feature>• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Okt. 2025) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die Honor Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notizen" type="end">
             <feature>1. Die Installation dieses Updates hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, es wird jedoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen
2. Entdecken Sie weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen in Tipps
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Honor-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein Honor-Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1032" name="el-gr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιώνει κυρίως την απόδοση του συστήματος. Πραγματοποιήστε ενημέρωση για να απολαύσετε τις βελτιώσεις</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Δυνατότητες προσβασιμότητας">
             <feature>• Πατήστε δύο φορές το πίσω μέρος για την εκκίνηση συγκεκριμένης συντόμευσης, κάτι που επιτρέπει τη γρήγορη πρόσβαση στο Google Assistant, την Ηχογράφηση, την Αντίστροφη μέτρηση και άλλες εφαρμογές. Δοκιμάστε το μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Δυνατότητες προσβασιμότητας > Συντομεύσεις και χειρονομίες > Διπλό πάτημα στο πίσω μέρος</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Κάμερα">
             <feature>• Βελτιστοποιεί το αποτέλεσμα λήψης της Κάμερας σε ορισμένα σενάρια</feature>
             <feature>• Βελτιώνει τη σταθερότητα της Κάμερας σε ορισμένα σενάρια</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Σταθερότητα">
             <feature>• Βελτιώνει τη σταθερότητα του συστήματος</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Απόδοση">
             <feature>• Βελτιώνει την απόδοση του συστήματος</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφάλειας">
             <feature>• Η ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας Android (Οκτώβριος 2025) ενσωματώθηκε για την ασφάλεια του συστήματος. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις ενημερώσεις της Ασφάλειας Honor, επισκεφθείτε τον ιστότοπό μας https://www.honor.com/gr/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Σημειώσεις" type="end">
             <feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα επηρεάσει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, αλλά ακόμη και έτσι συνιστάται η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας των δεδομένων σας πριν από την ενημέρωση
2. Ανακαλύψτε περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις δυνατότητες του προϊόντος στις Συμβουλές
3. Αν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, μπορείτε να λάβετε τη βοήθειά μας καλώντας την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή εξυπηρέτησης της Honor ή με επίσκεψη σε ένα Κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2057" name="en-GB">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Dear user, this update mainly enhances the system performance. Update to enjoy the improvements</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Accessibility features">
             <feature>• Double-tap the back to launch a specific shortcut, enabling quick access to Google Assistant, Recorder, Timer, and other apps. Try it out by going to: Settings > Accessibility features > Shortcuts &amp; gestures > Double back-tap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Camera">
             <feature>• Optimises the shooting effect of Camera in some scenarios</feature>
             <feature>• Enhances the stability of Camera in some scenarios</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stability">
             <feature>• Improves the system stability</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Performance">
             <feature>• Improves the system performance</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Security patch">
             <feature>• Android security patch (Oct 2025) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about Honor Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating
2. Discover more information on product features in Tips
3. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling Honor service hotline or visiting Honor Customer Service Centre.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1034" name="es-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado/a usuario/a, esta actualización mejora principalmente el rendimiento del sistema. Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funciones de accesibilidad">
             <feature>• Toque dos veces la parte posterior para iniciar un acceso directo específico, lo que permite un acceso rápido a Asistente de Google, Grabadora, Temporizador y otras aplicaciones. Pruébelo en Ajustes > Funciones de accesibilidad > Accesos directos y gestos > Doble toque en la parte posterior</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Cámara">
             <feature>• Optimiza el efecto de disparo de la cámara en determinadas situaciones</feature>
             <feature>• Mejora la estabilidad de la cámara en algunos escenarios</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilidad">
             <feature>• Mejora la estabilidad del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Rendimiento">
             <feature>• Mejora el rendimiento del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Parche de seguridad">
             <feature>• Se incorporó el parche de seguridad de Android (octubre de 2025) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de Honor, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/es/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar
2. Descubra más información sobre las características de los productos en Sugerencias
3. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, puede obtener nuestra ayuda si llama a la línea de atención al cliente de Honor o si visita el Centro de servicios de atención al cliente de Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="21514" name="es-us">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización mejora principalmente el rendimiento del sistema. Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funciones de accesibilidad">
             <feature>• Toque dos veces la parte posterior para iniciar un acceso directo específico, lo que permite acceder rápidamente al Asistente de Google, la Grabadora, el Temporizador y otras aplicaciones. Pruebe la función en: Ajustes > Funciones de accesibilidad > Accesos directos y gestos > Dar dos toques en la parte posterior</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Cámara">
             <feature>• Optimiza el rendimiento fotográfico de la Cámara en ciertos escenarios</feature>
             <feature>• Mejora la estabilidad de la cámara en determinadas situaciones</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilidad">
             <feature>• Mejora la estabilidad del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Rendimiento">
             <feature>• Mejora el rendimiento del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Parche de seguridad">
             <feature>• Se incorporó un parche de seguridad de Android (octubre de 2025) para mejorar la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de Honor, visite nuestro sitio web https://www.honor.com/latam/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de respaldo de sus datos antes de actualizar
2. Descubra más información sobre las funciones del producto en Sugerencias
3. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, puede llamar a la línea de atención al cliente de Honor o visitar el Centro de servicios al cliente de Honor para recibir asistencia.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1061" name="et-ee">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hea kasutaja! See värskendus parandab peamiselt süsteemi jõudlust. Värskendage täiustuste nautimiseks</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Hõlbustusfunktsioonid">
             <feature>• Topeltpuudutage tagakülge, et käivitada konkreetne otsetee, mis võimaldab kiiret juurdepääsu Google Assistantile, Helisalvestile, Taimerile ja muudele rakendustele. Proovige seda, avades Sätted > Hõlbustusfunktsioonid > Otseteed ja liigutused > Topeltpuudutus tagumisel poolel</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kaamera">
             <feature>•Optimeerib mõnes olukorras Kaamera jäädvustamisefekti</feature>
             <feature>• Parandab Kaamera stabiilsust teatud olukordades</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabiilsus">
             <feature>• Parandab süsteemi stabiilsust</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Jõudlus">
             <feature>• Parandas süsteemi jõudlust</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Turvapaik">
             <feature>• Süsteemi turvalisuse tagamiseks rakendati Androidi turvapaik (oktoober 2025). Lisateavet Honori turvavärskenduste kohta leiate meie veebisaidilt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Märkused" type="end">
             <feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei mõjuta teie isiklikke andmeid, aga soovitame ikkagi enne värskendamist andmed varundada
2. Toote funktsioonide kohta leiate lisateavet rakendusest Tips
3. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, saate meilt abi, helistades Honori klienditoe infoliinile või külastades Honori klienditeeninduskeskust.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1069" name="eu-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Erabiltzaile agurgarria: eguneratze honek sistemaren errendimendua hobetzen du nagusiki. Eguneratu hobekuntzez gozatzeko</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Erabilerraztasun-eginbideak">
             <feature>• Ukitu bi aldiz atzealdea, sarbide espezifiko bat abiarazteko, eta Google Assistant-erako, Grabagailurako, Tenporizadorerako eta beste aplikazio batzuetarako sarbide azkarra gaitzeko. Probatzeko, joan hona: Ezarpenak > Erabilerraztasun-funtzioak > Lasterbideak eta keinuak > Sakatu bi aldiz atzealdea</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Kameraren argazkiak ateratzeko efektua optimizatu da zenbait egoeratan</feature>
             <feature>• Kameraren egonkortasuna hobetu da egoera batzuetan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Egonkortasuna">
             <feature>• Sistemaren egonkortasuna hobetu da</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Errendimendua">
             <feature>• Sistemaren errendimendua hobetu da</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Segurtasun-adabakia">
             <feature>• Android-en segurtasun-adabakia (2025eko urria) gehitu da sistemaren segurtasuna bermatzeko. Honor Segurtasun-eguneratzeei buruzko informazio gehiago lortzeko, ikusi gure gunea: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Oharrak" type="end">
             <feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzeak ez du eraginik izango datu pertsonaletan, baina, eguneratu baino lehen, datuen babeskopia egitea gomendatzen da
2. Ezagutu produktuaren eginbideei buruzko informazio gehiago Aholkuak atalean
3. Eguneratzean arazorik aurkitzen baduzu, gure laguntza eskura dezakezu Honor-en telefonozko arreta-lineara deituta edo Honor-en bezeroaren zerbitzu-zentroa bisitatuta.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1065" name="fa-ir">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>کاربر گرامی، این به‌روزرسانی به‌طور عمده عملکرد سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد. با انجام این به‌روزرسانی، از این بهبودها بهره‌مند شوید</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="امکانات مربوط به قابلیت دسترسی">
             <feature>‏• با دوبار ضربه‌زدن به پشت دستگاه، یک میانبر خاص اجرا می‌شود و امکان دسترسی سریع به «Google Assistant»، «ضبط‌کنندۀ صدا»، «زمان‌سنج» و سایر برنامه‌ها را فراهم می‌کند. برای امتحان کردن به این مسیر بروید: «تنظیمات > امکانات مربوط به قابلیت دسترسی > میانبرها و فرمان‌های حرکتی > دوبار ضربه به پشت»</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="دوربین">
             <feature>‏‏• جلوه عکس‌برداری «دوربین» را در برخی شرایط بهینه می‌کند</feature>
             <feature>‏‏• پایداری «دوربین» را در برخی شرایط بهینه می‌کند</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="پایداری">
             <feature>‏‏• پایداری سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="عملکرد">
             <feature>‏‏• عملکرد سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="وصلۀ امنیتی">
             <feature>‏• برای حفظ امنیت سیستم، «وصلۀ امنیتی Android (اکتبر ۲۰۲۵)» گنجانده شده است. برای کسب اطلاعات بیشتر دربارۀ به‌روزرسانی‌های «امنیت Honor»، لطفاً به وب‌سایت ما مراجعه کنید: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="یادداشت‌ها" type="end">
             <feature>‏۱. نصب این به‌روزرسانی روی داده‌های شخصی شما تأثیری نخواهد داشت. بااین‌وجود، توصیه می‌شود قبل از به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید
‏۲. اطلاعات بیشتر مربوط به قابلیت‌های محصول را در «نکات» می‌توانید بیابید
‏۳. اگر در طول به‌روزرسانی با هرگونه مشکلی مواجه شدید، می‌توانید با تماس با تلفن مستقیم خدمات Honor یا مراجعه به مرکز خدمات مشتریان Honor از ما کمک بگیرید.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1035" name="fi-fi">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä päivitys parantaa ensisijaisesti järjestelmän suorituskykyä. Päivitä, niin pääset nauttimaan parannuksista</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Helppokäyttöominaisuudet">
             <feature>• Taustapuolen kaksoisnapautus käynnistää yksittäisen pikatoiminnon ja mahdollistaa Google-avustajan, Tallentimen, Ajastimen ja muiden sovellusten nopean käytön. Voit kokeilla sitä menemällä kohtaan: Asetukset > Helppokäyttöominaisuudet > Pikakuvakkeet ja eleet > Taustapuolen kaksoisnapautus</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Optimoi Kameran kuvaustuloksen joissakin tilanteissa</feature>
             <feature>• Parantaa Kameran vakautta tietyissä tilanteissa</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vakaus">
             <feature>• Parantaa järjestelmän vakautta</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Suorituskyky">
             <feature>• Parantaa järjestelmän suorituskykyä</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Turvallisuuskorjaus">
             <feature>• Android-turvallisuuskorjaus (lokakuu 2025) on lisätty järjestelmän turvallisuutta varten. Lisätietoja Honorin turvallisuuspäivityksistä on saatavilla verkkosivustollamme osoitteessa https://www.honor.com/fi/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Muistiinpanot" type="end">
             <feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei vaikuta henkilökohtaisiin tietoihisi, mutta tietojen varmuuskopiointi ennen päivittämistä on kuitenkin suositeltavaa
2. Lisätietoja tuoteominaisuuksista on Vihjeitä-sovelluksessa
3. Jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia, saat apua soittamalla Honorin palvelunumeroon tai käymällä Honorin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1036" name="fr-fr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour améliore principalement les performances du système. Effectuez la mise à jour pour profiter des améliorations</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fonctionnalités d'accessibilité">
             <feature>• Appuyez deux fois sur l'arrière pour lancer un raccourci spécifique, permettant un accès rapide à Google Assistant, Enregistreur sonore, Minuteur et d'autres applications. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Fonctionnalités d'accessibilité > Raccourcis &amp; gestes > Double appui à l'arrière</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Appareil photo">
             <feature>• Optimise l'effet de prise de vue d'Appareil photo dans certains scénarios</feature>
             <feature>• Améliore la stabilité d'Appareil photo dans certains scénarios</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilité">
             <feature>• Améliore la stabilité du système</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Intensité d'utilisation">
             <feature>• Améliore les performances du système</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Correctif de sécurité">
             <feature>• Un correctif de sécurité Android (octobre 2025) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité Honor, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour
2. Découvrez plus d'informations sur les fonctionnalités du produit dans Astuces
3. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes pendant la mise à jour, vous pouvez obtenir de l'aide en contactant la hotline de service Honor ou en vous rendant dans un centre de services clients Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1110" name="gl-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado usuario, a novidade principal desta actualización é a mellora do rendemento do sistema. Realice a actualización para gozar das melloras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Características de accesibilidade">
             <feature>• Toque dúas veces a parte posterior para iniciar un atallo específico e active o acceso rápido a Asistente de Google, Gravadora, Temporizador e outras aplicacións. Pode realizar unha proba en Configuración > Características de accesibilidade > Atallos e xestos > Tocar dúas veces a parte de atrás</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Cámara">
             <feature>• Optimiza o efecto de captura da cámara en determinadas situacións</feature>
             <feature>• Mellora a estabilidade da cámara nalgunhas situacións</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilidade">
             <feature>• Mellora a estabilidade do sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Rendemento">
             <feature>• Mellora o rendemento do sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Parche de seguranza">
             <feature>• Incorporárase un parche de seguranza de Android (outubro de 2025) para a seguranza do sistema. Para obter máis información sobre as actualizacións de seguranza de Honor, visite o noso sitio web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalar esta actualización non afectará os seus datos persoais, pero recoméndase que realice unha copia de seguranza dos datos antes da actualización
2. Descubra máis información sobre as funcionalidades do produto en Consellos
3. Se ten algún problema durante a actualización, chame á liña directa de servizo de Honor ou visite o Centro de servizos de atención ao cliente de Honor para obter axuda.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1095" name="gu-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ અપડેટ મુખ્યત્વે સિસ્ટમની કામગીરીને વધારે છે. સુધારાનો આનંદ માણવા માટે અપડેટ કરો</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ઍક્સેસિબિલિટી સુવિધાઓ">
             <feature>• ચોક્કસ શૉર્ટકટ શરૂ કરવા માટે પાછળ બે વાર ટૅપ કરો, જેનાથી Google આસિસ્ટન્ટ, રેકોર્ડર, ટાઇમર અને અન્ય એપ્લિકેશન્સનો ઝડપી ઍક્સેસ સક્ષમ બને. સેટિંગ્સ > ઍક્સેસિબિલિટી સુવિધાઓ > શૉર્ટકટ અને સંકેતો > બે વાર પાછળ ટૅપ: પર જઈને તેને અજમાવી જુઓ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="કૅમેરા">
             <feature>• કેટલીક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં કૅમેરાના શૂટિંગ પ્રભાવને ઑપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે</feature>
             <feature>• કેટલીક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં કૅમેરાની સ્થિરતાને વધારે છે</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="સ્થિરતા">
             <feature>• સિસ્ટમની સ્થિરતામાં સુધારો કરે છે</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="કાર્યપ્રદર્શન">
             <feature>• સિસ્ટમ પ્રદર્શનમાં સુધારો કરે છે</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="સુરક્ષા પેચ">
             <feature>• Android સુરક્ષા પેચ (ઑક્ટોબર 2025) સિસ્ટમ સુરક્ષા માટે સામેલ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. Honor સુરક્ષા અપડેટ્સ વિશે વધુ માહિતી માટે, કૃપા કરીને અમારી વેબસાઇટની મુલાકાત લો https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="નોંધો" type="end">
             <feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારા વ્યક્તિગત ડેટાને અસર થશે નહીં, પરંતુ અપડેટ કરતા પહેલાં તમારા ડેટાનો બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે
2. ટિપ્સમાં ઉત્પાદન સુવિધાઓ વિશે વધુ માહિતી મેળવો
3. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે છે, તો તમે Honor સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરીને અથવા Honor ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્રની મુલાકાત લઈને અમારી મદદ મેળવી શકો છો.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1081" name="hi-in">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>नमस्ते उपयोगकर्ता, इस अद्यतन से मुख्य रूप से सिस्टम प्रदर्शन को बढ़ाया जाता है। सुधारों का फ़ायदा उठाने के लिए अद्यतन करें</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="पहुँच क्षमता सुविधाएँ">
             <feature>• खास शॉर्टकट को लॉन्च करने के लिए पिछले हिस्से पर दो बार टैप करें जिससे Google Assistant, रिकॉर्डर, टाइमर और अन्य ऐप्स तक त्वरित पहुँच सक्षम हो जाती है। यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़माएँ: सेटिंग्स > पहुँच क्षमता सुविधाएँ > शॉर्टकट्स और जेस्चर्स > पिछले हिस्से पर दो बार टैप करें</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="कैमरा">
             <feature>• कुछ परिदृश्यों में कैमरा के शूटिंग प्रभाव को अनुकूलित किया जाता है</feature>
             <feature>• कुछ परिदृश्यों में कैमरे की स्थिरता को बढ़ाया जाता है</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्थिरता">
             <feature>• सिस्टम स्थिरता में सुधार किया जाता है</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="प्रदर्शन">
             <feature>• सिस्टम के प्रदर्शन में सुधार किया जाता है</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षा पैच">
             <feature>• सिस्टम की सुरक्षा के लिए Android सुरक्षा पैच (अक्टूबर, 2025) शामिल किया गया है। Honor सुरक्षा अद्यतनों के बारे में अधिक जानकारी के लिए, हमारी वेबसाइट: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10 पर जाएँ</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोट्स" type="end">
             <feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपके व्यक्तिगत डेटा पर कोई प्रभाव नहीं पड़ेगा, लेकिन फिर भी अद्यतन करने से पहले अपने डेटा का बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है
2. युक्तियाँ में जाकर उत्पाद की सुविधाओं के बारे में अधिक जानकारी खोजें
3. अगर आपको अद्यतन के दौरान कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो आप Honor सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करके या Honor ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाकर हमारी सहायता पा सकते हैं।</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1050" name="hr-hr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim se ažuriranjem uglavnom poboljšavaju performanse sustava. Ažurirajte kako biste uživali u poboljšanjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Značajke dostupnosti">
             <feature>• Dvaput dodirnite stražnju stranu za pokretanje određenog prečaca, što omogućuje brzi pristup uslugama Google Assistant, Snimač zvuka, Mjerač vremena i drugim aplikacijama. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Značajke dostupnosti > Prečaci i geste > Dvostruki dodir unatrag</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fotoaparat">
             <feature>• Optimizira se efekt snimanja Fotoaparatom u nekim scenarijima</feature>
             <feature>• Poboljšava se stabilnost Fotoaparata u nekim scenarijima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Poboljšava se stabilnost sustava</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Izvođenje">
             <feature>• Poboljšavaju se performanse sustava</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sigurnosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (listopad 2025.) za sigurnost sustava. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima značajke Honor Sigurnost posjetite naše web-mjesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Bilješke" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće utjecati na osobne podatke, ali se svejedno preporučuje izraditi sigurnosnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja
2. Idite u aplikaciju Savjeti kako biste doznali više informacija o značajkama proizvoda
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tijekom ažuriranja, našu pomoć možete dobiti tako da nazovete Honor dežurnu liniju ili posjetite Honor servisni centar.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1038" name="hu-hu">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez a frissítés elsősorban a rendszerteljesítményt javítja. Végezze el a frissítést, hogy élvezhesse a továbbfejlesztéseket</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kisegítő lehetőségek">
             <feature>• Érintse meg duplán a hátoldalt a megfelelő gyorsindító elindításához a Google Segéd, a Hangrögzítő, az Időzítő és más alkalmazások gyors eléréséhez. Próbálja ki itt: Beállítások > Kisegítő lehetőségek > Gyorsindítók és gesztusok > Dupla érintés</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Bizonyos helyzetekben optimalizálja a Kamera fényképezési hatását</feature>
             <feature>• Bizonyos helyzetekben javítja a Kamera stabilitását</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitás">
             <feature>• Javítja a rendszer stabilitását</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Teljesítmény">
             <feature>• Javítja a rendszer teljesítményét</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Biztonsági javítás">
             <feature>• A rendszerbiztonság érdekében a frissítés az Android biztonsági frissítését (2025. október) is tartalmazza. A Honor biztonsági javításaival kapcsolatos további információkért keresse fel weboldalunkat: https://www.honor.com/hu/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Jegyzetek" type="end">
             <feature>1. A jelen frissítés telepítése nem lesz hatással személyes adataira, de a frissítés előtt az adatokról továbbra is ajánlott biztonsági másolatot készíteni
2. A termékfunkciókkal kapcsolatos további információkat a Tippek alkalmazásban tekintheti meg
3. Ha a frissítés során bármilyen problémába ütközik, forduljon hozzánk segítségért a Honor-szerviz forródrótján, vagy látogasson el a Honor ügyfélszolgálatai központjába.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1057" name="in-id">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini utamanya meningkatkan kinerja sistem. Instal pembaruan untuk menikmati berbagai peningkatan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fitur aksesibilitas">
             <feature>• Ketuk dua kali bagian belakang untuk meluncurkan pintasan spesifik, yang memungkinkan akses cepat ke Asisten Google, Perekam Suara, Pengatur waktu, dan aplikasi lainnya. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Fitur aksesibilitas > Pintasan &amp; gerakan > Ketuk bagian belakang dua kali</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Mengoptimalkan efek pengambilan gambar Kamera di beberapa skenario</feature>
             <feature>• Meningkatkan stabilitas Kamera di beberapa skenario</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitas">
             <feature>• Meningkatkan stabilitas sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kinerja">
             <feature>• Meningkatkan kinerja sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Penambal keamanan">
             <feature>• Penambal keamanan Android (Okt 2025) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan Honor, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Catatan" type="end">
             <feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan untuk mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui
2. Pelajari informasi selengkapnya terkait fitur produk di Kiat
3. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan Honor atau mengunjungi Pusat Layanan Pelanggan Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1040" name="it-it">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento migliora principalmente le prestazioni del sistema. Esegui l'aggiornamento per usufruire dei miglioramenti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funzioni accessibilità">
             <feature>• È possibile avviare una scorciatoia specifica toccando due volte il retro del dispositivo, per accedere rapidamente all'Assistente Google, al Registratore, al Timer e ad altre app. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Funzioni accessibilità > Scorciatoie e gesture > Doppio tocco posteriore</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fotocamera">
             <feature>• Viene ottimizzato l'effetto di scatto della Fotocamera in alcuni scenari</feature>
             <feature>• Viene migliorata la stabilità della Fotocamera in alcuni scenari</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilità">
             <feature>• Viene migliorata la stabilità del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Prestazioni">
             <feature>• Sono state migliorate le prestazioni del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch di sicurezza">
             <feature>• È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (ottobre 2025) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza Honor, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Note" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup dei dati prima di procedere
2. Scopri ulteriori informazioni sulle funzioni del prodotto in Suggerimenti
3. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center Honor o visitando un Servizio clienti Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1037" name="iw-il">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה משפר בעיקר את ביצועי המערכת. עדכן כדי ליהנות מהשיפורים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="תכונות נגישות">
             <feature>‏• הקש פעמיים על גב ההתקן כדי להפעיל קיצור דרך ספציפי, המאפשר גישה מהירה ל-Google Assistant, ל'רשמקול', ל'טיימר' וליישומים אחרים. כדי לנסות, אפשר לעבור אל: הגדרות > תכונות נגישות > קיצורים ומחוות > הקש פעמיים על גב ההתקן</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="מצלמה">
             <feature>‏‏• ממטב את אפקט הצילום של המצלמה בתרחישים מסוימים</feature>
             <feature>‏‏• משפר את יציבות המצלמה בתרחישים מסוימים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="יציבות">
             <feature>‏‏• משפר את יציבות המערכת</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ביצועים">
             <feature>‏‏• משפר את ביצועי המערכת</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="תיקון אבטחה">
             <feature>‏• 'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מאוקט' 2025) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של Honor', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="הערות" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון
‏2. גלה מידע נוסף על תכונות המוצר ב'טיפים'
‏3. אם נתקלת בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, תוכל לקבל עזרה מאיתנו על ידי התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של Honor או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1041" name="ja-jp">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ユーザーの皆様、今回の更新では主にシステムのパフォーマンスが強化されます。更新して、改善をお楽しみください</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ユーザー補助機能">
             <feature>• 背面を2回タップすると特定のショートカットが起動し、Googleアシスタント、音声レコーダー、タイマー、その他のアプリにすばやくアクセスできます。この機能を試すには、[設定] > [ユーザー補助機能] > [ショートカットとジェスチャー] > [背面を2回タップ]に移動してください</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="カメラ">
             <feature>• 一部のシナリオにおけるカメラの撮影効果が最適化されます</feature>
             <feature>• 一部のシナリオにおけるカメラの安定性が強化されます</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安定性">
             <feature>• システムの安定性が改善します</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="パフォーマンス">
             <feature>• システムパフォーマンスが改善されます</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="セキュリティパッチ">
             <feature>• システムセキュリティのためにAndroidセキュリティパッチ（2025年10月）が組み込まれました。Honorのセキュリティ更新の詳細については、当社のWebサイトをご覧ください：https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="メモ" type="end">
             <feature>1. この更新をインストールしても個人情報への影響はありませんが、更新前に個人情報をバックアップしておくことをおすすめします
2. 製品機能の詳細はヒントアプリで確認してください
3. 更新中に問題が発生した場合、Honorサービスホットラインにお電話をいただくか、Honorカスタマーサービスセンターにご来店いただき、サポートを受けてください。</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1079" name="ka-ge">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ეს განახლება ძირითადად აუმჯობესებს სისტემის ეფექტიანობას. განაახლეთ და ისიამოვნეთ გაუმჯობესებებით</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ხელმისაწვდომობის ფუნქციები">
             <feature>• უკანა მხარეს ორმაგად შეხებით შეგიძლიათ გაუშვათ კონკრეტული მალსახმობი, რაც უზრუნველყოფს სწრაფ წვდომას Google Assistant-ზე, ხმის ჩამწერზე, ტაიმერზე და სხვა აპებზე. ცადეთ მენიუში: პარამეტრები > ხელმისაწვდომობის ფუნქციები > მალსახმობები და ჟესტები > უკან ორჯერ შეხება</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="კამერა">
             <feature>• ახდენს კამერის გადაღების ეფექტის ოპტიმიზებას გარკვეულ სცენარებში</feature>
             <feature>• აძლიერებს კამერის სტაბილურობას ზოგიერთ სცენარში</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="სტაბილურობა">
             <feature>• აუმჯობესებს სისტემის სტაბილურობას</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ეფექტურობა">
             <feature>• აუმჯობესებს სისტემის მუშაობას</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="უსაფრთხოების შესწორება">
             <feature>• სისტემის უსაფრთხოებისთვის ჩაირთო Android-ის უსაფრთხოების შესწორება (2025 წლის ოქტომბერი). Honor-ის უსაფრთხოების განახლებების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაციისთვის ეწვიეთ ჩვენს ვებსაიტს: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="შენიშვნები" type="end">
             <feature>1. ამ განახლების დაინსტალირება არ იმოქმედებს თქვენს პერსონალურ მონაცემებზე, თუმცა რეკომენდებულია განახლებამდე მონაცემების სარეზერვო ასლის შექმნა
2. გაეცანით დამატებით ინფორმაციას რჩევებში პროდუქტის ფუნქციების შესახებ
3. თუ განახლების დროს რაიმე პრობლემას წააწყდებით, შეგიძლიათ დახმარებისთვის მიმართოთ Honor-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზს ან ეწვიოთ Honor-ის კლიენტთა მომსახურების სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1087" name="kk-kz">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл жаңарту негізінен жүйе өнімділігін жақсартады. Жақсартуларды пайдалану үшін жаңартыңыз</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Арнайы мүмкіндіктер">
             <feature>• Google Assistant, «Дыбыс жазу құралы», «Таймер» және басқа қолданбаларға жылдам қатынасуға мүмкіндік беретін белгілі бір төте жолды іске қосу үшін артқы жағын екі рет түртіңіз. «Параметрлер» > «Арнайы мүмкіндіктер» > «Таңбашалар және қимылдар» > «Артқы жағын екі рет түрту» тармағына өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Камера">
             <feature>• Кейбір сценарийлерде Камераның түсіру әсерін оңтайландырады</feature>
             <feature>• Кейбір сценарийлерде Камера тұрақтылығын жақсартады</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Тұрақтылық">
             <feature>• Жүйе тұрақтылығын жақсартады</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Өнімділік">
             <feature>• Жүйе өнімділігін жақсартады</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Қауіпсіздік патчы">
             <feature>• Android қауіпсіздік патчы (қазан, 2025) жүйе қауіпсіздігі үшін біріктірілген. Honor қауіпсіздік жаңартулары туралы қосымша ақпарат алу үшін біздің веб-сайтқа кіріңіз: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Ескертпелер" type="end">
             <feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнату жеке деректеріңізге әсер етпейді, бірақ жаңарту алдында деректердің сақтық көшірмесін жасау ұсынылады
2. «Кеңестер» қолданбасында өнім мүмкіндіктері туралы қосымша ақпаратты табыңыз
3. Жаңарту кезінде қандай да бір мәселе орын алса, Honor қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне қоңырау шалу не Honor тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына бару арқылы көмегімізді ала аласыз.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1107" name="km-kh">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះធ្វើឱ្យប្រតិបត្តិការប្រព័ន្ធប្រសើរឡើងជាចម្បង។ ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព ដើម្បីរីករាយនឹងការកែលម្អទាំងនេះ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="មុខងារភាពងាយស្រួលប្រើប្រាស់">
             <feature>• ប៉ះផ្នែកខាងក្រោយពីរដង ដើម្បីបើកដំណើរការផ្លូវកាត់ជាក់លាក់ ការបើកការចូលប្រើរហ័សទៅកាន់ Google ជំនួយការ, កម្មវិធីថតសំឡេង, គ្រឿងកំណត់ពេល និងកម្មវិធីផ្សេងទៀត។ សាកល្បងវាដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > មុខងារភាពងាយស្រួលប្រើប្រាស់ > ផ្លូវកាត់ និងកាយវិការ > ប៉ះខាងខ្នងពីរដង</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="កាមេរ៉ា​">
             <feature>• ធ្វើឱ្យបែបផែនថតរបស់កាមេរ៉ាប្រសើរឡើងក្នុងសេណារីយោមួយចំនួន</feature>
             <feature>• បង្កើនស្ដិរភាពនៃកាមេរ៉ានៅក្នុងសេណារីយ៉ូមួយចំនួន</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ស្ថិរភាព">
             <feature>• កែលម្អស្ថិរភាពប្រព័ន្ធ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ដំណើរការ">
             <feature>• កែលម្អប្រតិបត្តិការ​ប្រព័ន្ធ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="បំណះសន្តិសុខ">
             <feature>• បំណះសន្តិសុខ Android (តុលា 2025) ត្រូវបាន​រួមបញ្ចូល​សម្រាប់​សន្តិសុខ​ប្រព័ន្ធ។ សម្រាប់​ព័ត៌មាន​បន្ថែម​អំពី​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​សន្តិសុខ Honor សូមចូលទៅ​គេហទំព័រ​របស់យើង https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់" type="end">
             <feature>1. ការដំឡើងបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះនឹងមិនប៉ះពាល់ដល់ទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួនរបស់អ្នកទេ ប៉ុន្តែសូមណែនាំឱ្យបម្រុងទុកទិន្នន័យរបស់អ្នក មុននឹងធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព
2. ស្វែងយល់បន្ថែមអំពីលក្ខណៈពិសេសផលិតផលនៅក្នុងគន្លឹះ
3. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបប្រទះបញ្ហាណាមួយអំឡុងពេលធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព អ្នកអាចទទួលបានជំនួយរបស់យើងដោយហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅលេខខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សរបស់សេវាកម្ម Honor ឬចូលមើលមជ្ឈមណ្ឌលសេវាកម្មអតិថិជន Honor។</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1099" name="kn-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಮುಖ್ಯವಾಗಿ ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಕಾರ್ಯಕ್ಷಮತೆಯನ್ನು ವರ್ಧಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಸುಧಾರಣೆಗಳನ್ನು ಆನಂದಿಸಲು ನವೀಕರಿಸಿ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಪ್ರವೇಶಾರ್ಹತೆ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯಗಳು">
             <feature>• ನಿರ್ದಿಷ್ಟ ಶಾರ್ಟ್‌ಕಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಪ್ರಾರಂಭಿಸಲು ಹಿಂಬದಿಯನ್ನು ಡಬಲ್-ಟ್ಯಾಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ, ಇದು Google ಸಹಾಯಕ, ರೆಕಾರ್ಡರ್, ಟೈಮರ್ ಮತ್ತು ಇತರೆ ಆ್ಯಪ್‍‍ಗಳಿಗೆ ತ್ವರಿತ ಆ್ಯಕ್ಸೆಸ್ ಅನ್ನು ನೀಡುತ್ತದೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಪ್ರವೇಶಾರ್ಹತೆ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯಗಳು > ಶಾರ್ಟ್‌ಕಟ್‌ಗಳು ಮತ್ತು ಗೆಶ್ಚರ್‌ಗಳು > ಡಬಲ್ ಬ್ಯಾಕ್-ಟ್ಯಾಪ್</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾ">
             <feature>• ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾದ ಶೂಟಿಂಗ್ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ</feature>
             <feature>• ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾದ ಸ್ಥಿರತೆಯನ್ನು ವರ್ಧಿಸುತ್ತದೆ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಸ್ಥಿರತೆ">
             <feature>• ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಸ್ಥಿರತೆಯನ್ನು ಸುಧಾರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಕಾರ್ಯನಿರ್ವಹಣೆ">
             <feature>• ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಕಾರ್ಯಕ್ಷಮತೆಯನ್ನು ಸುಧಾರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್">
             <feature>• ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಭದ್ರತೆಗಾಗಿ Android ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ (ಅಕ್ಟೋಬರ್ 2025) ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. Honor ಭದ್ರತಾ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಗಾಗಿ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಮ್ಮ ವೆಬ್‌ಸೈಟ್‌ಗೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡಿ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು" type="end">
             <feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾದ ಮೇಲೆ ಪರಿಣಾಮ ಬೀರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೂ ಸಹ ನವೀಕರಿಸುವ ಮೊದಲು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಬ್ಯಾಕ್ ಅಪ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ
2. ಉತ್ಪನ್ನ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಯನ್ನು ಸಲಹೆಗಳು ಎಂಬುದರಲ್ಲಿ ಕಂಡುಕೊಳ್ಳಿ
3. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ನೀವು Honor ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಅಥವಾ Honor ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ನಮ್ಮ ಸಹಾಯವನ್ನು ಪಡೆಯಬಹುದು.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1042" name="ko-kr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>사용자 여러분, 이번 업데이트는 주로 시스템 성능을 향상시킵니다. 업데이트하고 개선된 기능을 즐겨 보세요</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="접근성 기능">
             <feature>• 뒷면을 두 번 탭하면 특정 바로가기가 실행되어 Google 어시스턴트, 녹음기, 타이머 및 기타 앱에 빠르게 액세스할 수 있습니다. 설정 > 접근성 기능 > 바로가기 및 제스처 > 뒷면 두 번 탭으로 이동하여 사용해 보세요</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="카메라">
             <feature>• 일부 시나리오에서 카메라 촬영 효과가 최적화되었습니다</feature>
             <feature>• 일부 시나리오에서 카메라의 안정성이 향상되었습니다</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="안정성">
             <feature>• 시스템 안정성이 개선되었습니다</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="성능">
             <feature>• 시스템 성능이 개선되었습니다</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="보안 패치">
             <feature>• 시스템 보안을 위해 Android 보안 패치(2025년 10월)가 통합되었습니다. Honor 보안 업데이트에 대해 자세히 알아보려면 당사 웹사이트(https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10)를 방문하세요.</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="공지" type="end">
             <feature>1. 이 업데이트 설치는 개인 데이터에 영향을 미치지 않지만, 업데이트하기 전에 데이터를 백업하는 것이 좋습니다
2. Tips에서 제품 기능에 대한 자세한 정보를 알아보세요
3. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 Honor 서비스 핫라인으로 전화하거나 Honor 고객 서비스 센터를 방문하여 도움을 받을 수 있습니다.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1108" name="lo-la">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ສະ​ບາຍ​ດີ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​​ນີ້​ຍົກ​ລະ​ດັບ​ປະ​ສິດ​ທິ​ພາບ​ຂອງ​ລະ​ບົບ​ເປັນຫຼັກ. ອັບ​ເດດ​ເພື່ອ​ມ່ວ​ນ​ຊື່​ນກັບ​ການ​ປັບ​ປຸງ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ຄຸນສົມບັດ​ການ​ຊ່ວຍ​ເຂົ້າ​ເຖິງ">
             <feature>• ແຕະ​ດ້ານຫຼັງ​ສອງ​ຄັ້ງ​ເພື່ອ​ເປີດ​ໃຊ້​ທາງ​ລັດ​ສະ​ເພາະ, ເຊິ່ງ​ເປີດ​ໃຊ້​ງານ​ການ​ເຂົ້າ​ເຖິງ​ດ່ວນ​ຫາຕົວ​ຊ່ວຍ Google, ເຄື່ອງ​ບັນ​ທຶກ​ສຽງ, ໂມງ​ຕັ້ງ​ເວ​ລາ ແລະ ແອັບ​ອື່ນໆ. ​ລອງໃຊ້ມັນເບິ່ງ​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການຕັ້ງຄ່າ > ຄຸນສົມບັດການຊ່ວຍເຂົ້າເຖິງ > ທາງລັດ ແລະ ທ່າທາງ > ການແຕະດ້ານຫຼັງສອງເທື່ອ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ກ້ອງຖ່າຍຮູບ">
             <feature>• ປັບເອັບ​ເຝັກການ​ຖ່າຍ​ຮູບຂອງ​​ກ້ອງ​ຖ່າຍ​ຮູບໃນບາງສະພາບການ​ໃຫ້ເໝາະສົມ</feature>
             <feature>• ຍົກ​ລະ​ດັບ​ຄວາມ​ສະ​ຖຽນ​ຂອງກ້ອງ​ຖ່າຍ​ຮູບ​ໃນ​ບາງ​ສະ​ຖາ​ນະ​ການ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ຄວາມສະ​ຖຽນ">
             <feature>• ປັບປຸງຄວາມສະຖຽນຂອງລະບົບ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ການປະຕິບັດ">
             <feature>• ປັບປຸງປະ​ສິດ​ທິ​ພາບຂອງລະບົບ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ">
             <feature>• ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ຂອງ Android (ຕຸ​ລາ 2025) ​ໄດ້ຖືກລວມ​​ເຂົ້າ​ເປັນ​ການ​ຮັກ​ສາ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ລະ​ບົບ. ສຳລັບຂໍ້ມູນເພີ່ມເຕີມກ່ຽວກັບການອັບເດດດ້ານຄວາມປອດໄພຂອງ Honor, ກະລຸນາເຂົ້າໄປ​ທີ່ເວັບໄຊຂອງພວກເຮົາ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ການ​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ສົ່ງ​ຜົນ​ຕໍ່​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ, ແຕ່​ຍັງ​ຄົງ​ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ສຳ​ຮອງ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄວ້ກ່ອນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ
2. ຄົ້ນ​ຫາ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ເພີ່ມ​ເຕີມ​ກ່ຽວ​ກັບ​ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດ​ຜະ​ລິດ​ຕະ​ພັນ​ໃນ​​ເຄັດ​ລັບ
3. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ທ່ານສາມາດຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອຈາກພວກເຮົາໄດ້ ໂດຍການໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນ​ບໍ​ລິ​ການ Honor ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1063" name="lt-lt">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šis naujinys daugiausiai pagerina sistemos našumą. Atnaujinkite ir mėgaukitės patobulinimais.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pritaikymo neįgaliesiems funkcijos">
             <feature>• Dukart palieskite nugarėlę, kad paleistumėte tam tikrą nuorodą ir galėtumėte greitai pasiekti „Google Assistant“, Diktofoną, Laikmatį ir kitas programėles. Išbandykite tai nuėję į „Nuostatos > Pritaikymo neįgaliesiems funkcijos > Nuorodos ir gestai > Dvigubas nugarėlės bakstelėjimas“</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Kai kuriais atvejais optimizuojamas Kameros fotografavimo efektas</feature>
             <feature>• Kai kuriais atvejais pagerinamas Kameros stabilumas</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilumas">
             <feature>• Pagerinamas sistemos stabilumas</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Našumas">
             <feature>• Pagerinamas sistemos veikimas</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Saugumo pataisa">
             <feature>• Siekiant užtikrinti sistemos saugumą, įtraukta „Android“ saugumo pataisa (2025 m. spalio mėn.). Jei reikia daugiau informacijos apie Honor saugumo naujinius, apsilankykite mūsų svetainėje https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Pastabos" type="end">
             <feature>1. Šio naujinio įdiegimas neturės įtakos jūsų asmeniniams duomenims, tačiau prieš atnaujinant rekomenduojama sukurti atsarginę duomenų kopiją
2. Daugiau informacijos apie gaminio funkcijas rasite Patarimuose
3. Jei naujinimo metu kiltų bet kokių problemų, galite kreiptis į mus pagalbos paskambindami „Honor“ priežiūros karštąja linija arba apsilankydami „Honor“ klientų aptarnavimo centre.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1062" name="lv-lv">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo atjauninājumu galvenokārt ir uzlabota sistēmas veiktspēja. Atjauniniet, lai izbaudītu uzlabojumus</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pieejamības funkcijas">
             <feature>• Veiciet dubultskārienu aizmugurē, lai palaistu konkrētu saīsni, kas nodrošina ātru piekļuvi lietotnēm Google asistents, Skaņas ierakstītājs, Taimeris un citām lietotnēm. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Iestatījumi > Pieejamības funkcijas > Saīsnes un žesti > Divreiz pieskaries aizmugurē</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Optimizē lietotnes Kamera uzņemšanas efektu dažiem scenārijiem</feature>
             <feature>• Uzlabo lietotnes Kamera stabilitāti dažos gadījumos</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitāte">
             <feature>• Uzlabo sistēmas stabilitāti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Veiktspēja">
             <feature>• Uzlabo sistēmas veiktspēju</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Drošības ielāps">
             <feature>• Sistēmas drošībai iekļauts Android drošības ielāps (2025. gada oktobris). Lai iegūtu papildinformāciju par Honor drošības atjauninājumiem, lūdzu, apmeklējiet mūsu vietni https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Piezīmes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Šī atjauninājuma instalēšana neietekmēs jūsu personas datus, taču joprojām ir ieteicams pirms atjaunināšanas dublēt datus
2. Lietotnē Padomi atklājiet vairāk par produkta funkcijām
3. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, varat saņemt mūsu palīdzību, zvanot uz Honor klientu apkalpošanas dienesta tālruni vai apmeklējot Honor klientu pakalpojumu centru.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="mai-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, ई अपडेट मुख्य रूप सँ सिस्टमक कार्य-क्षमता केँ वर्धित करैत अछि। सुधार सभक आनंद लेबाक लेल अपडेट करू</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="एक्सेसिबिलिटी फीचर">
             <feature>• कोनो विशिष्ट शॉर्टकट केँ लॉन्च करबाक लेल पछिला भाग केँ दू-बेर टैप करू, जाहि सँ Google असिस्‍टेंट, रिकॉर्डर, टाइमर आ अन्य एप सभ धरि त्वरित एक्सेस सक्षम भए जायत। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: सेटिंग्स > एक्सेसिबिलिटी फीचर > शॉर्टकट आ संकेत सभ > पाछू वला हिस्सा पर दू-बेर टैप करू</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="कैमरा">
             <feature>• किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे कैमरा केर शूटिंग प्रभाव केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि</feature>
             <feature>• किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे कैमराक स्थिरता केँ वर्धित करैत अछि</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्थिरता">
             <feature>• सिस्टमक स्थिरता मे सुधार करैत अछि</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="प्रदर्शन">
             <feature>• सिस्टमक प्रदर्शन मे सुधार करैत अछि</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षा पैच">
             <feature>सिस्टमक सुरक्षाक लेल Android सुरक्षा पैच (अक्टूबर 2025) समाविष्ट कयल गेल अछि। Honor सुरक्षा अपडेट सभक विषय मे आओर जानकारीक लेल, कृपाकए हमरासभक वेबसाइट केँ देखू: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोट्स" type="end">
             <feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा प्रभावित नहि होयत, मुदा तैयो अपडेट करए सँ पहिने अहाँ केँ डेटाक बैकअप लेबाक सुझाव देल जाइत अछि
2. टिप्स मे उत्पाद विशेषता सभ पर आओर जानकारी डिस्‍कवर करू
3. अपडेट केर दरमियान यदि अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' अहाँ Honor सेवा हॉटलाइन केँ कॉल कए वा Honor ग्राहक सर्विस सेंटर पर जा कए हमरासभक मदति लए सकैत छी।</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1153" name="mi-NZ">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>E te kaiwhakamahi aroha, ko tēnei whakahoutanga e whakarei ake ana i te mahinga pūnaha. Whakahōu ki te oaoa i te whakapai ake</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ngā āhuahira urutanga">
             <feature>• Pato-rua ki te tuara hei whakarewatanga i tētahi pokatata motuhake, kia uru wawe ki a Pūāwhina Google, Pūhopu, Matawā, me tētahi atu ngā taupānga. Whakamātauria mā te haere ki: Ngā Tautuhinga > Ngā āhuahira urutanga > Ngā pokatata me ngā tohu ā-ringa > Pato tuarua ki hoki</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kāmera">
             <feature>• Ka arotau i te pānga whakairoiro o te Kāmera i ētahi āhuatanga</feature>
             <feature>• Ka whakarei i te pūmautanga o te Kāmera i ētahi āhuatanga</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pūmautanga">
             <feature>• Ka whakapai ake i te pūmautanga o te pūnaha</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tutukinga">
             <feature>• Ka whakapai ake i te mahinga o te pūnaha</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Āpure haumarutanga">
             <feature>• Kua whakaurua te pūrei haumarutanga Android (Oketopa 2025) mō te haumarutanga pūnaha. Mō ētahi anō mōhiohio mō ngā whakahōutanga Haumarutanga Honor, haere koa ki tā mātou paetukutuku https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Ngā Tuhipoka" type="end">
             <feature>1. Mā te tāuta i tēnei whakahōutanga e kore tō raraunga whaiaro e pāngia, engari e taunaki ana kia tāruatia ō raraunga i mua i te whakahōutanga
2. Tūhura mōhiohio ētahi anō mō ngā āhuahira o te hua i Ngā Aki
3. Mēnā ka pāngia koe e ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōutanga, ka taea e koe te tiki āwhina mā te waea atu ki te waeawera ratonga Honor, mā te toro atu rānei ki te Pokapū Ratonga Kiritaki a Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1071" name="mk-mk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Почитуван кориснику, ова ажурирање главно ги подобрува перформансите на системот. Ажурирајте за да уживате во подобрувањата</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Карактеристики за пристапност">
             <feature>• Допрете двапати на задниот дел за да активирате конкретна кратенка, овозможувајќи брз пристап до Google Assistant, Диктафон, Тајмер и други апликации. Пробајте така што ќе отидете во: Нагодување > Карактеристики за пристапност > Кратенки и гестови > Двоен допир на задниот дел</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Камера">
             <feature>• Го оптимизира ефектот на сликање на Камера во некои сценарија</feature>
             <feature>• Ја подобрува стабилноста на Камера во некои сценарија</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Стабилност">
             <feature>• Ја подобрува стабилноста на системот</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Изведба">
             <feature>• Ги подобрува перформансите на системот</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Безбедносна крпеница">
             <feature>• Вградена е безбедносна крпеница за Android (октомври 2025) за безбедност на системот. За повеќе информации за ажурирања на безбедноста од Honor, посетете ја нашата веб-локација https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Белешки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да влијае врз вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува да направите резервна копија од податоците пред да ажурирате
2. Откријте повеќе информации за карактеристиките на производот во Совети
3. Ако наидете на какви било проблеми при ажурирањето, може да ја добиете нашата помош со повикување на телефонскиот број на службата на Honor или посета на Центарот за услуги за корисници на Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1100" name="ml-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് പ്രധാനമായും സിസ്റ്റം പ്രകടനം മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു. മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തലുകൾ ആസ്വദിക്കാൻ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുക</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ആക്സസബിലിറ്റി സവിശേഷതകൾ">
             <feature>• Google Assistant, റെക്കോർഡർ, ടൈമർ എന്നിവയിലേക്കും മറ്റ് ആപ്പുകളിലേക്കും ദ്രുത ആക്‌സസ് പ്രവർത്തനസജ്ജമാക്കുന്ന ഒരു നിർദ്ദിഷ്‌ട എളുപ്പവഴി സമാരംഭിക്കാൻ പിന്നിൽ രണ്ടുതവണ ടാപ്പ് ചെയ്യുക. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്രമീകരണം > ആക്സസബിലിറ്റി സവിശേഷതകൾ > എളുപ്പവഴികളും ആംഗ്യങ്ങളും > പിന്നിൽ രണ്ടുതവണ ടാപ്പ് ചെയ്യുക</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ക്യാമറ">
             <feature>• ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിൽ ക്യാമറയുടെ ഷൂട്ടിംഗ് ഇഫക്റ്റ് ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുന്നു</feature>
             <feature>• ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിൽ ക്യാമറയുടെ സ്ഥിരത മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="സ്ഥിരത">
             <feature>• സിസ്റ്റം സ്ഥിരത മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="പ്രകടനം">
             <feature>• സിസ്റ്റം പ്രകടനം മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച്">
             <feature>• സിസ്റ്റം സുരക്ഷയ്‌ക്കായി Android സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് (ഒക്‌ടോബർ 2025) ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. Honor സുരക്ഷാ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾക്ക്, ഞങ്ങളുടെ വെബ്‌സൈറ്റ് സന്ദർശിക്കുക: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ ബാധിക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിന് മുമ്പായി നിങ്ങളുടെ ഡാറ്റ ബാക്കപ്പ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു
2. 'നുറുങ്ങുകൾ' എന്നതിൽ ഉൽപ്പന്ന സവിശേഷതകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾ കണ്ടെത്തുക
3. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ നിങ്ങൾക്ക് എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, Honor സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ Honor ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്‌ത് ഞങ്ങളുടെ സഹായം കരസ്ഥമാക്കാവുന്നതാണ്.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1104" name="mn-MN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэ шинэчлэлтээр голчлон системийн гүйцэтгэлийг сайжрууллаа. Шинэчлээд, сайжруулсан хэрэглээг мэдрээрэй</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Хялбар ашиглалт">
             <feature>• Ар талыг хоёр удаа товшиж тодорхой заасан товчилборыг нээж, Google Туслах, Бичигч, Цаг болон бусад апп руу шуурхай нэвтэрнэ. Тохиргоо > Хялбар ашиглалт > Товчилбор ба дохио зангаа > Ар талыг хоёр удаа товших руу очиж туршиж үзнэ үү</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Камер">
             <feature>• Зарим тохиолдолд Камераар зураг авах эффектийг оновчилно</feature>
             <feature>• Зарим тохиолдолд Камерын тогтвортой байдлыг нэмэгдүүлсэн</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Тогтвортой байдал">
             <feature>• Системийн тогтвортой байдлыг сайжруулсан</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Гүйцэтгэл">
             <feature>• Системийн гүйцэтгэлийг сайжруулна</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Хамгаалалтын нөхөөс">
             <feature>• Системийн хамгаалалтад зориулж Андройд хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг (2025 оны аравдугаар сар) багтаав. Honor-н хамгаалалтын шинэчлэлтийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэл авах бол манай дараах вебсайтад зочилно уу: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Тэмдэглэл" type="end">
             <feature>1. Энэхүү шинэчлэлтийг суулгахад таны хувийн мэдээлэлд нөлөөлөхгүй ч шинэчлэхээс өмнө өгөгдлөө нөөцлөхийг зөвлөж байна
2. Зөвлөгөө дотроос бүтээгдэхүүний онцлогийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэлтэй танилцана уу
3. Шинэчлэх үеэр асуудал тулгарвал Honor үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утсаар залгаж эсвэл Honor-н хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төвд зочилж тусламж авах боломжтой.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1102" name="mr-in">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, हे अद्यतन प्रामुख्याने सिस्टम कार्यप्रदर्शन वाढवते. सुधारणांचा आनंद घेण्यासाठी अद्यतनित करा</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुलभता वैशिष्‍ट्ये">
             <feature>• विशिष्ट शॉर्टकट लाँच करण्यासाठी मागील बाजूस दोनदा टॅप करा, ज्यामुळे Google असिस्टंट, रेकॉर्डर, टाइमर आणि अन्य अ‍ॅप्समध्ये जलद अ‍ॅक्‍सेस मिळेल. येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पहा: सेटिंग्ज > सुलभता वैशिष्‍ट्ये > शॉर्टकट आणि जेश्चर > दोनदा बॅक-टॅप करा</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="कॅमेरा">
             <feature>• काही परिस्थितींमध्ये कॅमेऱ्याचा शूटिंग प्रभाव ऑप्टिमाइझ करते</feature>
             <feature>• काही परिस्थितींमध्ये कॅमेऱ्याची स्थिरता वाढवते</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्थिरता">
             <feature>• सिस्टम स्थिरता सुधारते</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="कार्यप्रदर्शन">
             <feature>• सिस्टम कार्यक्षमता सुधारते</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षितता पॅच">
             <feature>• सिस्टम सुरक्षिततेसाठी Android सुरक्षितता पॅच (ऑक्टो 2025) समाविष्ट करण्यात आला आहे. Honor सुरक्षितता अद्यतनांबद्दल अधिक माहितीसाठी, कृपया आमच्या वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोट्स" type="end">
             <feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्‍थापित केल्याने आपल्या वैयक्तिक डेटावर परिणाम होणार नाही, परंतु तरीही अद्यतनित करण्यापूर्वी आपल्या डेटाचा बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते
2. उत्पादन वैशिष्ट्यांबद्दल अधिक माहिती Tips मध्ये शोधा
3. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, आपण Honor सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करून किंवा Honor ग्राहक सेवा केंद्राला भेट देऊन आमची मदत मिळवू शकता.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1086" name="ms-my">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini ini meningkatkan prestasi sistem terutamanya. Kemas kini untuk menikmati penambahbaikan tersebut</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kebolehaksesan">
             <feature>• Ketik dua kali bahagian belakang untuk melancarkan pintasan tertentu, membolehkan akses pantas kepada Pembantu Google, Perakam, Pemasa dan aplikasi lain. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Kebolehaksesan > Pintasan &amp; gerak isyarat > Ketik belakang dua kali</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Mengoptimumkan kesan penangkapan Kamera dalam beberapa senario</feature>
             <feature>• Meningkatkan kestabilan Kamera dalam beberapa senario</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kestabilan">
             <feature>• Meningkatkan kestabilan sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Prestasi">
             <feature>• Meningkatkan prestasi sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tampalan keselamatan">
             <feature>• Tampalan keselamatan Android (Okt 2025) telah dimasukkan untuk tujuan keselamatan sistem. Untuk mendapatkan maklumat lanjut tentang kemas kini Keselamatan Honor, sila lawati laman web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Nota" type="end">
             <feature>1. Memasang kemas kini ini tidak akan menjejaskan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda masih disyorkan agar menyandarkan data sebelum melakukan kemas kini
2. Temui maklumat lanjut tentang ciri produk dalam Tip
3. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, anda boleh mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi talian hotline perkhidmatan Honor atau melawati Pusat Khidmat Pelanggan Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1109" name="my-mm">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် စနစ် စွမ်းဆောင်ရည်ကို အဓိက မြှင့်တင်ပေးသည်။ တိုးတက်ကောင်းမွန်အောင်လုပ်ထားသည်များကို သုံးစွဲခံစားရန် အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="အထောက်အကူပြု လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်များ">
             <feature>• သတ်မှတ်ရှော့(တ်)ကတ်ကို ဖွင့်ရန် ကျောဘက်ကို နှစ်ချက်နှိပ်ပါက Google Assistant၊ အသံဖမ်းစက်၊ တိုင်မာနှင့် အခြားအက်ပ်များကို အမြန် ရယူသုံးစွဲနိုင်ပါသည်။ ဖော်ပြပါအတိုင်းသွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ဆက်တင် > အထောက်အကူပြု လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်များ > ရှော့(တ်)ကတ်များနှင့် ဟန်ပန်များ > ကျောဘက်ကို နှစ်ချက်နှိပ်ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ကင်မရာ">
             <feature>• အချို့အခြေအနေများ၌ ကင်မရာရိုက်ကူးရာတွင် ပိုမိုကောင်းမွန်စေရန် အကောင်းဆုံးချိန်ညှိပေးသည်</feature>
             <feature>• အချို့အခြေအနေများတွင် ကင်မရာ တည်ငြိမ်မှုကို မြှင့်တင်ပေးသည်</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="တည်ငြိမ်မှု">
             <feature>• စနစ် ပိုမိုတည်ငြိမ်စေရန် မြှင့်တင်ပေးသည်</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="စွမ်းဆောင်မှု">
             <feature>• စနစ်စွမ်းဆောင်ရည်ကို မြှင့်တင်ပေးသည်</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ">
             <feature>• စနစ်လုံခြုံရေးအတွက် Android လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ (အောက်တိုဘာ 2025) ကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ Honor လုံခြုံရေး အပ်ဒိတ်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို သိရှိရန် ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ ဖော်ပြပါဝက်ဘ်ဆိုဒ်သို့ သွားရောက်ကြည့်ရှုပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="မှတ်ချက်" type="end">
             <feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းက သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာကို ထိခိုက်စေမည်မဟုတ်သော်လည်း အပ်ဒိတ်မလုပ်မီ သင့်ဒေတာကို ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ထားရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်
2. Tips တွင် ကုန်ပစ္စည်း လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို လေ့လာပါ
3. အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်စဉ် ပြဿနာ တစ်စုံတစ်ရာ ကြုံရပါက Honor ဝန်ဆောင်မှုဌာန ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ဖုန်းခေါ်ဆို၍ သို့မဟုတ် Honor သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားရောက်၍ ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏အကူအညီကို ရယူနိုင်သည်။</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1109" name="my-zg">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ စနစ္ စြမ္းေဆာင္ရည္ကို အဓိက ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးသည္။ တိုးတက္ေကာင္းမြန္ေအာင္လုပ္ထားသည္မ်ားကို သုံးစြဲခံစားရန္ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="အေထာက္အကူျပဳ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္မ်ား">
             <feature>• သတ္မွတ္ေရွာ့(တ္)ကတ္ကို ဖြင့္ရန္ ေက်ာဘက္ကို ႏွစ္ခ်က္ႏွိပ္ပါက Google Assistant၊ အသံဖမ္းစက္၊ တိုင္မာႏွင့္ အျခားအက္ပ္မ်ားကို အျမန္ ရယူသုံးစြဲႏိုင္ပါသည္။ ေဖာ္ျပပါအတိုင္းသြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ဆက္တင္ > အေထာက္အကူျပဳ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္မ်ား > ေရွာ့(တ္)ကတ္မ်ားႏွင့္ ဟန္ပန္မ်ား > ေက်ာဘက္ကို ႏွစ္ခ်က္ႏွိပ္ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ကင္မရာ">
             <feature>• အခ်ိဳ႕အေျခအေနမ်ား၌ ကင္မရာ႐ိုက္ကူးရာတြင္ ပိုမိုေကာင္းမြန္ေစရန္ အေကာင္းဆုံးခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္</feature>
             <feature>• အခ်ိဳ႕အေျခအေနမ်ားတြင္ ကင္မရာ တည္ၿငိမ္မႈကို ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးသည္</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="တည္ၿငိမ္မႈ">
             <feature>• စနစ္ ပိုမိုတည္ၿငိမ္ေစရန္ ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးသည္</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="စြမ္းေဆာင္မႈ">
             <feature>• စနစ္စြမ္းေဆာင္ရည္ကို ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးသည္</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="လုံျခံဳေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ">
             <feature>• စနစ္လုံၿခဳံေရးအတြက္ Android လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ (ေအာက္တိုဘာ 2025) ကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ Honor လုံၿခဳံေရး အပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို သိရွိရန္ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ ေဖာ္ျပပါဝက္ဘ္ဆိုဒ္သို႔ သြားေရာက္ၾကည့္ရႈပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="မွတ္ခ်က္" type="end">
             <feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းက သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာကို ထိခိုက္ေစမည္မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း အပ္ဒိတ္မလုပ္မီ သင့္ေဒတာကို ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ထားရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္
2. Tips တြင္ ကုန္ပစၥည္း လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို ေလ့လာပါ
3. အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္စဥ္ ျပႆနာ တစ္စုံတစ္ရာ ႀကဳံရပါက Honor ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈဌာန ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ဖုန္းေခၚဆို၍ သို႔မဟုတ္ Honor သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားေရာက္၍ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏အကူအညီကို ရယူႏိုင္သည္။</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1044" name="nb-no">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Kjære bruker. Denne oppdateringen forbedrer hovedsakelig systemytelsen. Oppdater for å få forbedringene</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tilgjengelighetsfunksjoner">
             <feature>• Dobbelttrykk på baksiden for å åpne en bestemt snarvei. Dette kan gi deg rask tilgang til Google Assistent, Lydopptak, Tidtaker og andre apper. Prøv det ved å gå til Innstillinger > Tilgjengelighetsfunksjoner > Snarveier og bevegelser > Dobbelttrykk på baksiden</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Optimaliserer bruken av Kamera i enkelte scenarioer</feature>
             <feature>• Forbedrer stabiliteten i Kamera i enkelte scenarioer</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitet">
             <feature>• Gjør systemet mer stabilt</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ytelse">
             <feature>• Forbedrer systemets ytelse</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sikkerhetsoppdatering">
             <feature>• Android-sikkerhetsoppdatering (okt 2025) er innlemmet for systemsikkerheten. For mer informasjon om sikkerhetsoppdateringer fra Honor, besøk nettstedet vårt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Merknader" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installeringen av denne oppdateringen påvirker ikke personopplysningene dine, men det anbefales likevel å sikkerhetskopiere dataene dine før du oppdaterer
2. Finn mer informasjon om produktfunksjoner i Tips
3. Hvis det oppstår problemer under oppdateringen, kan du få hjelp ved å ringe Honors kundeservice eller gå til Honors kundeservicesenter.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1121" name="ne-np">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, यो अपडेटले मुख्य गरी प्रणालीको कार्यसम्पादन परिष्कार गर्छ । सुधार गरिएका सुविधाहरूको आनन्द लिन अपडेट गर्नुहोस्</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="उपलब्धता सुविधाहरू">
             <feature>• खास सर्टकट लन्च गर्न पछाडि दुई पटक ट्याप गर्नुहोस् र Google सहायक, रेकर्डर, टाइमर र अन्य एपहरू द्रुत रूपमा पहुँच गर्नुहोस् । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > उपलब्धता सुविधाहरू > सर्टकट र इशाराहरू > पछाडि भागमा दुई पटक ट्याप गर्नुहोस्</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="क्यामेरा">
             <feature>• यसले केही परिदृश्यहरूमा क्यामेराको सुटिङको प्रभाव अप्टिमाइज गर्छ</feature>
             <feature>• केही परिदृश्यमा क्यामेराको स्थिरता परिष्कार गर्छ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्थिरता">
             <feature>• प्रणालीको स्थिरता सुधार गर्छ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="कार्यप्रदर्शन">
             <feature>• प्रणालीको कार्यसम्पादन सुधार गर्छ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षा प्याच">
             <feature>• एन्ड्रोइड सुरक्षा प्याच (अक्टोबर 2025) प्रणाली सुरक्षाका लागि समावेश गरिएको छ । Honor सुरक्षा अपडेटहरूबारे थप जानकारीका लागि कृपया हाम्रो वेबसाइटमा जानुहोस्: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोटहरू" type="end">
             <feature>1. तपाईंले यो एप स्थापना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटामा कुनै प्रभाव नपर्ने भए पनि तपाईंलाई अपडेट गर्नुअघि आफ्नो डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ
2. सुझावहरूमा गई उत्पादनका सुविधाहरूका बारेमा थप जानकारी हेर्नुहोस्
3. अपडेटको क्रममा तपाईंले कुनै समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईं Honor सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गरेर वा Honor ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा गएर हाम्रो मद्दत प्राप्त गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ ।</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1043" name="nl-nl">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Beste gebruiker, deze update verbetert vooral de systeemprestaties. Werk bij om van de verbeteringen te genieten</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Toegankelijkheidsfuncties">
             <feature>• Dubbeltik op de achterkant om een specifieke snelkoppeling te starten, waardoor snelle toegang tot Google Assistent, Geluidsrecorder, Timer en andere apps mogelijk is. Probeer het uit via: Instellingen > Toegankelijkheidsfuncties > Snelkoppelingen en gebaren > Dubbeltikken op de achterkant</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Camera">
             <feature>• Optimaliseert het opname-effect van Camera in bepaalde scenario's</feature>
             <feature>• Verbetert de stabiliteit van Camera in bepaalde scenario's</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabiliteit">
             <feature>• Verbetert de systeemstabiliteit</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Prestaties">
             <feature>• Verbetert de systeemprestaties</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Beveiligingspatch">
             <feature>• Android-beveiligingspatch (oktober 2025) is opgenomen voor systeembeveiliging. Voor meer informatie over Honor-beveiligingsupdates kunt u terecht op onze website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notities" type="end">
             <feature>1. Het installeren van deze update heeft geen invloed op uw persoonlijke gegevens, maar het wordt nog steeds aanbevolen om een back-up van uw gegevens te maken voordat u deze update uitvoert
2. Ontdek meer informatie over productfuncties in Tips
3. Als u tijdens de update problemen ondervindt, kunt u onze hulp krijgen door de Honor-servicehotline te bellen of naar het Honor-klantenservicecentrum te gaan.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1096" name="or-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ମୁଖ୍ୟତଃ ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ର କାର୍ଯ୍ୟଦକ୍ଷତାକୁ ବଢାଏ। ଉନ୍ନତିଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଉପଭୋଗ କରିବାକୁ ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରନ୍ତୁ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ପ୍ରବେଶଯୋଗ୍ୟ ବିଶେଷତା">
             <feature>• ଏକ ନିର୍ଦ୍ଦିଷ୍ଟ ସର୍ଟକଟ୍ ଲଞ୍ଚ କରିବା ପାଇଁ ପଛ ପଟେ ଦୁଇଥର ଟାପ୍ କରନ୍ତୁ, ଯାହା Google Assistant, ରେକର୍ଡର, ଟାଇମର୍ ଏବଂ ଅନ୍ୟାନ୍ୟ ଆପସ୍‌କୁ ଦ୍ରୁତ ଆକସେସ୍ କରିପାରିବ। ନିମ୍ନଲିଖିତକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାକୁ ବ୍ୟବହାର କରି ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ପ୍ରବେଶଯୋଗ୍ୟ ବିଶେଷତା > ସର୍ଟକଟ୍ ଏବଂ ଜେଶ୍ଚରଗୁଡିକ > ଦୁଇଥର ବ୍ୟାକ୍‌-ଟାପ୍ କରନ୍ତୁ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="କ୍ୟାମେରା">
             <feature>• କେତେକ ପରିଦୃଶ୍ୟରେ କ୍ୟାମେରାର ଶୁଟିଂ ପ୍ରଭାବକୁ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ</feature>
             <feature>• କିଛି ପରିସ୍ଥିତିରେ କ୍ୟାମେରାର ସ୍ଥିରତାକୁ ବଢାଏ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ସ୍ଥିରତା">
             <feature>• ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ ସ୍ଥିରତା ଉନ୍ନତ କରେ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ସଞ୍ଚାଳନ">
             <feature>• ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ କାର୍ଯ୍ୟଦକ୍ଷତାରେ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌">
             <feature>• Android ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ (ଅକ୍ଟୋବର 2025) ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପାଇଁ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି। Honor ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ବିଷୟରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି ଆମ ୱେବସାଇଟ୍‌ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10 ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ପ୍ରଭାବିତ ହେବ ନାହିଁ, ତଥାପି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରିବା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡାଟାର ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି
2. ଟିପ୍ସରେ ଉତ୍ପାଦ ବିଶେଷତାଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଉପରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ଆବିଷ୍କାର କରନ୍ତୁ
3. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରିବା ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ତେବେ ଆପଣ Honor ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌କୁ କଲ୍‌ କରି କିମ୍ବା Honor ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଇ, ଆମ ସହାୟତା ପାଇପାରିବେ।</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1094" name="pa-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਮੁੱਖ ਤੌਰ 'ਤੇ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੀ ਕਾਰਗੁਜ਼ਾਰੀ ਨੂੰ ਬਿਹਤਰ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਸੁਧਾਰਾਂ ਦਾ ਅਨੰਦ ਲੈਣ ਲਈ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰੋ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਪਹੁੰਚਣਯੋਗਤਾ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾਵਾਂ">
             <feature>• ਇੱਕ ਖਾਸ ਸ਼ੌਰਟਕੱਟ ਲਾਂਚ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਪਿਛਲੇ ਪਾਸੇ 'ਤੇ ਦੋ ਵਾਰ ਟੈਪ ਕਰੋ, ਜਿਸ ਨਾਲ Google ਅਸਿਸਟੈਂਟ, ਰਿਕਾਰਡਰ, ਟਾਈਮਰ, ਅਤੇ ਹੋਰ ਐਪਾਂ 'ਤੇ ਤੇਜ਼ ਐਕਸੈਸ ਸਮਰੱਥ ਹੋ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ। ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਪਹੁੰਚਣਯੋਗਤਾ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾਵਾਂ > ਸ਼ੌਰਟਕੱਟ ਅਤੇ ਸੰਕੇਤ > ਪਿਛਲੇ ਪਾਸੇ 'ਤੇ ਦੋ ਵਾਰ ਟੈਪ ਕਰੋ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਕੈਮਰਾ">
             <feature>• ਕੁਝ ਦ੍ਰਿਸ਼ਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਕੈਮਰੇ ਦੇ ਸ਼ੂਟਿੰਗ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ</feature>
             <feature>• ਕੁਝ ਦ੍ਰਿਸ਼ਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਕੈਮਰੇ ਦੀ ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਨੂੰ ਬਿਹਤਰ ਬਣਾਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਸਥਿਰਤਾ">
             <feature>• ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੀ ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੁਧਾਰ ਕਰਦੀ ਹੈ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਕਾਰਗੁਜ਼ਾਰੀ">
             <feature>• ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੀ ਕਾਰਗੁਜ਼ਾਰੀ ਨੂੰ ਸੁਧਾਰਦੀ ਹੈ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ">
             <feature>• ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਲਈ Android ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ (ਅਕਤੂਬਰ 2025) ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। Honor ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਲਈ, ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਵੈੱਬਸਾਈਟ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ਨੋਟਸ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ 'ਤੇ ਕੋਈ ਅਸਰ ਨਹੀਂ ਪਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਹਾਲੇ ਵੀ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਦਾ ਬੈਕ ਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ
2. ਸੁਝਾਅ ਐਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਉਤਪਾਦ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾਵਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਦੀ ਖੋਜ ਕਰੋ
3. ਜੇ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਕੋਈ ਵੀ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਤੁਸੀਂ Honor ਸੇਵਾ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰ ਕੇ ਜਾਂ Honor ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ ਵਿਖੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਮਦਦ ਪ੍ਰਾਪਤ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ।</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1045" name="pl-pl">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Szanowny użytkowniku, ta aktualizacja w głównej mierze podnosi wydajność systemu. Zainstaluj ją, aby korzystać z ulepszeń</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkcje ułatwień dostępu">
             <feature>• Dwukrotne dotknięcie z tyłu uruchamia określony skrót, umożliwiający szybki dostęp do Asystenta Google, Dyktafonu, Minutnika i innych aplikacji. Wypróbuj, wybierając Ustawienia > Funkcje ułatwień dostępu > Skróty i gesty > Dwukrotne dotknięcie z tyłu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Aparat">
             <feature>• Zoptymalizowano robienie zdjęć w Aparacie w niektórych sytuacjach</feature>
             <feature>• Zwiększono stabilność Aparatu w niektórych sytuacjach</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilność">
             <feature>• Poprawiono stabilność systemu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Wydajność">
             <feature>• Poprawiono wydajność systemu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Poprawka zabezpieczeń">
             <feature>• Aktualizacja zawiera Poprawkę zabezpieczeń systemu Android (październik 2025 r.). Więcej informacji o aktualizacjach zabezpieczeń urządzeń Honor można znaleźć w naszej witrynie internetowej: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notatki" type="end">
             <feature>1. Ta aktualizacja nie ma wpływu na Twoje dane osobowe, jednak przed jej zainstalowaniem zaleca się wykonanie kopii zapasowej danych
2. Więcej informacji o funkcjach produktu znajdziesz w Poradach
3. W razie jakichkolwiek problemów podczas aktualizacji możesz uzyskać pomoc, dzwoniąc na infolinię Honor lub odwiedzając punkt serwisowy Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1046" name="pt-br">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Prezado(a) usuário(a), essa atualização aprimora principalmente o desempenho do sistema. Atualize para aproveitar as melhorias</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Recursos de acessibilidade">
             <feature>• Toque duas vezes na parte de trás para abrir um atalho específico, permitindo acesso rápido ao Google Assistente, Gravador de som, Temporizador e outros aplicativos. Experimente acessando: Configurações > Recursos de acessibilidade > Atalhos e gestos > Toque duplo atrás</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Câmera">
             <feature>• Otimiza o efeito de captura da Câmera em alguns cenários</feature>
             <feature>• Aprimora a estabilidade da Câmera em alguns cenários</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilidade">
             <feature>• Melhora a estabilidade do sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Desempenho">
             <feature>• Melhora o desempenho do sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch de segurança">
             <feature>• Patch de segurança do Android (outubro de 2025) incorporado para a segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da Honor, visite nosso site: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. A instalação desta atualização não afetará os dados pessoais, mas ainda é recomendável fazer backup dos dados antes de atualizar
2. Descubra mais informações sobre os recursos do produto em Dicas
3. Se tiver algum problema durante a atualização, você poderá obter ajuda ligando para a linha de atendimento da Honor ou visitando a Central de serviços ao cliente da Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2070" name="pt-pt">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Caro utilizador, esta atualização melhora principalmente o desempenho do sistema. Atualize para aproveitar as melhorias</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funcionalidades de acessibilidade">
             <feature>• Toque duas vezes na parte posterior para iniciar um atalho específico, permitindo acesso rápido ao Assistente do Google, Gravador, Temporizador e outras aplicações. Experimente, acedendo a: Definições > Funcionalidades de acessibilidade > Atalhos e gestos > Tocar duas vezes na parte posterior</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Câmara">
             <feature>• Otimiza o efeito de disparo da Câmara em alguns cenários</feature>
             <feature>• Melhora a estabilidade da Câmara em alguns cenários</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilidade">
             <feature>• Melhora a estabilidade do sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Nível de utilização">
             <feature>• Melhora o desempenho do sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Correção de segurança">
             <feature>• Foi incorporada uma correção de segurança do Android (outubro de 2025) para segurança do sistema. Para mais informações sobre as atualizações de Segurança Honor, visite o nosso website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não afetará os seus dados pessoais, mas ainda assim é recomendável efetuar uma cópia de segurança dos seus dados antes de atualizar
2. Descobrir mais informações sobre as funcionalidades do produto em Sugestões
3. Caso se depare com algum problema durante a atualização, pode obter ajuda, contactando a linha direta de assistência Honor ou visitando o Centro de Serviços ao Cliente Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1048" name="ro-ro">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Stimate utilizator, această actualizare îmbunătățește în principal performanța sistemului. Actualizați pentru a beneficia de îmbunătățiri</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funcții de accesibilitate">
             <feature>• Atingeți de două ori butonul Înapoi pentru a lansa o comandă rapidă specifică, permițând accesul rapid la Asistentul Google, Recorder, Temporizator și alte aplicații. Încercați-l accesând: Setări > Funcții de accesibilitate > Comenzi rapide și gesturi > Atingeți de două ori spatele</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Cameră foto">
             <feature>• Optimizează efectul de fotografiere al Camerei foto în anumite situații</feature>
             <feature>• Îmbunătățește stabilitatea Camerei foto în anumite situații</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitate">
             <feature>• Îmbunătățește stabilitatea sistemului</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Performanță">
             <feature>• Îmbunătățește performanța sistemului</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Corecție de securitate">
             <feature>• Pentru securitatea sistemului, a fost încorporată o corecție de securitate Android (octombrie 2025). Pentru mai multe informații despre actualizările de securitate Honor, vă rugăm să vizitați site-ul nostru web: https://www.honor.com/ro/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notițe" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalarea acestei actualizări nu va afecta datele dvs. cu caracter personal, dar este totuși recomandat să faceți o copie de rezervă a datelor înainte de actualizare
2. Descoperiți mai multe informații despre caracteristicile produsului în Sugestii
3. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, puteți obține ajutorul nostru apelând linia telefonică de asistență Honor sau vizitând Centrul de servicii pentru clienții Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1049" name="ru-ru">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Мы выпустили это обновление, чтобы улучшить производительность системы. Установите его, чтобы оценить изменения</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Специальные возможности">
             <feature>• Дважды нажмите на обратную сторону, чтобы вызвать определенный значок для быстрого доступа к Google Ассистенту, «Диктофону», «Таймеру» и другим приложениям. Чтобы опробовать эту функцию, выберите Настройки > Специальные возможности > Быстрый доступ и жесты > Двойное касание задней крышки</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Камера">
             <feature>• Оптимизирует эффект съемки Камеры в некоторых сценариях</feature>
             <feature>• Повышает стабильность Камеры в некоторых сценариях</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Стабильность">
             <feature>• Повышает стабильность системы</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Уровень производительности">
             <feature>• Повышает производительность системы</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Исправление безопасности">
             <feature>• В обновление включено исправление безопасности для Android (октябрь 2025 г.). Чтобы получить подробную информацию об обновлениях безопасности Honor, посетите наш сайт: https://www.honor.com/eurasia/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Заметки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Установка этого обновления не приведет к удалению ваших персональных данных, но мы все равно рекомендуем вам создать резервную копию своих данных перед обновлением
2. Изучите дополнительную информацию о функциях продукта в «Советах»
3. Если у вас возникнут проблемы во время обновления, вы можете получить нашу помощь, позвонив на горячую линию службы поддержки Honor или посетив Центр обслуживания клиентов Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1115" name="si-lk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, මෙම යාවත්කාලීන කිරීම ප්‍රධාන වශයෙන් පද්ධතියේ කාර්යසාධනය උසස් කරයි. වැඩිදියුණු කිරීම් අත්විඳීමට යාවත්කාල කරන්න</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ප්‍රවේශ්‍යතා විශේෂාංග">
             <feature>• Google සහායක, රෙකෝඩරය, ටයිමරය සහ වෙනත් යෙදුම් වෙත ඉක්මන් පිවිසීම සක්‍රීය කරමින් නිශ්චිත කෙටි මඟක් දියත් කිරීමට පිටුපස ද්වි-තට්ටු කරන්න. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: සැකසුම් > ප්‍රවේශ්‍යතා විශේෂාංග > කෙටිමං සහ අභින > පසුපසට ද්වි-තට්ටු කරන්න</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="කැමරාව">
             <feature>• සමහර අවස්ථාවල දී කැමරාවේ රූගත කිරීමේ ප්‍රයෝගය ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි</feature>
             <feature>• සමහර අවස්ථාවල දී කැමරාවේ ස්ථායීතාව උසස් කරයි</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ස්ථායීතාවය">
             <feature>• පද්ධතියේ ස්ථායිතාව වැඩිදියුණු කරයි</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ක්‍රියාකාරීත්වය">
             <feature>• පද්ධතියේ කාර්ය සාධනය වැඩි දියුණු කරයි</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක">
             <feature>• පද්ධති ආරක්ෂාව සඳහා Android ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක (2025 ඔක්) යොදාගෙන ඇත. Honor ආරක්ෂක යාවත්කාල පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සඳහා, කරුණාකර අපගේ වෙබ් අඩවිය වෙත යන්න https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="සටහන්" type="end">
             <feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්තවලට බල නොපානු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් යාවත්කාල කිරීමට පෙර ඔබගේ දත්ත උපස්ථ කිරීමට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ
2. ඉඟි තුළ නිෂ්පාදන විශේෂාංග පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සොයා ගන්න
3. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේදී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, ඔබට Honor සේවා හොට්ලයින් ඇමතීමෙන් හෝ Honor පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට පිවිසීමෙන් අපගේ උපකාර ලබා ගත හැකිය.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1051" name="sk-sk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Vážený používateľ, táto aktualizácia hlavne zvyšuje výkon systému. Aktualizujte, aby ste si užili zlepšenia</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkcie uľahčenia prístupu">
             <feature>• Dvojitým ťuknutím na zadnú stranu spustíte konkrétnu skratku, ktorá umožní rýchly prístup k aplikáciám Asistent Google, Záznam zvuku, Časovač a ďalším aplikáciám. Vyskúšajte to v časti: Nastavenia > Funkcie uľahčenia prístupu > Skratky a gestá > Dvojité ťuknutie na zadnú stranu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fotoaparát">
             <feature>• Optimalizuje efekt snímania pomocou Fotoaparátu v niektorých situáciách</feature>
             <feature>• Zlepšuje stabilitu Fotoaparátu v niektorých situáciách</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilita">
             <feature>• Zlepšuje stabilitu systému</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Výkonnosť">
             <feature>• Zlepšuje výkon systému</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezpečnostná oprava">
             <feature>• Súčasťou zabezpečenia systému je bezpečnostná oprava systému Android (z októbra 2025). Ak potrebujete viac informácií o bezpečnostných aktualizáciách spoločnosti Honor, navštívte webovú stránku https://www.honor.com/sk/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Poznámky" type="end">
             <feature>1. Inštalácia tejto aktualizácie neovplyvní vaše osobné údaje, ale aj tak sa odporúča pred aktualizáciou si ich zálohovať
2. Ďalšie informácie o funkciách produktu si pozrite v aplikácii Tipy
3. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytne problém, pomoc môžete získať na zákazníckej linke Honor alebo navštívením Centra služieb zákazníkom Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1060" name="sl-si">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, ta posodobitev izboljša predvsem delovanje sistema. Posodobite, da boste lahko izkoristili izboljšave</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkcije za dostopnost">
             <feature>• Dvakrat se dotaknite hrbtne strani, da odprete posamezno bližnjico ter omogočite hitri dostop do Pomočnika Google, Snemalnika zvoka, Časovnika in drugih aplikacij. Preizkusite tukaj: Nastavitve > Funkcije za dostopnost > Bližnjice in poteze > Dvojni dotik hrbtne strani</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Optimizira učinek fotografiranja s kamero v nekaterih scenarijih</feature>
             <feature>• Izboljša stabilnost kamere v nekaterih scenarijih</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Izboljša stabilnost sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Izvajanje">
             <feature>• Izboljša delovanje sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Varnostni popravek">
             <feature>• Varnostni popravki za Android (oktober 2025) so vključeni za varnost sistema. Za več informacij o varnostnih posodobitvah Honor obiščite spletno mesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zapiski" type="end">
             <feature>1. Namestitev te posodobitve ne vpliva na vaše osebne podatke, vendar je kljub temu priporočljivo, da podatke pred posodobitvijo varnostno kopirate
2. Več informacij o funkcijah izdelka je na voljo v razdelku Nasveti
3. Če med posodabljanjem pride do težav, lahko pokličete odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom družbe Honor ali obiščete servisni center družbe Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1053" name="sv-se">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Bästa användare, den här uppdateringen förbättrar främst systemets prestanda. Uppdatera för att ta del av förbättringarna</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tillgänglighetsfunktioner">
             <feature>• Dubbeltryck på baksidan för att starta en viss genväg, vilket ger snabbåtkomst till Google Assistant, Ljudinspelare, Timer och andra appar. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Tillgänglighetsfunktioner > Genvägar och gester > Dubbeltryck på baksidan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Optimerar fotograferingseffekten för Kamera i vissa scenarier</feature>
             <feature>• Förbättrar stabiliteten för Kamera i vissa scenarier</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitet">
             <feature>• Förbättrar systemets stabilitet</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Prestanda">
             <feature>• Förbättrar systemets prestanda</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Säkerhetskorrigering">
             <feature>• Säkerhetskorrigering för Android (oktober 2025) har implementerats för systemsäkerhet. Vill du ha mer information om säkerhetsuppdateringar för Honor går du till vår webbplats https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Noteringar" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installation av den här uppdateringen påverkar inte dina personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du säkerhetskopierar alla data innan du uppdaterar
2. Upptäck mer information om produktfunktioner i Tips
3. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa Honors hotline för service eller besöka Honors servicecenter för att få hjälp.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1089" name="sw-KE">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, sasisho hili kwa kiasi kikubwa linaboresha utendaji wa mfumo. Sasisha ili ufurahie maboresho</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vipengele vya zana za walemavu">
             <feature>• Gusa mara mbili sehemu ya nyuma ili kuzindua njia mahususi ya mkato, kuwezesha ufikiaji wa haraka kwenye Kisaidizi cha Google, Kinakili Sauti, Kipima saa na programu zingine. Ijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Vipengele vya zana za walemavu > Njia za mkato na ishara > Gusa upande wa nyuma mara mbili</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Linaboresha athari ya upigaji picha ya Kamera katika baadhi ya miktadha</feature>
             <feature>• Linaboresha uthabiti wa Kamera katika baadhi ya miktadha</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Uthabiti">
             <feature>• Linaboresha uthabiti wa mfumo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Utendaji">
             <feature>• Linaboresha utendaji wa mfumo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Rekebisho la usalama">
             <feature>• Rekebisho la usalama wa Android (Okt 2025) limejumuishwa kwa ajili ya usalama wa mfumo. Ili kupata maelezo zaidi kuhusu masasisho ya Usalama wa Honor, tafadhali tembelea tovuti yetu: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Madokezo" type="end">
             <feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutaathiri data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado inapendekezwa ili kuweka hifadhi rudufu ya data yako kabla ya kusasisha
2. Gundua maelezo zaidi kwenye vipengele vya bidhaa kwenye Vidokezo
3. Ukitatizika unaposasisha, unaweza kupata usaidizi wetu kwa kupiga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya Honor au kutembelea Kituo cha Huduma kwa Wateja cha Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1097" name="ta-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு முதன்மையாக சிஸ்டம் செயல்திறனை மேம்படுத்துகிறது. மேம்பாடுகளைப் பெற, புதுப்பிக்கவும்</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="அணுகல்திறன் அம்சங்கள்">
             <feature>• குறிப்பிட்ட குறுக்குவழியைத் தொடங்க பின்புறத்தில் இருமுறை தட்டவும், இதனால் Google அசிஸ்டண்ட், ஒலிப் பதிவி, டைமர் மற்றும் பிற செயலிகளை விரைவாக அணுக முடியும். இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: அமைப்புகள் > அணுகல்திறன் அம்சங்கள் > குறுக்குவழிகள் &amp; சைகைகள் > இருமுறை பின்பக்கத்தைத் தட்டுதல்</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="கேமரா">
             <feature>• சில சூழ்நிலைகளில் கேமராவின் ஷூட்டிங் விளைவை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது</feature>
             <feature>• சில சூழ்நிலைகளில் கேமராவின் நிலைத்தன்மையை மேம்படுத்துகிறது</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="நிலைத்தன்மை">
             <feature>• சிஸ்டம் நிலைத்தன்மையை மேம்படுத்துகிறது</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="செயல்திறன்">
             <feature>• சிஸ்டம் செயல்திறனை மேம்படுத்துகிறது</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு">
             <feature>• சிஸ்டம் பாதுகாப்பிற்காக Android பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு (அக் 2025) சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. Honor பாதுகாப்புப் புதுப்பிப்புகளைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களுக்கு, எங்கள் வலைத்தளத்தைப் பார்க்கவும்: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="குறிப்புகள்" type="end">
             <feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவைப் பாதிக்காது, எனினும் புதுப்பிப்பதற்கு முன்பு உங்கள் தரவைக் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுப்பது இன்னும் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது
2. உதவிக்குறிப்புகளில் தயாரிப்பு அம்சங்களைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களைக் கண்டறிக
3. புதுப்பிக்கும்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், Honor சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைப்பதன் மூலமோ அல்லது Honor வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்தைப் பார்வையிடுவதன் மூலமோ எங்கள் உதவியைப் பெறலாம்.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1098" name="te-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారుకు, ఈ అప్‌డేట్ ప్రధానంగా సిస్టమ్ పనితీరును మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది. మెరుగుదలలను ఆనందించడానికి అప్‌డేట్ చేయండి</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="యాక్సెసబిలిటీ ఫీచర్‌లు">
             <feature>• నిర్దిష్ట సత్వరమార్గాన్ని లాంచ్ చేయడానికి వెనుక భాగాన్ని రెండుసార్లు ట్యాప్ చేయండి, ఇది Google అసిస్టెంట్, రికార్డర్, టైమర్ మరియు ఇతర అప్లికేషన్‌ల త్వరిత యాక్సెస్‌ను అనుమతిస్తుంది. ఇక్కడికి వెళ్ళి దానిని ప్రయత్నించండి: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > యాక్సెసబిలిటీ ఫీచర్‌లు > సత్వరమార్గాలు &amp; సంజ్ఞలు > వెనుకన రెండుసార్లు ట్యాప్</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="కెమెరా">
             <feature>• కొన్ని సందర్భాల్లో కెమెరా షూటింగ్ ప్రభావాన్ని ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది</feature>
             <feature>• కొన్ని సందర్భాల్లో కెమెరా స్థిరత్వాన్ని మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="స్థిరత్వం">
             <feature>• సిస్టమ్ స్థిరత్వాన్ని మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="పనితీరు">
             <feature>• సిస్టమ్ పనితీరు మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="భద్రతా ప్యాచ్">
             <feature>• సిస్టమ్ భద్రత కోసం Android భద్రతా ప్యాచ్ (అక్టో 2025) చేర్చబడింది. Honor భద్రత అప్‌డేట్‌ల గురించి మరింత సమాచారం కోసం, దయచేసి మా వెబ్‌సైట్‌ను సందర్శించండి: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="గమనికలు" type="end">
             <feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్ ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వలన మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటా ప్రభావితం కాదు, కాని అప్‌డేట్ చేయడానికి ముందు మీ డేటాను బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని ఇంకా సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది
2. చిట్కాల్లో ఉత్పత్తి ఫీచర్లపై మరింత సమాచారాన్ని తెలుసుకోండి
3. మీరు అప్‌డేట్‌లో ఏవైనా సమస్యలను ఎదుర్కొంటే, మీరు Honor సేవా హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేయడం లేదా Honor కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రాన్ని సందర్శించడం ద్వారా మా సహాయం పొందవచ్చు.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1054" name="th-th">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตครั้งนี้เน้นปรับปรุงประสิทธิภาพระบบเป็นหลัก โปรดอัปเดตเพื่อใช้การปรับปรุง</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ฟีเจอร์การเข้าถึง">
             <feature>• แตะสองครั้งที่ด้านหลังเพื่อเปิดใช้งานทางลัดที่เฉพาะเจาะจง เปิดใช้งานการเข้าถึงด่วนไปยังผู้ช่วย Google, เครื่องบันทึกเสียง, ตัวจับเวลา และแอปอื่นๆ ลองใช้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > ฟีเจอร์การเข้าถึง > ทางลัดและท่าทางสัมผัส > แตะที่ด้านหลังสองครั้ง</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="กล้องถ่ายรูป">
             <feature>• ปรับปรุงเอฟเฟ็กต์การถ่ายของกล้องถ่ายรูปในบางสถานการณ์</feature>
             <feature>• ปรับปรุงความเสถียรของกล้องถ่ายรูปในบางสถานการณ์</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ความเสถียร">
             <feature>• ปรับปรุงความเสถียรของระบบ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ประสิทธิภาพ">
             <feature>• ปรับปรุงประสิทธิภาพของระบบ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="แพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัย">
             <feature>• มีการรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัย Android (ต.ค. 2025) เพื่อความปลอดภัยของระบบ ดูข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับการอัปเดตด้านความปลอดภัยของ Honor ได้โดยไปที่เว็บไซต์ของเรา https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="โน้ต" type="end">
             <feature>1. การติดตั้งการอัปเดตนี้จะไม่ส่งผลต่อข้อมูลส่วนตัว แต่เราขอแนะนำให้คุณสำรองข้อมูลก่อนอัปเดต
2. ค้นพบข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับฟีเจอร์ผลิตภัณฑ์ในเคล็ดลับ
3. หากคุณพบปัญหาใดๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต โปรดโทรติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการลูกค้าของ Honor หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ Honor เพื่อขอความช่วยเหลือจากเรา</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1124" name="tl-ph">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Minamahal na user, pangunahing pinapahusay ng update na ito ang performance ng system. I-update para i-enjoy ang mga pagpapahusay</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Mga feature ng accessibility">
             <feature>• I-tap nang dalawang beses ang likod para maglunsad ng partikular na shortcut, na nagbibigay-daan sa mabilisang pag-access sa Google Assistant, Recorder, Timer, at iba pang app. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Mga feature ng accessibility > Mga shortcut at gesture > Pindutin nang dalawang beses ang likod</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Camera">
             <feature>• Ino-optimize ang effect sa pag-shoot ng Camera sa ilang sitwasyon</feature>
             <feature>• Pinapahusay ang stability ng Camera sa ilang sitwasyon</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stability">
             <feature>• Pinapahusay ang stability ng system</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pagganap">
             <feature>• Pinapahusay ang performance ng system</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Panseguridad na patch">
             <feature>• Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Okt 2025) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa mga Panseguridad na update ng Honor, bisitahin ang aming website sa https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Mga Tala" type="end">
             <feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto ang pag-install sa update na ito sa iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update
2. Tuklasin ang higit pang impormasyon sa mga feature ng produkto sa Mga Tip
3. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, makukuha mo ang tulong namin sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng Honor o pagbisita sa Customer Service Center ng Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1055" name="tr-tr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Değerli kullanıcımız, bu güncelleme ile çoğunlukla sistem performansı artırılmıştır. İyileştirmelerin tadını çıkarmak için güncelleyin</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Erişilebilirlik özellikleri">
             <feature>• Belirli bir kısayolu başlatmak için cihazın arkasına iki kez dokunun. Bu; Google Asistan, Ses Kaydedici, Zamanlayıcı ve diğer uygulamalara hızlı erişim sağlar. Şu adımları takip ederek deneyebilirsiniz: Ayarlar > Erişilebilirlik özellikleri > Kısayollar ve hareketler > Arkaya çift dokunma</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Bazı senaryolarda Kameranın fotoğraf çekme efekti optimize edildi</feature>
             <feature>• Bazı senaryolarda Kamera kararlılığı artırıldı</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kararlılık">
             <feature>• Sistem kararlılığı iyileştirildi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Performans">
             <feature>• Sistem performansı iyileştirildi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Güvenlik yaması">
             <feature>• Sistem güvenliği için Android güvenlik yamasını (Ekim 2025) içermektedir. Honor Güvenlik güncellemeleri ile ilgili daha fazla bilgi için lütfen web sitemizi ziyaret edin: https://www.honor.com/tr/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notlar" type="end">
             <feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi etkilemeyecektir ancak yine de güncellemeden önce verilerinizi yedeklemeniz önerilir
2. İpuçları bölümünden ürün özellikleri hakkında daha fazla bilgiyi keşfedin
3. Güncelleme sırasında herhangi bir sorunla karşılaşırsanız Honor servis yardım hattını arayarak veya Honor Müşteri Hizmetleri Merkezini ziyaret ederek yardım alabilirsiniz.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1058" name="uk-ua">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Шановний користувачу! Це оновлення насамперед підвищує продуктивність системи. Установіть його, щоб відчути покращення</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Функції спеціальних можливостей">
             <feature>• Двічі торкніться задньої панелі, щоб запустити певний ярлик, який забезпечує швидкий доступ до додатків "Google Асистент", "Звукозапис", "Таймер" тощо. Щоб спробувати, перейдіть до меню: Налаштування > Функції спеціальних можливостей > Ярлики та жести > Подвійне торкання задньої панелі</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Камера">
             <feature>• Оптимізовано процес знімання Камерою в деяких сценаріях</feature>
             <feature>• Підвищено стабільність роботи Камери в деяких сценаріях</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Стабільність">
             <feature>• Покращено стабільність роботи системи</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Продуктивність">
             <feature>• Підвищено продуктивність роботи системи</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Виправлення системи безпеки">
             <feature>• Виправлення безпеки Android від жовтня 2025 року впроваджено для посилення безпеки системи. Додаткову інформацію про оновлення для системи безпеки Honor див. на нашому вебсайті https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Нотатки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Установлення цього оновлення не вплине на ваші особисті дані, однак рекомендовано спочатку створити їхні резервні копії
2. Дізнайтеся більше про функції продукту в розділі "Підказки"
3. Якщо під час оновлення у вас виникнуть проблеми, ви можете отримати допомогу, зателефонувавши на гарячу лінію обслуговування клієнтів Honor або відвідавши сервісний центр Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1056" name="ur-pk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>محترم صارف، یہ اپ ڈیٹ بنیادی طور پر سسٹم کی کارکردگی کو بڑھاتی ہے۔ بہتریوں سے لطف اندوز ہونے کے لیے اپ ڈیٹ کریں</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="رسائی پذیری کی خصوصیات">
             <feature>‏• Google اسِسٹنٹ، ریکارڈر، ٹائمر اور دیگر ایپس تک جلدی رسائی کو فعال کر کے، مخصوص شارٹ کٹ شروع کرنے کے لیے پیچھے دو مرتبہ ٹیپ کریں۔ یہاں جا کر اسے آزمائیں: ترتیبات > رسائی پذیری کی خصوصیات > شارٹ کٹس اور اشارے > دو مرتبہ واپس ٹیپ کریں</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="کیمرہ">
             <feature>‏‏• کچھ منظرناموں میں کیمرے کے شوٹنگ کے اثر کو بہتر بناتی ہے</feature>
             <feature>‏‏• کچھ منظرناموں میں کیمرہ کے استحکام کو بڑھاتی ہے</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="استحکام">
             <feature>‏‏• سسٹم کے استحکام کو بہتر بناتی ہے</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="کارکردگی">
             <feature>‏‏• سسٹم کی کارکردگی کو بہتر بناتی ہے</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="سکیورٹی پیچ">
             <feature>‏• Android سکیورٹی پیچ (اکتوبر 2025) شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔ Honor سکیورٹی اپ ڈیٹس کے بارے میں مزید معلومات کے لیے، براہ کرم ہماری ویب سائٹ ملاحظہ کریں: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="نوٹس" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا متاثر نہیں ہو گا، لیکن اپ ڈیٹ کرنے سے پہلے اب بھی اپنے ڈیٹا کا بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے
‏2. تجاویز میں پروڈکٹس کی خصوصیات کے بارے میں مزید معلومات دریافت کریں
‏3. اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کوئی مسئلہ درپیش ہوتا ہے، تو آپ آنر سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کر کے یا آنر کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جا کر ہماری مدد حاصل کر سکتے ہیں۔</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2115" name="uz-uz">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu yangilanish asosan tizim unumdorligini oshiradi. Takomillashtirishlardan foydalanish uchun yangilang</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Maxsus imkoniyatlar funksiyalari">
             <feature>• Google Assistent, Diktofon, Taymer va boshqa ilovalarga tezkor kirish imkonini beradigan maxsus tezkor amalni ishga tushirish uchun orqa tomonni ikki marta bosing. Bu yerda sinang: Sozlamalar > Maxsus imkoniyatlar funksiyalari > Tezkor tugmalar va imo-ishoralar > Ikki marta orqaga teginish</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Ayrim holatlardagi Kamera tasvirga olish effekti optimallandi</feature>
             <feature>• Kameraning ayrim holatlardagi barqarorligi oshirildi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Barqarorlik">
             <feature>• Tizim barqarorligi yaxshilandi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Unumdorlik">
             <feature>• Tizim unumdorligi oshirildi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Xavfsizlik tuzatmasi">
             <feature>• Tizim xavfsizligi uchun Android xavfsizlik tuzatmasi (2025-yil, oktabr) kiritildi. Honor Xavfsizlik yangilanishlari haqida batafsil axborot olish uchun veb-saytimizga tashrif buyuring: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Eslatmalar" type="end">
             <feature>1. Bu yangilanishni oʻrnatish shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringizga taʼsir qilmaydi, lekin yangilashdan oldin maʼlumotlaringizni zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi
2. Maslahatlar ilovasida mahsulot xususiyatlari bilan batafsilroq tanishing
3. Agar yangilash paytida biror muammoga duch kelsangiz, Honor xizmatining tezkor raqamiga telefon qilish yoki Honor mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyurish orqali yordam olishingiz mumkin.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1066" name="vi-vn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật này chủ yếu nâng cao hiệu suất hệ thống. Hãy cập nhật để tận hưởng các cải tiến</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tính năng Trợ năng">
             <feature>• Chạm đúp vào mặt sau để mở một lối tắt cụ thể, cho phép truy cập nhanh vào Google Assistant, Máy ghi âm, Bộ hẹn giờ và các ứng dụng khác. Hãy thử bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Tính năng Trợ năng > Lối tắt &amp; cử chỉ > Chạm hai lần vào mặt lưng</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Máy ảnh">
             <feature>• Tối ưu hóa hiệu ứng quay/chụp của Máy ảnh trong một số tình huống</feature>
             <feature>• Cải thiện độ ổn định của Máy ảnh trong một số tình huống</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Độ ổn định">
             <feature>• Cải thiện độ ổn định của hệ thống</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Hiệu suất">
             <feature>• Cải thiện hiệu suất hệ thống</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bản vá bảo mật">
             <feature>• Bản cập nhật này tích hợp Bản vá bảo mật Android (tháng 10 năm 2025) để bảo mật hệ thống. Để biết thêm thông tin về các Bản cập nhật bảo mật của Honor, vui lòng truy cập trang web của chúng tôi: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Ghi chú" type="end">
             <feature>1. Việc cài đặt bản cập nhật này sẽ không ảnh hưởng đến dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn, nhưng bạn vẫn nên sao lưu dữ liệu trước khi cập nhật
2. Khám phá thêm thông tin về các tính năng sản phẩm trong ứng dụng Mẹo
3. Nếu bạn gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, bạn có thể nhận được sự trợ giúp của chúng tôi bằng cách gọi đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ hoặc đến Trung tâm Dịch vụ Khách hàng của Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="3076" name="zh-hk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新主要針對系統進行了優化，建議您進行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="輔助功能">
             <feature>•  新增敲擊背部兩次啟動指定快捷功能，助您快速啟用 Google 助理、錄音機、計時器等應用程式。操作路徑：設定 > 輔助功能 > 捷徑及手勢 > 敲擊背部兩次</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="相機">
             <feature>• 優化部分場景相機拍攝效果</feature>
             <feature>• 提升部分場景相機使用穩定性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="穩定性">
             <feature>• 提升系統穩定性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="性能">
             <feature>• 優化系統性能</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安全性修補程式">
             <feature>• 整合 Android 2025年10月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需了解有關榮耀軟件安全更新內容的資訊，請瀏覽榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="更新注意事項" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份
2. 更多精彩功能介紹，請瀏覽「玩機技巧」應用程式
3. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線，或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1028" name="zh-tw">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新主要針對系統進行了最佳化，建議您進行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="無障礙功能">
             <feature>•  新增敲擊背蓋兩次啟動指定捷徑功能，幫您快速開啟 Google 助理、錄音程式、計時器等應用程式。操作路徑：設定 > 無障礙功能 > 捷徑啟動及手勢 > 敲擊背蓋兩次</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="相機">
             <feature>• 最佳化在部分場景下的相機拍攝效果</feature>
             <feature>• 提升在部分場景下的相機使用穩定性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="穩定性">
             <feature>• 提升系統穩定性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="效能">
             <feature>• 最佳化系統效能</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安全性修補程式">
             <feature>• 整合 Android 2025 年 10 月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟體安全更新內容的資訊，請造訪榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="更新注意事項" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份
2. 如需更多精彩功能介紹，請查看「玩機技巧」應用程式
3. 在更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1152" name="ug-cn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا ئاساسلىقى سىستېمىغا قارىتا ئەلالاشتۇرۇش ئېلىپ بېرىلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ياردەمچى ئىقتىدار">
             <feature>‏•  ئارقا تەرىپىنى ئىككى چېكىش ئارقىلىق بەلگىلەنگەن تېزلەتمە ئىقتىدارنى قوزغىتىش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، Google ياردەمچىسى، ئۈنئالغۇ، ۋاقىت ھېسابلىغۇچ قاتارلىق ئەپلەرنى تېزلىكتە قوزغىتىشىڭىزغا ياردەم بېرىدۇ. مەشغۇلات يولى: تەڭشەك > ياردەمچى ئىقتىدار > تېزلەتمە ۋە ئىشارە > ‏ئارقا تەرىپىنى ئىككى چېكىش</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏كامېرا">
             <feature>‏• كامېرانىڭ بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى سۈرەتكە ئېلىش ئۈنۈمى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى</feature>
             <feature>‏• بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى كامېرانى ئىشلىتىش مۇقىملىقى يۇقىرى كۆتۈرۈلدى</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏مۇقىملىق">
             <feature>‏• سىستېمىنىڭ مۇقىملىقى يۇقىرى كۆتۈرۈلدى</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ئىقتىدار">
             <feature>‏• سىستېما ئىقتىدارى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى">
             <feature>‏• ئاندرويدنىڭ 2025-يىل 10-ئايلىق بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، سىستېما بىخەتەرلىكى كۈچەيتىلدى. روڭياۋ يۇمشاق دېتالىنىڭ بىخەتەرلىك يېڭىلاش مەزمۇنىغا ئالاقىدار ئۇچۇرلار ئۈچۈن روڭياۋ ئورگان تەرەپ تور بېكىتى https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/10 نى زىيارەت قىلىڭ.</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="‏يېڭىلاش بىلدۈرگۈسى" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، لېكىن يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتنى زاپاسلاشنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز
‏2. تېخىمۇ كۆپ سەرخىل ئىقتىدارلارنى «ئىشلىتىش كۆرسەتمىسى» ئەپىنى زىيارەت قىلىپ كۆرۈڭ
‏3. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركا مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1031" name="de-at">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung verbessert hauptsächlich die Systemleistung. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bedienungshilfen">
             <feature>• Tippen Sie doppelt auf die Rückseite, um eine bestimmte Verknüpfung zu starten, die Schnellzugriff auf Google Assistant, Rekorder, Timer und andere Apps ermöglicht. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Bedienungshilfen > Verknüpfungen und Gesten > Doppeltes Tippen auf die Rückseite</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Optimiert den Aufnahmeeffekt der Kamera in einigen Szenarien</feature>
             <feature>• Verbessert die Stabilität der Kamera in einigen Szenarien</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilität">
             <feature>• Verbessert die Systemstabilität</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Leistung">
             <feature>• Verbessert die Systemleistung</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sicherheitspatch">
             <feature>• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Okt. 2025) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die Honor Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notizen" type="end">
             <feature>1. Die Installation dieses Updates hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, es wird jedoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen
2. Entdecken Sie weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen in Tipps
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Honor-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein Honor-Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1031" name="de-ch">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung verbessert hauptsächlich die Systemleistung. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bedienungshilfen">
             <feature>• Tippen Sie doppelt auf die Rückseite, um eine bestimmte Verknüpfung zu starten, die Schnellzugriff auf Google Assistant, Rekorder, Timer und andere Apps ermöglicht. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Bedienungshilfen > Verknüpfungen und Gesten > Doppeltes Tippen auf die Rückseite</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Optimiert den Aufnahmeeffekt der Kamera in einigen Szenarien</feature>
             <feature>• Verbessert die Stabilität der Kamera in einigen Szenarien</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilität">
             <feature>• Verbessert die Systemstabilität</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Leistung">
             <feature>• Verbessert die Systemleistung</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sicherheitspatch">
             <feature>• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Okt. 2025) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die Honor Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notizen" type="end">
             <feature>1. Die Installation dieses Updates hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, es wird jedoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen
2. Entdecken Sie weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen in Tipps
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Honor-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein Honor-Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1036" name="fr-ch">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour améliore principalement les performances du système. Effectuez la mise à jour pour profiter des améliorations</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fonctionnalités d'accessibilité">
             <feature>• Appuyez deux fois sur l'arrière pour lancer un raccourci spécifique, permettant un accès rapide à Google Assistant, Enregistreur sonore, Minuteur et d'autres applications. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Fonctionnalités d'accessibilité > Raccourcis &amp; gestes > Double appui à l'arrière</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Appareil photo">
             <feature>• Optimise l'effet de prise de vue d'Appareil photo dans certains scénarios</feature>
             <feature>• Améliore la stabilité d'Appareil photo dans certains scénarios</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilité">
             <feature>• Améliore la stabilité du système</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Intensité d'utilisation">
             <feature>• Améliore les performances du système</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Correctif de sécurité">
             <feature>• Un correctif de sécurité Android (octobre 2025) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité Honor, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour
2. Découvrez plus d'informations sur les fonctionnalités du produit dans Astuces
3. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes pendant la mise à jour, vous pouvez obtenir de l'aide en contactant la hotline de service Honor ou en vous rendant dans un centre de services clients Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1040" name="it-ch">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento migliora principalmente le prestazioni del sistema. Esegui l'aggiornamento per usufruire dei miglioramenti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funzioni accessibilità">
             <feature>• È possibile avviare una scorciatoia specifica toccando due volte il retro del dispositivo, per accedere rapidamente all'Assistente Google, al Registratore, al Timer e ad altre app. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Funzioni accessibilità > Scorciatoie e gesture > Doppio tocco posteriore</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fotocamera">
             <feature>• Viene ottimizzato l'effetto di scatto della Fotocamera in alcuni scenari</feature>
             <feature>• Viene migliorata la stabilità della Fotocamera in alcuni scenari</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilità">
             <feature>• Viene migliorata la stabilità del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Prestazioni">
             <feature>• Sono state migliorate le prestazioni del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch di sicurezza">
             <feature>• È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (ottobre 2025) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza Honor, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Note" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup dei dati prima di procedere
2. Scopri ulteriori informazioni sulle funzioni del prodotto in Suggerimenti
3. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center Honor o visitando un Servizio clienti Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2074" name="sr-ba">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se unapređuju performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u unapređenjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkcije pristupačnosti">
             <feature>• Dvaput dodirnite poleđinu da biste pokrenuli određenu prečicu, omogućavajući brzi pristup Google pomoćniku, Snimaču zvuka, Tajmeru i drugim aplikacijama. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići u opciju: Podešavanja > Funkcije pristupačnosti > Prečice i pokreti > Dvostruki dodir zadnjeg dela uređaja</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Optimizuje učinak snimanja Kamere u pojedinim situacijama</feature>
             <feature>• Povećava stabilnost Kamere u nekim situacijama</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Poboljšava stabilnost sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Učinak">
             <feature>• Poboljšava performanse sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezbednosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (oktobar 2025.) radi bezbednosti sistema. Za još informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima kompanije Honor, posetite naš veb-sajt https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zabeleške" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka pre ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o karakteristikama proizvoda u odeljku Saveti
3. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, možete da dobijete našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati dežurnu liniju Honor servisa ili posetiti Centar za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2074" name="sr-me">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se unapređuju performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u unapređenjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkcije pristupačnosti">
             <feature>• Dvaput dodirnite poleđinu da biste pokrenuli određenu prečicu, omogućavajući brzi pristup Google pomoćniku, Snimaču zvuka, Tajmeru i drugim aplikacijama. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići u opciju: Podešavanja > Funkcije pristupačnosti > Prečice i pokreti > Dvostruki dodir zadnjeg dela uređaja</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Optimizuje učinak snimanja Kamere u pojedinim situacijama</feature>
             <feature>• Povećava stabilnost Kamere u nekim situacijama</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Poboljšava stabilnost sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Učinak">
             <feature>• Poboljšava performanse sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezbednosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (oktobar 2025.) radi bezbednosti sistema. Za još informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima kompanije Honor, posetite naš veb-sajt https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zabeleške" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka pre ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o karakteristikama proizvoda u odeljku Saveti
3. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, možete da dobijete našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati dežurnu liniju Honor servisa ili posetiti Centar za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1057" name="id-">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini utamanya meningkatkan kinerja sistem. Instal pembaruan untuk menikmati berbagai peningkatan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fitur aksesibilitas">
             <feature>• Ketuk dua kali bagian belakang untuk meluncurkan pintasan spesifik, yang memungkinkan akses cepat ke Asisten Google, Perekam Suara, Pengatur waktu, dan aplikasi lainnya. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Fitur aksesibilitas > Pintasan &amp; gerakan > Ketuk bagian belakang dua kali</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Mengoptimalkan efek pengambilan gambar Kamera di beberapa skenario</feature>
             <feature>• Meningkatkan stabilitas Kamera di beberapa skenario</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitas">
             <feature>• Meningkatkan stabilitas sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kinerja">
             <feature>• Meningkatkan kinerja sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Penambal keamanan">
             <feature>• Penambal keamanan Android (Okt 2025) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan Honor, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Catatan" type="end">
             <feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan untuk mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui
2. Pelajari informasi selengkapnya terkait fitur produk di Kiat
3. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan Honor atau mengunjungi Pusat Layanan Pelanggan Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1037" name="he-">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה משפר בעיקר את ביצועי המערכת. עדכן כדי ליהנות מהשיפורים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="תכונות נגישות">
             <feature>‏• הקש פעמיים על גב ההתקן כדי להפעיל קיצור דרך ספציפי, המאפשר גישה מהירה ל-Google Assistant, ל'רשמקול', ל'טיימר' וליישומים אחרים. כדי לנסות, אפשר לעבור אל: הגדרות > תכונות נגישות > קיצורים ומחוות > הקש פעמיים על גב ההתקן</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="מצלמה">
             <feature>‏‏• ממטב את אפקט הצילום של המצלמה בתרחישים מסוימים</feature>
             <feature>‏‏• משפר את יציבות המצלמה בתרחישים מסוימים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="יציבות">
             <feature>‏‏• משפר את יציבות המערכת</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ביצועים">
             <feature>‏‏• משפר את ביצועי המערכת</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="תיקון אבטחה">
             <feature>‏• 'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מאוקט' 2025) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של Honor', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="הערות" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון
‏2. גלה מידע נוסף על תכונות המוצר ב'טיפים'
‏3. אם נתקלת בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, תוכל לקבל עזרה מאיתנו על ידי התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של Honor או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1124" name="fil-ph">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Minamahal na user, pangunahing pinapahusay ng update na ito ang performance ng system. I-update para i-enjoy ang mga pagpapahusay</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Mga feature ng accessibility">
             <feature>• I-tap nang dalawang beses ang likod para maglunsad ng partikular na shortcut, na nagbibigay-daan sa mabilisang pag-access sa Google Assistant, Recorder, Timer, at iba pang app. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Mga feature ng accessibility > Mga shortcut at gesture > Pindutin nang dalawang beses ang likod</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Camera">
             <feature>• Ino-optimize ang effect sa pag-shoot ng Camera sa ilang sitwasyon</feature>
             <feature>• Pinapahusay ang stability ng Camera sa ilang sitwasyon</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stability">
             <feature>• Pinapahusay ang stability ng system</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pagganap">
             <feature>• Pinapahusay ang performance ng system</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Panseguridad na patch">
             <feature>• Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Okt 2025) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa mga Panseguridad na update ng Honor, bisitahin ang aming website sa https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/10</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Mga Tala" type="end">
             <feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto ang pag-install sa update na ito sa iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update
2. Tuklasin ang higit pang impormasyon sa mga feature ng produkto sa Mga Tip
3. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, makukuha mo ang tulong namin sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng Honor o pagbisita sa Customer Service Center ng Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <imgs>
            </imgs>
</root>