<root>
    <component name="TCPU" version="请自行修改"></component>
    <default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
    <language code="2052" name="zh-cn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新主要针对系统进行了优化，推荐您进行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="相机">
             <feature>•  新增息屏录像功能，体验路径：相机 > 设置 > 熄屏录制</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="桌面">
             <feature>•  新增通透模式，提升卡片、文件夹等元素的通透效果，带来极致通透体验。体验路径：设置 > 桌面和个性化 > 桌面设置 > 通透模式</feature>
             <feature>•  新增长按桌面空白区域进入编辑模式功能</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="锁屏">
             <feature>•  新增多种锁屏时钟样式，体验路径：锁屏双指捏合 > 自定义 > 点击时钟即可编辑</feature>
             <feature>•  新增密码解锁和控制中心界面按压通透光感效果</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="状态栏">
             <feature>•  新增状态栏图标自定义功能，可自由选择需要显示的状态栏图标。体验路径：设置 > 通知和状态栏 > 状态栏</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="灵动胶囊">
             <feature>•  新增人脸解锁接入胶囊。体验路径：设置 > 通知和状态栏 > 灵动胶囊 > 人脸识别</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="荣耀互联">
             <feature>•  新增支持荣耀手机之间的一碰传，实现文件高速传输，好玩又快捷，体验路径：设置 > 更多连接 > 一碰传</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="性能">
             <feature>•  优化部分场景使用卡顿问题，提升整机流畅性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="稳定性">
             <feature>•  提升系统稳定性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安全补丁">
             <feature>•  合入安卓 2025 年 11 月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="更新注意事项" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份
2. 更多精彩功能介绍，请访问“玩机技巧”应用
3. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="en-us">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Dear user, this update mainly enhances the system performance. Update to enjoy the improvements</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Camera">
             <feature>• Screen-off recording is now available. Try it out by going to: Camera > Settings > Screen-off recording</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Home screen">
             <feature>• Transparency mode optimizes the transparency effects of elements such as cards and folders, delivering an exceptional visual experience. Try it out by going to: Settings > Home screen &amp; style > Home screen settings > Transparency mode</feature>
             <feature>• Long press the blank area of the home screen to start editing</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Lock screen">
             <feature>• The lock screen offers more clock styles. Pinch with two fingers on the lock screen, tap Custom, then tap the clock to edit</feature>
             <feature>• A tactile light effect responds to your tap on the password unlock screen and in Control Center</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Status bar">
             <feature>• Status bar enables icon customization, allowing you to choose which status bar icons to display. Try it out by going to: Settings > Notifications &amp; status bar > Status bar</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic Capsule">
             <feature>• Face recognition is integrated into Magic Capsule. Try it out by going to: Settings > Notifications &amp; status bar > Magic Capsule > Face recognition</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap enables seamless file transfer between Honor devices, combining speed with ease and fun. Try it out by going to: Settings > More connections > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Performance">
             <feature>• Resolves the occasional stuttering issues to enhance the overall smoothness of the device</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stability">
             <feature>• Improves the system stability</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Security patch">
             <feature>• Android security patch (Nov 2025) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about Honor Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating
2. Discover more information on product features in Tips
3. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling Honor service hotline or visiting Honor customer service center</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1118" name="am-ET">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ ይህ ዝማኔ በዋነኛነት የስርዓቱን አፈጻጸም ያሻሽላል። በማሻሻያዎቹ ለመደሰት ያዘምኑ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ካሜራ">
             <feature>• ከማያ ውጭ ቀረጻ አሁን ይገኛል። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ካሜራ > ቅንብሮች > ከማያ ውጭ ቀረጻ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="መነሻ ገጽ">
             <feature>• የግልጽነት ሁነታው እንደ ካርዶች እና አቃፊዎች ያሉ የክፍለ-አካላት የግልጽነት ተጽዕኖዎችን ያተባል፣ በዚህም ልዩ የሆነ ምስላዊ ተሞክሮን ያቀርባል። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > መነሻ ማያ ገጽ እና ቅጥ > የመነሻ ማያ ቅንብሮች > የግልጽነት ሁነታ</feature>
             <feature>• አርትዖት ለመጀመር የመነሻ ማያው ባዶ ቦታ በረጅሙ ይጫኑ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ማያን መቆለፊያ">
             <feature>• የመቆለፊያ ማያው ተጨማሪ የሰዓት ቅጦችን ያቀርባል። በመቆለፊያ ማያው ላይ በሁለት ጣቶች ይቆንጥጡ፣ ብጁን መታ ያድርጉ፣ ከዚያ ለማርትዕ ሰዓቱን መታ ያድርጉት</feature>
             <feature>• እርስዎ በይለፍ ቃል መክፈቻ ማያ ላይ እና በመቆጣጠሪያ ማዕከል ውስጥ መታ ሲያደርጉ የሚዳሰስ የብርሃን ተጽዕኖ ምላሽ ይሰጣል</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="የሁኔታ አሞሌ">
             <feature>• የሁኔታ አሞሌ አዶን ማበጀትን ያስችላል፣ በዚህም እርስዎ የትኛዎቹ የሁኔታ አሞሌ አዶዎች እንዲታዩ እንዲመርጡ ያስችልዎታል። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > ማሳወቂያዎች እና ሁኔታ አሞሌ > ሁኔታ አሞሌ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="አስማታዊ ካፕሱል">
             <feature>• ፊት ማወቂያ ከአስማታዊ ካፕሱል ጋር ተዋህዷል። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > ማሳወቂያዎች እና ሁኔታ አሞሌ > አስማታዊ ካፕሱል > ፊት ማወቂያ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ግንኙነት">
             <feature>• OneTap ፍጥነትን ከቅለት እና መዝናኛ ጋር በማጣመር በHonor መሳሪያዎች መካከል እንከን የለሽ የፋይል ማስተላለፍን ያስችላል። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > ተጨማሪ ግንኙነቶች > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="አፈጻጸም">
             <feature>• የመሳሪያውን አጠቃላይ ለስላሳነት ለማሻሻል አልፎ አልፎ የመንተባተብ ችግሮችን ይፈታል</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="መረጋጋት">
             <feature>• የስርዓቱን እርጋታ ያሻሽላል</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="የደህንነት መጠገኛ">
             <feature>• የአንድሮይድ የደህንነት መጠገኛ (ኖቬምበር 2025) ለስርዓት ደህንነት ተካትቷል። ስለHonor ደህንነት ዝማኔዎች ተጨማሪ መረጃ ለማግኘት እባክዎ የእኛን ድረ-ገጽ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11 ይጎብኙ</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ማስታወሻዎች" type="end">
             <feature>1. ይህን ዝማኔ መጫን በእርስዎ የግል ውሂብ ላይ ተጽዕኖ አያሳርፍም፣ ነገር ግን አሁንም ከማዘመንዎ በፊት የውሂብዎን መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ ይመከራል
2. በጠቃሚ ምክሮች ውስጥ ስለምርት ባህሪያት ተጨማሪ መረጃ ያግኙ
3. በዝማኔው ጊዜ ማናቸውም ችግሮች ካጋጠሙዎት ወደ የHonor አገልግሎት ቀጥታ መስመር በመደወል ወይም የHonor ደንበኛ አገልግሎት ማዕከልን በመጎብኘት የእኛን እርዳታ ማግኘት ይችላሉ</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="3073" name="ar-eg">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، يحسّن هذا التحديث أداء النظام بشكل أساسي. للاستمتاع بالتحسينات، ما عليك سوى التحديث</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="الكاميرا">
             <feature>• التسجيل مع إيقاف تشغيل الشاشة متاح الآن. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الكاميرا > الإعدادات > تسجيل مع إيقاف تشغيل الشاشة</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="الشاشة الرئيسية">
             <feature>• يحسّن وضع الشفافية تأثيرات الشفافية على عناصر مثل البطاقات والمجلدات، مما يؤدي إلى تقديم تجربة بصرية استثنائية. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > الشاشة الرئيسية والنمط > إعدادات الشاشة الرئيسية > وضع الشفافية</feature>
             <feature>• اضغط مطولاً على المنطقة الفارغة من الشاشة الرئيسية لبدء التعديل</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="شاشة القفل">
             <feature>• توفر شاشة القفل المزيد من أنماط الساعة. ضع إصبعين على شاشة القفل وضمهما لبعضهما، واضغط على مخصص، ثم اضغط على الساعة لإجراء التعديل</feature>
             <feature>• يستجيب تأثير إضاءة لمسي عندما تضغط على شاشة إلغاء القفل بكلمة مرور وفي مركز التحكم</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="شريط الحالة">
             <feature>• يمكّن شريط الحالة تخصيص الأيقونات، مما يسمح لك باختيار أيقونات شريط الحالة التي تريد عرضها. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > الإشعارات وشريط الحالة > شريط الحالة</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏Magic Capsule">
             <feature>• تم دمج ميزة التعرف على الوجه في Magic Capsule. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > الإشعارات وشريط الحالة > ‏Magic Capsule > التعرف على الوجه</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="الاتصال من Honor">
             <feature>• تسمح ميزة OneTap بنقل الملفات بسلاسة بين أجهزة Honor، مما يجمع بين السرعة والسهولة والمتعة. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > طرق توصيل أخرى > ‏OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="الأداء">
             <feature>• يحل مشاكل التقطّع العرضية لتحسين سلاسة الجهاز بشكل عام</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="الاستقرار">
             <feature>• يحسّن استقرار النظام</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="تصحيح الأمان">
             <feature>• تم تضمين تصحيح أمان أندرويد (نوفمبر 2025) لأمان النظام. لمزيد من المعلومات حول تحديثات الأمان في Honor، يرجى زيارة موقعنا على الويب https://www.honor.com/ae-ar/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ملاحظات" type="end">
             <feature>1. لن يؤثر تثبيت هذا التحديث على بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن لا يزال من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية لبياناتك قبل التحديث
2. اكتشف المزيد من المعلومات حول ميزات المنتج في تطبيق التلميحات
3. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيمكنك الحصول على مساعدتنا عن طريق الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة عملاء Honor أو زيارة مركز خدمة عملاء Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1101" name="as-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই আপডেটটোৱে মূলতঃ ছিষ্টেমৰ কাৰ্যদক্ষতা উন্নত কৰে। উন্নতিসমূহৰ আনন্দ ল'বলৈ আপডেট কৰক</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="কেমেৰা">
             <feature>• স্ক্ৰীণ-অফ ৰেকৰ্ডিং এতিয়া উপলব্ধ। ইয়ালৈ গৈ এইটো ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: কেমেৰা > ছেটিংছ > স্ক্ৰীণ-অফ ৰেকৰ্ডিং</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="হোম স্ক্ৰীণ">
             <feature>• স্বচ্ছতা মোডে কাৰ্ড আৰু ফ'ল্ডাৰৰ দৰে উপাদানসমূহৰ স্বচ্ছতা প্ৰভাৱ অনুকূলন কৰে, যিয়ে এক ব্যতিক্ৰমী দৃশ্যমান অভিজ্ঞতা প্ৰদান কৰে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ এইটো ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ছেটিংছ > হোম স্ক্ৰীণ আৰু শৈলী > হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ ছেটিংছ > স্বচ্ছতা মোড</feature>
             <feature>• সম্পাদনা কৰা আৰম্ভ কৰিবলৈ হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ খালী ঠাইখিনিত দীঘলীয়াকৈ দবাওক</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="লক স্ক্ৰীণ">
             <feature>• লক স্ক্ৰীণে অধিক ঘড়ীৰ ষ্টাইল প্ৰদান কৰে। লক স্ক্ৰীণত দুটা আঙুলিৰে পিঞ্চ কৰক, কাষ্টম টিপক, তাৰপিছত সম্পাদনা কৰিবলৈ ঘড়ীটো টিপক</feature>
             <feature>• পাছৱৰ্ড আনলক স্ক্ৰীণ আৰু নিয়ন্ত্ৰণ কেন্দ্ৰত আপোনাৰ টেপৰ প্ৰতি এটা স্পৰ্শকাতৰ লাইটৰ প্ৰভাৱে দেখা যায়</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="স্থিতি দণ্ডিকা">
             <feature>• স্থিতি দণ্ডিকাই চিহ্ন অনুকূলিতকৰণ সক্ষম কৰে, যিয়ে আপোনাক কোনবোৰ স্থিতি দণ্ডিকাৰ চিহ্ন প্ৰদৰ্শন কৰিব সেয়া পচন্দ কৰিবলৈ অনুমতি দিয়ে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ এইটো ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ছেটিংছ > অধিসূচনাসমূহ আৰু স্থিতি দণ্ডিকা > স্থিতি দণ্ডিকা</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="মেজিক কেপচুল">
             <feature>• চেহেৰা চিনাক্তকৰণ মেজিক কেপচুলত একত্ৰিত কৰা হয়। ইয়ালৈ গৈ এইটো ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ছেটিংছ > অধিসূচনাসমূহ আৰু স্থিতি দণ্ডিকা > মেজিক কেপচুল > চেহেৰা চিনাক্তকৰণ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor সংযোগ">
             <feature>• OneTap-এ সহজ আৰু মনোৰঞ্জনৰে গতি একত্ৰিত কৰি Honor ডিভাইচসমূহৰ মাজত মসৃণ ফাইল ট্ৰান্সফাৰ সক্ষম কৰে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ এইটো ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ছেটিংছ > অধিক সংযোগ > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="কাৰ্যদক্ষতা">
             <feature>• ডিভাইচটোৰ সামগ্ৰিক মসৃণতা উন্নত কৰিবলৈ মাজে মাজে ৰৈ যোৱাৰ সমস্যাসমূহ সমাধান কৰে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="স্থিৰতা">
             <feature>• ছিষ্টেমৰ স্থিৰতা উন্নত কৰে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ">
             <feature>• ছিষ্টেমৰ নিৰাপত্তাৰ বাবে Android নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ (নবেম্বৰ 2025) অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হৈছে। Honor নিৰাপত্তা আপডেটৰ বিষয়ে অধিক তথ্যৰ বাবে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি আমাৰ ৱেবছাইট দৰ্শন কৰক: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="টোকাসমূহ" type="end">
             <feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটাত প্ৰভাৱ নপৰিব, কিন্তু আপডেট কৰাৰ পূৰ্বে আপোনাৰ ডাটাৰ বেক আপ ল'বলৈ এতিয়াও পৰামৰ্শ দিয়া হয়
2. আভাসত প্ৰ'ডাক্টৰ ফিচাৰসমূহৰ ওপৰত অধিক তথ্য অনুসন্ধান কৰক
3. আপুনি আপডেটৰ সময়ত কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হ'লে, আপুনি Honor সেৱা হটলাইনত কল কৰি বা Honor গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ গৈ সহায় লাভ কৰিব পাৰে</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1068" name="az-az">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, bu yeniləmə əsasən sistemin performansını artırır. Təkmilləşdirmələrdən yararlanmaq üçün yeniləyin</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>Sönülü ekranda qeydəalma artıq əlçatandır. Kamera > Parametrlər > Sönülü ekranda qeydəalma bölməsinə keçməklə yoxlayın</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Əsas ekran">
             <feature>• Şəffaflıq rejimi kartlar və qovluqlar kimi elementlərin şəffaflıq effektlərini optimallaşdıraraq müstəsna vizual təcrübə təqdim edir. Buraya keçərək sınaqdan keçirin: Parametrlər > Əsas ekran və üslub > Əsas ekran parametrləri > Şəffaflıq rejimi</feature>
             <feature>• Redaktəyə başlamaq üçün əsas ekranın boş sahəsinə basıb saxlayın</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kilid ekranı">
             <feature>• Kilid ekranı daha çox saat üslubu təklif edir. Redaktə etmək üçün kilid ekranında iki barmağınızı birləşdirin, Fərdi üzərinə, sonra isə saata toxunun</feature>
             <feature>• Parolla kilidaçma ekranında və İdarə Mərkəzində toxunduğunuz zaman toxunma işıq effekti işə düşür</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Status paneli">
             <feature>• Status paneli hansı status paneli nişanlarının göstəriləcəyini seçməyə imkan verən nişan fərdiləşdirməsini təmin edir. Buraya keçərək sınaqdan keçirin: Parametrlər > Bildirişlər və status paneli > Status paneli</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sehrli Kapsul">
             <feature>• Üz tanınması Sehrli Kapsula inteqrasiya edilir. Buraya keçərək sınaqdan keçirin: Parametrlər > Bildirişlər və status paneli > Sehrli Kapsul > Üz tanınması</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap sürəti asan proses və əyləncə ilə birləşdirərək faylların Honor cihazları arasında problemsiz şəkildə ötürülməsinə imkan verir. Parametrlər > Daha çox bağlantı > OneTap bölməsinə keçməklə yoxlayın</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Məhsuldarlıq">
             <feature>• Cihazın ümumi rahatlığını artırmaq üçün təsadüfi ilişmə problemlərini aradan qaldırır</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabillik">
             <feature>• Sistemin sabitliyini yaxşılaşdırır</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Təhlükəsizlik paketi">
             <feature>• Sistem təhlükəsizliyi üçün Android təhlükəsizlik paketi (noyabr 2025-ci il) daxil edilib. Honor Təhlükəsizlik yeniləmələri haqqında ətraflı məlumat üçün veb-saytımıza daxil olun: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Qeydlər" type="end">
             <feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınıza təsir etməyəcək, lakin yenə də yeniləməmişdən əvvəl verilənlərin ehtiyat nüsxəsini çıxarmaq tövsiyə olunur
2. İpuclarında məhsul xüsusiyyətləri haqqında daha çox məlumat əldə edin
3. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlə qarşılaşsanız, Honor xidmət qaynar xəttinə zəng etməklə və ya Honor müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə yaxınlaşaraq yardım ala bilərsiniz</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="jv-id">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran iki utamane ningkatake kinerja sistem. Anyarake kanggo ngrasakake pangapikane</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Rekaman kanthi layar mati saiki sumadhiya. Coba fitur kuwi kanthi mbukak: Kamera > Setelan > Rekaman kanthi layar mati</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Layar ngarep">
             <feature>• Mode transparansi ngoptimalake efek transparansi unsur, kayata kertu lan folder saengga menehi pangalaman visual sing apik banget. Coba kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Layar ngarep &amp; gaya > Setelan layar ngarep > Mode transparansi</feature>
             <feature>• Penet suwe area kosong ing layar ngarep kanggo miwiti ngedit</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Layar kunci">
             <feature>• Layar kunci nawakake luwih akeh gaya jam. Jiwit nganggo rong driji ing layar kunci, tutul Kustom, banjur tutul jam kanggo ngedit</feature>
             <feature>• Efek cahya taktil tumindak minangka tanggapan kanggo tutulan sampeyan ing sandhi kanggo mbukak kunci layar lan ing Pusat Kontrol</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Garis status">
             <feature>• Garis status ndhukung kustomisasi ikon, sing mbisakake sampeyan milih ikon garis status sing pengin ditampilake. Coba kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Notifikasi &amp; garis status > Garis status</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kapsul Ajaib">
             <feature>• Pangenalan rai digabungake menyang Kapsul Ajaib. Coba kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Notifikasi &amp; garis status > Kapsul Ajaib > Pangenalan rai</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap mbisakake transfer file sing lancar ing antarane piranti Honor, sing nggabungake kacepetan kanthi gampang lan nyenengake. Coba fitur kuwi kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Sambungan liyane > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kinerja">
             <feature>• Ngrampungake masalah nyendat sing ora kerep kanggo ningkatake sakabehe lancarae piranti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitas">
             <feature>• Ngapikake stabilitas sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch keamanan">
             <feature>• Patch keamanan Android (Nov 2025) wis digabungake kanggo keamanan sistem. Kanggo mangerteni informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan panganyaran Keamanan Honor, bukak situs web kita https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Cathetan" type="end">
             <feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mengaruhi data pribadi sampeyan, nanging nggawe serep data dhisik tetep disaranake sadurunge nganyarake
2. Temokake informasi liyane babagan fitur prodhuk ing Tips
3. Yen ana masalah sajrone panganyaran, sampeyan bisa entuk bantuan kita kanthi nelpon hotline layanan Honor utawa nekani pusat layanan pelanggan Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2074" name="sr-rs">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se unapređuju performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u unapređenjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Snimanje sa isključenim ekranom je sada dostupno. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Kamera > Podešavanja > Snimanje sa isključenim ekranom</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Početni ekran">
             <feature>• Režim providnosti optimizuje efekte providnosti elemenata kao što su kartice i fascikle, pružajući izuzetno vizuelno iskustvo. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Početni ekran i stil > Podešavanja početnog ekrana > Režim providnosti</feature>
             <feature>• Dugo pritisnite prazno područje početnog ekrana da biste započeli uređivanje</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zaključani ekran">
             <feature>• Zaključani ekran nudi više stilova sata. Primaknite dva prsta na zaključanom ekranu, dodirnite Prilagođeno, a zatim dodirnite sat da biste menjali</feature>
             <feature>• Taktilni svetlosni efekat reaguje na vaš dodir na ekranu za otključavanje lozinkom i u Kontrolnom centru</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Statusna traka">
             <feature>• Statusna traka omogućava prilagođavanje ikona, omogućavajući vam da izaberete koje ikone statusne trake želite da prikažete. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Obaveštenja i statusna traka > Statusna traka</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magična kapsula">
             <feature>• Prepoznavanje lica je integrisano u Magičnu kapsulu. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Obaveštenja i statusna traka > Magična kapsula > Prepoznavanje lica</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Povezivanje">
             <feature>• OneTap omogućava besprekoran prenos datoteka između Honor uređaja, kombinujući brzinu sa lakoćom i zabavom. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Još veza > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Učinak">
             <feature>• Rešava povremene probleme sa isprekidanim radom kako bi se poboljšalo ukupno nesmetano funkcionisanje uređaja</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Poboljšava stabilnost sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezbednosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Android bezbednosna zakrpa (novembar 2025.) je integrisana radi bezbednosti sistema. Za još informacija o Honor bezbednosnim ažuriranjima, posetite naš veb-sajt https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zabeleške" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka pre ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o karakteristikama proizvoda u odeljku Saveti
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete dobiti našu pomoć pozivom dežurne linije kompanije Honor ili posetom centru za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1059" name="be-by">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта абнаўленне ў асноўным паляпшае прадукцыйнасць сістэмы. Каб палепшыць уражанні ад выкарыстання, устанавіце абнаўленне</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Камера">
             <feature>• Цяпер даступны запіс з выключаным экранам. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню: Камера > Налады > Запіс з выключаным экранам</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Галоўны экран">
             <feature>• Рэжым празрыстасці аптымізуе эфекты празрыстасці элементаў, такіх як карткі і папкі, што забяспечвае ўнікальны візуальны досвед. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Галоўны экран і стыль > Налады галоўнага экрана > Рэжым празрыстасці»</feature>
             <feature>• Каб пачаць рэдагаванне, націсніце на пустую вобласць галоўнага экрана</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Экран блакіроўкі">
             <feature>• Больш стыляў гадзіннікаў для экрана блакіроўкі. Звядзіце два пальцы на экране блакіроўкі, націсніце Карыстальніцкі, а затым націсніце на гадзіннік, каб рэдагаваць</feature>
             <feature>• Тактыльны эфект асвятлення рэагуе на ваш дотык на экране разблакіроўкі паролем і ў Цэнтры кіравання</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Панэль стану">
             <feature>• Панэль стану дазваляе персаналізаваць значкі і выбраць, якія значкі будуць адлюстроўвацца. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Панэль апавяшчэнняў і стану > Панэль стану»</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic Capsule">
             <feature>• Распазнаванне твару цяпер інтэгравана ў Чароўную капсулу. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Панэль апавяшчэнняў і стану > Чароўная капсула > Распазнаванне твару»</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap дазваляе выконваць бясшвовы перанос файлаў паміж прыладамі Honor, спалучаючы хуткасць з лёгкасцю і задавальненнем. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню: Налады > Дадатковыя падключэнні > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Прадукцыйнасць">
             <feature>• Выпраўляе перыядычныя праблемы з затрымкамі, каб палепшыць агульную плаўнасць працы прылады</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Устойлівасць">
             <feature>• Павышана стабільнасць сістэмы</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Выпраўленне сістэмы бяспекі">
             <feature>• Для павышэння бяспекі сістэмы ўключана выпраўленне функцый бяспекі Android (лістапад 2025 г.). Больш інфармацыі аб абнаўленні сістэмы бяспекі Honor можна знайсці на нашым афіцыйным вэб-сайце: https://www.honor.com/by/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Нататкі" type="end">
             <feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не закране вашы асабістыя даныя. Тым не менш рэкамендуецца стварыць рэзервовую копію даных перад абнаўленнем
2. Больш падрабязная інфармацыя аб характарыстыках прадукту даступная ў Падказках
3. Калі вы сутыкняцеся з праблемамі падчас абнаўлення, вы можаце атрымаць нашу дапамогу, патэлефанаваўшы на гарачую лінію службы падтрымкі кліентаў Honor або наведаўшы цэнтр абслугоўвання кліентаў Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1026" name="bg-bg">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Уважаеми потребители, тази актуализация подобрява основно ефективността на системата. Актуализирайте, за да се насладите на подобренията</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Камера">
             <feature>• Вече е наличен Запис при изключен екран. Изпробвайте го, като отидете на: „Камера > Настройки > Запис при изключен екран“</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Начален екран">
             <feature>• Режимът на прозрачност оптимизира ефектите на прозрачност на елементи като карти и папки, осигурявайки изключително визуално изживяване. Изпробвайте, като отидете на: „Настройки > Стил и начален екран > Настройки на началния екран > Режим на прозрачност“</feature>
             <feature>• Натиснете продължително празната област на началния екран, за да започнете редактиране</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Заключен екран">
             <feature>• Заключеният екран предлага повече стилове на часовници. Щипнете с два пръста по заключения екран, докоснете Индивидуален, след което докоснете часовника, за да редактирате</feature>
             <feature>• Тактилен светлинен ефект реагира на докосването ви на екрана за отключване с парола и в Центъра за управление</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Лента за състоянието">
             <feature>• Лентата за състоянието позволява персонализиране на иконите, което дава възможност да избирате кои икони в лентата за състоянието да се показват. Изпробвайте, като отидете на: „Настройки > Известия и лента за състоянието > Лента за състоянието“</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Магическа капсула">
             <feature>• Разпознаването на лице е интегрирано в „Магическа капсула“. Изпробвайте, като отидете на: „Настройки > Известия и лента за състоянието > Магическа капсула > Разпознаване на лице“</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap позволява безпроблемно прехвърляне на файлове между устройства Honor, съчетавайки скорост с лекота и забавление. Изпробвайте го, като отидете на: „Настройки > Още връзки > OneTap“</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ефективност">
             <feature>• Решава спорадичните проблеми със забавяне, за да подобри цялостната плавност на работа на устройството</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Стабилност">
             <feature>• Подобрява стабилността на системата</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Корекция за сигурност">
             <feature>• Корекцията за сигурност на Android (ноември 2025 г.) е включена за защита на системата. За още информация относно актуализациите за сигурност на Honor посетете нашия уебсайт https://www.honor.com/bg/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Бележки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да се отрази на вашите лични данни, но все пак е препоръчително да архивирате данните си преди актуализиране
2. Открийте повече информация за характеристиките на продукта в „Съвети“
3. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализацията, можете да получите нашата помощ, като се обадите на горещата линия за обслужване на Honor или посетите сервизен център на клиенти на Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2117" name="bn-bd">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই আপডেটটি মূলত সিস্টেমের কর্মক্ষমতা বাড়ায়। উন্নতি উপভোগ করতে আপডেট করুন</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ক্যামেরা">
             <feature>• এখন স্ক্রিন বন্ধ রেখে রেকর্ডিং উপলব্ধ। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: ক্যামেরা > সেটিংস > স্ক্রিন বন্ধ রেখে রেকর্ডিং</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="হোম স্ক্রিন">
             <feature>• স্বচ্ছতা মোড কার্ড এবং ফোল্ডারের মতো জিনিসগুলির ট্রান্সপারেন্সি এফেক্টগুলিকে অপ্টিমাইজ করে একটি ব্যতিক্রমী ভিজ্যুয়াল অভিজ্ঞতা প্রদান করে। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > হোম স্ক্রিন এবং স্টাইল > হোম স্ক্রিন সেটিংস > স্বচ্ছতা মোড</feature>
             <feature>• সম্পাদনা শুরু করতে হোম স্ক্রিনের ফাঁকা এলাকায় দীর্ঘক্ষণ টিপুন</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="লক স্ক্রিন">
             <feature>• লক স্ক্রিনটি আরো ঘড়ির স্টাইল অফার করে। লক স্ক্রিনে দুটি আঙুল দিয়ে পিঞ্চ করুন, কাস্টম ট্যাপ করুন, তারপর সম্পাদনা করতে ঘড়িতে ট্যাপ করুন</feature>
             <feature>• একটি ট্যাক্টাইল লাইট ইফেক্ট পাসওয়ার্ড আনলক স্ক্রিনে এবং নিয়ন্ত্রণ কেন্দ্রে আপনার ট্যাপে সাড়া দেয়</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="স্ট্যাটাস বার">
             <feature>• স্ট্যাটাস বার আইকন কাস্টমাইজেশন সক্রিয় করে, যা কোন স্ট্যাটাস বার আইকনগুলি প্রদর্শন করতে হবে তা আপনাকে বেছে নিতে দেয়। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > বিজ্ঞপ্তি ও স্ট্যাটাস বার > স্ট্যাটাস বার</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ম্যাজিক ক্যাপসুল">
             <feature>• ম্যাজিক ক্যাপসুলের মধ্যে ফেস শনাক্তকরণ একীভূত করা হয়েছে। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > বিজ্ঞপ্তি ও স্ট্যাটাস বার > ম্যাজিক ক্যাপসুল > ফেস শনাক্তকরণ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor কানেক্ট">
             <feature>• OneTap Honor ডিভাইসগুলির মধ্যে নিরবচ্ছিন্ন ফাইল স্থানান্তর সক্রিয় করে গতির সাথে সহজতা এবং মজাকে একত্রিত করে। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > আরো সংযোগসমূহ > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="পারফরম্যান্স">
             <feature>• ডিভাইসের সামগ্রিক মসৃণতা বৃদ্ধির জন্য মাঝে মাঝে আটকে যাওয়ার সমস্যার সমাধান করে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="স্থিতিশীলতা">
             <feature>• সিস্টেমের স্থিতিশীলতা উন্নত করে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ">
             <feature>• সিস্টেমের নিরাপত্তার জন্য Android নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ (নভেম্বর 2025) অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে। Honor-এর নিরাপত্তা আপডেটগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্যের জন্য, আমাদের ওয়েবসাইট দেখুন https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="নোট" type="end">
             <feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে তা আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটাকে প্রভাবিত করবে না, তবুও আপডেট করার আগে আপনার ডেটা ব্যাক আপ করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়
2. পরামর্শ-এ পণ্যের ফিচাতগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্য জানুন
3. আপডেট হওয়ার সময় আপনি কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে Honor সেবা হটলাইনে কল করে বা Honor গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে গিয়ে আমাদের সহায়তা পেতে পারেন</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1105" name="bo-cn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནི་གཙོ་བོ་རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ལ་དམིགས་ནས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུའི་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="པར་ཆས།">
             <feature>• ཡོལ་ཞི་ཕབ་བཟོའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། པར་ཆས་ནས་སྒྲིག་འགོད། དེ་ནས་ཡོལ་ཞི་ཕབ་བཟོ།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ཅོག་ངོས།">
             <feature>• དྭངས་གསལ་རྣམ་པ་གསར་སྣོན། བྱང་བུ་དང་ཡིག་ཆ་སོགས་གཞི་རྒྱུའི་དྭངས་གསལ་ཁྱད་ནུས་མཐོར་འདེགས་གཏོང་ཆེད། དྭངས་གསལ་ཉམས་ལེན་མཐར་སོན་ཁྱེར་ཡོང་། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་ཅོག་ངོས་དང་སྒེར་གཤིས་ཅན། དེ་ནས་ཅོག་ངོས་སྒྲིག་འགོད། དེ་ནས་དྭངས་གསལ་རྣམ་པ།</feature>
             <feature>• ཅོག་ངོས་ཀྱི་སྟོང་ཁུལ་ཡུན་རིང་གནོན་ནས་རྩོམ་སྒྲིག་རྣམ་པར་འཛུལ་བའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ཡོལ་ཟྭ།">
             <feature>• ཡོལ་ཟྭའི་ཆུ་ཚོད་ཀྱི་ཕྱི་རྣམ་རིགས་མང་པོ་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། ཡོལ་ཟྭ་མཛུབ་གཉིས་ཀྱིས་བཙིར་བ་དེ་ནས་རང་སྒྲིག དེ་ནས་དུས་ཚོད་ལ་བརྡབས་ནས་རྩོམ་སྒྲིག་བྱ་ཆོག</feature>
             <feature>• གསང་གྲངས་ཀྱིས་ཟྭ་ཕྱེ་བ་དང་ཚོད་འཛིན་ལྟེ་གནས་མཚམས་ངོས་སུ་གནོན་ན་དྭངས་གསལ་གྱི་འོད་ཚོར་ཁྱད་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="རྣམ་པའི་ཚན་བྱང་།">
             <feature>• རྣམ་པའི་ཚན་བྱང་གི་རིས་རྟགས་ཀྱི་རང་སྒྲིག་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན། རང་དབང་གིས་མངོན་སྟོན་བྱ་དགོས་པའི་རྣམ་པའི་ཚན་བྱང་གི་རིས་རྟགས་འདེམས་ཆོག ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་བརྡ་ཐོ་དང་རྣམ་པའི་ཚན་བྱང་། དེ་ནས་རྣམ་པའི་ཚན་བྱང་།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="འགུལ་རྣམ་སྦྱིན་ཐུམ།">
             <feature>• མིའི་ངོ་གདོང་གིས་ཟྭ་འབྱེད་པ་བྱས་ནས་སྦྱིན་ཐུམ་དུ་འཛུལ་བ་གསར་སྣོན། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་བརྡ་ཐོ་དང་རྣམ་པའི་ཚན་བྱང་། དེ་ནས་འགུལ་རྣམ་སྦྱིན་ཐུམ། དེ་ནས་མིའི་ངོ་གདོང་ངོས་འཛིན།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉམ་སྦྲེལ།">
             <feature>• རུང་ཡོའོ་ལག་ཁྱེར་ཁ་པར་བར་དུ་ཐུག་ཙམ་གྱིས་སྐུར་བར་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཡིག་ཆ་མྱུར་དུ་སྐྱེལ་གཏོང་བྱེད་པ་མངོན་འགྱུར་བྱེད། སྤྲོ་ལྡན་དང་མྱུར་སྟབས་ཡིན། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་འབྲེལ་མཐུད་དེ་ལས་མང་བ། དེ་ནས་ཐུག་ཙམ་གྱིས་སྐུར།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="གཤིས་ནུས།">
             <feature>• བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་བེད་སྤྱོད་ཐོགས་ཐུག་གི་གནད་དོན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། སྒྲིག་ཆས་ཀྱི་ཐོགས་ཐུག་མེད་པའི་རང་བཞིན་མཐོར་འདེགས་གཏོང་།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན།">
             <feature>• རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་ཡོད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ།">
             <feature>• ཨན་སྒྲོའི་ 2025 ལོའི་ཟླ་བ་ 11 པའི་བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདྲེས་འཇུག་བྱས་ཏེ། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་སྟོབས་སྒྱུར་གཏོང་། རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉེན་ཆས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནང་དོན་སྐོར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ། རུང་ཡོའོ་གཞུང་ཕྱོགས་དྲ་ཚིགས་ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/11 ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
             <feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གཞི་གྲངས་སུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་སྔོན་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. དེ་ལས་མང་བའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་ལེགས་པོའི་ངོ་སྤྲོད་ཐད་ཁ་པར་རྩེ་བའི་ལག་རྩལ་གྱི་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱ་རོགས།
3. གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་པའི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད་དུ། གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ། ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་མཁོ་མཁན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་ཕེབས་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་འཚོལ་རོགས།</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="5146" name="bs-ba">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo ažuriranje uglavnom poboljšava performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da uživate u poboljšanjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fotoaparat">
             <feature>• Snimanje s isključenim ekranom je sada dostupno. Isprobajte funkciju tako što ćete otići na: Fotoaparat > Postavke > Snimanje s isključenim ekranom</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Početni ekran">
             <feature>• Način providnosti optimizira efekte providnosti elemenata kao što su kartice i fascikle, pružajući izuzetno vizuelno iskustvo. Isprobajte funkciju tako što ćete otići na: Postavke > Početni ekran i stil > Postavke početnog ekrana > Način providnosti</feature>
             <feature>• Dugo pritisnite prazno područje početnog ekrana da biste započeli uređivanje</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zaključani ekran">
             <feature>• Zaključani ekran nudi više stilova sata. Primaknite dva prsta na zaključanom ekranu, dodirnite Prilagođeno, zatim dodirnite sat za uređivanje</feature>
             <feature>• Taktilni svjetlosni efekt reagira na vaš dodir na ekranu za otključavanje lozinkom i u Centru za kontrolu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Statusna traka">
             <feature>• Statusna traka omogućava prilagođavanje ikona, što vam omogućava da odaberete koje ikone statusne trake želite prikazati. Isprobajte funkciju tako što ćete otići na: Postavke > Obavještenja i statusna traka > Statusna traka</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magična kapsula">
             <feature>• Prepoznavanje lica je integrirano u Magičnu kapsulu. Isprobajte funkciju tako što ćete otići na: Postavke > Obavještenja i statusna traka > Magična kapsula > Prepoznavanje lica</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor povezivanje">
             <feature>• OneTap omogućava besprijekoran prijenos datoteka između Honor uređaja, kombinirajući brzinu s lakoćom i zabavom. Isprobajte funkciju tako što ćete otići na: Postavke > Više veza > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Performanse">
             <feature>• Rješava povremene probleme sa zastajkivanjem kako bi se poboljšala ukupna glatkoća rada uređaja</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Poboljšava stabilnost sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sigurnosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Ugrađena je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (novembar 2025.) radi sigurnosti sistema. Više informacija o Honor sigurnosnim ažuriranjima potražite na našoj web lokaciji https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Bilješke" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja ne utiče na lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o funkcijama proizvoda u Savjetima
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete zatražiti našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati Honor dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetiti Honor servisni centar za korisnike</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1027" name="ca-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització millora principalment el rendiment del sistema. Actualitzeu-la per gaudir de les millores</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Càmera">
             <feature>• Ja està disponible la Gravació amb la pantalla apagada. Proveu-la des de: Càmera > Configuració > Gravació amb la pantalla apagada</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla inicial">
             <feature>• El Mode de transparència optimitza els efectes de transparència d'elements com ara targetes i carpetes, la qual cosa ofereix una experiència visual excepcional. Per provar-ho, aneu a Configuració > Pantalla inicial i estil > Configuració de la pantalla inicial > Mode de transparència</feature>
             <feature>• Feu una pulsació llarga a l'àrea en blanc de la pantalla inicial per començar a editar</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla de bloqueig">
             <feature>• La pantalla de bloqueig ofereix més estils de rellotge. Ajunteu amb dos dits a la pantalla de bloqueig, toqueu Personalitzat i després toqueu el rellotge per editar-lo</feature>
             <feature>• Un efecte tàctil lluminós respon al vostre toc a la pantalla de desbloqueig amb contrasenya i al Centre de control</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Barra d'estat">
             <feature>• La barra d'estat habilita la personalització d'icones, la qual cosa us permet triar les icones de la barra d'estat que voleu mostrar. Per provar-ho, aneu a Configuració > Notificacions i barra d'estat > Barra d'estat</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Càpsula Màgica">
             <feature>• El Reconeixement facial està integrat en la Càpsula màgica. Per provar-ho, aneu a Configuració > Notificacions i barra d'estat > Càpsula màgica > Reconeixement facial</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap permet una transferència de fitxers perfecta entre dispositius Honor, combinant velocitat amb facilitat i diversió. Per provar-ho, aneu a: Configuració > Més connexions > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Rendiment">
             <feature>• Soluciona els problemes ocasionals de retards per millorar la fluïdesa general del dispositiu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilitat">
             <feature>• Millora l'estabilitat del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pedaç de seguretat">
             <feature>S'ha incorporat el pedaç de seguretat d'Android (novembre del 2025) per garantir la seguretat del sistema. Per obtenir més informació sobre les actualitzacions de seguretat d'Honor, consulteu el nostre lloc web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. El fet d'instal·lar aquesta actualització no afectarà les vostres dades personals, però es recomana fer una còpia de seguretat de les dades abans d'iniciar l'actualització
2. Descobriu més informació sobre les funcions del producte a Suggeriments
3. Si trobeu algun problema durant l'actualització, per obtenir la nostra ajuda truqueu a la Línia directa d'atenció al client d'Honor o visiteu el Centre d'atenció al client d'Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1029" name="cs-cz">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Vážený uživateli, tato aktualizace především zvyšuje výkon systému. Aktualizujte, abyste si mohli užít vylepšení</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fotoaparát">
             <feature>• Nyní je k dispozici záznam s vypnutou obrazovkou. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce Fotoaparát > Nastavení > Záznam s vypnutou obrazovkou</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Domovská obrazovka">
             <feature>• Režim průhlednosti optimalizuje efekty průhlednosti prvků, jako jsou karty a složky, a poskytuje tak výjimečný vizuální zážitek. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce Nastavení > Domovská obrazovka a styl > Nastavení domovské obrazovky > Režim průhlednosti</feature>
             <feature>• Dlouhým stisknutím prázdné oblasti domovské obrazovky spustíte úpravy</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Obrazovka uzamčení">
             <feature>• Zamčená obrazovka nabízí více stylů hodin. Sevřete dva prsty na zamčené obrazovce, klepněte na Vlastní a poté klepnutím na hodiny zahajte úpravu</feature>
             <feature>• Hmatový světelný efekt reaguje na klepnutí na obrazovce odemčení heslem a v Řídicím centru</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stavový řádek">
             <feature>• Stavový řádek umožňuje přizpůsobení ikon a výběr ikon stavového řádku, které se mají zobrazit. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce Nastavení > Oznámení a stavový řádek > Stavový řádek</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magická kapsle">
             <feature>• Rozpoznávání obličeje je integrováno do Magické kapsle. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce Nastavení > Oznámení a stavový řádek > Magická kapsle > Rozpoznávání obličeje</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap umožňuje bezproblémový přenos souborů mezi zařízeními Honor a kombinuje rychlost s jednoduchostí a zábavou. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce Nastavení > Další připojení > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Výkon">
             <feature>• Řeší občasné problémy se zasekáváním a zlepšuje celkovou plynulost zařízení</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilita">
             <feature>• Vylepšuje stabilitu systému.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Oprava zabezpečení">
             <feature>• Do systému byla začleněna bezpečnostní oprava (listopad 2025) pro systém Android pro zajištění bezpečnosti systému. Více informací o bezpečnostních aktualizacích Honor najdete na našem webu https://www.honor.com/cz/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Poznámky" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalace této aktualizace neovlivní vaše osobní data, ale přesto doporučujeme před aktualizací zálohovat data.
2. Další informace o funkcích produktu najdete v aplikaci Tipy.
3. Pokud během aktualizace narazíte na nějaké problémy, zavolejte na informační linku Honor nebo navštivte Centrum služeb zákazníkům Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1030" name="da-dk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Kære bruger. Denne opdatering forbedrer hovedsageligt systemets ydeevne. Opdater for at drage nytte af forbedringerne</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Optagelse med slukket skærm. Prøv det ved at gå til: Kamera > Indstillinger > Optagelse med slukket skærm</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Startskærm">
             <feature>• Gennemsigtighedstilstand optimerer gennemsigtighedseffekterne for elementer såsom kort og mapper og giver en enestående visuel oplevelse. Prøv det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Startskærm og stil > Indstillinger for startskærm > Gennemsigtighedstilstand</feature>
             <feature>• Tryk længe på det tomme område på startskærmen for at begynde at redigere</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Låseskærm">
             <feature>• Låseskærmen tilbyder flere urstile. Knib med to fingre på låseskærmen, tryk på Brugerdefineret, tryk derefter på uret for at redigere</feature>
             <feature>• En taktil lyseffekt reagerer på dit tryk på skærmen for adgangskodeåbning og i Kontrolcenter</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Statuslinje">
             <feature>• Statuslinjen gør det muligt at tilpasse ikoner, så du kan vælge, hvilke ikoner der skal vises på statuslinjen. Prøv det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Notifikationer og statuslinje > Statuslinje</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magisk kapsel">
             <feature>• Ansigtsgenkendelse er integreret i Magisk kapsel. Prøv det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Notifikationer og statuslinje > Magisk kapsel > Ansigtsgenkendelse</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Tilslut">
             <feature>• OneTap muliggør problemfri filoverførsel mellem Honor-enheder, der kombinerer hurtighed med lethed og sjov. Prøv det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Flere forbindelser > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Præstation">
             <feature>• Løser de lejlighedsvise hakkeproblemer for at forbedre enhedens samlede jævnhed</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitet">
             <feature>• Forbedrer systemstabiliteten</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sikkerhedspatch">
             <feature>• Android sikkerhedspatch (nov 2025) er blevet inkluderet for øget systemsikkerhed. Du kan få flere oplysninger om Honor-sikkerhedsopdateringer på vores websted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Noter" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering påvirker ikke dine personlige data, men vi anbefaler alligevel, at du sikkerhedskopierer dine data inden opdateringen
2. Få flere oplysninger om produktfunktioner i Tips
3. Hvis du oplever problemer under opdateringen, kan du få hjælp ved at ringe til Honors servicehotline eller besøge Honors kundeservicecenter</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1031" name="de-de">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung verbessert hauptsächlich die Systemleistung. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Aufnahme bei ausgeschaltetem Bildschirm ist jetzt verfügbar. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Kamera > Einstellungen > Aufnahme bei ausgeschaltetem Bildschirm</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Startbildschirm">
             <feature>• Der Transparenzmodus optimiert die Transparenzeffekte von Elementen wie Karten und Ordnern und sorgt so für ein außergewöhnliches Anzeigeerlebnis. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Startbildschirm und Stil > Startbildschirmeinstellungen > Transparenzmodus</feature>
             <feature>• Drücken Sie eine leere Stelle auf dem Startbildschirm lange, um die Bearbeitung zu starten</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bildschirm sperren">
             <feature>• Der Sperrbildschirm bietet mehr Uhrenstile. Ziehen Sie den Sperrbildschirm mit zwei Fingern zusammen, tippen Sie auf Benutzerdefiniert und tippen Sie dann zum Bearbeiten auf die Uhr</feature>
             <feature>• Ein taktiler Lichteffekt reagiert auf Ihr Tippen auf dem Bildschirm zum Entsperren des Passworts und im Kontrollzentrum</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Statusleiste">
             <feature>• Statusleiste ermöglicht die Anpassung von Symbolen, sodass Sie wählen können, welche Symbole in der Statusleiste angezeigt werden sollen. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Benachrichtigungen &amp; Statusleiste > Statusleiste</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic Capsule">
             <feature>• Gesichtserkennung ist in Magic Capsule integriert. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Benachrichtigungen &amp; Statusleiste > Magic Capsule > Gesichtserkennung</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Ein Tastendruck ermöglicht eine nahtlose Dateiübertragung zwischen Honor-Geräten und kombiniert dabei Geschwindigkeit mit Leichtigkeit und Spaß. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Weitere Verbindungen > Ein Tastendruck</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Leistung">
             <feature>• Behebt gelegentlich auftretende Probleme mit Ruckeln, um die allgemeine Laufruhe des Geräts zu verbessern</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilität">
             <feature>• Verbessert die Systemstabilität</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sicherheitspatch">
             <feature>• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Nov. 2025) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die Honor Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notizen" type="end">
             <feature>1. Die Installation dieses Updates hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, es wird jedoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen
2. Entdecken Sie weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen in Tipps
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Honor-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein Honor-Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1032" name="el-gr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιώνει κυρίως την απόδοση του συστήματος. Πραγματοποιήστε ενημέρωση για να απολαύσετε τις βελτιώσεις</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Κάμερα">
             <feature>• Η Ηχογράφηση με απενεργοποιημένη οθόνη είναι πλέον διαθέσιμη. Δοκιμάστε τη μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Κάμερα > Ρυθμίσεις > Ηχογράφηση με απενεργοποιημένη οθόνη</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Αρχική οθόνη">
             <feature>• Η Λειτουργία διαφάνειας βελτιστοποιεί τα εφέ διαφάνειας στοιχείων όπως κάρτες και φάκελοι, προσφέροντας μια εξαιρετική οπτική εμπειρία. Δοκιμάστε αυτή τη λειτουργία μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Αρχική οθόνη και στυλ > Ρυθμίσεις αρχικής οθόνης > Λειτουργία διαφάνειας</feature>
             <feature>• Πατήστε παρατεταμένα την κενή περιοχή της αρχικής οθόνης για να ξεκινήσετε την επεξεργασία</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Κλείδωμα οθόνης">
             <feature>• Η οθόνη κλειδώματος προσφέρει περισσότερα στυλ ρολογιού. Τσιμπήστε με δύο δάχτυλα την οθόνη κλειδώματος, πατήστε Εξατομικευμένο και, στη συνέχεια, πατήστε το ρολόι για επεξεργασία</feature>
             <feature>• Ένα απτικό εφέ φωτός ανταποκρίνεται στο άγγιγμά σας στην οθόνη ξεκλειδώματος με κωδικό πρόσβασης και στο Κέντρο ελέγχου</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Γραμμή κατάστασης">
             <feature>• Η γραμμή κατάστασης επιτρέπει την προσαρμογή εικονιδίων, επιτρέποντάς σας να επιλέξετε ποια εικονίδια της γραμμής κατάστασης θα εμφανίζονται. Δοκιμάστε αυτή τη λειτουργία μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Ειδοποιήσεις και γραμμή κατάστασης > Γραμμή κατάστασης</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Μαγική κάψουλα">
             <feature>• Η Αναγνώριση προσώπου είναι ενσωματωμένη στη Μαγική κάψουλα. Δοκιμάστε αυτή τη λειτουργία μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Ειδοποιήσεις και γραμμή κατάστασης > Μαγική κάψουλα > Αναγνώριση προσώπου</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Το OneTap επιτρέπει την απρόσκοπτη μεταφορά αρχείων μεταξύ συσκευών Honor, συνδυάζοντας την ταχύτητα με την ευκολία και τη διασκέδαση. Δοκιμάστε τη μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Περισσότερες συνδέσεις > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Απόδοση">
             <feature>• Επιλύει τα περιστασιακά προβλήματα τρεμοπαίγματος για τη βελτίωση της συνολικής ομαλότητας της συσκευής</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Σταθερότητα">
             <feature>• Βελτιώνει τη σταθερότητα του συστήματος</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφάλειας">
             <feature>• Η ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας Android (Νοέμβριος 2025) ενσωματώθηκε για την ασφάλεια του συστήματος. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις ενημερώσεις της Ασφάλειας Honor, επισκεφθείτε τον ιστότοπό μας https://www.honor.com/gr/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Σημειώσεις" type="end">
             <feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα επηρεάσει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, αλλά ακόμη και έτσι συνιστάται η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας των δεδομένων σας πριν από την ενημέρωση
2. Ανακαλύψτε περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις δυνατότητες του προϊόντος στις Συμβουλές
3. Αν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, μπορείτε να λάβετε τη βοήθειά μας καλώντας την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή εξυπηρέτησης της Honor ή με επίσκεψη σε ένα κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2057" name="en-GB">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Dear user, this update mainly enhances the system performance. Update to enjoy the improvements</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Camera">
             <feature>• Screen-off recording is now available. Try it out by going to: Camera > Settings > Screen-off recording</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Home screen">
             <feature>• Transparency mode optimizes the transparency effects of elements such as cards and folders, delivering an exceptional visual experience. Try it out by going to: Settings > Home screen &amp; style > Home screen settings > Transparency mode</feature>
             <feature>• Long press the blank area of the home screen to start editing</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Lock screen">
             <feature>• The lock screen offers more clock styles. Pinch with two fingers on the lock screen, tap Custom, then tap the clock to edit</feature>
             <feature>• A tactile light effect responds to your tap on the password unlock screen and in Control Centre</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Status bar">
             <feature>• Status bar enables icon customisation, allowing you to choose which status bar icons to display. Try it out by going to: Settings > Notifications &amp; status bar > Status bar</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic Capsule">
             <feature>• Face recognition is integrated into Magic Capsule. Try it out by going to: Settings > Notifications &amp; status bar > Magic Capsule > Face recognition</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap enables seamless file transfer between Honor devices, combining speed with ease and fun. Try it out by going to: Settings > More connections > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Performance">
             <feature>• Resolves the occasional stuttering issues to enhance the overall smoothness of the device</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stability">
             <feature>• Improves the system stability</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Security patch">
             <feature>• Android security patch (Nov 2025) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about Honor Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating
2. Discover more information on product features in Tips
3. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling Honor service hotline or visiting Honor customer service centre</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1034" name="es-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado/a usuario/a, esta actualización mejora principalmente el rendimiento del sistema. Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Cámara">
             <feature>• Grabación con la pantalla apagada ya está disponible. Pruébela en: Cámara > Ajustes > Grabación con la pantalla apagada</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla principal">
             <feature>• El modo de transparencia optimiza los efectos de transparencia de elementos como tarjetas y carpetas, lo que ofrece una experiencia visual excepcional. Pruébelo en Ajustes > Pantalla principal y estilo > Ajustes pantalla principal > Modo de transparencia</feature>
             <feature>• Mantenga pulsada el área vacía de la pantalla principal para comenzar a editar</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla de bloqueo">
             <feature>• La pantalla de bloqueo ofrece más estilos de reloj. Pellizque con dos dedos la pantalla de bloqueo, toque Personalizar y luego toque el reloj para editar</feature>
             <feature>• Un efecto de luz táctil responde a su toque en la pantalla de desbloqueo de contraseña y en el Centro de control</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Barra de estado">
             <feature>• En la barra de estado se pueden personalizar los iconos, lo que le permite elegir qué iconos se mostrarán en la barra de estado. Pruébela en: Ajustes > Notificaciones y barra de estado > Barra de estado</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Cápsula mágica">
             <feature>• Reconocimiento facial está integrado en Cápsula mágica. Pruébelo en Ajustes > Notificaciones y barra de estado > Cápsula mágica > Reconocimiento facial</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Un toque permite la transferencia de archivos fluida entre dispositivos Honor, combinando velocidad con facilidad y diversión. Pruébela en: Ajustes > Más conexiones > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Rendimiento">
             <feature>• Resuelve los problemas ocasionales de fluidez (stuttering) para mejorar la fluidez general del dispositivo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilidad">
             <feature>• Mejora la estabilidad del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Parche de seguridad">
             <feature>• Se ha incorporado el parche de seguridad de Android (noviembre de 2025) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de Honor, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/es/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar
2. Descubra más información sobre las características de los productos en Sugerencias
3. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, puede obtener nuestra ayuda si llama a la línea de atención al cliente de Honor o si visita el centro de servicios al cliente de Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="21514" name="es-us">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización mejora principalmente el rendimiento del sistema. Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Cámara">
             <feature>• Ahora está disponible la grabación con pantalla apagada. Puede probar esta función en: Cámara > Ajustes > Grabación con pantalla apagada</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla principal">
             <feature>• El Modo transparente optimiza los efectos de transparencia de elementos como tarjetas y carpetas, ofreciendo una experiencia visual excepcional. Pruebe la función en: Ajustes > Pantalla principal y estilo > Ajustes > Modo transparente</feature>
             <feature>• Mantenga presionada el área vacía de la pantalla de inicio para comenzar a editar</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla de bloqueo">
             <feature>• La pantalla de bloqueo ofrece más estilos de reloj. Haga un gesto de pellizco con dos dedos en la pantalla de bloqueo, toque Personalizado y luego el reloj para editar</feature>
             <feature>• Un efecto de luz táctil responde al toque en la pantalla de desbloqueo por contraseña y en el Centro de control</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Barra de estado">
             <feature>• La barra de estado permite personalizar los íconos, lo que le permite elegir cuáles mostrar. Puede probar esta opción si va a: Ajustes > Notificaciones y barra de estado > Barra de estado</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic Capsule">
             <feature>• El Reconocimiento facial está integrado en Magic Capsule. Pruebe la función en: Ajustes > Notificaciones y barra de estado > Magic Capsule > Reconocimiento facial</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Conecta con Honor">
             <feature>• OneTap permite transferir archivos sin interrupciones entre dispositivos Honor, combinando velocidad, facilidad y diversión. Puede probar esta función en: Ajustes > Más conexiones > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Rendimiento">
             <feature>• Corrige problemas ocasionales de tartamudeo para mejorar la fluidez general del dispositivo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilidad">
             <feature>• Mejora la estabilidad del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Parche de seguridad">
             <feature>• Se incorporó un parche de seguridad de Android (noviembre de 2025) para mejorar la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de Honor, visite nuestro sitio web https://www.honor.com/latam/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de respaldo de sus datos antes de actualizar
2. Descubra más información sobre las funciones del producto en Sugerencias
3. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, puede llamar a la línea de atención al cliente de Honor o visitar el centro de servicios al cliente de Honor para recibir asistencia</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1061" name="et-ee">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hea kasutaja! See värskendus parandab peamiselt süsteemi jõudlust. Värskendage täiustuste nautimiseks</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kaamera">
             <feature>• Väljalülitatud ekraaniga salvestamine on nüüd saadaval. Proovige seda, avades Kaamera > Sätted > Väljalülitatud ekraaniga salvestamine</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Avakuva">
             <feature>• Läbipaistvusrežiim optimeerib elementide, nagu kaartide ja kaustade läbipaistvuse efekte, pakkudes erakordset visuaalset kogemust. Proovige seda, avades Sätted > Avakuva ja stiil > Avakuva sätted > Läbipaistvusrežiim</feature>
             <feature>• Redigeerimise alustamiseks vajutage pikalt avakuva tühjale alale</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Lukustuskuva">
             <feature>• Lukustuskuval on rohkem kellastiile. Suruge lukustuskuval kahte sõrme kokku, puudutage Kohandatud ja seejärel puudutage kella, et seda redigeerida</feature>
             <feature>• Taktiilne valgusefekt reageerib teie puudutusele parooliga avamise ekraanil ja juhtimiskeskuses</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Olekuriba">
             <feature>• Olekuriba võimaldab ikoonide kohandamist, lubades teil valida, milliseid olekuriba ikoone kuvada. Proovige seda, avades Sätted > Teavitused ja olekuriba > Olekuriba</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Maagiline kapsel">
             <feature>• Näotuvastus on integreeritud Maagilisse kapslisse. Proovige seda, avades Sätted > Teavitused ja olekuriba > Maagiline kapsel > Näotuvastus</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap võimaldab sujuvat failiedastust Honori seadmete vahel, ühendades kiiruse lihtsuse ja nauditavusega. Proovige seda, avades Sätted > Rohkem ühendusi > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Jõudlus">
             <feature>• Lahendab aeg-ajalt esinevad hangumise probleemid, et muuta seadme üldine töö sujuvamaks</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabiilsus">
             <feature>• Parandab süsteemi stabiilsust</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Turvapaik">
             <feature>• Süsteemi turvalisuse tagamiseks rakendati Androidi turvapaik (november 2025). Lisateavet Honori turvavärskenduste kohta leiate meie veebisaidilt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Märkused" type="end">
             <feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei mõjuta teie isiklikke andmeid, aga soovitame ikkagi enne värskendamist andmed varundada
2. Toote funktsioonide kohta leiate lisateavet rakendusest Tips
3. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, saate meilt abi, helistades Honori klienditoe infoliinile või külastades Honori klienditeeninduskeskust</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1069" name="eu-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Erabiltzaile agurgarria: eguneratze honek sistemaren errendimendua hobetzen du nagusiki. Eguneratu hobekuntzez gozatzeko</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Orain pantaila itzalita duen grabazioa dago eskuragarri. Probatu hemen: Kamera > Ezarpenak > Pantaila itzalita grabatzea</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Hasierako pantaila">
             <feature>• Gardentasun moduak txartelen, karpeten eta antzeko elementuen gardentasun-efektuak optimizatzen ditu, ikusizko esperientzia bikaina emanez. Probatzeko, joan hona: Ezarpenak > Hasierako pantaila eta estiloa > Hasierako pantailako ezarpenak > Gardentasun modua</feature>
             <feature>• Sakatu luze hasierako pantailako eremu huts bat editatzen hasteko</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Blokeatutako pantaila">
             <feature>• Blokeo-pantailak erloju-estilo gehiago eskaintzen ditu. Atximur egin bi hatzekin blokeatutako pantailan, sakatu Pertsonalizatua eta, ondoren, sakatu erlojua editatzeko</feature>
             <feature>• Ukipenezko argi-efektu batek pasahitzarekin desblokeatzeko pantailan eta Kontrol-zentroan egiten duzun ukituari erantzuten dio</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Egoera-barra">
             <feature>• Egoera-barrak ikonoa pertsonalizatzea gaitzen du, bistaratzeko egoera-barraren ikonoa aukeratzeko gaitasuna emanez. Probatzeko joan hona: Ezarpenak > Jakinarazpenak eta egoera-barra > Egoera-barra</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kapsula magikoa">
             <feature>• Aurpegi bidezko ezagutza Kapsula magikoan integratuta dago. Probatzeko, joan hona: Ezarpenak > Jakinarazpenak eta egoera-barra > Kapsula magikoa > Aurpegi bidezko ezagutza</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap-ek aukera ematen du fitxategiak arazorik gabe transferitzeko Honor gailuen artean, abiadura erraz eta ondo pasatzeko moduan konbinatuz. Probatu hemen: Ezarpenak > Konexio gehiago > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Errendimendua">
             <feature>• Totelkako noizbehinkako arazoak ebazten ditu, gailuaren arintasun orokorra hobetzeko</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Egonkortasuna">
             <feature>• Sistemaren egonkortasuna hobetu da</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Segurtasun-adabakia">
             <feature>• Android-en segurtasun-adabakia (2025eko azaroa) gehitu da sistemaren segurtasuna bermatzeko. Honor Segurtasun-eguneratzeei buruzko informazio gehiago lortzeko, ikusi gure gunea: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Oharrak" type="end">
             <feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzeak ez du eraginik izango datu pertsonaletan, baina, eguneratu baino lehen, datuen babeskopia egitea gomendatzen da
2. Ezagutu produktuaren eginbideei buruzko informazio gehiago Aholkuak atalean
3. Eguneratzean arazoren bat baduzu, gure laguntza eska dezakezu Honor-en telefonozko arreta-lineara deituz edo Honor-en bezeroaren zerbitzu-zentrora joanez</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1065" name="fa-ir">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>کاربر گرامی، این به‌روزرسانی به‌طور عمده عملکرد سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد. با انجام این به‌روزرسانی، از این بهبودها بهره‌مند شوید</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="دوربین">
             <feature>‏‏• «ضبط با صفحۀ نمایش خاموش» اکنون در دسترس است. آن را با رفتن به این مسیر امتحان کنید: دوربین > تنظيمات > ضبط با صفحۀ نمایش خاموش</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏صفحۀ اصلی">
             <feature>‏• حالت شفافیت، جلوه‌های شفاف عناصر مختلف مانند کارت‌ها و پوشه‌ها را بهینه می‌کند و تجربهٔ بصری منحصربه‌فردی ارائه می‌دهد. برای امتحان کردن آن، این مسیر را طی کنید: تنظیمات > صفحۀ اصلی و سبک > تنظیمات صفحۀ اصلی > حالت شفافیت</feature>
             <feature>‏• ناحیهٔ خالی صفحهٔ اصلی را فشار دهید و نگه دارید تا وارد حالت ویرایش شوید</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="صفحۀ قفل">
             <feature>‏‏• سبک‌های ساعت بیشتری در صفحۀ قفل ارائه می‌شوند. برای ویرایش، دو انگشتتان را روی صفحۀ قفل به هم نزدیک کنید، روی سفارشی ضربه بزنید، سپس روی ساعت ضربه بزنید</feature>
             <feature>‏‏• در واکنش به ضربه زدن روی صفحه قفل‌گشایی با رمز ورود و «مرکز کنترل»، یک جلوه نوری وابسته به لمس نمایش داده می‌شود</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="نوار وضعیت">
             <feature>‏• نوار وضعیت اکنون از سفارشی‌سازی آیکون‌ها پشتیبانی می‌کند و می‌توانید انتخاب کنید کدام آیکون‌های نوار وضعیت نمایش داده شوند. برای امتحان کردن آن، این مسیر را طی کنید: تنظیمات > اعلان‌ها و نوار وضعیت > نوار وضعیت</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏کپسول جادویی">
             <feature>‏• «شناسایی چهره» با «کپسول جادویی» ادغام شده است. برای امتحان کردن آن، این مسیر را طی کنید: تنظیمات > اعلان‌ها و نوار وضعیت > ‏کپسول جادویی > شناسایی چهره</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="اتصال Honor">
             <feature>‏‏• قابلیت «تک‌ضربه» انتقال یکپارچه فایل بین دستگاه‌های Honor را فراهم و سرعت و راحتی و جذابیت را با هم ترکیب می‌کند. آن را با رفتن به این مسیر امتحان کنید: تنظیمات > سایر ارتباطات > تک‌ضربه</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="عملکرد">
             <feature>‏‏• مشکلات گاه‌به‌گاه کند شدن را برطرف می‌کند تا دستگاه به‌طور کلی روان‌تر کار کند</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="پایداری">
             <feature>‏‏• پایداری سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="وصلۀ امنیتی">
             <feature>‏• برای حفظ امنیت سیستم، «وصلۀ امنیتی Android (نوامبر ۲۰۲۵)» گنجانده شده است. برای کسب اطلاعات بیشتر دربارۀ به‌روزرسانی‌های «امنیت Honor»، لطفاً به وب‌سایت ما مراجعه کنید: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="یادداشت‌ها" type="end">
             <feature>‏۱. نصب این به‌روزرسانی روی داده‌های شخصی شما تأثیری نخواهد داشت. بااین‌وجود، توصیه می‌شود قبل از به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید
‏۲. اطلاعات بیشتر مربوط به قابلیت‌های محصول را در «نکات» می‌توانید بیابید
‏۳. اگر در طول به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، می‌توانید از طریق تماس با تلفن مستقیم خدمات Honor یا مراجعه به مرکز خدمات مشتریان Honor از ما کمک بگیرید</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1035" name="fi-fi">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä päivitys parantaa ensisijaisesti järjestelmän suorituskykyä. Päivitä, niin pääset nauttimaan parannuksista</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Tallennus näytön ollessa sammutettuna on nyt käytettävissä. Voit kokeilla sitä seuraavassa kohdassa: Kamera > Asetukset > Tallennus näytön ollessa sammutettuna</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Aloitusnäyttö">
             <feature>• Läpinäkyvyystila optimoi korttien ja kansioiden kaltaisten elementtien läpinäkyvyystehosteet tarjoten poikkeuksellisen visuaalisen kokemuksen. Voit kokeilla sitä seuraavassa kohdassa: Asetukset > Aloitusnäyttö ja tyyli > Aloitusnäytön asetukset > Läpinäkyvyystila</feature>
             <feature>• Aloita muokkaaminen painamalla pitkään tyhjää kohtaa aloitusnäytöllä</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Lukitusnäyttö">
             <feature>• Lukitusnäyttö tarjoaa nyt lisää kellotyylejä. Nipistä kaksi sormea yhteen lukitusnäytöllä, napauta kohtaa Mukautettu ja napauta sitten kelloa muokkaamista varten</feature>
             <feature>• Napautusta seuraa kosketuksen valotehoste salasanalukituksen avauksen yhteydessä ja Ohjauskeskuksessa</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tilapalkki">
             <feature>• Tilapalkin kuvakkeita voi nyt muokata, joten voit valita mitkä kuvakkeet tilapalkissa näytetään. Voit kokeilla sitä seuraavassa kohdassa: Asetukset > Ilmoitukset ja tilapalkki > Tilapalkki</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic-kapseli">
             <feature>• Kasvojentunnistus on integroitu Magic-kapseliin. Voit kokeilla sitä seuraavassa kohdassa: Asetukset > Ilmoitukset ja tilapalkki > Magic-kapseli > Kasvojentunnistus</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap mahdollistaa saumattoman tiedostonsiirron Honor-laitteiden välillä. Voit kokeilla sitä seuraavassa kohdassa: Asetukset > Lisää yhteyksiä > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Suorituskyky">
             <feature>• Parantaa laitteen yleistä toimivuutta ratkaisemalla satunnaiset nykimisongelmat</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vakaus">
             <feature>• Parantaa järjestelmän vakautta</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Turvallisuuskorjaus">
             <feature>• Android-turvallisuuskorjaus (marraskuu 2025) on lisätty järjestelmän turvallisuutta varten. Lisätietoja Honorin turvallisuuspäivityksistä on saatavilla verkkosivustollamme osoitteessa https://www.honor.com/fi/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Muistiinpanot" type="end">
             <feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei vaikuta henkilökohtaisiin tietoihisi, mutta tietojen varmuuskopiointi ennen päivittämistä on kuitenkin suositeltavaa
2. Lisätietoja tuoteominaisuuksista on Vihjeitä-sovelluksessa
3. Jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia, saat apua soittamalla Honorin palvelunumeroon tai käymällä Honorin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1036" name="fr-fr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour améliore principalement les performances du système. Effectuez la mise à jour pour profiter des améliorations</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Appareil photo">
             <feature>• Enregistrement écran éteint est désormais disponible. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Appareil photo > Paramètres > Enregistrement écran éteint</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Écran d'accueil">
             <feature>• Le mode transparence optimise les effets de transparence d'éléments tels que les cartes et les dossiers, procurant une expérience visuelle exceptionnelle. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Écran d'accueil et style > Paramètres de l'écran d'accueil > Mode transparence</feature>
             <feature>• Appuyez longuement sur la zone vide de l'écran d'accueil pour commencer la modification</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Écran verrouillé">
             <feature>• L'écran verrouillé propose plus de styles d'horloge. Pincez avec deux doigts sur l'écran verrouillé, appuyez sur Personnaliser, puis appuyez sur l'horloge pour la modifier</feature>
             <feature>• Un effet lumineux tactile répond à votre appui sur l'écran de déverrouillage du mot de passe et dans le Centre de contrôle</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Barre d'état">
             <feature>• La barre d'état autorise la personnalisation des icônes, vous permettant de choisir les icônes à afficher dans la barre d'état. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Notifications et barre d'état > Barre d'état</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic Capsule">
             <feature>• Reconnaissance faciale est intégrée à Magic Capsule. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Notifications et barre d'état > Magic Capsule > Reconnaissance faciale</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap permet des transferts de fichiers transparents entre les appareils Honor, associant vitesse, facilité et plaisir. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Plus de paramètres de connectivité > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Intensité d'utilisation">
             <feature>• Résout les problèmes occasionnels de saccades pour améliorer la fluidité globale de l'appareil</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilité">
             <feature>• Améliore la stabilité du système</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Correctif de sécurité">
             <feature>• Un correctif de sécurité Android (novembre 2025) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité Honor, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour
2. Découvrez plus d'informations sur les fonctionnalités du produit dans Astuces
3. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes pendant la mise à jour, vous pouvez obtenir de l'aide en contactant la hotline de service Honor ou en vous rendant dans un centre de services clients Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1110" name="gl-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado usuario, a novidade principal desta actualización é a mellora do rendemento do sistema. Realice a actualización para gozar das melloras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Cámara">
             <feature>• Agora está dispoñible a Gravación coa pantalla apagada. Próbea facendo o seguinte: Cámara > Configuración > Gravación coa pantalla apagada</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla de inicio">
             <feature>• O modo de transparencia optimiza os efectos de transparencia de elementos como tarxetas e carpetas, o que ofrece unha experiencia visual excepcional. Próbeo facendo o seguinte: Configuración > Pantalla de inicio e estilo > Configuración da pantalla de inicio > Modo de transparencia</feature>
             <feature>• Manteña premida a área en branco da pantalla de inicio para comezar a editar</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla de bloqueo">
             <feature>• A pantalla de bloqueo ofrece máis estilos de reloxo. Belisque con dous dedos na pantalla de bloqueo, toque Personalizado e, a seguir, toque o reloxo para editar</feature>
             <feature>• Un efecto de luz táctil responde ao seu toque na pantalla de desbloqueo con contrasinal e no Centro de control</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Barra de estado">
             <feature>• A barra de estado permite a personalización das iconas, o que lle permite escoller que iconas mostrar na devandita barra de estado. Próbea facendo o seguinte: Configuración > Notificacións e barra de estado > Barra de estado</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Cápsula máxica">
             <feature>• O recoñecemento facial está integrado en Cápsula máxica. Próbeo facendo o seguinte: Configuración > Notificacións e barra de estado > Cápsula máxica > Recoñecemento facial</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Conexión de Honor">
             <feature>• OneTap permite a transferencia de ficheiros sen problemas entre dispositivos Honor, combinando velocidade con facilidade e diversión. Próbeo facendo o seguinte: Configuración > Máis conexións > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Rendemento">
             <feature>• Resolve os problemas ocasionais de tartamudeo a fin de mellorar a fluidez xeral do dispositivo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilidade">
             <feature>• Mellora a estabilidade do sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Parche de seguranza">
             <feature>• Incorporárase un parche de seguranza de Android (novembro de 2025) para a seguranza do sistema. Para obter máis información sobre as actualizacións de seguranza de Honor, visite o noso sitio web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalar esta actualización non afectará os seus datos persoais, pero recoméndase que realice unha copia de seguranza dos datos antes da actualización
2. Descubra máis información sobre as funcionalidades do produto en Consellos
3. Se experimenta problemas durante a actualización, pode chamar á liña directa de servizo de Honor ou ir a un centro de servizos ao cliente de Honor para que lle fornezamos axuda</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1095" name="gu-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ અપડેટ મુખ્યત્વે સિસ્ટમની કામગીરીને વધારે છે. સુધારાનો આનંદ માણવા માટે અપડેટ કરો</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="કૅમેરા">
             <feature>• સ્ક્રીન-બંધ રેકોર્ડિંગ હવે ઉપલબ્ધ છે. કૅમેરા > સેટિંગ્સ > સ્ક્રીન-બંધ રેકોર્ડિંગ પર જઈને તેને અજમાવી જુઓ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="હોમ સ્ક્રીન">
             <feature>• પારદર્શિતા મોડ કાર્ડ્સ અને ફોલ્ડર્સ જેવા તત્વોના પારદર્શિતા પ્રભાવોને ઑપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે, જે એક અસાધારણ દ્રશ્ય અનુભવ પ્રદાન કરે છે. અહીં જઈને તેને અજમાવી જુઓ: સેટિંગ્સ > હોમ સ્ક્રીન અને શૈલી > હોમ સ્ક્રીન સેટિંગ > પારદર્શિતા મોડ</feature>
             <feature>• સંપાદન શરૂ કરવા માટે હોમ સ્ક્રીનના ખાલી ભાગને લાંબા સમય સુધી દબાવો</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="લૉક સ્ક્રીન">
             <feature>• લૉક સ્ક્રીન ઘડિયાળની વધુ શૈલીઓ ઓફર કરે છે. લૉક સ્ક્રીન પર બે આંગળીથી પિંચ કરો, કસ્ટમ પર ટૅપ કરો, પછી સંપાદિત કરવા માટે ઘડિયાળ પર ટૅપ કરો</feature>
             <feature>• સ્પર્શેન્દ્રિય લાઇટ પ્રભાવ પાસવર્ડ અનલૉક સ્ક્રીન પર અને નિયંત્રણ કેન્દ્રમાં તમારા ટૅપનો પ્રતિભાવ આપે છે</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="સ્થિતિ પટ્ટી">
             <feature>• સ્થિતિ પટ્ટી ચિહ્ન કસ્ટમાઇઝેશનને સક્ષમ કરે છે, જેનાથી તમે કયા સ્થિતિ પટ્ટી ચિહ્ન પ્રદર્શિત કરવા તે પસંદ કરી શકો છો. અહીં જઈને તેને અજમાવી જુઓ: સેટિંગ્સ > સૂચનાઓ અને સ્થિતિ પટ્ટી > સ્થિતિ પટ્ટી</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="મેજિક કેપ્સ્યુલ">
             <feature>• ચહેરાની ઓળખ મેજિક કેપ્સ્યુલમાં સંકલિત છે. અહીં જઈને તેને અજમાવી જુઓ: સેટિંગ્સ > સૂચનાઓ અને સ્થિતિ પટ્ટી > મેજિક કેપ્સ્યુલ > ચહેરા ઓળખ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor કનેક્ટ">
             <feature>• ઝડપને સરળતા અને મનોરંજન સાથે જોડીને, OneTap Honor ઉપકરણો વચ્ચે સરળ ફાઇલ ટ્રાન્સફરને સક્ષમ કરે છે. સેટિંગ્સ > વધુ કનેક્શનો > OneTap પર જઈને તેને અજમાવી જુઓ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="કાર્યપ્રદર્શન">
             <feature>• ઉપકરણની એકંદર સુગમતા વધારવા માટે ક્યારેક ક્યારેક થતી સ્ટટરિંગની સમસ્યાઓનું નિરાકરણ કરે છે</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="સ્થિરતા">
             <feature>• સિસ્ટમની સ્થિરતામાં સુધારો કરે છે</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="સુરક્ષા પેચ">
             <feature>• Android સુરક્ષા પેચ (નવેમ્બર 2025) સિસ્ટમ સુરક્ષા માટે સામેલ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. Honor સુરક્ષા અપડેટ્સ વિશે વધુ માહિતી માટે, કૃપા કરીને અમારી વેબસાઇટ ની મુલાકાત લો https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="નોંધો" type="end">
             <feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારા વ્યક્તિગત ડેટાને અસર થશે નહીં, પરંતુ અપડેટ કરતા પહેલાં તમારા ડેટાનો બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે
2. ટિપ્સમાં ઉત્પાદન સુવિધાઓ વિશે વધુ માહિતી મેળવો
3. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો તમે Honor સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરીને અથવા Honor ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્રની મુલાકાત લઈને અમારી મદદ મેળવી શકો છો</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1081" name="hi-in">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>नमस्ते उपयोगकर्ता, इस अद्यतन से मुख्य रूप से सिस्टम प्रदर्शन को बढ़ाया जाता है। सुधारों का फ़ायदा उठाने के लिए अद्यतन करें</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="कैमरा">
             <feature>• बंद स्क्रीन पर रिकॉर्डिंग अब उपलब्ध है। यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़माएँ: कैमरा > सेटिंग्स > बंद स्क्रीन पर रिकॉर्डिंग</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="होम स्क्रीन">
             <feature>• पारदर्शिता मोड से, कार्ड और फ़ोल्डर जैसे तत्वों के पारदर्शिता प्रभावों को अनुकूलित किया जाता है जिससे असाधारण विज़ुअल अनुभव प्राप्त होता है। यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़माएँ: सेटिंग्स > होम स्क्रीन और शैली > होम स्क्रीन सेटिंग्स > पारदर्शिता मोड</feature>
             <feature>• संपादन शुरू करने के लिए होम स्क्रीन खाली जगह पर देर तक दबाएँ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्क्रीन लॉक करें">
             <feature>• लॉक स्क्रीन पर अब घड़ी की और शैलियाँ उपलब्ध हैं। लॉक स्क्रीन पर दो उंगलियों से पिंच करें, कस्टम पर टैप करें, उसके बाद संपादित करने के लिए घड़ी पर टैप करें</feature>
             <feature>• पासवर्ड अनलॉक स्क्रीन और नियंत्रण केंद्र पर आपके टैप पर टैक्टाइल प्रकाश प्रभाव दिखता है</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्थिति बार">
             <feature>• स्थिति बार से आइकन का अनुकूलन सक्षम होता है जिससे आप यह चुन सकते हैं कि कौन-से स्थिति बार आइकन दिखाए जाएँ। यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़माएँ: सेटिंग्स > अधिसूचनाएँ और स्थिति बार > स्थिति बार</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="मैजिक कैप्सूल">
             <feature>• मैजिक कैप्सूल में चेहरा पहचान को एकीकृत किया गया है। यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़माएँ: सेटिंग्स > अधिसूचनाएँ और स्थिति बार > मैजिक कैप्सूल > चेहरा पहचान</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap से Honor डिवाइसेस के बीच आसान फ़ाइल ट्रांसफ़र की सुविधा सक्षम हो जाती है, ताकि स्पीड को आसान और मज़ेदार बनाया जा सके। यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़माएँ: सेटिंग्स > अधिक कनेक्शन > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="प्रदर्शन">
             <feature>• डिवाइस की कुल सुचारुता को बेहतर बनाने के लिए कभी-कभार होने वाली रुकावट की समस्याओं का समाधान किया जाता है</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्थिरता">
             <feature>• सिस्टम स्थिरता में सुधार किया जाता है</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षा पैच">
             <feature>• सिस्टम की सुरक्षा के लिए Android सुरक्षा पैच (नवंबर, 2025) शामिल किया गया है। Honor सुरक्षा अद्यतनों के बारे में अधिक जानकारी के लिए, हमारी वेबसाइट पर जाएँ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोट्स" type="end">
             <feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपके व्यक्तिगत डेटा पर कोई प्रभाव नहीं पड़ेगा, लेकिन फिर भी अद्यतन करने से पहले अपने डेटा का बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है
2. युक्तियाँ में जाकर उत्पाद की सुविधाओं के बारे में अधिक जानकारी खोजें
3. अगर आपको अद्यतन के दौरान कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो आप Honor सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करके या Honor ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाकर हमारी सहायता पा सकते हैं</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1050" name="hr-hr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim se ažuriranjem uglavnom poboljšavaju performanse sustava. Ažurirajte kako biste uživali u poboljšanjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fotoaparat">
             <feature>• Sada je dostupna značajka Snimanje uz isključeni zaslon. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Fotoaparat > Postavke > Snimanje uz isključeni zaslon</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Početni zaslon">
             <feature>• Način transparentnosti optimizira efekte transparentnosti elemenata poput kartica i mapa za iznimno vizualno iskustvo. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Početni zaslon i stil > Postavke početnog zaslona > Način transparentnosti</feature>
             <feature>• Dugo pritisnite prazno područje na početnom zaslonu za početak uređivanja</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zaključani zaslon">
             <feature>• Zaključani zaslon pruža više stilova sata. Približite dva prsta na zaključanom zaslonu, dodirnite opciju Prilagođeno, a zatim dodirnite sat za uređivanje</feature>
             <feature>• Taktilni svjetlosni efekt reagira na vaš dodir na zaslonu za otključavanje lozinkom i u Kontrolnom centru</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Statusna traka">
             <feature>• Statusna traka omogućuje prilagođavanje ikona pa možete odabrati ikone na statusnoj traci za prikaz. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Obavijesti i statusna traka > Statusna traka</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magična kapsula">
             <feature>• Prepoznavanje lica integrirano je u Magičnu kapsulu. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Obavijesti i statusna traka > Magična kapsula > Prepoznavanje lica</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Povezivanje">
             <feature>• OneTap omogućuje besprijekoran prijenos datoteka među Honor uređajima, kombinirajući brzinu s jednostavnošću i zabavom. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Više veza > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Izvođenje">
             <feature>• Otklonjeni su povremeni problemi sa zastojem kako bi se poboljšalo cjelokupno glatko funkcioniranje uređaja</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Poboljšava se stabilnost sustava</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sigurnosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (studeni 2025.) za sigurnost sustava. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima značajke Honor Sigurnost posjetite naše web-mjesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Bilješke" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće utjecati na osobne podatke, ali se svejedno preporučuje izraditi sigurnosnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja
2. Idite u aplikaciju Savjeti kako biste doznali više informacija o značajkama proizvoda
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tijekom ažuriranja, našu pomoć možete dobiti tako da nazovete Honor dežurnu liniju ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1038" name="hu-hu">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez a frissítés elsősorban a rendszerteljesítményt javítja. Végezze el a frissítést, hogy élvezhesse a továbbfejlesztéseket</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• A Kikapcsolt képernyős felvételkészítés mostantól elérhető. Próbálja ki itt: Kamera > Beállítások > Kikapcsolt képernyős felvételkészítés</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Főképernyő">
             <feature>• Az Áttetszőség mód optimalizálja az olyan elemek, mint a kártyák és mappák átlátszósági hatásait, kivételes vizuális élményt nyújtva. Próbálja ki itt: Beállítások > Főképernyő és stílus > Főképernyő-beállítások > Áttetszőség mód</feature>
             <feature>• A szerkesztés megkezdéséhez tartsa nyomva hosszan a főképernyő üres területét</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zárképernyő">
             <feature>• A zárképernyő több órastílust kínál. Csippentse össze két ujját az zárképernyőn, érintse meg a(z) Egyéni gombot, majd a szerkesztéshez érintse meg az órát</feature>
             <feature>• A képernyő megérintésekor fényeffektus reagál a jelszavas feloldó képernyőn és a Vezérlőközpontban</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Állapotsáv">
             <feature>• Az állapotsáv lehetővé teszi az ikonok testreszabását, így kiválaszthatja, hogy mely állapotsávikonok jelenjenek meg. Próbálja ki itt: Beállítások > Értesítések és állapotsáv > Állapotsáv</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic Capsule">
             <feature>• Az Arcfelismerés funkció a Mágikus kapszulába van integrálva. Próbálja ki itt: Beállítások > Értesítések és állapotsáv > Mágikus kapszula > Arcfelismerés</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• A OneTap zökkenőmentes fájlátvitelt tesz lehetővé a Honor készülékek, ötvözve a sebességet a könnyedséggel és a szórakozással. Próbálja ki itt: Beállítások > További kapcsolatok > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Teljesítmény">
             <feature>• Megoldja az esetenként jelentkező akadozási problémákat, hogy javítsa a készülék átfogó, zökkenőmentes működését</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitás">
             <feature>• Javítja a rendszer stabilitását</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Biztonsági javítás">
             <feature>• A rendszerbiztonság érdekében a frissítés az Android biztonsági frissítését (2025. november) is tartalmazza. A Honor biztonsági javításaival kapcsolatos további információkért keresse fel weboldalunkat: https://www.honor.com/hu/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Jegyzetek" type="end">
             <feature>1. A jelen frissítés telepítése nem lesz hatással személyes adataira, de a frissítés előtt az adatokról továbbra is ajánlott biztonsági másolatot készíteni
2. A termékfunkciókkal kapcsolatos további információkat a Tippek alkalmazásban tekintheti meg
3. Ha a frissítés során bármilyen problémába ütközik, forduljon hozzánk segítségért a Honor-szerviz forródrótján, vagy látogasson el a Honor ügyfélszolgálati központjába</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1057" name="in-id">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini utamanya meningkatkan kinerja sistem. Instal pembaruan untuk menikmati berbagai peningkatan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Perekaman saat layar mati kini tersedia. Cobalah dengan membuka: Kamera > Pengaturan > Perekaman saat layar mati</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Layar beranda">
             <feature>• Mode transparansi mengoptimalkan efek tembus pandang pada elemen seperti kartu dan folder sehingga menghadirkan pengalaman visual yang menakjubkan. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Gaya &amp; layar beranda > Pengaturan layar beranda > Mode transparansi</feature>
             <feature>• Tekan lama area kosong pada layar beranda untuk mulai mengedit</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Layar kunci">
             <feature>• Layar kunci menawarkan lebih banyak gaya jam. Jepit dengan dua jari di layar kunci, ketuk Khusus, lalu ketuk jam untuk mengedit</feature>
             <feature>• Efek cahaya taktil yang merespons ketukan Anda di layar buka kunci dengan kata sandi dan di Pusat Kontrol</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bilah status">
             <feature>• Bilah status memungkinkan penyesuaian ikon, sehingga Anda dapat memilih ikon bilah status untuk ditampilkan. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Notifikasi &amp; bilah status > Bilah status</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kapsul Ajaib">
             <feature>• Pengenalan wajah terintegrasi dalam Kapsul Ajaib. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Notifikasi &amp; bilah status > Kapsul Ajaib > Pengenalan wajah</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Koneksi">
             <feature>• OneTap memungkinkan transfer file yang lancar antarperangkat Honor. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Koneksi lainnya > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kinerja">
             <feature>• Menyelesaikan masalah tersendat yang terjadi sesekali untuk meningkatkan kelancaran perangkat secara keseluruhan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitas">
             <feature>• Meningkatkan stabilitas sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Penambal keamanan">
             <feature>• Penambal Keamanan Android (Nov 2025) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan Honor, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Catatan" type="end">
             <feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan untuk mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui
2. Pelajari informasi selengkapnya terkait fitur produk di Kiat
3. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan Honor atau mengunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1040" name="it-it">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento migliora principalmente le prestazioni del sistema. Esegui l'aggiornamento per usufruire dei miglioramenti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fotocamera">
             <feature>• È ora disponibile Registrazione a schermo spento. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Fotocamera > Impostazioni > Registrazione a schermo spento</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Schermata Home">
             <feature>• La modalità trasparenza ottimizza gli effetti di trasparenza di elementi quali schede e cartelle, offrendo un'esperienza visiva eccezionale. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Schermata Home e stile > Impostazioni schermata Home > Modalità trasparenza</feature>
             <feature>• Premi a lungo l'area vuota della schermata Home per iniziare a modificare</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Blocca schermo">
             <feature>• La schermata di blocco offre più stili di orologio. Avvicina due dita sulla schermata di blocco, tocca Personalizzato, quindi tocca l'orologio per modificare</feature>
             <feature>• Un effetto luminoso tattile risponde al tocco sulla schermata di sblocco con la password e nel Centro di controllo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Barra di stato">
             <feature>• La barra di stato consente di personalizzare le icone, consentendo di scegliere le icone della barra di stato da visualizzare. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Notifiche e barra di stato > Barra di stato</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Capsula Magica">
             <feature>• Riconoscimento del viso è integrato in Magic Capsule. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Notifiche e barra di stato > Magic Capsule > Riconoscimento del viso</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap consente il trasferimento ottimale di file tra dispositivi Honor, abbinando velocità, semplicità e divertimento. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Altre connessioni > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Prestazioni">
             <feature>• Vengono risolti i problemi occasionali di immagini a scatto per migliorare la fluidità complessiva del dispositivo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilità">
             <feature>• Viene migliorata la stabilità del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch di sicurezza">
             <feature>• È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (novembre 2025) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza Honor, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Note" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup dei dati prima di procedere
2. Scopri ulteriori informazioni sulle funzioni del prodotto in Suggerimenti
3. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center Honor o visitando un centro servizio clienti Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1037" name="iw-il">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה משפר בעיקר את ביצועי המערכת. עדכן כדי ליהנות מהשיפורים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="מצלמה">
             <feature>‏‏• הקלטה במצב מסך כבוי זמינה כעת. כדי לנסות אותה, אפשר לעבור אל: 'מצלמה' > 'הגדרות' > 'הקלטה במצב מסך כבוי'</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="מסך הבית">
             <feature>‏• מצב 'שקיפות' ממטב את אפקטי השקיפות של אלמנטים כמו כרטיסים ותיקיות, לחוויה חזותית יוצאת מן הכלל. כדי לנסות אותו, אפשר לעבור אל: הגדרות > מסך הבית וסגנון > הגדרות מסך הבית > מצב 'שקיפות'</feature>
             <feature>‏• כדי להתחיל לערוך, לחץ לחיצה ארוכה על השטח הריק במסך הבית</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="מסך נעילה">
             <feature>‏‏• מסך הנעילה מציע סגנונות שעון נוספים. צבוט בשתי אצבעות במסך הנעילה, הקש על האפשרות 'מותאם אישית', ואז הקש על השעון כדי לערוך</feature>
             <feature>‏‏• אפקט אור מישושי מגיב להקשה על מסך ביטול הנעילה באמצעות סיסמה, וגם ב'מרכז בקרה'</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="שורת מצב">
             <feature>‏• שורת המצב מאפשרת התאמה אישית של סמלים, וכך ניתן לבחור אילו סמלים יופיעו בשורת המצב. כדי לנסות זאת, אפשר לעבור אל: הגדרות > התראות ושורת המצב > שורת מצב</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏קפסולת קסם">
             <feature>‏• התכונה 'זיהוי פנים' משולבת ב'קפסולת קסם'. כדי לנסות זאת, אפשר לעבור אל: הגדרות > התראות ושורת המצב > ‏קפסולת קסם > זיהוי פנים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏Honor Connect">
             <feature>‏‏• ‏OneTap מאפשר העברת קבצים חלקה בין התקני Honor, והוא נותן תפקוד מהיר, קל ומהנה. כדי לנסות אותו, אפשר לעבור אל: 'הגדרות' > 'עוד חיבורים' > ‏OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ביצועים">
             <feature>‏‏• פותר את הבעיה של תפקוד תקוע מדי פעם, לשיפור של פעולת ההתקן החלקה באופן כללי</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="יציבות">
             <feature>‏‏• משפר את יציבות המערכת</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="תיקון אבטחה">
             <feature>‏• 'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מנוב' 2025) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של Honor', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="הערות" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון
‏2. גלה מידע נוסף על תכונות המוצר ב'טיפים'
‏3. אם תיתקל בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, ניתן לקבל עזרה מאיתנו באמצעות התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של Honor או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1041" name="ja-jp">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ユーザーの皆様、今回の更新では主にシステムのパフォーマンスが強化されます。更新して、改善をお楽しみください</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="カメラ">
             <feature>• 画面オフ状態の録画を利用できるようになりました。[カメラ] > [設定] > [画面オフ状態の録画]に移動して試してみてください</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ホーム画面">
             <feature>• 透明モードでは、カードやフォルダなどの要素の透明効果が最適化され、非常に優れた視覚体験が実現します。この機能を試すには、[設定] > [ホーム画面とスタイル] > [ホーム画面設定] > [透明モード]に移動してください</feature>
             <feature>• ホーム画面の空白部分を長押しして編集を開始できます</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ロック画面">
             <feature>• ロック画面により多くの時計スタイルが導入されます。ロック画面を2本の指でピンチして、カスタムをタップし、次に時計をタップすると編集できます</feature>
             <feature>• タクタイルライト効果は、パスワードロック解除画面とコントロールセンター内でタップに反応します</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ステータスバー">
             <feature>• ステータスバーでアイコンのカスタマイズが可能になり、表示するステータスバーのアイコンを選択できるようになります。この機能を試すには、[設定] > [通知とステータスバー] > [ステータスバー]に移動してください</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="マジックカプセル">
             <feature>• 顔認証がマジックカプセルに統合されます。この機能を試すには、[設定] > [通知とステータスバー] > [マジックカプセル] > [顔認証]に移動してください</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honorコネクト">
             <feature>• OneTapによって、Honorデバイス間のシームレスなファイル転送が可能になり、スピードに手軽さと楽しさが加わります。[設定] > [その他の接続] > [OneTap]に移動して試してみてください</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="パフォーマンス">
             <feature>• 時折発生するカクつきの問題が解消され、デバイスの全体的なスムーズさが向上します</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安定性">
             <feature>• システムの安定性が改善します</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="セキュリティパッチ">
             <feature>• システムセキュリティのためにAndroidセキュリティパッチ（2025年11月）が組み込まれました。Honorのセキュリティ更新の詳細については、当社のWebサイトをご覧ください：https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="メモ" type="end">
             <feature>1. この更新をインストールしても個人情報への影響はありませんが、更新前に個人情報をバックアップしておくことをおすすめします
2. 製品機能の詳細はヒントアプリで確認してください
3. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、Honorサービスコールセンターにお電話をいただくか、Honorカスタマーサービスセンターにご来店いただき、サポートを受けてください</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1079" name="ka-ge">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ეს განახლება ძირითადად აუმჯობესებს სისტემის ეფექტიანობას. განაახლეთ და ისიამოვნეთ გაუმჯობესებებით</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="კამერა">
             <feature>• ეკრანის გამორთულ მდგომარეობაში ჩაწერა ახლა ხელმისაწვდომია. სცადეთ ის შემდეგზე გადასვლით: კამერა > პარამეტრები > ეკრანის გამორთულ მდგომარეობაში ჩაწერა</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="საწყისი ეკრანი">
             <feature>• გამჭვირვალობის რეჟიმი ოპტიმიზაციას უკეთებს ისეთი ელემენტების გამჭვირვალობის ეფექტებს, როგორიცაა ბარათები და საქაღალდეები, რაც განსაკუთრებულ ვიზუალურ გამოცდილებას უზრუნველყოფს. სცადეთ ეს შემდეგზე გადასვლით: პარამეტრები > საწყისი ეკრანი და სტილი > საწყისი ეკრანის პარამეტრები > გამჭვირვალობის რეჟიმი</feature>
             <feature>• რედაქტირების დასაწყებად ხანგრძლივად დააჭირეთ მთავარი ეკრანის ცარიელ ადგილს</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ჩაკეტილი ეკრანი">
             <feature>• ჩაკეტილი ეკრანი იძლევა საათის მეტ სტილებს. მოუჭირეთ ორი თითი ჩაკეტილ ეკრანზე, შეეხეთ შემდეგს: მორგება, შემდეგ შეეხეთ საათს რედაქტირებისთვის</feature>
             <feature>• ტაქტილური სინათლის ეფექტი რეაგირებს თქვენს შეხებაზე პაროლით განსაბლოკ ეკრანზე და მართვის ცენტრში</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="სტატუსის ზოლი">
             <feature>• სტატუსის ზოლი საშუალებას გაძლევთ, პიქტოგრამების პერსონალიზაცია მოახდინოთ, რაც საშუალებას გაძლევთ აირჩიოთ, თუ რომელი სტატუსის ზოლის პიქტოგრამები გამოჩნდეს. სცადეთ ის შემდეგზე გადასვლით: პარამეტრები > შეტყობინებები და სტატუსის ზოლი > სტატუსის ზოლი</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ჯადოსნური კაფსულა">
             <feature>• სახის ამოცნობის ფუნქცია ინტეგრირებულია ჯადოსნურ კაფსულაში. სცადეთ ეს შემდეგზე გადასვლით: პარამეტრები > შეტყობინებები და სტატუსის ზოლი > ჯადოსნური კაფსულა > სახის ამოცნობა</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor კავშირი">
             <feature>• OneTap უზრუნველყოფს ფაილების შეუფერხებელ გადაცემას Honor მოწყობილობებს შორის, აერთიანებს რა სიჩქარეს სიმარტივესთან და ხალისთან. სცადეთ ის შემდეგზე გადასვლით: პარამეტრები > სხვა კავშირები > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ეფექტურობა">
             <feature>• აგვარებს ხანდახან წარმოქმნილ შეფერხების პრობლემებს მოწყობილობის საერთო შეუფერხებელი მუშაობის გასაუმჯობესებლად</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="სტაბილურობა">
             <feature>• აუმჯობესებს სისტემის სტაბილურობას</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="უსაფრთხოების შესწორება">
             <feature>• სისტემის უსაფრთხოებისთვის ჩაირთო Android-ის უსაფრთხოების შესწორება (2025 წლის ნოემბერი). Honor-ის უსაფრთხოების განახლებების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაციისთვის ეწვიეთ ჩვენს ვებსაიტს: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="შენიშვნები" type="end">
             <feature>1. ამ განახლების დაინსტალირება არ იმოქმედებს თქვენს პერსონალურ მონაცემებზე, თუმცა რეკომენდებულია განახლებამდე მონაცემების სარეზერვო ასლის შექმნა
2. გაეცანით დამატებით ინფორმაციას რჩევებში პროდუქტის ფუნქციების შესახებ
3. თუ განახლებისას გარკვეულ პრობლემებს წააწყდით, დახმარებისთვის დარეკეთ Honor-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან ეწვიეთ Honor-ის სერვისცენტრს</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1087" name="kk-kz">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл жаңарту негізінен жүйе өнімділігін жақсартады. Жақсартуларды пайдалану үшін жаңартыңыз</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Камера">
             <feature>• Өшірулі экран жазбасы енді қолжетімді. «Kамера» > «Параметрлер» > «Өшірулі экран жазбасы» тармағына өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Негізгі экран">
             <feature>• Мөлдірлік режимі карталар мен қалталар сияқты элементтердің мөлдірлік әсерлерін оңтайландырады, ерекше визуалды тәжірибе береді. «Параметрлер» > «Негізгі экран және стиль» > «Негізгі экран параметрлері» > «Мөлдірлік режимі» тармағына өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз</feature>
             <feature>• Өңдеуді бастау үшін негізгі экранның бос аймағын ұзақ басыңыз</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Құлыптау экраны">
             <feature>• Құлыптау экраны көбірек сағат стильдерін ұсынады. Құлыптау экранында екі саусақты бір-біріне жақындатып, Реттелетін түймесін түртіп, өңдейтін сағатты түртіңіз</feature>
             <feature>• Тактильді жарық әсері құпиясөзді ашу экранында және Басқару орталығында түртуге жауап береді</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Күй жолағы">
             <feature>• Күй жолағы белгішені реттеуге мүмкіндік береді, бұл сізге қай күй жолағы белгішелерін көрсету керектігін таңдауға рұқсат етеді. «Параметрлер» > «Хабарландырулар мен күй жолағы» > «Күй жолағы» тармағына өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Сиқырлы капсула">
             <feature>• «Бетті тану» мүмкіндігі «Сиқырлы капсула» мүмкіндігіне біріктірілген. «Параметрлер» > «Хабарландырулар мен күй жолағы» > «Сиқырлы капсула» > «Бетті тану» тармағына өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Қосылу">
             <feature>• OneTap қызметі Honor құрылғылары арасында үздіксіз файлды тасымалдауға мүмкіндік береді, бұл жылдамдық, оңайлық пен көңілділікті біріктіреді. «Параметрлер» > «Қосымша байланыстар» > «OneTap» тармағына өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Өнімділік">
             <feature>• Құрылғының жалпы бірқалыптылығын жақсарту үшін анда-санда кідіріс мәселелерін шешеді</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Тұрақтылық">
             <feature>• Жүйе тұрақтылығын жақсартады</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Қауіпсіздік патчы">
             <feature>• Android қауіпсіздік патчы (қараша, 2025) жүйе қауіпсіздігі үшін біріктірілген. Honor қауіпсіздік жаңартулары туралы қосымша ақпарат алу үшін біздің веб-сайтқа кіріңіз: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Ескертпелер" type="end">
             <feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнату жеке деректеріңізге әсер етпейді, бірақ жаңарту алдында деректердің сақтық көшірмесін жасау ұсынылады
2. «Кеңестер» қолданбасында өнім мүмкіндіктері туралы қосымша ақпаратты табыңыз
3. Жаңарту кезінде қандай да бір мәселе орын алса, Honor қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне қоңырау шалу не Honor тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына бару арқылы көмегімізді ала аласыз</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1107" name="km-kh">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះធ្វើឱ្យប្រតិបត្តិការប្រព័ន្ធប្រសើរឡើងជាចម្បង។ ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព ដើម្បីរីករាយនឹងការកែលម្អទាំងនេះ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="កាមេរ៉ា​">
             <feature>• ការថតដោយអេក្រង់បិទឥឡូវអាចប្រើបានហើយ។ សាកល្បងប្រើដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ កាមេរ៉ា > ការកំណត់ > ការថតដោយបិទអេក្រង់</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="អេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម">
             <feature>• ម៉ូដថ្លាធ្វើឱ្យប្រសើរឡើងនូវបែបផែនថ្លានៃធាតុដូចជាកាត និងថតឯកសារ ដោយផ្ដល់នូវបទពិសោធមើលឃើញដ៏ល្អឥតខ្ចោះ។ សាកល្បងប្រើដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ការកំណត់ > រចនាប័ទ្ម និងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម > ការកំណត់អេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម > ម៉ូដថ្លា</feature>
             <feature>• ចុចឱ្យជាប់លើផ្ទៃទទេនៃអេក្រង់ដើមដើម្បីចាប់ផ្ដើមកែ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="អេក្រង់ជាប់សោ">
             <feature>• អេក្រង់ចាក់សោផ្ដល់នូវរចនាបថនាឡិកាជាច្រើន។ ខ្ទាស់ដោយប្រើម្រាមដៃពីរនៅលើអេក្រង់ចាក់សោ ប៉ះតាមតម្រូវការ បន្ទាប់មកប៉ះនាឡិកាដើម្បីកែសម្រួល</feature>
             <feature>• បែបផែន​ពន្លឺ​រំញ័រឆ្លើយតប​ទៅនឹង​ការ​ប៉ះ​របស់​អ្នក​នៅ​លើ​អេក្រង់​ដោះ​សោ​ពាក្យសម្ងាត់ និង​ក្នុង​មជ្ឈមណ្ឌល​គ្រប់គ្រង</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="របារ​ស្ថានភាព">
             <feature>• របារស្ថានភាពអនុញ្ញាតឱ្យប្ដូររូបតំណាងតាមបំណង ដែលអនុញ្ញាតឱ្យអ្នកជ្រើសរើសរូបតំណាងរបារស្ថានភាពដែលត្រូវបង្ហាញ។ សាកល្បងប្រើដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > ការជូនដំណឹង និងរបារស្ថានភាព > របារស្ថានភាព</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ខេបស៊ូលវេទមន្ត">
             <feature>• ការចំណាំ​ភិនភាគមុខ​ត្រូវបានរួមបញ្ចូលទៅក្នុង ខេបស៊ូលវេទមន្ត។ សាកល្បងប្រើដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > ការជូនដំណឹង និងរបារស្ថានភាព > ខេបស៊ូលវេទមន្ត > ការចំណាំភិនភាគមុខ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap បើកដំណើរការផ្ទេរឯកសាររវាងឧបករណ៍ Honor ដោយរលូន រួមបញ្ចូលគ្នានូវល្បឿនជាមួយនឹងភាពងាយស្រួល និងរីករាយ។ សាកល្បងប្រើដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > ការតភ្ជាប់ច្រើនទៀត > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ដំណើរការ">
             <feature>• ដោះស្រាយបញ្ហាការជាប់គាំងម្ដងម្កាល ដើម្បីបង្កើនភាពរលូននៃឧបករណ៍ទាំងមូល</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ស្ថិរភាព">
             <feature>• កែលម្អស្ថិរភាពប្រព័ន្ធ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="បំណះសន្តិសុខ">
             <feature>• បំណះសន្តិសុខ Android (វិច្ឆិកា 2025) ត្រូវបាន​រួមបញ្ចូល​សម្រាប់​សន្តិសុខ​ប្រព័ន្ធ។ សម្រាប់​ព័ត៌មាន​បន្ថែម​អំពី​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​សន្តិសុខ Honor សូមចូលទៅ​គេហទំព័រ​របស់យើង https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់" type="end">
             <feature>1. ការដំឡើងបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះនឹងមិនប៉ះពាល់ដល់ទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួនរបស់អ្នកទេ ប៉ុន្តែសូមណែនាំឱ្យបម្រុងទុកទិន្នន័យរបស់អ្នក មុននឹងធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព
2. ស្វែងយល់បន្ថែមអំពីលក្ខណៈពិសេសផលិតផលនៅក្នុងគន្លឹះ
3. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបប្រទះបញ្ហាណាមួយអំឡុងពេលធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព អ្នកអាចទទួលបានជំនួយរបស់យើងដោយហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សនៃសេវាកម្ម Honor ឬចូលទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌលសេវាកម្មអតិថិជន Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1099" name="kn-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಮುಖ್ಯವಾಗಿ ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಕಾರ್ಯಕ್ಷಮತೆಯನ್ನು ವರ್ಧಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಸುಧಾರಣೆಗಳನ್ನು ಆನಂದಿಸಲು ನವೀಕರಿಸಿ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾ">
             <feature>• ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್-ಆಫ್ ರೆಕಾರ್ಡಿಂಗ್ ಈಗ ಲಭ್ಯವಿದೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ: ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾ > ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್‌-ಆಫ್ ರೆಕಾರ್ಡಿಂಗ್‌</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್">
             <feature>• ಕಾರ್ಡ್‌ಗಳು ಮತ್ತು ಫೋಲ್ಡರ್‌ಗಳಂತಹ ಎಲಿಮೆಂಟ್‌ಗಳ ಪಾರದರ್ಶಕತೆ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಪಾರದರ್ಶಕತೆ ಮೋಡ್ ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ, ಇದು ಅಸಾಧಾರಣ ದೃಶ್ಯ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ನೀಡುತ್ತದೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ ನೋಡಿ: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಮತ್ತು ಶೈಲಿ > ಹೋಮ್‌ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಪಾರದರ್ಶಕತೆ ಮೋಡ್</feature>
             <feature>• ಎಡಿಟಿಂಗ್ ಪ್ರಾರಂಭಿಸಲು ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್‌ನ ಖಾಲಿ ಜಾಗವನ್ನು ದೀರ್ಘವಾಗಿ ಒತ್ತಿರಿ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಲಾಕ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್">
             <feature>• ಲಾಕ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಗಡಿಯಾರ ಶೈಲಿಗಳನ್ನು ನೀಡುತ್ತದೆ. ಲಾಕ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಮೇಲೆ ಎರಡು ಬೆರಳುಗಳಿಂದ ಪಿಂಚ್ ಮಾಡಿ, ಕಸ್ಟಮ್ ಟ್ಯಾಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ, ನಂತರ ಎಡಿಟ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಗಡಿಯಾರವನ್ನು ಟ್ಯಾಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ</feature>
             <feature>• ಗುಪ್ತಪದ ಅನ್‌ಲಾಕ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಮತ್ತು ಕಂಟ್ರೋಲ್ ಸೆಂಟರ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ನಿಮ್ಮ ಟ್ಯಾಪ್‌ಗೆ ಸ್ಪರ್ಶ ಸಂಬಂಧಿ ಬೆಳಕಿನ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಪ್ರತಿಕ್ರಿಯಿಸುತ್ತದೆ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಸ್ಥಿತಿ ಪಟ್ಟಿ">
             <feature>• ಸ್ಥಿತಿ ಪಟ್ಟಿಯು ಐಕಾನ್ ಕಸ್ಟಮೈಸೇಶನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಸಕ್ರಿಯಗೊಳಿಸುತ್ತದೆ, ಇದು ಯಾವ ಸ್ಥಿತಿ ಪಟ್ಟಿ ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಪ್ರದರ್ಶಿಸಬೇಕೆಂಬುದನ್ನು ಆಯ್ಕೆ ಮಾಡಲು ನಿಮಗೆ ಅನುಮತಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ ನೋಡಿ: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಅಧಿಸೂಚನೆಗಳು ಮತ್ತು ಸ್ಥಿತಿ ಪಟ್ಟಿ > ಸ್ಥಿತಿ ಪಟ್ಟಿ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಮ್ಯಾಜಿಕ್ ಕ್ಯಾಪ್ಸೂಲ್">
             <feature>• ಮ್ಯಾಜಿಕ್ ಕ್ಯಾಪ್ಸೂಲ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಮುಖ ಗುರುತಿಸುವಿಕೆಯನ್ನು ಏಕೀಕೃತಗೊಳಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ ನೋಡಿ: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಅಧಿಸೂಚನೆಗಳು ಮತ್ತು ಸ್ಥಿತಿ ಪಟ್ಟಿ > ಮ್ಯಾಜಿಕ್ ಕ್ಯಾಪ್ಸೂಲ್ > ಮುಖ ಗುರುತಿಸುವಿಕೆ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ಕನೆಕ್ಟ್">
             <feature>• OneTap ನಿಮಗೆ Honor ಸಾಧನಗಳ ನಡುವೆ ಸರಾಗ ಫೈಲ್ ವರ್ಗಾವಣೆಯನ್ನು ಸಕ್ರಿಯಗೊಳಿಸುತ್ತದೆ, ವೇಗವನ್ನು ಸರಾಗತೆ ಮತ್ತು ಮೋಜಿನೊಂದಿಗೆ ಸಂಯೋಜಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಇನ್ನೂ ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಸಂಪರ್ಕಗಳು > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಕಾರ್ಯನಿರ್ವಹಣೆ">
             <feature>• ಸಾಧನದ ಒಟ್ಟಾರೆ ಸ್ಮೂಥ್‌ನೆಸ್ ಅನ್ನು ವರ್ಧಿಸಲು ಸಾಂದರ್ಭಿಕ ಸ್ಟಟರಿಂಗ್ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಪರಿಹರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಸ್ಥಿರತೆ">
             <feature>• ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಸ್ಥಿರತೆಯನ್ನು ಸುಧಾರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್">
             <feature>• ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಭದ್ರತೆಗಾಗಿ Android ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ (ನವೆಂಬರ್ 2025) ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. Honor ಭದ್ರತಾ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಗಾಗಿ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಮ್ಮ ವೆಬ್‌ಸೈಟ್‌ಗೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡಿ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು" type="end">
             <feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾದ ಮೇಲೆ ಪರಿಣಾಮ ಬೀರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೂ ಸಹ ನವೀಕರಿಸುವ ಮೊದಲು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಬ್ಯಾಕ್ ಅಪ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ
2. ಉತ್ಪನ್ನ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಯನ್ನು ಸಲಹೆಗಳು ಎಂಬುದರಲ್ಲಿ ಕಂಡುಕೊಳ್ಳಿ
3. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನಿಮಗೆ ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳು ಎದುರಾದರೆ, ನೀವು Honor ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಅಥವಾ Honor ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ನಮ್ಮ ಸಹಾಯವನ್ನು ಪಡೆಯಬಹುದು</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1042" name="ko-kr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>사용자 여러분, 이번 업데이트는 주로 시스템 성능을 향상시킵니다. 업데이트하고 개선된 기능을 즐겨 보세요</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="카메라">
             <feature>• 이제 화면이 꺼진 상태에서 녹화 기능을 사용할 수 있습니다. 카메라 > 설정 > 화면이 꺼진 상태에서 녹화(으)로 이동하여 사용해 보세요</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="홈 화면">
             <feature>• 투명 모드는 카드, 폴더와 같은 요소의 투명 효과를 최적화하여 뛰어난 시각적 경험을 제공합니다. 설정 > 홈 화면 및 스타일 > 홈 화면 설정 > 투명 모드로 이동하여 사용해 보세요</feature>
             <feature>• 홈 화면의 빈 공간을 길게 누르면 편집을 시작할 수 있습니다</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="잠금 화면">
             <feature>• 잠금 화면에서 더 다양한 시계 스타일을 이용할 수 있습니다. 편집하려면 잠금 화면에서 두 손가락을 모으고 사용자 설정을 탭한 후 시계를 탭하세요</feature>
             <feature>• 암호 잠금 해제 화면과 컨트롤 센터에 탭하면 반응하는 촉각적 조명 효과가 적용되었습니다</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="상태 표시줄">
             <feature>• 상태 표시줄에서 아이콘 사용자 설정을 지원하여 표시할 상태 표시줄 아이콘을 선택할 수 있습니다. 설정 > 알림 및 상태 표시줄 > 상태 표시줄로 이동하여 사용해 보세요</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="매직 캡슐">
             <feature>• 얼굴 인식이 매직 캡슐에 통합되었습니다. 설정 > 알림 및 상태 표시줄 > 매직 캡슐 > 얼굴 인식으로 이동하여 사용해 보세요</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor 커넥트">
             <feature>• OneTap은 Honor 장치 간의 원활한 파일 전송을 지원하여 빠르고 편리하며 재미있게 이용할 수 있습니다. 설정 > 연결 더 보기 > OneTap(으)로 이동하여 사용해 보세요</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="성능">
             <feature>• 가끔씩 발생하는 끊김 문제가 해결되어 장치가 전반적으로 더욱 매끄럽게 작동합니다</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="안정성">
             <feature>• 시스템 안정성이 개선되었습니다</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="보안 패치">
             <feature>• 시스템 보안을 위해 Android 보안 패치(2025년 11월)가 통합되었습니다. Honor 보안 업데이트에 대해 자세히 알아보려면 당사 웹사이트(https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11)를 방문하세요.</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="공지" type="end">
             <feature>1. 이 업데이트 설치는 개인 데이터에 영향을 미치지 않지만, 업데이트하기 전에 데이터를 백업하는 것이 좋습니다
2. Tips에서 제품 기능에 대한 자세한 정보를 알아보세요
3. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 Honor 서비스 핫라인으로 전화하거나 Honor 고객 서비스 센터를 방문하여 도움을 받을 수 있습니다</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1108" name="lo-la">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ສະ​ບາຍ​ດີ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​​ນີ້​ຍົກ​ລະ​ດັບ​ປະ​ສິດ​ທິ​ພາບ​ຂອງ​ລະ​ບົບ​ເປັນຫຼັກ. ອັບ​ເດດ​ເພື່ອ​ມ່ວ​ນ​ຊື່​ນກັບ​ການ​ປັບ​ປຸງ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ກ້ອງຖ່າຍຮູບ">
             <feature>• ການບັນທຶກ​​ດ້ວຍໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ປິດ​ສາ​ມາດ​ໃຊ້​ໄດ້​ແລ້ວ​ຕອນ​ນີ້. ​ລອງໃຊ້ມັນເບິ່ງ​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ກ້ອງຖ່າຍຮູບ > ການຕັ້ງຄ່າ > ການບັນທຶກດ້ວຍໜ້າຈໍປິດ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ">
             <feature>• ໂໝດ​ຄວາມ​ໂປ່ງ​ໃສປັບ​ເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ຄວາມ​ໂປ່ງ​ໃ​ສ​ຂອງ​ອົງ​ປະ​ກອບ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ ເຊັ່ນ: ​ບັດ ແລະ ໂຟ​ລ​ເດີ, ເຊິ່ງ​ໃຫ້​ປະ​ສົບ​ການ​ພາບພິ​ເສດ. ​ລອງໃຊ້ມັນເບິ່ງ​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການຕັ້ງຄ່າ > ໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ ແລະ ຮູບແບບ > ການຕັ້ງຄ່າໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ > ໂໝດຄວາມໂປ່ງໃສ</feature>
             <feature>• ກົດ​​ພື້ນ​ທີ່​ຫວ່າງ​ເປົ່າ​ຂອງ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ​ຄ້າງໄວ້ ເພື່ອເລີ່ມ​ຕົ້ນ​ການ​ແກ້​ໄຂ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ໜ້າຈໍລັອກ">
             <feature>• ໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ​ສະ​ເໜີ​ໃຫ້​ຮູບ​ແບບ​ໂມງ​ເພີ່ມ​ເຕີມ. ຢິບ​ເຂົ້າ​ດ້ວຍ​ນິ້ວ​ມື​ສອງ​ນິ້ວ​ໃນ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍລັອກ, ແຕະ ກຳນົດເອງ, ຈາກນັ້ນ​ແຕະ​ໂມງ​ເພື່ອ​ແກ້​ໄຂ</feature>
             <feature>• ​ເອັບ​ເຝັກແສງ​ສຳ​ຜັດ​ຕອບ​ສະ​ໜອງ​ຕໍ່​ການ​ແຕະ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໃນ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ການ​ປົດ​ລັອກ​ດ້ວຍ​ລະ​ຫັດ​ຜ່ານ ແລະ ໃນ​ສູນ​ການ​ແຈ້ງ​ເຕືອນ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ແຖບສະຖານະ">
             <feature>• ແຖບ​ສະ​ຖາ​ນະ​ເປີດ​ໃຊ້​ງານ​ການ​ກຳ​ນົດ​ໄອ​ຄອນ​ເອງ, ເຊິ່ງ​ອະ​ນຸ​ຍາດ​ໃຫ້​ທ່ານ​ເລືອກ​ວ່າ​ໃຫ້ໄອ​ຄອນແຖບສະຖານະ​ໃດ​ສະ​ແດງ. ​ລອງໃຊ້ມັນເບິ່ງ​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການຕັ້ງຄ່າ > ການແຈ້ງເຕືອນ ແລະ ແຖບສະຖານະ > ແຖບສະຖານະ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ແຄັບ​ຊູ​ລ​ເມ​ຈິກ">
             <feature>• ການ​ຮັບ​ຮູ້​ໃບ​ໜ້າຖືກ​ລວມ​ເຂົ້າ​ກັບແຄັບ​ຊູ​ລ​ເມ​ຈິກ. ​ລອງໃຊ້ມັນເບິ່ງ​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການຕັ້ງຄ່າ > ການແຈ້ງເຕືອນ ແລະ ແຖບສະຖານະ > ແຄັບຊູລເມຈິກ > ການຮັບຮູ້ໃບໜ້າ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap ເປີດ​ໃຊ້​ງານ​ການ​ໂອນ​ໄຟ​ລ໌​ທີ່​ຄ່ອງ​ຕົວ​ລະ​ຫວ່າງ​ອຸ​ປະ​ກອນ Honor, ເຊິ່ງປະ​ສົມ​ປະ​ສານ​ຄວາມ​ໄວ​ກັບ​ຄວາມ​ງ່າຍ​ດາຍ ແລະ ຄວາມ​​ມ່ວນ​ຊື່ນ. ​ລອງໃຊ້ມັນເບິ່ງ​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການຕັ້ງຄ່າ > ການເຊື່ອມຕໍ່ເພີ່ມເຕີມ > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ການປະຕິບັດ">
             <feature>• ແກ້​ໄຂ​ບັນ​ຫາການ​ສະ​ດຸດ​ເປັນ​ບາງ​ຄັ້ງ​ຄາ​ວ ເພື່ອ​ຍົກ​ລະ​ດັບ​ຄວາມ​ຄ່ອງ​​​ຕົວ​ໂດຍ​ລວມ​ຂອງ​ອຸ​ປະ​ກອນ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ຄວາມສະ​ຖຽນ">
             <feature>• ປັບປຸງຄວາມສະຖຽນຂອງລະບົບ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ">
             <feature>• ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ຂອງ Android (ພະ​ຈິກ 2025) ​ໄດ້ຖືກລວມ​​ເຂົ້າ​ເປັນ​ການ​ຮັກ​ສາ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ລະ​ບົບ. ສຳລັບຂໍ້ມູນເພີ່ມເຕີມກ່ຽວກັບການອັບເດດດ້ານຄວາມປອດໄພຂອງ Honor, ກະລຸນາເຂົ້າໄປ​ທີ່ເວັບໄຊຂອງພວກເຮົາ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ການ​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ສົ່ງ​ຜົນ​ຕໍ່​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ, ແຕ່​ຍັງ​ຄົງ​ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ສຳ​ຮອງ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄວ້ກ່ອນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ
2. ຄົ້ນ​ຫາ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ເພີ່ມ​ເຕີມ​ກ່ຽວ​ກັບ​ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດ​ຜະ​ລິດ​ຕະ​ພັນ​ໃນ​​ເຄັດ​ລັບ
3. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ທ່ານສາມາດຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອຈາກພວກເຮົາໄດ້ ໂດຍການໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນ​ບໍ​ລິ​ການ Honor ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1063" name="lt-lt">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šis naujinys daugiausiai pagerina sistemos našumą. Atnaujinkite ir mėgaukitės patobulinimais.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Nuo šiol galima naudotis įrašymo išjungus ekraną funkcija. Išbandykite ta nuėję į „Kamera > Nuostatos > Įrašymas išjungus ekraną“</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pradžios ekranas">
             <feature>• Skaidrumo režimas optimizuoja kortelių, aplankų ir kitų elementų skaidrumo efektus, užtikrinant išskirtinę vizualinę patirtį. Išbandykite jį nuėję į „Nuostatos > Pradžios ekranas ir stilius > Pradžios ekrano nuostatos > Skaidrumo režimas“</feature>
             <feature>• Paspauskite ir palaikykite tuščią pradžios ekrano sritį, kad pradėtumėte redaguoti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Užrakinimo ekranas">
             <feature>• Užrakinimo ekrane siūloma daugiau laikrodžio stilių. Suspauskite du pirštus užrakinimo ekrane, palieskite Tinkintas, tada palieskite laikrodį, kad galėtumėte redaguoti</feature>
             <feature>• Į lietimą slaptažodžio atrakinimo ekrane ir valdymo centre reaguoja lietimui jautrus šviesos efektas</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Būsenos juosta">
             <feature>• Būsenos juostoje galima tinkinti piktogramas, leidžiant pasirinkti, kurios būsenos juostos piktogramos bus rodomos. Išbandykite tai, nuėję į „Nuostatos > Pranešimai ir būsenos juosta > Būsenos juosta“</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stebuklingoji kapsulė">
             <feature>• Veido atpažinimo funkcija yra integruota į stebuklingąją kapsulę. Išbandykite ją, nuėję į „Nuostatos > Pranešimai ir būsenos juosta > Stebuklingoji kapsulė > Veido atpažinimas“</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="„Honor Connect“">
             <feature>• „OneTap“ leidžia sklandžiai persiųsti failus tarp „Honor“ įrenginių, kad galėtumėte naudotis sparčiai, lengvai ir smagiai. Išbandykite ją nuėję į „Nuostatos > Daugiau ryšio galimybių > „OneTap““</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Našumas">
             <feature>• Išspręsti retkarčiais pasitaikantys užstrigimo sutrikimai, kad įrenginys veiktų sklandžiau</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilumas">
             <feature>• Pagerinamas sistemos stabilumas</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Saugumo pataisa">
             <feature>• Siekiant užtikrinti sistemos saugumą, įtraukta „Android“ saugumo pataisa (2025 m. lapkričio mėn.). Jei reikia daugiau informacijos apie Honor saugumo naujinius, apsilankykite mūsų svetainėje https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Pastabos" type="end">
             <feature>1. Šio naujinio įdiegimas neturės įtakos jūsų asmeniniams duomenims, tačiau prieš atnaujinant rekomenduojama sukurti atsarginę duomenų kopiją
2. Daugiau informacijos apie gaminio funkcijas rasite Patarimuose
3. Jei naujinimo metu kiltų bet kokių problemų, galite kreiptis į mus pagalbos paskambindami „Honor priežiūros karštąja linija arba apsilankydami „Honor“ klientų aptarnavimo centre</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1062" name="lv-lv">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo atjauninājumu galvenokārt ir uzlabota sistēmas veiktspēja. Atjauniniet, lai izbaudītu uzlabojumus</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Tagad ir pieejama funkcija Izslēgta ekrāna ieraksts. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Kamera > Iestatījumi > Izslēgta ekrāna ieraksts</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sākuma ekrāns">
             <feature>• Caurspīdīguma režīms optimizē tādu elementu kā karšu un mapju caurspīdības efektus, nodrošinot izcilu vizuālo pieredzi. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Iestatījumi > Sākuma ekrāns un stils > Sākuma ekrāna iestatījumi > Caurspīdīguma režīms</feature>
             <feature>• Lai sāktu rediģēšanu, ilgi nospiediet sākuma ekrāna tukšo laukumu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bloķēšanas ekrāns">
             <feature>• Bloķēšanas ekrānā ir pieejami vairāk pulksteņa stilu. Bloķēšanas ekrānā saspiediet divus pirkstus, pieskarieties Pielāgots un pēc tam pieskarieties pulkstenim, lai rediģētu</feature>
             <feature>• Taktilās gaismas efekts reaģē uz pieskārienu paroles atbloķēšanas ekrānā un vadības centrā</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Statusa josla">
             <feature>• Statusa josla ļauj pielāgot ikonas, ļaujot izvēlēties, kuras statusa joslas ikonas rādīt. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Iestatījumi > Paziņojumi un statusa josla > Statusa josla</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Maģijas kapsula">
             <feature>• Sejas atpazīšana ir integrēta Maģijas kapsulā. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Iestatījumi > Paziņojumi un statusa josla > Maģijas kapsula > Sejas atpazīšana</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap nodrošina netraucētu failu pārsūtīšanu starp Honor ierīcēm, apvienojot ātrumu ar vienkāršību un jautrību. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Iestatījumi > Citi savienojumi > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Veiktspēja">
             <feature>• Novērš neregulāras raustīšanās problēmas, lai uzlabotu ierīces kopējo vienmērīgumu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitāte">
             <feature>• Uzlabo sistēmas stabilitāti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Drošības ielāps">
             <feature>• Sistēmas drošībai iekļauts Android drošības ielāps (2025. gada novembris). Lai iegūtu papildinformāciju par Honor drošības atjauninājumiem, lūdzu, apmeklējiet mūsu vietni https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Piezīmes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Šī atjauninājuma instalēšana neietekmēs jūsu personas datus, taču joprojām ir ieteicams pirms atjaunināšanas dublēt datus
2. Lietotnē Padomi atklājiet vairāk par produkta funkcijām
3. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, varat saņemt mūsu palīdzību, zvanot uz Honor klientu apkalpošanas dienesta tālruni vai apmeklējot Honor klientu pakalpojumu centru.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="mai-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, ई अपडेट मुख्य रूप सँ सिस्टमक कार्य-क्षमता केँ वर्धित करैत अछि। सुधार सभक आनंद लेबाक लेल अपडेट करू</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="कैमरा">
             <feature>• स्क्रीन-बंद रिकॉर्डिंग आब उपलब्ध अछि। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: कैमरा > सेटिंग्स > स्क्रीन-बंद रिकॉर्डिंग</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="होम स्क्रीन">
             <feature>• पारदर्शी मोड कार्ड आ फोल्डर सभ सन तत्व सभक पारदर्शी प्रभाव सभ केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि, जाहि सँ असाधारण दृश्य अनुभव प्रदान कयल जा सकए। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: सेटिंग्स > होम स्क्रीन आ शैली > होम स्क्रीनक सेटिंग्स > पारदर्शी मोड</feature>
             <feature>• संपादन शुरू करबाक लेल होम स्क्रीन केर रिक्त क्षेत्र केँ जोर सँ दबाउ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="लॉक स्क्रीन">
             <feature>• लॉक स्क्रीन आओर घड़ी शैली सभ प्रस्तुत करैत अछि। लॉक स्क्रीन पर संपादित करबाक लेल दूटा आँगुर सँ पिंच करू, अनुकूलन केँ टैप करू, तकर बाद घड़ी पर टैप करू</feature>
             <feature>• पासवर्ड अनलॉक स्क्रीन आ नियंत्रण केंद्र पर अहाँक टैप कयला सँ एकटा स्पर्शनीय प्रकाश प्रभाव देखाय दैत अछि</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्टेटस बार">
             <feature>• स्थिति बार आइकन समायोजन केँ सक्षम करैत अछि, जे अहाँ केँ डिस्प्ले लेल स्थिति बार चुनबाक अनुमति दैत अछि। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: सेटिंग्स > अधिसूचना आ स्थिति बार > स्थिति बार</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="मैजिक कैप्सूल">
             <feature>• चेहरा पहिचान मैजिक कैप्सूल मे एकीकृत कयल अछि। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: सेटिंग्स > अधिसूचना आ स्थिति बार > मैजिक कैप्सूल > चेहरा पहिचान</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor कनेक्ट">
             <feature>• OneTap Honor डिवाइस सभक बीच निर्बाध फाइल ट्रांसफर केँ सक्षम करैत अछि, जे गति केर संग आसानी आ मनोरंजन केर संयोजन करैत अछि। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: सेटिंग्स > आओर कनेक्शन सभ > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="प्रदर्शन">
             <feature>• डिवाइसक समग्र सहजता केँ बढ़यबाक लेल कखनो-काल होमए वला झलमलेबाक समस्याक समाधान करैत अछि</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्थिरता">
             <feature>• सिस्टमक स्थिरता मे सुधार करैत अछि</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षा पैच">
             <feature>सिस्टमक सुरक्षाक लेल Android सुरक्षा पैच (नवंबर 2025) समाविष्ट कयल गेल अछि। Honor सुरक्षा अपडेट सभक विषय मे आओर जानकारीक लेल, कृपाकए हमरासभक वेबसाइट केँ देखू: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोट्स" type="end">
             <feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा प्रभावित नहि होयत, मुदा तैयो अपडेट करए सँ पहिने अहाँ केँ डेटाक बैकअप लेबाक सुझाव देल जाइत अछि
2. टिप्स मे उत्पाद विशेषता सभ पर आओर जानकारी डिस्‍कवर करू
3. यदि अपडेट केर दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' अहाँ Honor सेवा हॉटलाइन केँ कॉल कए वा Honor सर्विस सेंटर जा कए हमरासभक मदति प्राप्त कए सकैत छी</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1153" name="mi-NZ">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>E te kaiwhakamahi aroha, ko tēnei whakahoutanga e whakarei ake ana i te mahinga pūnaha. Whakahōu ki te oaoa i te whakapai ake</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kāmera">
             <feature>• Kua wātea ināianei te Hopukanga whakaweto te mata. Whakamātauria mā te haere ki: Kāmera > Ngā tautuhinga > Hopukanga whakaweto te mata</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Mata kāinga">
             <feature>• Ka arotau e te Aratau te mārama ngā pānga te mārama o ngā wāhanga pēnei i ngā kāri me ngā kōpaki, hei whakarato wheako tirohanga tino pai. Whakamātauria mā te haere ki: Ngā Tautuhinga > Mata kāinga &amp; kāhua > Ngā tautuhinga mata kāinga > Aratau te mārama</feature>
             <feature>• Pato roa i te wāhi kau o te mata kāinga hei tīmata i te whakatika</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Mata maukati">
             <feature>• Ka tukuna e te mata maukati he maha atu momo kāhua karaka. Kinikini ki ngā maihao e rua i runga i te mata maukati, pato Ritenga ake, katahi ka pato i te karaka hei whakatika</feature>
             <feature>• He rākeitanga rama ā-tinana ka urupare ki tō pato i te mata wetemaukati kupuhipa me te Pokapū Mana</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pae tūnga">
             <feature>• Ka whakahohe te Pae tūnga i te whakarite ata, ā, ka taea e koe te kōwhiri ko ēhea ata Pae tūnga hei whakaatu. Whakamātauria mā te haere ki: Ngā Tautuhinga > Ngā whakamōhiotanga &amp; pae tūnga > Pae tūnga</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pūmatua Tūmatarau">
             <feature>• Kua whakaurua te Āhukahuka Kanohi ki roto i te Pūmatua Tūmatarau. Whakamātauria mā te haere ki: Ngā Tautuhinga > Ngā whakamōhiotanga &amp; pae tūnga > Pūmatua Tūmatarau > Āhukahuka Kanohi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tūhono Honor">
             <feature>• Ka whakahohe a OneTap ki te whakawhiti kōnae tere, ngāwari, me te ngahau i waenga i ngā pūrere Honor. Whakamātauria mā te haere ki: Ngā Tautuhinga > Ētahi tūhononga atu anō > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tutukinga">
             <feature>• Ka whakatika i ngā raruraru tōaitia o te tūpuhi kia pai ake te maeneene o te pūrere</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pūmautanga">
             <feature>• Ka whakapai ake i te pūmautanga o te pūnaha</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Āpure haumarutanga">
             <feature>• Kua whakaurua te pūrei haumarutanga Android (Noema 2025) mō te haumarutanga pūnaha. Mō ētahi anō mōhiohio mō ngā whakahōutanga Haumarutanga Honor, haere koa ki tā mātou paetukutuku https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Ngā Tuhipoka" type="end">
             <feature>1. Mā te tāuta i tēnei whakahōutanga e kore tō raraunga whaiaro e pāngia, engari e taunaki ana kia tāruatia ō raraunga i mua i te whakahōutanga
2. Tūhura mōhiohio ētahi anō mō ngā āhuahira o te hua i Ngā Aki
3. Mēnā ka pāngia koe e ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōutanga, ka taea e koe te tiki āwhina mā te waea atu ki te waeawera ratonga Honor, mā te toro atu rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki a Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1071" name="mk-mk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Почитуван кориснику, ова ажурирање главно ги подобрува перформансите на системот. Ажурирајте за да уживате во подобрувањата</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Камера">
             <feature>• Исклучување на екранот при снимање е сега достапно. Пробајте го така што ќе одите во: Камера > Нагодување > Исклучување на екранот при снимање</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Почетен екран">
             <feature>• Режимот на проѕирност ги оптимизира ефектите на проѕирност на елементи како картички и папки, овозможувајќи исклучително визуелно искуство. Пробајте го така што ќе одите во: Нагодување > Почетен екран и стил > Поставки за почетниот екран > Режим на проѕирност</feature>
             <feature>• Долго притиснете на празното место на почетниот екран за да започнете со уредување</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Екран на заклучен уред">
             <feature>• Екранот на заклучен уред нуди повеќе стилови на часовник. Штипнете со два прста на екранот на заклучениот уред, допрете Приспособено, а потоа допрете го часовникот за да уредите</feature>
             <feature>• Тактилен ефект на осветлување реагира на вашиот допир на екранот за отклучување со лозинка и во Контролниот центар</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Статусна лента">
             <feature>• Статусната лента овозможува прилагодување на иконите, дозволувајќи ви да изберете кои икони на статусната лента да се прикажат. Пробајте го така што ќе одите во: Нагодување > Известувања и статусна лента > Статусна лента</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Магична капсула">
             <feature>• „Препознавање лице“ е интегрирано во „Магична капсула“. Пробајте го така што ќе одите во: Нагодување > Известувања и статусна лента > Магична капсула > Препознавање лице</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Поврзување од Honor">
             <feature>• OneTap овозможува непречен пренос на датотеки помеѓу Honor уредите, комбинирајќи брзина со леснотија и забава. Пробајте го така што ќе одите во: Нагодување > Повеќе поврзувања > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Изведба">
             <feature>• Ги решава повремените проблеми со заматување за да се подобри целокупната глаткост на уредот</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Стабилност">
             <feature>• Ја подобрува стабилноста на системот</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Безбедносна крпеница">
             <feature>• Вградена е безбедносна крпеница за Android (ноември 2025) за безбедност на системот. За повеќе информации за ажурирања на безбедноста од Honor, посетете ја нашата веб-локација https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Белешки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да влијае врз вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува да направите резервна копија од податоците пред да ажурирате
2. Откријте повеќе информации за карактеристиките на производот во Совети
3. Ако наидете на какви било проблеми при ажурирањето, може да ја добиете нашата помош со повикување на телефонскиот број на службата на Honor или посета на сервисниот центар за корисници на Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1100" name="ml-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് പ്രധാനമായും സിസ്റ്റം പ്രകടനം മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു. മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തലുകൾ ആസ്വദിക്കാൻ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുക</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ക്യാമറ">
             <feature>• സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഓഫ് ചെയ്‌ത് കൊണ്ടുള്ള റെക്കോർഡിംഗ് ഇപ്പോൾ ലഭ്യമാണ്. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്യാമറ > സെറ്റിങ്‌സ് > സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഓഫ് ചെയ്‌ത് കൊണ്ടുള്ള റെക്കോർഡിംഗ്</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ">
             <feature>• ഒരു സവിശേഷമായ ദൃശ്യാനുഭവം നൽകുന്നതിനായി, സുതാര്യതാ മോഡ് കാർഡുകളും ഫോൾഡറുകളും പോലുള്ള ഘടകങ്ങളുടെ സുതാര്യതാ ഇഫക്റ്റുകൾ ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുന്നു. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്രമീകരണം > ഹോം സ്ക്രീനും ശൈലിയും > ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ക്രമീകരണം > സുതാര്യതാ മോഡ്</feature>
             <feature>• എഡിറ്റ് ചെയ്യൽ ആരംഭിക്കാൻ ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീനിലെ ശൂന്യമായ ഭാഗത്ത് ദീർഘനേരം അമർത്തിപ്പിടിക്കുക</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ലോക്ക് സ്‌ക്രീൻ">
             <feature>• ലോക്ക് സ്‌ക്രീൻ കൂടുതൽ ക്ലോക്ക് ശൈലികൾ നൽകുന്നു. ലോക്ക് സ്‌ക്രീനിൽ രണ്ട് വിരലുകൾ ഉപയോഗിച്ച് പിഞ്ച് ചെയ്‌ത് 'ഇഷ്‌ടാനുസൃതം' എന്നതിൽ ടാപ്പ് ചെയ്‌ത ശേഷം, എഡിറ്റ് ചെയ്യേണ്ട ക്ലോക്കിൽ ടാപ്പ് ചെയ്യുക</feature>
             <feature>• നിങ്ങൾ പാസ്‌വേഡ് അൺലോക്ക് സ്‌ക്രീനിലും നിയന്ത്രണ കേന്ദ്രത്തിലും ടാപ്പ് ചെയ്യുമ്പോൾ ഒരു സ്‌പർശ പ്രകാശ ഇഫക്റ്റ് പ്രതികരിക്കുന്നു</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="സ്റ്റാറ്റസ് ബാർ">
             <feature>• ഐക്കൺ ഇഷ്‌ടാനുസൃതമാക്കുന്നതിനെ സ്റ്റാറ്റസ് ബാർ പ്രവർത്തനസജ്ജമാക്കുന്നു, പ്രദർശിപ്പിക്കേണ്ട സ്റ്റാറ്റസ് ബാർ ഐക്കണുകൾ തിരഞ്ഞെടുക്കാൻ ഇത് നിങ്ങളെ അനുവദിക്കുന്നു. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്രമീകരണം > നോട്ടിഫിക്കേഷനുകളും സ്റ്റാറ്റസ് ബാറും > സ്റ്റാറ്റസ് ബാർ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="മാജിക്ക് ക്യാപ്‌സൂൾ">
             <feature>• മുഖം തിരിച്ചറിയൽ എന്നത് മാജിക്ക് ക്യാപ്‌സൂളുമായി സംയോജിപ്പിച്ചിരിക്കുന്നു. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്രമീകരണം > നോട്ടിഫിക്കേഷനുകളും സ്റ്റാറ്റസ് ബാറും > മാജിക്ക് ക്യാപ്‌സൂൾ > മുഖം തിരിച്ചറിയൽ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• വേഗതയും ലാളിത്യവും ആസ്വാദ്യതയും സംയോജിപ്പിച്ചുകൊണ്ട്, Honor ഉപകരണങ്ങൾ തമ്മിലുള്ള സുഗമമായ ഫയൽ കൈമാറ്റം OneTap സാധ്യമാക്കുന്നു. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്രമീകരണം > കൂടുതൽ കണക്ഷനുകൾ > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="പ്രകടനം">
             <feature>• ഉപകരണത്തിന്റെ മൊത്തത്തിലുള്ള സ്‌മൂത്ത്‌നസ്സ് മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്താൻ വല്ലപ്പോഴുമുള്ള ഇടവിട്ട് പ്രവർത്തിക്കൽ പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ പരിഹരിക്കുന്നു</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="സ്ഥിരത">
             <feature>• സിസ്റ്റം സ്ഥിരത മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച്">
             <feature>• സിസ്റ്റം സുരക്ഷയ്‌ക്കായി Android സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് (നവംബർ 2025) ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. Honor സുരക്ഷാ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾക്ക്, ഞങ്ങളുടെ വെബ്‌സൈറ്റ് സന്ദർശിക്കുക: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ ബാധിക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിന് മുമ്പായി നിങ്ങളുടെ ഡാറ്റ ബാക്കപ്പ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു
2. 'നുറുങ്ങുകൾ' എന്നതിൽ ഉൽപ്പന്ന സവിശേഷതകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾ കണ്ടെത്തുക
3. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ നിങ്ങൾക്ക് എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, Honor സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ Honor ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്‌ത് ഞങ്ങളുടെ സഹായം കരസ്ഥമാക്കാവുന്നതാണ്</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1104" name="mn-MN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэ шинэчлэлтээр голчлон системийн гүйцэтгэлийг сайжрууллаа. Шинэчлээд, сайжруулсан хэрэглээг мэдрээрэй</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Камер">
             <feature>• Дэлгэц унтраалттай бичлэг хийх боломжтой боллоо. Камер > Тохиргоо > Дэлгэц унтраалттай бичих руу очиж туршиж үзнэ үү</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Үндсэн дэлгэц">
             <feature>• Тунгалаг горим карт, хавтас гэх мэт элементийн тунгалагших эффектийг оновчилж, онцгой үзэмжтэй болгоно. Тохиргоо > Үндсэн дэлгэц, хэв маяг > Үндсэн дэлгэцийн тохиргоо > Тунгалаг горим руу очиж туршиж үзнэ үү</feature>
             <feature>• Засаж эхлэхийн тулд үндсэн дэлгэцийн хоосон талбар дээр удаан дарна уу</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Түгжээ дэлгэц">
             <feature>• Түгжээ дэлгэцийн цаг илүү олон хэв маягтай боллоо. Түгжээ дэлгэцийг хоёр хуруугаар чимхээд, Тусгай дээр товшиж, дараа цаг дээр товшиж засна уу</feature>
             <feature>• Нууц үгээр түгжээ тайлах дэлгэц ба Удирдлагын төвд товшиход хариу үйлдэл үзүүлэх мэдрэгддэг гэрлийн эффект</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Төлөвийн мөр">
             <feature>• Төлөвийн мөрд шигтгээ зургийг тусгайлан тохируулах боломжтой болсон тул төлөвийн мөрийн аль шигтгээ зургийг харуулахаа сонгож болно гэсэн үг. Тохиргоо > Мэдэгдэл ба төлөвийн мөр > Төлөвийн мөр хэсгээс туршиж үзнэ үү</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Шидэт капсул">
             <feature>• Шидэт капсулд Царай таниулагчийг нэгтгэлээ. Тохиргоо > Мэдэгдэл ба төлөвийн мөр > Шидэт капсул > Царай таниулагч хэсгээс туршиж үзнэ үү</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap-г ашиглан Honor төхөөрөмжүүд хооронд файл саадгүй дамжуулж, хурд, хялбар байдал, хөгжилтэй байдлаар хослуулна. Тохиргоо > Нэмэлт холболтууд > OneTap руу очиж туршиж үзнэ үү</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Гүйцэтгэл">
             <feature>• Төхөөрөмжийн ерөнхий жигд байдлыг сайжруулж, заримдаа гацдаг асуудлыг шийдвэрлэсэн</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Тогтвортой байдал">
             <feature>• Системийн тогтвортой байдлыг сайжруулсан</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Хамгаалалтын нөхөөс">
             <feature>• Системийн хамгаалалтад зориулж Андройд хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг (2025 оны арван нэгдүгээр сар) багтаав. Honor-н хамгаалалтын шинэчлэлтийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэл авах бол манай дараах вебсайтад зочилно уу: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Тэмдэглэл" type="end">
             <feature>1. Энэхүү шинэчлэлтийг суулгахад таны хувийн мэдээлэлд нөлөөлөхгүй ч шинэчлэхээс өмнө өгөгдлөө нөөцлөхийг зөвлөж байна
2. Зөвлөгөө дотроос бүтээгдэхүүний онцлогийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэлтэй танилцана уу
3. Шинэчлэх үед асуудал гарвал Honor-н үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгах буюу Honor-н хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төвд зочилж болно</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1102" name="mr-in">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, हे अद्यतन प्रामुख्याने सिस्टम कार्यप्रदर्शन वाढवते. सुधारणांचा आनंद घेण्यासाठी अद्यतनित करा</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="कॅमेरा">
             <feature>• स्क्रीन-ऑफ रेकॉर्डिंग आता उपलब्ध आहे. वापरून पाहण्यासाठी येथे जा: कॅमेरा > सेटिंग्ज > स्क्रीन-ऑफ रेकॉर्डिंग</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="मुख्य स्क्रीन">
             <feature>• पारदर्शकता मोड कार्ड आणि फोल्डर्स सारख्या घटकांच्या पारदर्शकता प्रभावांना ऑप्टिमाइझ करतो, एक अपवादात्मक दृश्य अनुभव देतो. येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पहा: सेटिंग्ज > मुख्य स्क्रीन आणि शैली > मुख्य स्क्रीन सेटिंग्ज > पारदर्शकता मोड</feature>
             <feature>• संपादन सुरू करण्यासाठी मुख्य स्क्रीनवरील रिकाम्या जागेवर जास्त वेळ दाबा</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="लॉक स्क्रीन">
             <feature>• लॉक स्क्रीन अधिक घड्याळ शैली प्रदान करते. लॉक स्क्रीनवर दोन बोटांनी पिंच करा, सानुकूल वर टॅप करा, नंतर संपादित करण्यासाठी घड्याळावर टॅप करा</feature>
             <feature>• संकेतशब्द अनलॉक स्क्रीन आणि नियंत्रण केंद्रामध्ये आपल्या स्पर्शाला प्रतिसाद देणारा स्पर्शसंवेदक प्रकाश परिणाम दिसतो</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्टेटस बार">
             <feature>• स्टेटस बार आयकॉन कस्टमायझेशन सक्षम करतो, ज्यामुळे आपल्याला कोणते स्टेटस बार आयकॉन प्रदर्शित करायचे ते निवडता येते. येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पहा: सेटिंग्ज > सूचना आणि स्टेटस बार > स्टेटस बार</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="जादूई कॅप्सूल">
             <feature>• चेहरा ओळख पडताळणी जादूई कॅप्सूलमध्ये एकत्रित केली आहे. येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पहा: सेटिंग्ज > सूचना आणि स्टेटस बार > जादूई कॅप्सूल > चेहरा ओळख पडताळणी</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor कनेक्ट">
             <feature>• OneTap Honor उपकरणांमध्ये अखंडपणे फाइल स्थानांतरण सक्षम करते, गतीसह सहजता आणि मजेची सांगड घालते. वापरून पाहण्यासाठी येथे जा: सेटिंग्ज > अधिक कनेक्शन्स > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="कार्यप्रदर्शन">
             <feature>• उपकरणाची कार्यक्षमता सुधारण्यासाठी अधूनमधून होणाऱ्या अडखळण्याच्या समस्या सोडवते</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्थिरता">
             <feature>• सिस्टम स्थिरता सुधारते</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षितता पॅच">
             <feature>• सिस्टम सुरक्षिततेसाठी Android सुरक्षितता पॅच (नोव्हें 2025) समाविष्ट करण्यात आला आहे. Honor सुरक्षितता अद्यतनांबद्दल अधिक माहितीसाठी, कृपया आमच्या वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11 वर जा</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोट्स" type="end">
             <feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्‍थापित केल्याने आपल्या वैयक्तिक डेटावर परिणाम होणार नाही, परंतु तरीही अद्यतनित करण्यापूर्वी आपल्या डेटाचा बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते
2. उत्पादन वैशिष्ट्यांबद्दल अधिक माहिती Tips मध्ये शोधा
3. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, आपण Honor सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करून किंवा Honor ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जाऊन आमची मदत घेऊ शकता</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1086" name="ms-my">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini ini meningkatkan prestasi sistem terutamanya. Kemas kini untuk menikmati penambahbaikan tersebut</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Rakaman skrin dimatikan kini tersedia. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Kamera > Tetapan > Rakaman skrin dimatikan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Skrin utama">
             <feature>• Mod lut sinar mengoptimumkan kesan lut sinar elemen seperti kad dan folder, memberikan pengalaman visual yang luar biasa. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Skrin utama &amp; gaya > Tetapan skrin utama > Mod lut sinar</feature>
             <feature>• Tekan lama pada kawasan kosong skrin utama untuk mula mengedit</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Skrin kunci">
             <feature>• Skrin kunci menawarkan lebih banyak gaya jam. Picit dengan dua jari pada skrin kunci, ketik Tersuai, kemudian ketik jam untuk mengedit</feature>
             <feature>• Kesan cahaya sentuhan bertindak balas kepada ketikan anda pada skrin buka kunci kata laluan dan dalam Pusat Kawalan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bar status">
             <feature>• Bar status membolehkan penyesuaian ikon, membolehkan anda memilih ikon bar status yang ingin dipaparkan. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Pemberitahuan &amp; bar status > Bar status</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kapsul Magic">
             <feature>• Pengecaman wajah disepadukan ke dalam Kapsul Magic. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Pemberitahuan &amp; bar status > Kapsul Magic > Pengecaman wajah</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap membolehkan pemindahan fail yang lancar antara peranti Honor, menggabungkan kelajuan dengan mudah dan menyeronokkan. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Lebih banyak sambungan > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Prestasi">
             <feature>• Menyelesaikan isu tersentak-sentak sekali-sekala untuk meningkatkan kelancaran keseluruhan peranti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kestabilan">
             <feature>• Meningkatkan kestabilan sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tampalan keselamatan">
             <feature>• Tampalan keselamatan Android (Nov 2025) telah dimasukkan untuk tujuan keselamatan sistem. Untuk mendapatkan maklumat lanjut tentang kemas kini Keselamatan Honor, sila lawati laman web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Nota" type="end">
             <feature>1. Memasang kemas kini ini tidak akan menjejaskan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda masih disyorkan agar menyandarkan data sebelum melakukan kemas kini
2. Temui maklumat lanjut tentang ciri produk dalam Tip
3. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, anda boleh mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi talian penting perkhidmatan Honor atau melawati pusat khidmat pelanggan Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1109" name="my-mm">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် စနစ် စွမ်းဆောင်ရည်ကို အဓိက မြှင့်တင်ပေးသည်။ တိုးတက်ကောင်းမွန်အောင်လုပ်ထားသည်များကို သုံးစွဲခံစားရန် အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ကင်မရာ">
             <feature>• မျက်နှာပြင်ပိတ်၍ မှတ်တမ်းတင်ခြင်းကို ယခုရနိုင်ပါပြီ။ ဖော်ပြပါအတိုင်းသွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ကင်မရာ > ဆက်တင် > မျက်နှာပြင်ပိတ်၍ မှတ်တမ်းတင်ခြင်း</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်">
             <feature>• ကြည်လင်ပြတ်သားမှု မုဒ်သည် ကတ်များနှင့် ဖိုင်တွဲများကဲ့သို့ ပစ္စည်းများ၏ ကြည်လင်ပြတ်သားမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်များကို အကောင်းဆုံး မြှင့်တင်ပေးပြီး ထူးခြားသော ကြည့်ရှုမှုအတွေ့အကြုံကို ပေးအပ်သည်။ ဖော်ပြပါအတိုင်းသွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ဆက်တင် > ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်နှင့် ပုံစံ > ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင် ဆက်တင် > ကြည်လင်ပြတ်သားမှု မုဒ်</feature>
             <feature>• ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်ရှိ နေရာလွတ်ကို ကြာကြာနှိပ်ပြီး စတင်တည်းဖြတ်ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="လော့ခ်မျက်နှာပြင်">
             <feature>• လော့ခ်မျက်နှာပြင်တွင် နောက်ထပ်နာရီပုံစံများ ထည့်ပေးထားသည်။ လော့ခ်မျက်နှာပြင်ပေါ်တွင် လက်နှစ်ချောင်းဖြင့် ချုံ့ချဲ့လုပ်ပြီး စိတ်ကြိုက် ကို နှိပ်ပါ၊ ထို့နောက် တည်းဖြတ်ရန် နာရီကို နှိပ်ပါ</feature>
             <feature>• စကားဝှက် လော့ခ်ဖြေ မျက်နှာပြင်နှင့် ထိန်းချုပ်ရေး စင်တာတွင် သင်၏ထိနှိပ်မှုကို အလင်း ထိတွေ့မှုအာရုံခံ အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်က တုံ့ပြန်သည်</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="အခြေအနေပြဘား">
             <feature>• အခြေအနေပြဘားတွင် အိုင်ကွန်ကို စိတ်ကြိုက်ပြုလုပ်နိုင်သဖြင့် မည်သည့် အခြေအနေပြဘားအိုင်ကွန်များ ပြသမည်ကို ရွေးချယ်နိုင်သည်။ ဖော်ပြပါအတိုင်းသွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ဆက်တင် > အသိပေး အချက်ပြမှုများနှင့် အခြေအနေပြဘား > အခြေအနေပြဘား</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic ဆေးတောင့်ရှည်">
             <feature>• မျက်နှာသွင်ပြင် အသိအမှတ်ပြုမှုကို Magic ဆေးတောင့်ရှည်တွင် ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းထားသည်။ ဖော်ပြပါအတိုင်းသွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ဆက်တင် > အသိပေး အချက်ပြမှုများနှင့် အခြေအနေပြဘား > Magic ဆေးတောင့်ရှည် > မျက်နှာသွင်ပြင် အသိအမှတ်ပြုမှု</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ချိတ်ဆက်မှု">
             <feature>• တစ်ချက်နှိပ်ကို သုံး၍ Honor စက်များအကြား ဖိုင်များကို အလွယ်တကူ ချောမွေ့လျင်မြန်စွာ လွှဲပြောင်းနိုင်သဖြင့် ပျော်စရာကောင်းသည်။ ဖော်ပြပါအတိုင်းသွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ဆက်တင် > နောက်ထပ် ချိတ်ဆက်မှုများ > တစ်ချက်နှိပ်</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="စွမ်းဆောင်မှု">
             <feature>• စက်ကို ဘက်စုံထောင့်စုံမှ ချောမွေ့စေရန် မကြာခဏ ထစ်သွားသည့် ပြဿနာများကို ဖြေရှင်းပေးသည်</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="တည်ငြိမ်မှု">
             <feature>• စနစ် ပိုမိုတည်ငြိမ်စေရန် မြှင့်တင်ပေးသည်</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ">
             <feature>• စနစ်လုံခြုံရေးအတွက် Android လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့် ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ (နိုဝင်ဘာ 2025) ကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ Honor လုံခြုံရေး အပ်ဒိတ်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို သိရှိရန် ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ ဖော်ပြပါဝက်ဘ်ဆိုဒ်သို့ သွားရောက်ကြည့်ရှုပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="မှတ်ချက်" type="end">
             <feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းက သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာကို ထိခိုက်စေမည်မဟုတ်သော်လည်း အပ်ဒိတ်မလုပ်မီ သင့်ဒေတာကို ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ထားရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်
2. Tips တွင် ကုန်ပစ္စည်း လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို လေ့လာပါ
3. အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်နေစဉ် ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခုနှင့် ကြုံရပါက Honor ဝန်ဆောင်မှု ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ဖုန်းခေါ်၍ သို့မဟုတ် Honor ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားရောက်၍ အကူအညီရယူနိုင်သည်</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1109" name="my-zg">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ စနစ္ စြမ္းေဆာင္ရည္ကို အဓိက ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးသည္။ တိုးတက္ေကာင္းမြန္ေအာင္လုပ္ထားသည္မ်ားကို သုံးစြဲခံစားရန္ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ကင္မရာ">
             <feature>• မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ပိတ္၍ မွတ္တမ္းတင္ျခင္းကို ယခုရႏိုင္ပါၿပီ။ ေဖာ္ျပပါအတိုင္းသြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ကင္မရာ > ဆက္တင္ > မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ပိတ္၍ မွတ္တမ္းတင္ျခင္း</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္">
             <feature>• ၾကည္လင္ျပတ္သားမႈ မုဒ္သည္ ကတ္မ်ားႏွင့္ ဖိုင္တြဲမ်ားကဲ့သို႔ ပစၥည္းမ်ား၏ ၾကည္လင္ျပတ္သားမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္မ်ားကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးၿပီး ထူးျခားေသာ ၾကည့္ရႈမႈအေတြ႕အႀကဳံကို ေပးအပ္သည္။ ေဖာ္ျပပါအတိုင္းသြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ဆက္တင္ > ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ႏွင့္ ပုံစံ > ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ ဆက္တင္ > ၾကည္လင္ျပတ္သားမႈ မုဒ္</feature>
             <feature>• ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ရွိ ေနရာလြတ္ကို ၾကာၾကာႏွိပ္ၿပီး စတင္တည္းျဖတ္ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ေလာ့ခ္မ်က္ႏွာျပင္">
             <feature>• ေလာ့ခ္မ်က္ႏွာျပင္တြင္ ေနာက္ထပ္နာရီပုံစံမ်ား ထည့္ေပးထားသည္။ ေလာ့ခ္မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ေပၚတြင္ လက္ႏွစ္ေခ်ာင္းျဖင့္ ခ်ဳံ႕ခ်ဲ႕လုပ္ၿပီး စိတ္ၾကိဳက္ ကို ႏွိပ္ပါ၊ ထို႔ေနာက္ တည္းျဖတ္ရန္ နာရီကို ႏွိပ္ပါ</feature>
             <feature>• စကားဝွက္ ေလာ့ခ္ေျဖ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ႏွင့္ ထိန္းခ်ဳပ္ေရး စင္တာတြင္ သင္၏ထိႏွိပ္မႈကို အလင္း ထိေတြ႕မႈအာ႐ုံခံ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္က တုံ႔ျပန္သည္</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="အေျခအေနျပဘား">
             <feature>• အေျခအေနျပဘားတြင္ အိုင္ကြန္ကို စိတ္ႀကိဳက္ျပဳလုပ္ႏိုင္သျဖင့္ မည္သည့္ အေျခအေနျပဘားအိုင္ကြန္မ်ား ျပသမည္ကို ေ႐ြးခ်ယ္ႏိုင္သည္။ ေဖာ္ျပပါအတိုင္းသြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ဆက္တင္ > အသိေပး အခ်က္ျပမႈမ်ားႏွင့္ အေျခအေနျပဘား > အေျခအေနျပဘား</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic ေဆးေတာင့္ရွည္">
             <feature>• မ်က္ႏွာသြင္ျပင္ အသိအမွတ္ျပဳမႈကို Magic ေဆးေတာင့္ရွည္တြင္ ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းထားသည္။ ေဖာ္ျပပါအတိုင္းသြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ဆက္တင္ > အသိေပး အခ်က္ျပမႈမ်ားႏွင့္ အေျခအေနျပဘား > Magic ေဆးေတာင့္ရွည္ > မ်က္ႏွာသြင္ျပင္ အသိအမွတ္ျပဳမႈ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ခ်ိတ္ဆက္မႈ">
             <feature>• တစ္ခ်က္ႏွိပ္ကို သုံး၍ Honor စက္မ်ားအၾကား ဖိုင္မ်ားကို အလြယ္တကူ ေခ်ာေမြ႕လ်င္ျမန္စြာ လႊဲေျပာင္းႏိုင္သျဖင့္ ေပ်ာ္စရာေကာင္းသည္။ ေဖာ္ျပပါအတိုင္းသြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ဆက္တင္ > ေနာက္ထပ္ ခ်ိတ္ဆက္မႈမ်ား > တစ္ခ်က္ႏွိပ္</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="စြမ္းေဆာင္မႈ">
             <feature>• စက္ကို ဘက္စုံေထာင့္စုံမွ ေခ်ာေမြ႕ေစရန္ မၾကာခဏ ထစ္သြားသည့္ ျပႆနာမ်ားကို ေျဖရွင္းေပးသည္</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="တည္ၿငိမ္မႈ">
             <feature>• စနစ္ ပိုမိုတည္ၿငိမ္ေစရန္ ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးသည္</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="လုံျခံဳေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ">
             <feature>• စနစ္လုံၿခဳံေရးအတြက္ Android လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ (ႏိုဝင္ဘာ 2025) ကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ Honor လုံၿခဳံေရး အပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို သိရွိရန္ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ ေဖာ္ျပပါဝက္ဘ္ဆိုဒ္သို႔ သြားေရာက္ၾကည့္ရႈပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="မွတ္ခ်က္" type="end">
             <feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းက သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာကို ထိခိုက္ေစမည္မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း အပ္ဒိတ္မလုပ္မီ သင့္ေဒတာကို ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ထားရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္
2. Tips တြင္ ကုန္ပစၥည္း လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို ေလ့လာပါ
3. အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ေနစဥ္ ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခုႏွင့္ ႀကဳံရပါက Honor ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈ ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ဖုန္းေခၚ၍ သို႔မဟုတ္ Honor ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားေရာက္၍ အကူအညီရယူႏိုင္သည္</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1044" name="nb-no">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Kjære bruker. Denne oppdateringen forbedrer hovedsakelig systemytelsen. Oppdater for å få forbedringene</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Skjerm av-innspilling er nå tilgjengelig. Prøv funksjonen ved å gå til Kamera > Innstillinger > Skjerm av-innspilling</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Startskjerm">
             <feature>• Gjennomsiktighetsmodus optimaliserer gjennomsiktighetseffektene til elementer som kort og mapper, og gir en eksepsjonell visuell opplevelse. Prøv funksjonen ved å gå til Innstillinger > Startskjerm og stil > Innstillinger for startskjerm > Gjennomsiktighetsmodus</feature>
             <feature>• Trykk lenge på det tomme området på startskjermen for å begynne å redigere</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Låseskjerm">
             <feature>• Låseskjermen har flere klokkestiler. Press sammen to fingre på låseskjermen, trykk på Egendefinert og trykk deretter på klokken for å redigere den</feature>
             <feature>• En taktil lyseffekt reagerer på trykk på skjermen for passordopplåsing og i Kontrollsenteret</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Statuslinje">
             <feature>• Det er mulig å tilpasse ikonene på statuslinjen, slik at du kan velge hvilke statuslinjeikoner som skal vises. Prøv funksjonen ved å gå til Innstillinger > Varsler og statuslinje > Statuslinje</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magisk kapsel">
             <feature>• Ansiktsgjenkjenning er integrert i Magisk kapsel. Prøv funksjonen ved å gå til Innstillinger > Varsler og statuslinje > Magisk kapsel > Ansiktsgjenkjenning</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Tilkobling">
             <feature>• OneTap muliggjør sømløs filoverføring mellom Honor-enheter, og kombinerer hastighet med brukervennlighet og moro. Prøv funksjonen ved å gå til Innstillinger > Flere tilkoblinger > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ytelse">
             <feature>• Løser problemer med sporadisk hakking for å gjøre enhetsopplevelsen jevnere</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitet">
             <feature>• Gjør systemet mer stabilt</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sikkerhetsoppdatering">
             <feature>• Android-sikkerhetsoppdatering (nov 2025) er innlemmet for systemsikkerheten. For mer informasjon om sikkerhetsoppdateringer fra Honor, besøk nettstedet vårt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Merknader" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installeringen av denne oppdateringen påvirker ikke personopplysningene dine, men det anbefales likevel å sikkerhetskopiere dataene dine før du oppdaterer
2. Finn mer informasjon om produktfunksjoner i Tips
3. Hvis det oppstår problemer under oppdateringen, kan du få hjelp ved å ringe Honors kundeservice eller gå til Honors kundeservicesenter</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1121" name="ne-np">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, यो अपडेटले मुख्य गरी प्रणालीको कार्यसम्पादन परिष्कार गर्छ । सुधार गरिएका सुविधाहरूको आनन्द लिन अपडेट गर्नुहोस्</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="क्यामेरा">
             <feature>• स्क्रिन अफ गरेर रेकर्डिङ गर्ने सुविधा अब उपलब्ध भएको छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: क्यामेरा > सेटिङहरू > स्क्रिन अफ गरेर रेकर्डिङ गर्ने सुविधा</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="गृह स्क्रिन">
             <feature>• पारदर्शिता मोडले कार्ड र फोल्डरहरू जस्ता एलिमेन्टहरूको पारदर्शिता प्रभावहरू अप्टिमाइज गर्छ र अद्भुत भिजुअल अनुभव प्रदान गर्छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > गृह स्क्रिन र शैली > गृह स्क्रिन सेटिङहरू > पारदर्शिता मोड</feature>
             <feature>• सम्पादन गर्न थाल्न गृह स्क्रिनको खाली क्षेत्रमा लामो समयसम्म थिच्नुहोस्</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="लक स्क्रिन">
             <feature>• लक स्क्रिनमा घडीका थप शैलीहरू उपलब्ध गराइएका छन् । लक स्क्रिनमा दुई औँलाले पिन्च गर्नुहोस्, अनुकूलन मा ट्याप गर्नुहोस् अनि सम्पादन गर्न घडीमा ट्याप गर्नुहोस्</feature>
             <feature>• तपाईंले पासवर्ड अनलक स्क्रिन र नियन्त्रण केन्द्रमा ट्याप गर्दा छुन मिल्ने प्रकाशको प्रभाव देखिन्छ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्थिति पट्टी">
             <feature>• स्थिति पट्टीमा आइकन अनुकूलन गर्न सकिन्छ र तपाईं स्थिति पट्टीमा कुन कुन आइकनहरू देखाउने भन्ने कुरा छनौट गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > सूचना र स्थिति पट्टी > स्थिति पट्टी</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="म्याजिक क्याप्सुल">
             <feature>• अनुहार पहिचान गर्ने सुविधा म्याजिक क्याप्सुलमा इन्टिग्रेट गरिएको छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > सूचना र स्थिति पट्टी > म्याजिक क्याप्सुल > अनुहार पहिचान</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap का सहायताले Honor का यन्त्रहरूका बिचमा तीव्र गतिमा सजिलै र रमाइलोसँग निर्बाध रूपमा फाइल स्थानान्तरण गर्न सकिन्छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > थप जडानहरू > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="कार्यप्रदर्शन">
             <feature>• यन्त्रको समग्र सहजता परिष्कार गर्न कहिलेकाहीँ अड्किने समस्याहरू समाधान गर्छ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्थिरता">
             <feature>• प्रणालीको स्थिरता सुधार गर्छ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षा प्याच">
             <feature>• एन्ड्रोइड सुरक्षा प्याच (नोभेम्बर 2025) प्रणाली सुरक्षाका लागि समावेश गरिएको छ । Honor सुरक्षा अपडेटहरूबारे थप जानकारीका लागि कृपया हाम्रो वेबसाइटमा जानुहोस्: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोटहरू" type="end">
             <feature>1. तपाईंले यो एप स्थापना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटामा कुनै प्रभाव नपर्ने भए पनि तपाईंलाई अपडेट गर्नुअघि आफ्नो डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ
2. सुझावहरूमा गई उत्पादनका सुविधाहरूका बारेमा थप जानकारी हेर्नुहोस्
3. अपडेटको क्रममा तपाईंले कुनै समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईं Honor सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गरेर वा Honor ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा गएर हाम्रो मद्दत प्राप्त गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ ।</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1043" name="nl-nl">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Beste gebruiker, deze update verbetert vooral de systeemprestaties. Werk bij om van de verbeteringen te genieten</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Camera">
             <feature>• Opname met uitgeschakeld scherm is nu beschikbaar. Probeer het uit via: Camera > Instellingen > Opname met uitgeschakeld scherm</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Startscherm">
             <feature>• De Transparantiemodus optimaliseert de transparantie-effecten van elementen zoals kaarten en mappen en levert een uitzonderlijke visuele ervaring. Probeer het uit via: Instellingen > Startscherm en stijl > Startscherminstellingen > Transparantiemodus</feature>
             <feature>• Druk lang op het lege gedeelte van het startscherm om te beginnen met bewerken</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vergrendelscherm">
             <feature>• Het vergrendelscherm biedt meer klokstijlen. Knijp met twee vingers samen op het vergrendelscherm, tik op Aangepast en tik vervolgens op de klok om te bewerken</feature>
             <feature>• Een tactiel lichteffect reageert op uw tik op het wachtwoordontgrendelscherm en in het Controlecentrum</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Statusbalk">
             <feature>• Statusbalk maakt het aanpassen van pictogrammen mogelijk, zodat u kunt kiezen welke statusbalkpictogrammen er moeten worden weergegeven. Probeer het uit via: Instellingen > Meldingen &amp; statusbalk > Statusbalk</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magische capsule">
             <feature>• Gezichtsherkenning is geïntegreerd in Magische capsule. Probeer het uit via: Instellingen > Meldingen &amp; statusbalk > Magische capsule > Gezichtsherkenning</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap maakt naadloze bestandsoverdracht tussen Honor-apparaten mogelijk, waarbij snelheid wordt gecombineerd met gemak en plezier. Probeer het uit via: Instellingen > Meer verbindingen > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Prestaties">
             <feature>• Lost de schokproblemen op die af en toe optreden om de algehele soepelheid van het apparaat te verbeteren</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabiliteit">
             <feature>• Verbetert de systeemstabiliteit</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Beveiligingspatch">
             <feature>• Android-beveiligingspatch (november 2025) is opgenomen voor systeembeveiliging. Voor meer informatie over Honor-beveiligingsupdates kunt u terecht op onze website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notities" type="end">
             <feature>1. Het installeren van deze update heeft geen invloed op uw persoonlijke gegevens, maar het wordt nog steeds aanbevolen om een back-up van uw gegevens te maken voordat u deze update uitvoert
2. Ontdek meer informatie over productfuncties in Tips
3. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, kunt u onze hulp krijgen door de Honor-servicehotline te bellen of naar het Honor-klantenservicecentrum te gaan</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1096" name="or-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ମୁଖ୍ୟତଃ ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ର କାର୍ଯ୍ୟଦକ୍ଷତାକୁ ବଢାଏ। ଉନ୍ନତିଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଉପଭୋଗ କରିବାକୁ ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରନ୍ତୁ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="କ୍ୟାମେରା">
             <feature>• ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍-ଅଫ୍ ରେକର୍ଡିଂ ବର୍ତ୍ତମାନ ଉପଲବ୍ଧ। ଏଠାକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାକୁ ବ୍ୟବହାର କରି ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ: କ୍ୟାମେରା > ସେଟିଂସ୍‌ > ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍-ଅଫ୍ ରେକର୍ଡିଂ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌">
             <feature>• ପାରଦର୍ଶିତା ମୋଡ୍ କାର୍ଡ ଏବଂ ଫୋଲ୍ଡର ଭଳି ଉପାଦାନଗୁଡ଼ିକର ସ୍ୱଚ୍ଛତା ପ୍ରଭାବକୁ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍ କରେ, ଏକ ଅସାଧାରଣ ଦୃଶ୍ୟ ଅନୁଭୂତି ପ୍ରଦାନ କରେ। ଏଠାକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାକୁ ବ୍ୟବହାର କରି ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ଓ ଷ୍ଟାଇଲ୍ > ହୋମ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ପାରଦର୍ଶିତା ମୋଡ୍</feature>
             <feature>• ସମ୍ପାଦନ ଆରମ୍ଭ କରିବା ପାଇଁ ହୋମ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ର ଖାଲି ସ୍ଥାନକୁ ଦୀର୍ଘ ସମୟ ଦବାନ୍ତୁ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ଲକ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍">
             <feature>• ଲକ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ଅଧିକ ଘଣ୍ଟା ଷ୍ଟାଇଲ୍ ପ୍ରଦାନ କରେ। ଲକ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ଉପରେ ଦୁଇଟି ଆଙ୍ଗୁଠି ସାହାଯ୍ୟରେ ପିଞ୍ଚ କରନ୍ତୁ, କଷ୍ଟମ୍ ଟାପ୍ କରନ୍ତୁ, ତାପରେ ସମ୍ପାଦନ କରିବାକୁ ଘଣ୍ଟା ଉପରେ ଟାପ୍ କରନ୍ତୁ</feature>
             <feature>• ପାସୱାର୍ଡ ଅନଲକ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ଏବଂ ନିୟନ୍ତ୍ରଣ କେନ୍ଦ୍ରରେ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଟାପ୍‌କୁ ଏକ ସ୍ପର୍ଶକାତର ଆଲୋକ ପ୍ରଭାବ ପ୍ରତିକ୍ରିୟା କରେ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ସ୍ଥିତି ବାର୍‌">
             <feature>• ସ୍ଥିତି ବାର୍‌ ଆଇକନ୍ କଷ୍ଟୋମାଇଜେସନ୍ ସକ୍ଷମ କରେ, ଯାହା ଆପଣଙ୍କୁ କେଉଁ ସ୍ଥିତି ବାର୍‌ ଆଇକନ୍ ପ୍ରଦର୍ଶିତ କରିବେ ତାହା ବାଛିବାକୁ ଅନୁମତି ଦିଏ। ଏଠାକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାକୁ ବ୍ୟବହାର କରି ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ବିଜ୍ଞପ୍ତିଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଓ ସ୍ଥିତି ବାର୍ > ସ୍ଥିତି ବାର୍‌</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ମ୍ୟାଜିକ୍ କ୍ୟାପସୁଲ୍">
             <feature>• ମ୍ୟାଜିକ୍ କ୍ୟାପସୁଲ୍‌ରେ ମୁହଁ ଚିହ୍ନଟକରଣ ମିଶ୍ରିତ ହୋଇଛି। ଏଠାକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାକୁ ବ୍ୟବହାର କରି ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ବିଜ୍ଞପ୍ତିଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଓ ସ୍ଥିତି ବାର୍ > ମ୍ୟାଜିକ୍ କ୍ୟାପସୁଲ୍ > ମୁହଁ ଚିହ୍ନଟକରଣ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ସଂଯୋଗ">
             <feature>• OneTap Honor ଡିଭାଇସ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ମଧ୍ୟରେ ବାଧାହୀନ ଫାଇଲ୍ ଟ୍ରାନ୍ସଫରକୁ ସକ୍ଷମ କରିଥାଏ, ଯାହା ଗତି ସହିତ ସହଜ ଏବଂ ମଜାଦାର ମିଶ୍ରଣ କରିଥାଏ। ଏଠାକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାକୁ ବ୍ୟବହାର କରି ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ଅଧିକ ସଂଯୋଜନା > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ସଞ୍ଚାଳନ">
             <feature>• ଡିଭାଇସ୍‌ର ସାମଗ୍ରିକ ସ୍ମୁଥନେସକୁ ବୃଦ୍ଧି କରିବା ପାଇଁ ବେଳେବେଳେ ଘଟିବା ଶଟରିଂ ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମାଧାନ କରେ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ସ୍ଥିରତା">
             <feature>• ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ ସ୍ଥିରତା ଉନ୍ନତ କରେ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌">
             <feature>• Android ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ (ନଭେମ୍ବର 2025) ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପାଇଁ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି। Honor ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ବିଷୟରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି ଆମ ୱେବସାଇଟ୍‌ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11 ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ପ୍ରଭାବିତ ହେବ ନାହିଁ, ତଥାପି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରିବା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡାଟାର ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି
2. ଟିପ୍ସରେ ଉତ୍ପାଦ ବିଶେଷତାଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଉପରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ଆବିଷ୍କାର କରନ୍ତୁ
3. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରିବା ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଆପଣ Honor ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌କୁ କଲ୍‌ କରି କିମ୍ବା Honor ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଇ, ଆମ ସହାୟତା ପାଇପାରିବେ</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1094" name="pa-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਮੁੱਖ ਤੌਰ 'ਤੇ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੀ ਕਾਰਗੁਜ਼ਾਰੀ ਨੂੰ ਬਿਹਤਰ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਸੁਧਾਰਾਂ ਦਾ ਅਨੰਦ ਲੈਣ ਲਈ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰੋ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਕੈਮਰਾ">
             <feature>• ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ-ਬੰਦ ਰਿਕਾਰਡਿੰਗ ਹੁਣ ਉਪਲਬਧ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਕੈਮਰਾ > ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ-ਬੰਦ ਰਿਕਾਰਡਿੰਗ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ">
             <feature>• ਪਾਰਦਰਸ਼ਤਾ ਮੋਡ ਕਾਰਡਾਂ ਅਤੇ ਫੋਲਡਰਾਂ ਵਰਗੇ ਐਲੀਮੈਂਟਾਂ ਦੇ ਪਾਰਦਰਸ਼ਤਾ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਉਂਦਾ ਹੈ, ਇੱਕ ਸ਼ਾਨਦਾਰ ਵਿਜ਼ੂਅਲ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਪ੍ਰਦਾਨ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਅਤੇ ਸ਼ੈਲੀ > ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਪਾਰਦਰਸ਼ਤਾ ਮੋਡ</feature>
             <feature>• ਸੋਧ ਸ਼ੁਰੂ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਦੇ ਖਾਲੀ ਹਿੱਸੇ ਨੂੰ ਲੰਬਾ ਸਮਾਂ ਦਬਾਓ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਲੌਕ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ">
             <feature>• ਲੌਕ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਘੜੀ ਦੇ ਹੋਰ ਡਾਇਲ ਪੇਸ਼ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ। ਲੌਕ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ 'ਤੇ ਦੋ ਉਂਗਲਾਂ ਨਾਲ ਪਿੰਚ ਕਰੋ, ਕਸਟਮ 'ਤੇ ਟੈਪ ਕਰੋ, ਫਿਰ ਸੋਧ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਘੜੀ 'ਤੇ ਟੈਪ ਕਰੋ</feature>
             <feature>• ਪਾਸਵਰਡ ਅਨਲੌਕ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਅਤੇ ਕੰਟਰੋਲ ਸੈਂਟਰ ਵਿੱਚ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਟੈਪ ਦਾ ਜਵਾਬ ਦੇਣ ਲਈ ਇੱਕ ਸਪਰਸ਼ ਰੌਸ਼ਨੀ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਸਥਿਤੀ ਪੱਟੀ">
             <feature>• ਸਥਿਤੀ ਪੱਟੀ ਆਈਕੋਨ ਅਨੁਕੂਲਣ ਨੂੰ ਸਮਰੱਥ ਕਰਦੀ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਇਹ ਚੁਣਨ ਦੀ ਇਜਾਜ਼ਤ ਮਿਲਦੀ ਹੈ ਕਿ ਕਿਸ ਸਥਿਤੀ ਪੱਟੀ ਆਈਕੋਨ ਨੂੰ ਡਿਸਪਲੇ ਕਰਨਾ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਅਜਮਾਓ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਸੂਚਨਾਵਾਂ ਅਤੇ ਸਥਿਤੀ ਪੱਟੀ > ਸਥਿਤੀ ਪੱਟੀ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਮੈਜਿਕ ਕੈਪਸੂਲ">
             <feature>• ਚਿਹਰਾ ਪਛਾਣ ਮੈਜਿਕ ਕੈਪਸੂਲ ਵਿੱਚ ਏਕੀਕ੍ਰਿਤ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਸੂਚਨਾਵਾਂ ਅਤੇ ਸਥਿਤੀ ਪੱਟੀ > ਮੈਜਿਕ ਕੈਪਸੂਲ > ਚਿਹਰਾ ਪਛਾਣ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ਕਨੈਕਟ">
             <feature>• OneTap, Honor ਡਿਵਾਈਸਾਂ ਵਿਚਕਾਰ ਨਿਰਵਿਘਨਤਾ ਨਾਲ ਫ਼ਾਈਲ ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਨੂੰ ਸਮਰੱਥ ਬਣਾਉਂਦਾ ਹੈ, ਗਤੀ ਦਾ ਆਸਾਨ ਅਤੇ ਮਜ਼ੇਦਾਰ ਢੰਗ ਨਾਲ ਸੁਮੇਲ ਬਣਾਉਂਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਹੋਰ ਕਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਕਾਰਗੁਜ਼ਾਰੀ">
             <feature>• ਡਿਵਾਈਸ ਦੀ ਸਮੁੱਚੀ ਨਿਰਵਿਘਨਤਾ ਨੂੰ ਵਧਾਉਣ ਲਈ ਕਦੇ-ਕਦੇ ਆਉਣ ਵਾਲੀਆਂ ਅਟਕਣ ਦੀਆਂ ਸਮੱਸਿਆਵਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਹੱਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਸਥਿਰਤਾ">
             <feature>• ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੀ ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੁਧਾਰ ਕਰਦੀ ਹੈ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ">
             <feature>• ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਲਈ Android ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ (ਨਵੰ 2025) ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। Honor ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਲਈ, ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਵੈੱਬਸਾਈਟ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ਨੋਟਸ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ 'ਤੇ ਕੋਈ ਅਸਰ ਨਹੀਂ ਪਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਹਾਲੇ ਵੀ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਦਾ ਬੈਕ ਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ
2. ਸੁਝਾਅ ਐਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਉਤਪਾਦ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾਵਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਦੀ ਖੋਜ ਕਰੋ
3. ਜੇਕਰ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਤੁਸੀਂ Honor ਸੇਵਾ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰ ਕੇ ਜਾਂ Honor ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਮਦਦ ਲੈ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1045" name="pl-pl">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Szanowny użytkowniku, ta aktualizacja w głównej mierze podnosi wydajność systemu. Zainstaluj ją, aby korzystać z ulepszeń</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Aparat">
             <feature>• Dostępne jest już nagrywanie z wyłączonym ekranem. Aby wypróbować tę funkcję, wybierz „Aparat > Ustawienia > Nagrywanie z wyłączonym ekranem”</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ekran główny">
             <feature>• Tryb przezroczystości optymalizuje efekty przezroczystości elementów takich jak karty i foldery, zapewniając wyjątkowe wrażenia wizualne. Wypróbuj go, wybierając Ustawienia > Ekran główny i styl > Ustawienia ekranu głównego > Tryb przezroczystości</feature>
             <feature>• Naciśnij i przytrzymaj pusty obszar ekranu głównego, aby rozpocząć edycję</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ekran blokady">
             <feature>• Dostępna jest większa liczba stylów zegara na ekranie blokady. Aby edytować, zaciśnij dwa palce na ekranie blokady, dotknij pozycji Niestandardowy, a następnie dotknij zegara</feature>
             <feature>• Na ekranie odblokowania hasłem i w Centrum sterowania pojawia się efekt świetlny reagujący na dotyk</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pasek stanu">
             <feature>• Pasek stanu umożliwia personalizację ikon oraz wybór wyświetlanych ikon paska stanu. Wypróbuj tę funkcję, wybierając Ustawienia > Powiadomienia i pasek stanu > Pasek stanu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magiczna kapsuła">
             <feature>• Rozpoznawanie twarzy jest zintegrowane z Magiczną kapsułą. Wypróbuj tę funkcję, wybierając Ustawienia > Powiadomienia i pasek stanu > Magiczna kapsuła > Rozpoznawanie twarzy</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Połączenie Honor">
             <feature>• Korzystając z funkcji OneTap, można szybko, łatwo i wygodnie przesyłać pliki między urządzeniami Honor. Aby wypróbować tę funkcję, wybierz „Ustawienia > Więcej połączeń > OneTap”</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Wydajność">
             <feature>• Rozwiązano sporadyczne problemy z zacinaniem się, aby zapewnić lepszą ogólną płynność funkcjonowania urządzenia</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilność">
             <feature>• Poprawiono stabilność systemu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Poprawka zabezpieczeń">
             <feature>• Aktualizacja zawiera Poprawkę zabezpieczeń systemu Android (listopad 2025 r.). Więcej informacji o aktualizacjach zabezpieczeń urządzeń Honor można znaleźć w naszej witrynie internetowej: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notatki" type="end">
             <feature>1. Ta aktualizacja nie ma wpływu na Twoje dane osobowe, jednak przed jej zainstalowaniem zaleca się wykonanie kopii zapasowej danych
2. Więcej informacji o funkcjach produktu znajdziesz w Poradach
3. Jeśli podczas aktualizacji napotkasz jakiekolwiek problemy, możesz uzyskać pomoc, dzwoniąc na infolinię serwisu Honor lub odwiedzając punkt serwisowy Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1046" name="pt-br">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Prezado(a) usuário(a), essa atualização aprimora principalmente o desempenho do sistema. Atualize para aproveitar as melhorias</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Câmera">
             <feature>• A Gravação com tela desligada já está disponível. Experimente acessando: Câmera > Configurações > Gravação com tela desligada</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tela inicial">
             <feature>• O Modo Transparência otimiza os efeitos de transparência dos elementos como cartões e pastas, proporcionando uma experiência visual excepcional. Experimente acessando: Configurações > Tela inicial e estilo > Configurações da tela inicial > Modo Transparência</feature>
             <feature>• Pressione e segure a área em branco da tela inicial para começar a editar</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tela de bloqueio">
             <feature>• A tela de bloqueio oferece mais estilos de relógio. Pince com dois dedos na tela de bloqueio, toque em Personalizado e toque no relógio para editar</feature>
             <feature>• Um efeito de luz tátil responde a seu toque na tela de desbloqueio de senha e no Centro de controle</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Barra de status">
             <feature>• A barra de status permite a personalização dos ícones, permitindo que você escolha quais ícones de barra de status exibir. Experimente acessando: Configurações > Notificações e barra de status > Barra de status</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Cápsula mágica">
             <feature>• O Reconhecimento facial está integrado na Cápsula mágica. Experimente acessando: Configurações > Notificações e barra de status > Cápsula mágica > Reconhecimento facial</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• O OneTap permite a transferência perfeita de arquivos entre dispositivos Honor, combinando velocidade com facilidade e diversão. Experimente acessando: Configurações > Mais conexões > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Desempenho">
             <feature>• Resolve problemas ocasionais de travamento para melhorar a eficiência geral do dispositivo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilidade">
             <feature>• Melhora a estabilidade do sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch de segurança">
             <feature>• Patch de segurança do Android (novembro de 2025) incorporado para a segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da Honor, visite nosso site: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. A instalação desta atualização não afetará os dados pessoais, mas ainda é recomendável fazer backup dos dados antes de atualizar
2. Descubra mais informações sobre os recursos do produto em Dicas
3. Se você encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, poderá obter nossa ajuda ligando para a Linha de atendimento de serviço da Honor ou acessando a Central de serviços ao cliente da Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2070" name="pt-pt">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Caro utilizador, esta atualização melhora principalmente o desempenho do sistema. Atualize para aproveitar as melhorias</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Câmara">
             <feature>• A Gravação com ecrã desligado já está disponível. Experimente-a, acedendo a: Câmara > Definições > Gravação com ecrã desligado</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ecrã Inicial">
             <feature>• O Modo de transparência otimiza os efeitos de transparência de elementos como cartões e pastas, proporcionando uma experiência visual excecional. Experimente, acedendo a: Configurações > Ecrã inicial e estilo > Definições do ecrã inicial > Modo de transparência</feature>
             <feature>• Prima longamente a área em branco do ecrã inicial para iniciar a edição</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ecrã de bloqueio">
             <feature>• O ecrã de bloqueio oferece mais estilos de relógio. Aproxime/Afaste dois no ecrã de bloqueio e toque em Personalizar, de seguida toque no relógio para editar</feature>
             <feature>• Um efeito de luz tátil responde ao seu toque no ecrã que desbloqueia com palavra-passe e no Centro de controlo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Barra de estado">
             <feature>• A Barra de estado permite a personalização de ícones, permitindo que escolha quais ícones da Barra de estado serão exibidos. Experimente, acedendo a: Configurações > Notificações e barra de estado > Barra de estado</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Cápsula mágica">
             <feature>• O Reconhecimento facial está integrado na Cápsula mágica. Experimente, acedendo a: Configurações > Notificações e barra de estado > Cápsula mágica > Reconhecimento facial</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• O OneTap permite a transferência contínua de ficheiros entre dispositivos Honor, combinando velocidade com facilidade e diversão. Experimente-o, acedendo a: Configurações > Mais ligações > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Nível de utilização">
             <feature>• Resolve os problemas ocasionais de travamento para melhorar o desempenho geral do dispositivo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilidade">
             <feature>• Melhora a estabilidade do sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Correção de segurança">
             <feature>• Foi incorporada uma correção de segurança do Android (novembro de 2025) para segurança do sistema. Para mais informações sobre as atualizações de Segurança Honor, visite o nosso website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não afetará os seus dados pessoais, mas ainda assim é recomendável efetuar uma cópia de segurança dos seus dados antes de atualizar
2. Descobrir mais informações sobre as funcionalidades do produto em Sugestões
3. Se encontrar quaisquer problemas durante a atualização, pode obter ajuda ligando para a linha direta de assistência da Honor ou visitando o centro de apoio ao cliente da Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1048" name="ro-ro">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Stimate utilizator, această actualizare îmbunătățește în principal performanța sistemului. Actualizați pentru a beneficia de îmbunătățiri</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Cameră foto">
             <feature>• Înregistrare cu ecranul oprit este acum disponibilă. Încercați-o accesând: Cameră foto > Setări > Înregistrare cu ecranul oprit</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ecran de pornire">
             <feature>• Modul transparență optimizează efectele de transparență ale elementelor precum cardurile și folderele, oferind o experiență vizuală excepțională. Încercați-l accesând: Setări > Ecran de pornire și stil > Setări ecran de pornire > Mod transparență</feature>
             <feature>• Apăsați lung pe zona goală a ecranului de pornire pentru a începe editarea</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ecran de blocare">
             <feature>• Ecranul de blocare oferă mai multe stiluri de ceas. Apropiați două degete pe ecranul de blocare, atingeți Personalizare, apoi atingeți ceasul pentru a edita</feature>
             <feature>• Un efect luminos tactil răspunde la atingerea dvs. pe ecranul de deblocare a parolei și în Centru de control</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bară de stare">
             <feature>• Bara de stare permite personalizarea pictogramelor, permițându-vă să alegeți pictogramele barei de stare care să fie afișate. Încercați mergând la: Setări > Notificări și bară de stare > Bară de stare</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Capsulă magică">
             <feature>• Recunoașterea facială este integrată în Capsulă magică. Încercați mergând la: Setări > Notificări și bară de stare > Capsulă magică > Recunoaștere facială</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Conectare Honor">
             <feature>• OneTap permite transferul fără probleme al fișierelor între dispozitivele Honor, combinând viteza cu ușurința și distracția. Încercați-o accesând: Setări > Mai multe conexiuni > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Performanță">
             <feature>• Rezolvă problemele ocazionale de întrerupere a funcționării pentru a îmbunătăți fluiditatea generală a dispozitivului</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitate">
             <feature>• Îmbunătățește stabilitatea sistemului</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Corecție de securitate">
             <feature>• Pentru securitatea sistemului, a fost încorporată o corecție de securitate Android (noiembrie 2025). Pentru mai multe informații despre actualizările de securitate Honor, vă rugăm să vizitați site-ul nostru web: https://www.honor.com/ro/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notițe" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalarea acestei actualizări nu va afecta datele dvs. cu caracter personal, dar este totuși recomandat să faceți o copie de rezervă a datelor înainte de actualizare
2. Descoperiți mai multe informații despre caracteristicile produsului în Sugestii
3. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, puteți solicita ajutorul nostru apelând linia de asistență Honor sau vizitând Centrul de service pentru clienți Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1049" name="ru-ru">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Мы выпустили это обновление, чтобы улучшить производительность системы. Установите его, чтобы оценить изменения</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Камера">
             <feature>• Теперь доступна функция «Запись с выключенным экраном». Чтобы опробовать ее, перейдите в раздел Камера > Настройки > Запись с выключенным экраном</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Рабочий экран">
             <feature>• «Прозрачный режим» оптимизирует эффекты прозрачности таких элементов, как карты и папки, создавая профессиональное визуальное оформление. Чтобы опробовать эту функцию, выберите «Настройки > Рабочий экран и стиль > Настройки экрана > Прозрачный режим»</feature>
             <feature>• Чтобы начать редактирование, нажмите и удерживайте пустую область рабочего экрана</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Экран блокировки">
             <feature>• Экран блокировки предлагает больше стилей часов. Сведите два пальца на экране блокировки, нажмите Пользовательский, затем нажмите на часы, чтобы отредактировать</feature>
             <feature>• Тактильный эффект освещения реагирует на прикосновение на экране разблокировки паролем и в «Центре управления»</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Строка состояния">
             <feature>• Строка состояния поддерживает пользовательскую настройку значков, позволяя вам выбирать, какие значки отображать в строке. Чтобы опробовать эту функцию, выберите «Настройки > Уведомления и строка состояния > Строка состояния»</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic Capsule">
             <feature>• «Распознавание лица» встроено в Magic Capsule. Чтобы опробовать эту функцию, выберите «Настройки > Уведомления и строка состояния > Magic Capsule > Распознавание лица»</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Служба OneTap обеспечивает бесшовную передачу файлов между устройствами Honor, сочетая скорость с простотой и удовольствием. Чтобы опробовать эту функцию, перейдите в раздел Настройки > Другие соединения > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Уровень производительности">
             <feature>• Устраняет периодические проблемы с задержками и повышает общую плавность работы устройства</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Стабильность">
             <feature>• Повышает стабильность системы</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Исправление безопасности">
             <feature>• В обновление включено исправление безопасности для Android (ноябрь 2025 г.). Чтобы получить подробную информацию об обновлениях безопасности Honor, посетите наш сайт: https://www.honor.com/eurasia/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Заметки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Установка этого обновления не приведет к удалению ваших персональных данных, но мы все равно рекомендуем вам создать резервную копию своих данных перед обновлением
2. Изучите дополнительную информацию о функциях продукта в «Советах»
3. Если во время обновления у вас возникнут проблемы, обратитесь за помощью на горячую линию службы поддержки Honor или в сервисный центр для клиентов Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1115" name="si-lk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, මෙම යාවත්කාලීන කිරීම ප්‍රධාන වශයෙන් පද්ධතියේ කාර්යසාධනය උසස් කරයි. වැඩිදියුණු කිරීම් අත්විඳීමට යාවත්කාල කරන්න</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="කැමරාව">
             <feature>• තිරය අක්‍රියව පටිගත කිරීම දැන් ලබා ගත හැකිය. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: කැමරාව > සැකසුම් > තිරය අක්‍රියව පටිගත කිරීම</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="මුල් තිරය">
             <feature>• සුවිශේෂී දෘශ්‍ය අත්දැකීමක් ලබා දෙමින් විනිවිදභාවය ප්‍රකාරය කාඩ්පත් සහ ෆෝල්ඩර් වැනි සංරචකවල විනිවිදභාවය ප්‍රයෝග ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: සැකසුම් > මුල් තිරය සහ විලාසය > මුල් තිර සැකසුම් > විනිවිදභාවය ප්‍රකාරය</feature>
             <feature>• සංස්කරණය කිරීම ආරම්භ කිරීමට මුල් තිරයේ හිස් ප්‍රදේශය දීර්ඝව ඔබන්න</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="අගුළු තිරය">
             <feature>• අගුළු තිරය තවත් ඔරලෝසු විලාස පිරිනමයි. අගුළු තිරය මත ඇඟිලි දෙකකින් පින්ච් කරන්න, ගැළපුම් තට්ටු කරන්න, පසුව සංස්කරණය කිරීමට ඔරලෝසුව තට්ටු කරන්න</feature>
             <feature>• ස්පර්ශක ආලෝක ප්‍රයෝගයක් මුරපදය අගුළු හැරීමේ තිරයේ සහ පාලන මධ්‍යස්ථානයේ ඔබේ තට්ටු කිරීමට ප්‍රතිචාර දක්වයි</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="තත්ත්ව දණ්ඩ">
             <feature>• පෙන්විය යුතු තත්ත්ව දණ්ඩ අයිකන තෝරා ගැනීමට ඔබට ඉඩ දෙමින් තත්ත්ව දණ්ඩ මගින් අයිකන අභිරුචිකරණය සක්‍රීය කරයි. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: සැකසුම් > දැනුම්දීම් හා තත්ත්ව දණ්ඩ > තත්ත්ව දණ්ඩ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="මැජික් කැප්සියුලය">
             <feature>• මුහුණ හඳුනාගැනීම මැජික් කැප්සියුලයට ඒකාබද්ධ කර ඇත. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: සැකසුම් > දැනුම්දීම් හා තත්ත්ව දණ්ඩ > මැජික් කැප්සියුලය > මුහුණ හඳුනාගැනීම</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• වේගය පහසුවෙන් සහ විනෝදයෙන් ඒකාබද්ධ කරමින් OneTap Honor උපාංග අතර බාධාවකින් තොරව ගොනුව මාරු කරන්න සක්‍රීය කරයි. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: සැකසුම් > තවත් සම්බන්ධතා > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ක්‍රියාකාරීත්වය">
             <feature>• උපාංගයේ සමස්ත සුමට බව උසස් කිරීම සඳහා කලාතුරකින් ඇතිවන පැකිලීමේ ගැටළු විසඳයි</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ස්ථායීතාවය">
             <feature>• පද්ධතියේ ස්ථායිතාව වැඩිදියුණු කරයි</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක">
             <feature>• පද්ධති ආරක්ෂාව සඳහා Android ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක (2025 නොවැ) යොදාගෙන ඇත. Honor ආරක්ෂක යාවත්කාල පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සඳහා, කරුණාකර අපගේ වෙබ් අඩවිය වෙත යන්න https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="සටහන්" type="end">
             <feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්තවලට බල නොපානු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් යාවත්කාල කිරීමට පෙර ඔබගේ දත්ත උපස්ථ කිරීමට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ
2. ඉඟි තුළ නිෂ්පාදන විශේෂාංග පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සොයා ගන්න
3. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේදී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, ඔබට Honor සේවා හොට්ලයින් ඇමතීමෙන් හෝ Honor පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට පිවිසීමෙන් අපගේ උපකාර ලබා ගත හැකි වේ</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1051" name="sk-sk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Vážený používateľ, táto aktualizácia hlavne zvyšuje výkon systému. Aktualizujte, aby ste si užili zlepšenia</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fotoaparát">
             <feature>• K dispozícii je záznam s vypnutou obrazovkou. Vyskúšajte to v časti: Fotoaparát > Nastavenia > Záznam s vypnutou obrazovkou</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Domovská obrazovka">
             <feature>• Režim priehľadnosti optimalizuje efekty priehľadnosti prvkov, ako sú karty a priečinky, čím poskytuje výnimočný vizuálny zážitok. Vyskúšajte to v časti: Nastavenia > Domovská obrazovka a štýl > Nastavenia domovskej obrazovky > Režim priehľadnosti</feature>
             <feature>• Dlhým stlačením prázdnej oblasti domovskej obrazovky spustíte úpravy</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zamknutá obrazovka">
             <feature>• Zamknutá obrazovka ponúka viac štýlov hodín. Zoštipnite dva prsty na zamknutej obrazovke, ťuknite na položku Vlastný a potom na hodiny, ktoré chcete upraviť</feature>
             <feature>• Hmatový svetelný efekt reaguje na ťuknutie na obrazovke odomknutia heslom a v Centre ovládania</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stavový riadok">
             <feature>• Stavový riadok umožňuje prispôsobenie ikon a výber ikon stavového riadka, ktoré sa majú zobraziť. Vyskúšajte to v časti: Nastavenia > Upozornenia a stavový riadok > Stavový riadok</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magická kapsula">
             <feature>• Rozpoznávanie tváre je integrované do Magickej kapsuly. Vyskúšajte to v časti: Nastavenia > Upozornenia a stavový riadok > Magická kapsula > Rozpoznávanie tváre</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pripojenie Honor">
             <feature>• OneTap umožňuje bezproblémový prenos súborov medzi zariadeniami Honor, čím spája rýchlosť s jednoduchosťou a zábavou. Vyskúšajte to v časti: Nastavenia > Ďalšie pripojenia > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Výkonnosť">
             <feature>• Rieši občasné problémy so zasekávaním na zlepšenie celkovej plynulosti zariadenia</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilita">
             <feature>• Zlepšuje stabilitu systému</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezpečnostná oprava">
             <feature>• Súčasťou zabezpečenia systému je bezpečnostná oprava systému Android (z novembra 2025). Ak potrebujete viac informácií o bezpečnostných aktualizáciách spoločnosti Honor, navštívte webovú stránku https://www.honor.com/sk/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Poznámky" type="end">
             <feature>1. Inštalácia tejto aktualizácie neovplyvní vaše osobné údaje, ale aj tak sa odporúča pred aktualizáciou si ich zálohovať
2. Ďalšie informácie o funkciách produktu si pozrite v aplikácii Tipy
3. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytne problém, pomoc môžete získať na zákazníckej linke Honor alebo navštívením Centra služieb zákazníkom Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1060" name="sl-si">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, ta posodobitev izboljša predvsem delovanje sistema. Posodobite, da boste lahko izkoristili izboljšave</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Zdaj je na voljo funkcija Snemanje z izklopljenim zaslonom. Funkcijo lahko preizkusite tukaj: Kamera > Nastavitve > Snemanje z izklopljenim zaslonom</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Začetni zaslon">
             <feature>Način prosojnosti optimizira učinke prosojnosti elementov, kot so kartice in mape, ter zagotavlja vrhunsko vizualno izkušnjo. Preizkusite ga tako, da odprete: Nastavitve > Začetni zaslon in slog > Nastavitve začetnega zaslona > Način prosojnosti</feature>
             <feature>• Za začetek urejanja dolgo pritisnite prazno območje na začetnem zaslonu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zaklenjen zaslon">
             <feature>• Na zaklenjenem zaslonu je na voljo več slogov ure. Približajte prsta na zaklenjenem zaslonu, nato se dotaknite gumba Po meri in ure, da jo uredite</feature>
             <feature>• Taktilni svetlobni učinek se odzove na vaše dotike zaslona za odklepanje z geslom in v nadzornem središču</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vrstica stanja">
             <feature>• Vrstica stanja omogoča prilagajanje prikazanih ikon, tako da lahko izberete, katere ikone vrstice stanja bodo vidne. Preizkusite jo tako, da odprete: Nastavitve > Obvestila in vrstica stanja > Vrstica stanja</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Čarobna kapsula">
             <feature>• Čarobna kapsula zdaj podpira Prepoznavanje obraza. Preizkusite jo tako, da odprete: Nastavitve > Obvestila in vrstica stanja > Čarobna kapsula > Prepoznavanje obraza</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor povezovanje">
             <feature>• Funkcija OneTap omogoča nemoten prenos datotek med napravami Honor, pri čemer združuje hitrost z enostavnostjo uporabe in zabavo. Preizkusite jo tukaj: Nastavitve > Več povezav > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Izvajanje">
             <feature>• Odpravlja občasne težave s prekinitvami za izboljšano splošno delovanje naprave</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Izboljša stabilnost sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Varnostni popravek">
             <feature>• Varnostni popravki za Android (november 2025) so vključeni za varnost sistema. Za več informacij o varnostnih posodobitvah Honor obiščite spletno mesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zapiski" type="end">
             <feature>1. Namestitev te posodobitve ne vpliva na vaše osebne podatke, vendar je kljub temu priporočljivo, da podatke pred posodobitvijo varnostno kopirate
2. Več informacij o funkcijah izdelka je na voljo v razdelku Nasveti
3. Če med posodabljanjem pride do težav, lahko pokličete odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom družbe Honor ali obiščete servisni center družbe Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1053" name="sv-se">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Bästa användare, den här uppdateringen förbättrar främst systemets prestanda. Uppdatera för att ta del av förbättringarna</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Inspelning med avstängd skärm är nu tillgängligt. Prova genom att gå till: Kamera > Inställningar > Inspelning med avstängd skärm</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Startsida">
             <feature>• Transparensläge optimerar transparenseffekterna för element som kort och mappar, och ger en exceptionell visuell upplevelse. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Startsida och stil > Inställningar för startsidan > Transparensläge</feature>
             <feature>• Tryck länge på det tomma området på startsidan för att börja redigera</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Låsskärm">
             <feature>• Låsskärmen erbjuder fler klockstilar. Nyp ihop med två fingrar på låsskärmen, tryck på Anpassad och tryck sedan på klockan för att redigera</feature>
             <feature>• En taktil ljuseffekt reagerar på ditt tryck på skärmen för upplåsning med lösenord och i Kontrollcenter</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Statusfält">
             <feature>• Statusfältet möjliggör anpassning av ikoner, så att du kan välja vilka ikoner som ska visas i statusfältet. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Aviseringar och statusfält > Statusfält</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magisk kapsel">
             <feature>• Ansiktsigenkänning har integrerats i Magisk kapsel. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Aviseringar och statusfält > Magisk kapsel > Ansiktsigenkänning</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Anslut">
             <feature>• OneTap möjliggör sömlös filöverföring mellan Honor-enheter, och gör det både snabbt, enkelt och roligt. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Fler anslutningar > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Prestanda">
             <feature>• Löser tillfälliga problem med hackande och förbättrar enhetens jämnhet</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitet">
             <feature>• Förbättrar systemets stabilitet</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Säkerhetskorrigering">
             <feature>• Säkerhetskorrigering för Android (november 2025) har implementerats för systemsäkerhet. Vill du ha mer information om uppdateringar för Honor Säkerhet går du till vår webbplats https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Noteringar" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installation av den här uppdateringen påverkar inte dina personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du säkerhetskopierar alla data innan du uppdaterar
2. Upptäck mer information om produktfunktioner i Tips
3. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa Honors hotline för service eller besöka Honors kundtjänstcenter för att få hjälp</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1089" name="sw-TZ">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, sasisho hili kwa kiasi kikubwa linaboresha utendaji wa mfumo. Sasisha ili ufurahie maboresho</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Kurekodi ikiwa imezima skrini kunapatikana sasa. Ijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Kamera > Mipangilio > Kurekodi ikiwa imezima skrini</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Skrini ya mwanzo">
             <feature>• Hali ya uwazi huboresha athari za uwazi za elementi kama vile kadi na folda, hivyo basi kuwasilisha hali ya kipekee ya mwonekano. Ijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Skrini ya mwanzo na mtindo > Mipangilio ya skrini ya mwanzo > Hali ya uwazi</feature>
             <feature>• Bofya kwa muda mrefu eneo tupu la skrini ya mwanzo ili uanze kuhariri</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Skrini iliyofungwa">
             <feature>• Skrini iliyofungwa hutoa mitindo zaidi ya saa. Chuna kwa kutumia vidole viwili kwenye skrini iliyofungwa, gusa Maalum, kisha gusa saa ili uhariri</feature>
             <feature>• Athari ya mwangaza unapogusa huitikia unapogusa kwenye skrini ya kufungua kwa nenosiri na kwenye Kituo cha Udhibiti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Upau wa hali">
             <feature>• Upau wa hali huwezesha ubinafsishaji wa ikoni, hivyo basi kukuruhusu kuchagua ni ikoni gani za upau wa hali zitaonyesha. Jaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Upau wa hali na taarifa > Upau wa hali</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kapsuli ya Miujiza">
             <feature>• Utambuzi wa uso umejumuishwa kwenye Kapsuli ya Miujiza. Jaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Upau wa hali na taarifa > Kapsuli ya Miujiza > Utambuzi wa uso</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap huwezesha uhamishaji rahisi wa faili kati ya vifaa vya Honor, kwa kujumuisha kasi na urahisi na raha. Ijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Miunganisho zaidi > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Utendaji">
             <feature>• Hutatua masuala ya muda kwa muda ya kukwamakwama ili kuboresha ulaini kwa jumla wa kifaa</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Uthabiti">
             <feature>• Linaboresha uthabiti wa mfumo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Rekebisho la usalama">
             <feature>• Rekebisho la usalama wa Android (Nov 2025) limejumuishwa kwa ajili ya usalama wa mfumo. Ili kupata maelezo zaidi kuhusu masasisho ya Usalama wa Honor, tafadhali tembelea tovuti yetu: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Madokezo" type="end">
             <feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutaathiri data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado inapendekezwa ili kuweka hifadhi rudufu ya data yako kabla ya kusasisha
2. Gundua maelezo zaidi kwenye vipengele vya bidhaa kwenye Vidokezo
3. Ikiwa utakumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, unaweza kupata msaada wetu kwa kupiga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya Honor au tembelea kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1097" name="ta-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு முதன்மையாக சிஸ்டம் செயல்திறனை மேம்படுத்துகிறது. மேம்பாடுகளைப் பெற, புதுப்பிக்கவும்</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="கேமரா">
             <feature>• திரை-ஆஃப் பதிவு இப்போது கிடைக்கிறது. இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: கேமரா > அமைப்புகள் > திரை-ஆஃப் பதிவு</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="முகப்புத் திரை">
             <feature>• அட்டைகள் மற்றும் கோப்புறைகள் போன்ற கூறுகளின் ஒளிபுகு விளைவுகளை ஒளிபுகு முறை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது, இது ஒரு விதிவிலக்கான விஷுவல் அனுபவத்தை வழங்குகிறது. இங்குச் சென்று அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: அமைப்புகள் > முகப்புத் திரை &amp; ஸ்டைல் > முகப்புத் திரை அமைப்புகள் > ஒளிபுகு முறை</feature>
             <feature>• திருத்துவதைத் தொடங்க, முகப்புத் திரையில் காலியாக உள்ள பகுதியை நீண்ட நேரம் அழுத்தவும்</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="பூட்டுத் திரை">
             <feature>• பூட்டுத் திரை அதிக கடிகார ஸ்டைல்களை வழங்குகிறது. பூட்டுத் திரையில் இரண்டு விரல்களால் பின்ச் செய்து, தனிப்பயன் என்பதைத் தட்டி, பிறகு கடிகாரத்தைத் தட்டி திருத்தவும்</feature>
             <feature>• கடவுச்சொல் திறத்தல் திரையிலும் கட்டுப்பாட்டு மையத்திலும் நீங்கள் தட்டினால், ஒரு தொட்டுணரக்கூடிய ஒளி விளைவு பதிலளிக்கிறது</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="நிலைப் பட்டி">
             <feature>• நிலைப் பட்டி ஐகான் தனிப்பயனாக்கத்தைச் செயல்படுத்துகிறது, இது எந்த நிலைப் பட்டி ஐகான்களைக் காட்ட வேண்டும் என்பதைத் தேர்வுசெய்ய உங்களை அனுமதிக்கிறது. இங்குச் சென்று அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: அமைப்புகள் > அறிவிப்புகள் &amp; நிலைப் பட்டி > நிலைப் பட்டி</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="மேஜிக் கேப்சூல்">
             <feature>• முகம் அறிதல், மேஜிக் கேப்சூலில் ஒருங்கிணைக்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. இங்குச் சென்று அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: அமைப்புகள் > அறிவிப்புகள் &amp; நிலைப் பட்டி > மேஜிக் கேப்சூல் > முகம் அறிதல்</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap ஆனது Honor சாதனங்களுக்கு இடையில் தடையற்ற கோப்புப் பரிமாற்றத்தைச் செயல்படுத்துகிறது, இது வேகத்தை எளிமை மற்றும் வேடிக்கையுடன் இணைக்கிறது. இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: அமைப்புகள் > மேலும் இணைப்புகள் > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="செயல்திறன்">
             <feature>• சாதனத்தின் ஒட்டுமொத்த மென்மையை மேம்படுத்த அவ்வப்போது ஏற்படும் திணறல் சிக்கல்களைச் சரிசெய்கிறது</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="நிலைத்தன்மை">
             <feature>• சிஸ்டம் நிலைத்தன்மையை மேம்படுத்துகிறது</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு">
             <feature>• சிஸ்டம் பாதுகாப்பிற்காக Android பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு (நவ 2025) சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. Honor பாதுகாப்புப் புதுப்பிப்புகளைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களுக்கு, எங்கள் வலைத்தளத்தைப் பார்க்கவும்: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="குறிப்புகள்" type="end">
             <feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவைப் பாதிக்காது, எனினும் புதுப்பிப்பதற்கு முன்பு உங்கள் தரவைக் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுப்பது இன்னும் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது
2. உதவிக்குறிப்புகளில் தயாரிப்பு அம்சங்களைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களைக் கண்டறிக
3. புதுப்பிக்கும்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், Honor சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைப்பதன் மூலமோ அல்லது Honor வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்தைப் பார்வையிடுவதன் மூலமோ எங்கள் உதவியைப் பெறலாம்</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1098" name="te-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారుకు, ఈ అప్‌డేట్ ప్రధానంగా సిస్టమ్ పనితీరును మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది. మెరుగుదలలను ఆనందించడానికి అప్‌డేట్ చేయండి</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="కెమెరా">
             <feature>• స్క్రీన్ ఆఫ్ చేసి రికార్డింగ్ ఇప్పుడు అందుబాటులో ఉంది. ఇక్కడికి వెళ్ళి దానిని ప్రయత్నించండి: కెమెరా > సెట్టింగ్‌లు > స్క్రీన్ ఆఫ్ చేసి రికార్డింగ్</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="హోమ్ స్క్రీన్">
             <feature>• పారదర్శకత మోడ్ అనేది అద్భుతమైన విజువల్ అనుభవాన్ని అందిస్తూ, కార్డ్‌లు మరియు ఫోల్డర్‌లు వంటి ఎలిమెంట్‌ల పారదర్శక ప్రభావాలను ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది. ఇక్కడికి వెళ్ళి దానిని ప్రయత్నించండి: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ &amp; శైలి > హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ సెట్టింగ్‌లు > పారదర్శకత మోడ్</feature>
             <feature>• సవరణను ప్రారంభించడానికి హోమ్ స్క్రీన్‌లోని ఖాళీ ప్రాంతాన్ని కొంతసేపు నొక్కి, పట్టుకోండి</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="లాక్ స్క్రీన్">
             <feature>• లాక్ స్క్రీన్ మరిన్ని గడియార శైలులను అందిస్తుంది. లాక్ స్క్రీన్‌పై రెండు వేళ్ళతో పించ్ చేసి, అనుకూలం ట్యాప్ చేసి, ఆపై సవరించడానికి గడియారాన్ని ట్యాప్ చేయండి</feature>
             <feature>• వ్యూహాత్మక లైట్ ప్రభావం అనేది పాస్‌వర్డ్ అన్‌లాక్ స్క్రీన్ మరియు కంట్రోల్ సెంటర్‌లో మీ ట్యాప్‌కు ప్రతిస్పందిస్తుంది</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="స్థితి బార్">
             <feature>• స్థితి బార్ అనేది చిహ్నం అనుకూలీకరణను ప్రారంభిస్తుంది, ఇది ఏ స్థితి బార్ చిహ్నాలను ప్రదర్శించాలో ఎంచుకోవడానికి మిమ్మల్ని అనుమతిస్తుంది. ఇక్కడికి వెళ్ళి దానిని ప్రయత్నించండి: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > నోటిఫికేషన్‌లు &amp; స్థితి బార్ > స్థితి బార్</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="మేజిక్ క్యాప్సుల్">
             <feature>• ముఖ గుర్తింపు అనేది మేజిక్ క్యాప్సుల్‌లోకి ఇంటిగ్రేట్ చేయబడింది. ఇక్కడికి వెళ్ళి దానిని ప్రయత్నించండి: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > నోటిఫికేషన్‌లు &amp; స్థితి బార్ > మేజిక్ క్యాప్సుల్ > ముఖం గుర్తింపు</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor కనెక్ట్">
             <feature>• OneTap అనేది Honor పరికరాల మధ్య సులభమైన ఫైల్ బదిలీని ప్రారంభిస్తుంది, ఇది వేగంతో సరళత మరియు సరదాను అందిస్తుంది. ఇక్కడికి వెళ్ళి దానిని ప్రయత్నించండి: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > మరిన్ని కనెక్షన్‌లు > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="పనితీరు">
             <feature>• పరికరం యొక్క మొత్తం సరళతను మెరుగుపరచడానికి అప్పుడప్పుడు సంభవించే తడబడే సమస్యలను పరిష్కరిస్తుంది</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="స్థిరత్వం">
             <feature>• సిస్టమ్ స్థిరత్వాన్ని మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="భద్రతా ప్యాచ్">
             <feature>• సిస్టమ్ భద్రత కోసం Android భద్రతా ప్యాచ్ (నవం 2025) చేర్చబడింది. Honor భద్రత అప్‌డేట్‌ల గురించి మరింత సమాచారం కోసం, దయచేసి మా వెబ్‌సైట్‌ను సందర్శించండి: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="గమనికలు" type="end">
             <feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్ ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వలన మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటా ప్రభావితం కాదు, కాని అప్‌డేట్ చేయడానికి ముందు మీ డేటాను బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని ఇంకా సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది
2. చిట్కాల్లో ఉత్పత్తి ఫీచర్లపై మరింత సమాచారాన్ని తెలుసుకోండి
3. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో ఏవైనా సమస్యలను ఎదుర్కొంటే, మీరు Honor సర్వీస్ హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేసి లేదా Honor కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రాన్ని సందర్శించి మా సహాయం పొందవచ్చు</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1054" name="th-th">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตครั้งนี้เน้นปรับปรุงประสิทธิภาพระบบเป็นหลัก โปรดอัปเดตเพื่อใช้การปรับปรุง</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="กล้องถ่ายรูป">
             <feature>• การบันทึกขณะปิดหน้าจอพร้อมใช้งานแล้ว ลองใช้โดยไปที่: กล้องถ่ายรูป > การตั้งค่า > การบันทึกขณะปิดหน้าจอ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="หน้าจอหลัก">
             <feature>• โหมดความโปร่งใสจะปรับปรุงเอฟเฟ็กต์ความโปร่งใสขององค์ประกอบต่างๆ เช่น การ์ดและโฟลเดอร์ เพื่อมอบประสบการณ์การรับชมภาพที่ยอดเยี่ยม ลองใช้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > หน้าจอหลักและสไตล์ > การตั้งค่าหน้าจอหลัก > โหมดความโปร่งใส</feature>
             <feature>• กดค้างไว้ที่พื้นที่ว่างของหน้าจอหลักเพื่อเริ่มแก้ไข</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="หน้าจอล็อค">
             <feature>• หน้าจอล็อคมีสไตล์นาฬิกาเพิ่มขึ้น ใช้สองนิ้วจีบนิ้วบนหน้าจอล็อค แตะ กำหนดเอง จากนั้นแตะที่นาฬิกาเพื่อแก้ไข</feature>
             <feature>• เอฟเฟ็กต์แสงแบบสัมผัสจะตอบสนองต่อการแตะบนหน้าจอปลดล็อคด้วยรหัสผ่านและในศูนย์ควบคุม</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="แถบสถานะ">
             <feature>• แถบสถานะช่วยให้สามารถใช้การปรับแต่งไอคอนได้ ช่วยให้คุณเลือกว่าจะแสดงไอคอนแถบสถานะไอคอนใด ลองใช้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > การแจ้งเตือนและแถบสถานะ > แถบสถานะ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="เมจิกแคปซูล">
             <feature>• การจดจำใบหน้าจะผสานรวมกับเมจิกแคปซูล ลองใช้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > การแจ้งเตือนและแถบสถานะ > เมจิกแคปซูล > การจดจำใบหน้า</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap ช่วยให้คุณสามารถถ่ายโอนไฟล์ได้อย่างไร้รอยต่อระหว่างอุปกรณ์ Honor เพื่อผสมผสานความเร็วกับความง่ายดายและความสนุก ลองใช้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > การเชื่อมต่อเพิ่มเติม > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ประสิทธิภาพ">
             <feature>• แก้ไขปัญหาการกระตุกเป็นครั้งคราวเพื่อปรับปรุงความลื่นไหลโดยรวมของอุปกรณ์</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ความเสถียร">
             <feature>• ปรับปรุงความเสถียรของระบบ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="แพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัย">
             <feature>• มีการรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัย Android (พ.ย. 2025) เพื่อความปลอดภัยของระบบ ดูข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับการอัปเดตด้านความปลอดภัยของ Honor ได้โดยไปที่เว็บไซต์ของเรา https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="โน้ต" type="end">
             <feature>1. การติดตั้งการอัปเดตนี้จะไม่ส่งผลต่อข้อมูลส่วนตัว แต่เราขอแนะนำให้คุณสำรองข้อมูลก่อนอัปเดต
2. ค้นพบข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับฟีเจอร์ผลิตภัณฑ์ในเคล็ดลับ
3. หากคุณพบปัญหาใดๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต คุณสามารถรับความช่วยเหลือได้โดยการโทรติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการลูกค้าของ Honor หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1124" name="tl-ph">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Minamahal na user, pangunahing pinapahusay ng update na ito ang performance ng system. I-update para i-enjoy ang mga pagpapahusay</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Camera">
             <feature>• Available na ang Recording na naka-off ang screen. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Camera > Mga Setting > Recording na naka-off ang screen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Home screen">
             <feature>• Ino-optimize ang Transparency mode ang mga effect sa transparency ng mga element gaya ng mga card at folder, at naghahatid ng pinakamagandang visual na karanasan. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Home screen at estilo > Mga setting ng home screen > Transparency mode</feature>
             <feature>• Pindutin nang matagal ang blangkong bahagi ng home screen para simulang mag-edit</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Lock screen">
             <feature>• Nag-aalok ang lock screen ng mas maraming estilo ng orasan. I-pinch gamit ang dalawang daliri sa lock screen, i-tap ang Custom, pagkatapos ay i-tap ang orasan para i-edit</feature>
             <feature>• Tumutugon ang tactile light effect sa iyong pag-tap sa screen sa pag-unlock gamit ang password at sa Control Center</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Status bar">
             <feature>• Nagbibigay-daan ang Status bar sa pag-customize ng icon, na nagbibigay-daan sa iyong pumili kung aling mga icon ng status bar ang ipapakita. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Mga notification at status bar > Status bar</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic Capsule">
             <feature>• Kasama ang Pagtukoy ng mukha sa Magic Capsule. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Mga notification at status bar > Magic Capsule > Pagtukoy ng mukha</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Nagbibigay-daan ang OneTap sa tuluy-tuloy na paglilipat ng file sa pagitan ng mga Honor device, pinagsasama ang bilis at saya. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Higit pang koneksyon > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pagganap">
             <feature>• Nilulutas ang minsanang isyu ng paghintu-hinto para mapahusay ang kabuuang pagiging tuluy-tuloy ng device</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stability">
             <feature>• Pinapahusay ang stability ng system</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Panseguridad na patch">
             <feature>• Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Nob 2025) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa mga Panseguridad na update ng Honor, bisitahin ang aming website sa https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Mga Tala" type="end">
             <feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto ang pag-install sa update na ito sa iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update
2. Tuklasin ang higit pang impormasyon sa mga feature ng produkto sa Mga Tip
3. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, makukuha mo ang tulong namin sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng Honor o pagbisita sa customer service center ng Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1055" name="tr-tr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Değerli kullanıcımız, bu güncelleme ile çoğunlukla sistem performansı artırılmıştır. İyileştirmelerin tadını çıkarmak için güncelleyin</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Ekran kapalı kayıt özelliği eklendi. Şu adımları takip ederek deneyebilirsiniz: Kamera > Ayarlar > Ekran kapalı kayıt</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Başlangıç ekranı">
             <feature>• Saydamlık modu, kartlar ve klasörler gibi öğelerin saydamlık efektlerini optimize ederek olağanüstü bir görsel deneyim sunar. Şu adımları takip ederek deneyebilirsiniz: Ayarlar > Başlangıç ekranı ve stil > Başlangıç ekranı ayarları > Saydamlık modu</feature>
             <feature>• Düzenlemeye başlamak için başlangıç ekranındaki boş alana uzun basın</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kilit ekranı">
             <feature>• Kilit ekranına daha fazla saat stili eklendi. Kilit ekranında iki parmağınızla sıkıştırma hareketi yapın, Özel seçeneğine dokunun ve ardından saati düzenlemek için saate dokunun</feature>
             <feature>• Şifre ile kilit açma ekranında ve Kontrol Merkezi'nde ekrana dokunarak dokunsal ışık efektini deneyimleyebilirsiniz</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Durum çubuğu">
             <feature>• Durum çubuğunda hangi durum çubuğu simgelerinin görüntüleneceğini seçmenize olanak tanıyan simge özelleştirme özelliği eklendi. Şu adımları takip ederek deneyebilirsiniz: Ayarlar > Bildirimler ve durum çubuğu > Durum çubuğu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sihirli Kapsül">
             <feature>• Yüz tanıma özelliği Sihirli Kapsül'e entegre edildi. Şu adımları takip ederek deneyebilirsiniz: Ayarlar > Bildirimler ve durum çubuğu > Sihirli Kapsül > Yüz tanıma</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap, Honor cihazları arasında sorunsuz dosya aktarımı sağlar; hızı kolaylık ve eğlenceyle birleştirir. Şu adımları takip ederek deneyebilirsiniz: Ayarlar > Diğer bağlantılar > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Performans">
             <feature>• Cihazın genel akıcılığını artırmak için ara sıra yaşanan takılma sorunları giderildi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kararlılık">
             <feature>• Sistem kararlılığı iyileştirildi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Güvenlik yaması">
             <feature>• Sistem güvenliği için Android güvenlik yamasını (Kasım 2025) içermektedir. Honor Güvenlik güncellemeleri ile ilgili daha fazla bilgi için lütfen web sitemizi ziyaret edin: https://www.honor.com/tr/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notlar" type="end">
             <feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi etkilemeyecektir ancak yine de güncellemeden önce verilerinizi yedeklemeniz önerilir
2. İpuçları bölümünden ürün özellikleri hakkında daha fazla bilgiyi keşfedin
3. Güncelleme sırasında sorunla karşılaşırsanız Honor yardım hattını arayarak veya Honor müşteri hizmetleri merkezini ziyaret ederek yardım alabilirsiniz</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1058" name="uk-ua">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Шановний користувачу! Це оновлення насамперед підвищує продуктивність системи. Установіть його, щоб відчути покращення</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Камера">
             <feature>• Тепер доступна функція "Записування з вимкнутим екраном". Щоб спробувати, перейдіть до меню: Камера > Налаштування > Записування з вимкнутим екраном</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Головний екран">
             <feature>• Режим прозорості оптимізує ефекти прозорості елементів, як-от карток і папок, створюючи особливе візуальне подання. Щоб спробувати, виберіть "Налаштування" > "Головний екран і стиль" > "Налаштування головного екрана" > "Режим прозорості"</feature>
             <feature>• Натисніть будь-де у порожній області головного екрана й утримуйте палець, щоб розпочати редагування</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Екран блокування">
             <feature>• Екран блокування пропонує більше стилів годинників. Зведіть два пальці на екрані блокування, торкніться Користувацький, а потім торкніться годинника, щоб змінити</feature>
             <feature>• Тактильний світловий ефект реагує на ваш дотик до екрана розблокування паролем і в центрі керування</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Рядок стану">
             <feature>• У рядку стану можна налаштувати піктограми, вибравши конкретні піктограми для відображення. Щоб спробувати, виберіть "Налаштування" > "Сповіщення та рядок стану" > "Рядок стану"</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Магічна капсула">
             <feature>• До Магічної капсули додано функцію розпізнавання обличчя. Щоб спробувати, виберіть "Налаштування" > "Сповіщення та рядок стану" > "Магічна капсула" > "Розпізнавання обличчя"</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Сполучення Honor">
             <feature>• Функція OneTap забезпечує безперебійну передачу файлів між пристроями Honor, поєднуючи швидкість, простоту й зручність. Щоб спробувати, перейдіть до меню: Налаштування > Інші способи підключення > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Продуктивність">
             <feature>• Вирішує проблеми з випадковими зависаннями для покращення загальної плавної роботи пристрою</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Стабільність">
             <feature>• Покращено стабільність роботи системи</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Виправлення системи безпеки">
             <feature>• Виправлення безпеки Android від листопада 2025 року впроваджено для посилення безпеки системи. Додаткову інформацію про оновлення для системи безпеки Honor див. на нашому вебсайті https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Нотатки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Установлення цього оновлення не вплине на ваші особисті дані, однак рекомендовано спочатку створити їхні резервні копії
2. Дізнайтеся більше про функції продукту в розділі "Підказки"
3. Якщо під час оновлення у вас виникнуть будь-які проблеми, ви можете отримати нашу допомогу, зателефонувавши на гарячу лінію Honor або відвідавши центр послуг Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1056" name="ur-pk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>محترم صارف، یہ اپ ڈیٹ بنیادی طور پر سسٹم کی کارکردگی کو بڑھاتی ہے۔ بہتریوں سے لطف اندوز ہونے کے لیے اپ ڈیٹ کریں</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="کیمرہ">
             <feature>‏‏• اسکرین آف کر کے ریکارڈنگ اب دستیاب ہے۔ یہاں جا کر اسے آزمائیں: کیمرہ > ترتیبات > اسکرین آف کر کے ریکارڈنگ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ہوم اسکرین">
             <feature>‏• شفافیت موڈ ایک غیر معمولی بصری تجربہ فراہم کر کے، کارڈز اور فولڈرز جیسے عناصر کی شفافیت کے اثرات کو بہتر بناتا ہے۔ یہاں جا کر اسے آزمائیں: ترتیبات > ہوم اسکرین اور طرز > ہوم اسکرین کی ترتیبات > شفافیت موڈ</feature>
             <feature>‏• ترمیم شروع کرنے کے لیے ہوم اسکرین کے خالی حصے کو دیر تک دبائیں</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="لاک اسکرین">
             <feature>‏‏• لاک اسکرین گھڑی کے مزید اسٹائلز پیش کرتی ہے۔ لاک اسکرین پر دو انگلیوں سے بھینچیں، حسب ضرورت پر ٹیپ کریں، پھر ترمیم کرنے کے لیے گھڑی پر ٹیپ کریں</feature>
             <feature>‏‏• ایک ٹیکٹائل لائٹ اثر پاس ورڈ ان لاک کی اسکرین اور کنٹرول سینٹر میں آپ کے ٹیپ پر ردعمل دیتا ہے</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏اسٹیٹس بار">
             <feature>‏• اسٹیٹس بار آئیکن کی کسٹمائزیشن کو فعال کرتی ہے، جو آپ کو یہ منتخب کرنے کی اجازت دیتا ہے کہ کون سے اسٹیٹس بار آئیکن کو ڈسپلے کرنا ہے۔ یہاں جا کر اسے آزمائیں: ترتیبات > اطلاعات اور اسٹیٹس بار > اسٹیٹس بار</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏میجک کیپسول">
             <feature>‏• چہرے کی شناخت کو میجک کیپسول میں ضم کر دیا گیا ہے۔ یہاں جا کر اسے آزمائیں: ترتیبات > اطلاعات اور اسٹیٹس بار > ‏میجک کیپسول > چہرے کی شناخت</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏Honor Connect">
             <feature>‏‏• ‏OneTap رفتار کو آسانی اور تفریح کے ساتھ، Honor ڈیوائسز کے درمیان بغیر کسی رکاوٹ کے فائل کی منتقلی کو ممکن بناتی ہے۔ یہاں جا کر اسے آزمائیں: ترتیبات > مزید کنکشنز > ‏OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="کارکردگی">
             <feature>‏‏• ڈیوائس کی مجموعی ہمواری کو بڑھانے کے لیے کبھی کبھار رکاوٹ کے مسائل کو حل کرتی ہے</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="استحکام">
             <feature>‏‏• سسٹم کے استحکام کو بہتر بناتی ہے</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="سکیورٹی پیچ">
             <feature>‏• Android سکیورٹی پیچ (نومبر 2025) شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔ Honor سکیورٹی اپ ڈیٹس کے بارے میں مزید معلومات کے لیے، براہ کرم ہماری ویب سائٹ ملاحظہ کریں https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="نوٹس" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا متاثر نہیں ہو گا، لیکن اپ ڈیٹ کرنے سے پہلے اب بھی اپنے ڈیٹا کا بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے
‏2. تجاویز میں پروڈکٹس کی خصوصیات کے بارے میں مزید معلومات دریافت کریں
‏3. اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کوئی مسئلہ درپیش ہوتا ہے، تو آپ Honor سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کر کے یا Honor کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جا کر ہماری مدد حاصل کر سکتے ہیں</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2115" name="uz-uz">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu yangilanish asosan tizim unumdorligini oshiradi. Takomillashtirishlardan foydalanish uchun yangilang</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Endi Oʻchiq ekrandan yozib olish funksiyasidan foydalanish mumkin. Bu yerda sinang: Kamera > Sozlamalar > Oʻchiq ekrandan yozib olish</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bosh ekran">
             <feature>• Shaffoflik rejimi kartochkalar va jildlar kabi elementlarning shaffoflik effektlarini optimallaydi hamda ajoyib vizual taassurotni taqdim etadi. Bu yerda sinang: Sozlamalar > Bosh ekran va uslub > Bosh ekran sozlamalari > Shaffoflik rejimi</feature>
             <feature>• Tahrirlashni boshlash uchun bosh ekranning boʻsh joyini uzoq bosib turing</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ekranni qulflash">
             <feature>• Ekran qulfi yanada koʻproq soat uslublarini taklif qiladi. Ekran qulfida ikki barmoq bilan chimdib, Maxsus bandini bosing, keyin tahrirlash uchun soatni bosing</feature>
             <feature>• Parol bilan qulfni ochish ekrani va Boshqaruv markazini bosganingizga taktil yoritish effekti yuz beradi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Holat qatori">
             <feature>• Holat qatori belgilarni sozlash imkonini beradi va qaysi holat qatori belgilarining koʻrsatilishini tanlashingiz mumkin. Bu yerda sinang: Sozlamalar > Bildirishnomalar va holat qatori > Holat qatori</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sehrli kapsula">
             <feature>• Yuzni aniqlash funksiyasi Sehrli kapsulaga kiritildi. Bu yerda sinang: Sozlamalar > Bildirishnomalar va holat qatori > Sehrli kapsula > Yuzni aniqlash</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap Honor qurilmalari orasida fayllarni muammosiz uzatish imkonini beradi hamda tezlikni qulaylik va zavq bilan birlashtiradi. Bu yerda sinang: Sozlamalar > Boshqa ulanish usullari > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Unumdorlik">
             <feature>• Qurilmaning umumiy ishlash ravonligini yaxshilash uchun vaqti-vaqti bilan qotib ishlash muammolari hal etildi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Barqarorlik">
             <feature>• Tizim barqarorligi yaxshilandi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Xavfsizlik tuzatmasi">
             <feature>• Tizim xavfsizligi uchun Android xavfsizlik tuzatmasi (2025-yil, noyabr) kiritildi. Honor Xavfsizlik yangilanishlari haqida batafsil axborot olish uchun veb-saytimizga tashrif buyuring: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Eslatmalar" type="end">
             <feature>1. Bu yangilanishni oʻrnatish shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringizga taʼsir qilmaydi, lekin yangilashdan oldin maʼlumotlaringizni zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi
2. Maslahatlar ilovasida mahsulot xususiyatlari bilan batafsilroq tanishing
3. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, Honor xizmatining tezkor raqamiga telefon qilish yoki Honor mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyurish orqali yordam olishingiz mumkin</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1066" name="vi-vn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật này chủ yếu nâng cao hiệu suất hệ thống. Hãy cập nhật để tận hưởng các cải tiến</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Máy ảnh">
             <feature>• Giờ đây, bạn có thể Ghi âm khi màn hình tắt. Hãy thử bằng cách vào: Máy ảnh > Cài đặt > Ghi âm khi màn hình tắt</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Màn hình chính">
             <feature>• Chế độ trong suốt tối ưu hóa các hiệu ứng trong suốt của các thành phần như thẻ và thư mục, mang đến trải nghiệm hình ảnh đặc biệt. Hãy dùng thử bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Phong cách và màn hình chính > Cài đặt màn hình chính > Chế độ trong suốt</feature>
             <feature>• Nhấn và giữ vùng trống của màn hình chính để bắt đầu sửa</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Màn hình khóa">
             <feature>• Màn hình khóa cung cấp nhiều kiểu đồng hồ hơn. Đưa hai ngón tay về gần nhau trên màn hình khóa, chạm vào Tùy chỉnh, sau đó chạm vào đồng hồ để sửa</feature>
             <feature>• Hiệu ứng ánh sáng cảm ứng phản hồi khi bạn chạm vào màn hình mở khóa bằng mật khẩu và trong Trung tâm Điều khiển</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Thanh trạng thái">
             <feature>• Thanh trạng thái hiện hỗ trợ tùy chỉnh biểu tượng, cho phép bạn chọn các biểu tượng nào được hiển thị trên thanh trạng thái. Hãy dùng thử bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Thông báo và thanh trạng thái > Thanh trạng thái</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic Capsule">
             <feature>• Tính năng Nhận dạng khuôn mặt đã được tích hợp vào Magic Capsule. Hãy dùng thử bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Thông báo và thanh trạng thái > Magic Capsule > Nhận dạng khuôn mặt</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap cho phép truyền tệp tin liền mạch giữa các thiết bị Honor, kết hợp tốc độ với sự dễ dàng và thú vị. Hãy thử bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Kết nối khác > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Hiệu suất">
             <feature>• Khắc phục các sự cố giật hình thỉnh thoảng xảy ra để tăng cường độ mượt mà tổng thể của thiết bị</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Độ ổn định">
             <feature>• Cải thiện độ ổn định của hệ thống</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bản vá bảo mật">
             <feature>• Bản cập nhật này tích hợp Bản vá bảo mật Android (tháng 11 năm 2025) để bảo mật hệ thống. Để biết thêm thông tin về các Bản cập nhật bảo mật của Honor, vui lòng truy cập trang web của chúng tôi: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Ghi chú" type="end">
             <feature>1. Việc cài đặt bản cập nhật này sẽ không ảnh hưởng đến dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn, nhưng bạn vẫn nên sao lưu dữ liệu trước khi cập nhật
2. Khám phá thêm thông tin về các tính năng sản phẩm trong ứng dụng Mẹo
3. Nếu gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, bạn có thể nhận trợ giúp của chúng tôi bằng cách gọi đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ của Honor hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="3076" name="zh-hk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新主要針對系統進行了優化，建議您進行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="相機">
             <feature>• 新增息屏錄像功能，體驗路徑：相機 > 設定 > 息屏錄製</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="主屏幕">
             <feature>• 新增通透模式，提升卡片、資料夾等元素的通透效果，帶來極致通透體驗。體驗路徑：設定 > 主屏幕和個人化 > 主屏幕設定 > 通透模式</feature>
             <feature>• 新增長按主屏幕空白區域進入編輯模式功能</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="鎖屏">
             <feature>• 新增多種鎖屏時鐘樣式，體驗路徑：鎖屏雙指捏合 > 自訂 > 輕觸時鐘即可編輯</feature>
             <feature>• 新增密碼解鎖和控制中心介面按壓通透光感效果</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="狀態欄">
             <feature>• 新增狀態欄圖標自訂功能，可自由選擇需要顯示的狀態欄圖標。體驗路徑：設定 > 通知和狀態欄 > 狀態欄</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="靈動膠囊">
             <feature>• 新增臉部解鎖連接膠囊。體驗路徑：設定 > 通知和狀態欄 > 靈動膠囊 > 臉部識別</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="榮耀互聯">
             <feature>• 新增支援榮耀手機之間的一拍即傳，提供檔案高速傳輸，好玩又快捷。體驗路徑：設定 > 更多連接 > 一拍即傳</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="性能">
             <feature>• 優化部分場景使用不暢順問題，提升整機流暢性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="穩定性">
             <feature>• 提升系統穩定性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安全性修補程式">
             <feature>• 整合 Android 2025年11月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需了解有關榮耀軟件安全更新內容的資訊，請瀏覽榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="更新注意事項" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份
2. 更多精彩功能介紹，請瀏覽「玩機技巧」應用程式
3. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線或至榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1028" name="zh-tw">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新主要針對系統進行了最佳化，建議您進行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="相機">
             <feature>• 新增關閉螢幕錄影功能，體驗路徑：相機 > 設定 > 關閉螢幕錄製</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="桌面">
             <feature>•  新增通透模式，提升卡片、資料夾等元素的通透效果，帶來極致通透體驗。體驗路徑：設定 > 桌面和個人化 > 桌面設定 > 通透模式</feature>
             <feature>• 新增長按桌面空白區域進入編輯模式功能</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="鎖定螢幕">
             <feature>• 新增多種鎖定螢幕時鐘樣式，體驗路徑：在鎖定螢幕上雙指捏合 > 自訂 > 輕觸時鐘即可編輯</feature>
             <feature>• 新增密碼解鎖和控制中心介面按壓通透光感效果</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="狀態列">
             <feature>•  新增狀態列圖示自訂功能，可自由選取需要顯示的狀態列圖示。體驗路徑：設定 > 通知和狀態列 > 狀態列</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="靈動膠囊">
             <feature>•  新增人臉解鎖加入膠囊。體驗路徑：設定 > 通知和狀態列 > 靈動膠囊 > 人臉辨識</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="榮耀互聯">
             <feature>• 新增支援榮耀手機之間的一碰傳，實現檔案高速傳輸，好玩又快捷。體驗路徑：設定 > 更多連接方式 > 一碰傳</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="效能">
             <feature>• 最佳化在部分場景下的使用遲滯問題，提升整機流暢性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="穩定性">
             <feature>• 提升系統穩定性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安全性修補程式">
             <feature>• 整合 Android 2025 年 11 月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟體安全更新內容的資訊，請造訪榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="更新注意事項" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份
2. 如需更多精彩功能介紹，請查看「玩機技巧」應用程式
3. 在更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1152" name="ug-cn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا ئاساسلىقى سىستېمىغا قارىتا ئەلالاشتۇرۇش ئېلىپ بېرىلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏كامېرا">
             <feature>‏• ئۆچۈك ئېكراندا سىنغا ئېلىش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، ئىشلىتىش يولى: كامېرا > تەڭشەك > ئۆچۈك ئېكراندا سىنغا ئېلىش</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏ئۈستەليۈزى">
             <feature>‏•  سۈزۈك ھالەت يېڭىدىن قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، كارتا، ھۆججەت قاتارلىق ئېلېمېنتلارنىڭ سۈزۈكلۈك ئۈنۈمى يۇقىرى كۆتۈرۈلدى، ئېسىل سۈزۈك تەسىراتى ئېلىپ كېلىدۇ. ئىشلىتىش يولى: تەڭشەك > ئۈستەليۈزى ۋە خاسلاشتۇرۇش > ئۈستەليۈزى تەڭشىكى > ‏سۈزۈك ھالەت</feature>
             <feature>‏• ئۈستەليۈزىدىكى قۇرۇق رايوننى ئۇزۇن بېسىپ تەھرىرلەش ھالىتىگە كىرىش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏قۇلۇپ ئېكرانى">
             <feature>‏• كۆپ خىل ئېكران قۇلۇپى سائەت شەكىللىرى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، ئىشلىتىش يولى: قۇلۇپ ئېكرانىنى قوش بارماقتا يىغىش > ‏ئىختىيارىي > سائەتنى چېكىپ تەھرىرلەش</feature>
             <feature>‏• پارولدا ئېچىش ھەمدە تىزگىنلەش مەركىزى ئارايۈزىگە بېسىش مەشغۇلاتىنىڭ سۈزۈك ۋە نۇرلۇق ئۈنۈمى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏ھالەت بالدىقى">
             <feature>‏•  ھالەت بالدىقى سىنبەلگىسىنى خاسلاشتۇرۇش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، كۆرسىتىدىغان ھالەت بالدىقى سىنبەلگىسىنى خالىغانچە تاللاشقا بولىدۇ. ئىشلىتىش يولى: تەڭشەك > ئۇقتۇرۇش ۋە ھالەت بالدىقى > ھالەت بالدىقى</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏چاققان لەيلىگۈچ">
             <feature>‏•  يۈز ئارقىلىق ئېچىش لەيلىگۈچكە ئۇلاندى. ئىشلىتىش يولى: تەڭشەك > ئۇقتۇرۇش ۋە ھالەت بالدىقى > ‏چاققان لەيلىگۈچ > ‏يۈز تونۇش</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="روڭياۋ ئۇلاش">
             <feature>‏• روڭياۋ يانفونى ئارا تەگكۈزۈپ يوللاش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، ھۆججەتنى تېز يەتكۈزۈشنى ئەمەلگە ئاشۇرىدۇ، قىزىقارلىق ۋە ئەپچىل. ئىشلىتىش يولى: تەڭشەك > باشقا ئۇلىنىشلار > تەگكۈزۈپ يوللاش</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ئىقتىدار">
             <feature>‏• قىسىمەن كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى قېتىۋېلىش مەسىلىسى ھەل قىلىنغان بولۇپ، پۈتۈن ئۈسكۈنىنىڭ راۋانلىقى ئاشۇرۇلدى</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏مۇقىملىق">
             <feature>‏• سىستېمىنىڭ مۇقىملىقى يۇقىرى كۆتۈرۈلدى</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى">
             <feature>‏• ئاندرويدنىڭ 2025-يىل 11-ئايلىق بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، سىستېما بىخەتەرلىكى كۈچەيتىلدى. روڭياۋ يۇمشاق دېتالىنىڭ بىخەتەرلىك يېڭىلاش مەزمۇنىغا ئالاقىدار ئۇچۇرلار ئۈچۈن روڭياۋ ئورگان تەرەپ تور بېكىتى https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/11 نى زىيارەت قىلىڭ.</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="‏يېڭىلاش بىلدۈرگۈسى" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، لېكىن يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتنى زاپاسلاشنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز
‏2. تېخىمۇ كۆپ سەرخىل ئىقتىدارلارنى «ئىشلىتىش كۆرسەتمىسى» ئەپىنى زىيارەت قىلىپ كۆرۈڭ
‏3. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركىسى مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1031" name="de-at">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung verbessert hauptsächlich die Systemleistung. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Aufnahme bei ausgeschaltetem Bildschirm ist jetzt verfügbar. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Kamera > Einstellungen > Aufnahme bei ausgeschaltetem Bildschirm</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Startbildschirm">
             <feature>• Der Transparenzmodus optimiert die Transparenzeffekte von Elementen wie Karten und Ordnern und sorgt so für ein außergewöhnliches Anzeigeerlebnis. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Startbildschirm und Stil > Startbildschirmeinstellungen > Transparenzmodus</feature>
             <feature>• Drücken Sie eine leere Stelle auf dem Startbildschirm lange, um die Bearbeitung zu starten</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bildschirm sperren">
             <feature>• Der Sperrbildschirm bietet mehr Uhrenstile. Ziehen Sie den Sperrbildschirm mit zwei Fingern zusammen, tippen Sie auf Benutzerdefiniert und tippen Sie dann zum Bearbeiten auf die Uhr</feature>
             <feature>• Ein taktiler Lichteffekt reagiert auf Ihr Tippen auf dem Bildschirm zum Entsperren des Passworts und im Kontrollzentrum</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Statusleiste">
             <feature>• Statusleiste ermöglicht die Anpassung von Symbolen, sodass Sie wählen können, welche Symbole in der Statusleiste angezeigt werden sollen. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Benachrichtigungen &amp; Statusleiste > Statusleiste</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic Capsule">
             <feature>• Gesichtserkennung ist in Magic Capsule integriert. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Benachrichtigungen &amp; Statusleiste > Magic Capsule > Gesichtserkennung</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Ein Tastendruck ermöglicht eine nahtlose Dateiübertragung zwischen Honor-Geräten und kombiniert dabei Geschwindigkeit mit Leichtigkeit und Spaß. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Weitere Verbindungen > Ein Tastendruck</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Leistung">
             <feature>• Behebt gelegentlich auftretende Probleme mit Ruckeln, um die allgemeine Laufruhe des Geräts zu verbessern</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilität">
             <feature>• Verbessert die Systemstabilität</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sicherheitspatch">
             <feature>• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Nov. 2025) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die Honor Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notizen" type="end">
             <feature>1. Die Installation dieses Updates hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, es wird jedoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen
2. Entdecken Sie weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen in Tipps
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Honor-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein Honor-Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1031" name="de-ch">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung verbessert hauptsächlich die Systemleistung. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Aufnahme bei ausgeschaltetem Bildschirm ist jetzt verfügbar. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Kamera > Einstellungen > Aufnahme bei ausgeschaltetem Bildschirm</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Startbildschirm">
             <feature>• Der Transparenzmodus optimiert die Transparenzeffekte von Elementen wie Karten und Ordnern und sorgt so für ein außergewöhnliches Anzeigeerlebnis. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Startbildschirm und Stil > Startbildschirmeinstellungen > Transparenzmodus</feature>
             <feature>• Drücken Sie eine leere Stelle auf dem Startbildschirm lange, um die Bearbeitung zu starten</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bildschirm sperren">
             <feature>• Der Sperrbildschirm bietet mehr Uhrenstile. Ziehen Sie den Sperrbildschirm mit zwei Fingern zusammen, tippen Sie auf Benutzerdefiniert und tippen Sie dann zum Bearbeiten auf die Uhr</feature>
             <feature>• Ein taktiler Lichteffekt reagiert auf Ihr Tippen auf dem Bildschirm zum Entsperren des Passworts und im Kontrollzentrum</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Statusleiste">
             <feature>• Statusleiste ermöglicht die Anpassung von Symbolen, sodass Sie wählen können, welche Symbole in der Statusleiste angezeigt werden sollen. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Benachrichtigungen &amp; Statusleiste > Statusleiste</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic Capsule">
             <feature>• Gesichtserkennung ist in Magic Capsule integriert. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Benachrichtigungen &amp; Statusleiste > Magic Capsule > Gesichtserkennung</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Ein Tastendruck ermöglicht eine nahtlose Dateiübertragung zwischen Honor-Geräten und kombiniert dabei Geschwindigkeit mit Leichtigkeit und Spaß. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Weitere Verbindungen > Ein Tastendruck</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Leistung">
             <feature>• Behebt gelegentlich auftretende Probleme mit Ruckeln, um die allgemeine Laufruhe des Geräts zu verbessern</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilität">
             <feature>• Verbessert die Systemstabilität</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sicherheitspatch">
             <feature>• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Nov. 2025) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die Honor Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notizen" type="end">
             <feature>1. Die Installation dieses Updates hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, es wird jedoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen
2. Entdecken Sie weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen in Tipps
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Honor-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein Honor-Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1036" name="fr-ch">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour améliore principalement les performances du système. Effectuez la mise à jour pour profiter des améliorations</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Appareil photo">
             <feature>• Enregistrement écran éteint est désormais disponible. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Appareil photo > Paramètres > Enregistrement écran éteint</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Écran d'accueil">
             <feature>• Le mode transparence optimise les effets de transparence d'éléments tels que les cartes et les dossiers, procurant une expérience visuelle exceptionnelle. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Écran d'accueil et style > Paramètres de l'écran d'accueil > Mode transparence</feature>
             <feature>• Appuyez longuement sur la zone vide de l'écran d'accueil pour commencer la modification</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Écran verrouillé">
             <feature>• L'écran verrouillé propose plus de styles d'horloge. Pincez avec deux doigts sur l'écran verrouillé, appuyez sur Personnaliser, puis appuyez sur l'horloge pour la modifier</feature>
             <feature>• Un effet lumineux tactile répond à votre appui sur l'écran de déverrouillage du mot de passe et dans le Centre de contrôle</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Barre d'état">
             <feature>• La barre d'état autorise la personnalisation des icônes, vous permettant de choisir les icônes à afficher dans la barre d'état. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Notifications et barre d'état > Barre d'état</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic Capsule">
             <feature>• Reconnaissance faciale est intégrée à Magic Capsule. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Notifications et barre d'état > Magic Capsule > Reconnaissance faciale</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap permet des transferts de fichiers transparents entre les appareils Honor, associant vitesse, facilité et plaisir. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Plus de paramètres de connectivité > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Intensité d'utilisation">
             <feature>• Résout les problèmes occasionnels de saccades pour améliorer la fluidité globale de l'appareil</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilité">
             <feature>• Améliore la stabilité du système</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Correctif de sécurité">
             <feature>• Un correctif de sécurité Android (novembre 2025) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité Honor, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour
2. Découvrez plus d'informations sur les fonctionnalités du produit dans Astuces
3. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes pendant la mise à jour, vous pouvez obtenir de l'aide en contactant la hotline de service Honor ou en vous rendant dans un centre de services clients Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1040" name="it-ch">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento migliora principalmente le prestazioni del sistema. Esegui l'aggiornamento per usufruire dei miglioramenti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fotocamera">
             <feature>• È ora disponibile Registrazione a schermo spento. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Fotocamera > Impostazioni > Registrazione a schermo spento</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Schermata Home">
             <feature>• La modalità trasparenza ottimizza gli effetti di trasparenza di elementi quali schede e cartelle, offrendo un'esperienza visiva eccezionale. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Schermata Home e stile > Impostazioni schermata Home > Modalità trasparenza</feature>
             <feature>• Premi a lungo l'area vuota della schermata Home per iniziare a modificare</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Blocca schermo">
             <feature>• La schermata di blocco offre più stili di orologio. Avvicina due dita sulla schermata di blocco, tocca Personalizzato, quindi tocca l'orologio per modificare</feature>
             <feature>• Un effetto luminoso tattile risponde al tocco sulla schermata di sblocco con la password e nel Centro di controllo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Barra di stato">
             <feature>• La barra di stato consente di personalizzare le icone, consentendo di scegliere le icone della barra di stato da visualizzare. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Notifiche e barra di stato > Barra di stato</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Capsula Magica">
             <feature>• Riconoscimento del viso è integrato in Magic Capsule. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Notifiche e barra di stato > Magic Capsule > Riconoscimento del viso</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• OneTap consente il trasferimento ottimale di file tra dispositivi Honor, abbinando velocità, semplicità e divertimento. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Altre connessioni > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Prestazioni">
             <feature>• Vengono risolti i problemi occasionali di immagini a scatto per migliorare la fluidità complessiva del dispositivo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilità">
             <feature>• Viene migliorata la stabilità del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch di sicurezza">
             <feature>• È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (novembre 2025) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza Honor, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Note" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup dei dati prima di procedere
2. Scopri ulteriori informazioni sulle funzioni del prodotto in Suggerimenti
3. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center Honor o visitando un centro servizio clienti Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2074" name="sr-ba">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se unapređuju performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u unapređenjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Snimanje sa isključenim ekranom je sada dostupno. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Kamera > Podešavanja > Snimanje sa isključenim ekranom</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Početni ekran">
             <feature>• Režim providnosti optimizuje efekte providnosti elemenata kao što su kartice i fascikle, pružajući izuzetno vizuelno iskustvo. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Početni ekran i stil > Podešavanja početnog ekrana > Režim providnosti</feature>
             <feature>• Dugo pritisnite prazno područje početnog ekrana da biste započeli uređivanje</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zaključani ekran">
             <feature>• Zaključani ekran nudi više stilova sata. Primaknite dva prsta na zaključanom ekranu, dodirnite Prilagođeno, a zatim dodirnite sat da biste menjali</feature>
             <feature>• Taktilni svetlosni efekat reaguje na vaš dodir na ekranu za otključavanje lozinkom i u Kontrolnom centru</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Statusna traka">
             <feature>• Statusna traka omogućava prilagođavanje ikona, omogućavajući vam da izaberete koje ikone statusne trake želite da prikažete. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Obaveštenja i statusna traka > Statusna traka</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magična kapsula">
             <feature>• Prepoznavanje lica je integrisano u Magičnu kapsulu. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Obaveštenja i statusna traka > Magična kapsula > Prepoznavanje lica</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Povezivanje">
             <feature>• OneTap omogućava besprekoran prenos datoteka između Honor uređaja, kombinujući brzinu sa lakoćom i zabavom. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Još veza > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Učinak">
             <feature>• Rešava povremene probleme sa isprekidanim radom kako bi se poboljšalo ukupno nesmetano funkcionisanje uređaja</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Poboljšava stabilnost sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezbednosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Android bezbednosna zakrpa (novembar 2025.) je integrisana radi bezbednosti sistema. Za još informacija o Honor bezbednosnim ažuriranjima, posetite naš veb-sajt https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zabeleške" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka pre ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o karakteristikama proizvoda u odeljku Saveti
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete dobiti našu pomoć pozivom dežurne linije kompanije Honor ili posetom centru za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2074" name="sr-me">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se unapređuju performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u unapređenjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Snimanje sa isključenim ekranom je sada dostupno. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Kamera > Podešavanja > Snimanje sa isključenim ekranom</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Početni ekran">
             <feature>• Režim providnosti optimizuje efekte providnosti elemenata kao što su kartice i fascikle, pružajući izuzetno vizuelno iskustvo. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Početni ekran i stil > Podešavanja početnog ekrana > Režim providnosti</feature>
             <feature>• Dugo pritisnite prazno područje početnog ekrana da biste započeli uređivanje</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zaključani ekran">
             <feature>• Zaključani ekran nudi više stilova sata. Primaknite dva prsta na zaključanom ekranu, dodirnite Prilagođeno, a zatim dodirnite sat da biste menjali</feature>
             <feature>• Taktilni svetlosni efekat reaguje na vaš dodir na ekranu za otključavanje lozinkom i u Kontrolnom centru</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Statusna traka">
             <feature>• Statusna traka omogućava prilagođavanje ikona, omogućavajući vam da izaberete koje ikone statusne trake želite da prikažete. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Obaveštenja i statusna traka > Statusna traka</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magična kapsula">
             <feature>• Prepoznavanje lica je integrisano u Magičnu kapsulu. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Obaveštenja i statusna traka > Magična kapsula > Prepoznavanje lica</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Povezivanje">
             <feature>• OneTap omogućava besprekoran prenos datoteka između Honor uređaja, kombinujući brzinu sa lakoćom i zabavom. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Još veza > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Učinak">
             <feature>• Rešava povremene probleme sa isprekidanim radom kako bi se poboljšalo ukupno nesmetano funkcionisanje uređaja</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Poboljšava stabilnost sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezbednosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Android bezbednosna zakrpa (novembar 2025.) je integrisana radi bezbednosti sistema. Za još informacija o Honor bezbednosnim ažuriranjima, posetite naš veb-sajt https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zabeleške" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka pre ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o karakteristikama proizvoda u odeljku Saveti
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete dobiti našu pomoć pozivom dežurne linije kompanije Honor ili posetom centru za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1057" name="id-">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini utamanya meningkatkan kinerja sistem. Instal pembaruan untuk menikmati berbagai peningkatan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kamera">
             <feature>• Perekaman saat layar mati kini tersedia. Cobalah dengan membuka: Kamera > Pengaturan > Perekaman saat layar mati</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Layar beranda">
             <feature>• Mode transparansi mengoptimalkan efek tembus pandang pada elemen seperti kartu dan folder sehingga menghadirkan pengalaman visual yang menakjubkan. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Gaya &amp; layar beranda > Pengaturan layar beranda > Mode transparansi</feature>
             <feature>• Tekan lama area kosong pada layar beranda untuk mulai mengedit</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Layar kunci">
             <feature>• Layar kunci menawarkan lebih banyak gaya jam. Jepit dengan dua jari di layar kunci, ketuk Khusus, lalu ketuk jam untuk mengedit</feature>
             <feature>• Efek cahaya taktil yang merespons ketukan Anda di layar buka kunci dengan kata sandi dan di Pusat Kontrol</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bilah status">
             <feature>• Bilah status memungkinkan penyesuaian ikon, sehingga Anda dapat memilih ikon bilah status untuk ditampilkan. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Notifikasi &amp; bilah status > Bilah status</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kapsul Ajaib">
             <feature>• Pengenalan wajah terintegrasi dalam Kapsul Ajaib. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Notifikasi &amp; bilah status > Kapsul Ajaib > Pengenalan wajah</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Koneksi">
             <feature>• OneTap memungkinkan transfer file yang lancar antarperangkat Honor. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Koneksi lainnya > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kinerja">
             <feature>• Menyelesaikan masalah tersendat yang terjadi sesekali untuk meningkatkan kelancaran perangkat secara keseluruhan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitas">
             <feature>• Meningkatkan stabilitas sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Penambal keamanan">
             <feature>• Penambal Keamanan Android (Nov 2025) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan Honor, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Catatan" type="end">
             <feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan untuk mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui
2. Pelajari informasi selengkapnya terkait fitur produk di Kiat
3. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan Honor atau mengunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1037" name="he-">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה משפר בעיקר את ביצועי המערכת. עדכן כדי ליהנות מהשיפורים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="מצלמה">
             <feature>‏‏• הקלטה במצב מסך כבוי זמינה כעת. כדי לנסות אותה, אפשר לעבור אל: 'מצלמה' > 'הגדרות' > 'הקלטה במצב מסך כבוי'</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="מסך הבית">
             <feature>‏• מצב 'שקיפות' ממטב את אפקטי השקיפות של אלמנטים כמו כרטיסים ותיקיות, לחוויה חזותית יוצאת מן הכלל. כדי לנסות אותו, אפשר לעבור אל: הגדרות > מסך הבית וסגנון > הגדרות מסך הבית > מצב 'שקיפות'</feature>
             <feature>‏• כדי להתחיל לערוך, לחץ לחיצה ארוכה על השטח הריק במסך הבית</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="מסך נעילה">
             <feature>‏‏• מסך הנעילה מציע סגנונות שעון נוספים. צבוט בשתי אצבעות במסך הנעילה, הקש על האפשרות 'מותאם אישית', ואז הקש על השעון כדי לערוך</feature>
             <feature>‏‏• אפקט אור מישושי מגיב להקשה על מסך ביטול הנעילה באמצעות סיסמה, וגם ב'מרכז בקרה'</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="שורת מצב">
             <feature>‏• שורת המצב מאפשרת התאמה אישית של סמלים, וכך ניתן לבחור אילו סמלים יופיעו בשורת המצב. כדי לנסות זאת, אפשר לעבור אל: הגדרות > התראות ושורת המצב > שורת מצב</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏קפסולת קסם">
             <feature>‏• התכונה 'זיהוי פנים' משולבת ב'קפסולת קסם'. כדי לנסות זאת, אפשר לעבור אל: הגדרות > התראות ושורת המצב > ‏קפסולת קסם > זיהוי פנים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏Honor Connect">
             <feature>‏‏• ‏OneTap מאפשר העברת קבצים חלקה בין התקני Honor, והוא נותן תפקוד מהיר, קל ומהנה. כדי לנסות אותו, אפשר לעבור אל: 'הגדרות' > 'עוד חיבורים' > ‏OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ביצועים">
             <feature>‏‏• פותר את הבעיה של תפקוד תקוע מדי פעם, לשיפור של פעולת ההתקן החלקה באופן כללי</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="יציבות">
             <feature>‏‏• משפר את יציבות המערכת</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="תיקון אבטחה">
             <feature>‏• 'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מנוב' 2025) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של Honor', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="הערות" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון
‏2. גלה מידע נוסף על תכונות המוצר ב'טיפים'
‏3. אם תיתקל בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, ניתן לקבל עזרה מאיתנו באמצעות התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של Honor או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1124" name="fil-ph">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Minamahal na user, pangunahing pinapahusay ng update na ito ang performance ng system. I-update para i-enjoy ang mga pagpapahusay</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Camera">
             <feature>• Available na ang Recording na naka-off ang screen. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Camera > Mga Setting > Recording na naka-off ang screen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Home screen">
             <feature>• Ino-optimize ang Transparency mode ang mga effect sa transparency ng mga element gaya ng mga card at folder, at naghahatid ng pinakamagandang visual na karanasan. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Home screen at estilo > Mga setting ng home screen > Transparency mode</feature>
             <feature>• Pindutin nang matagal ang blangkong bahagi ng home screen para simulang mag-edit</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Lock screen">
             <feature>• Nag-aalok ang lock screen ng mas maraming estilo ng orasan. I-pinch gamit ang dalawang daliri sa lock screen, i-tap ang Custom, pagkatapos ay i-tap ang orasan para i-edit</feature>
             <feature>• Tumutugon ang tactile light effect sa iyong pag-tap sa screen sa pag-unlock gamit ang password at sa Control Center</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Status bar">
             <feature>• Nagbibigay-daan ang Status bar sa pag-customize ng icon, na nagbibigay-daan sa iyong pumili kung aling mga icon ng status bar ang ipapakita. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Mga notification at status bar > Status bar</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Magic Capsule">
             <feature>• Kasama ang Pagtukoy ng mukha sa Magic Capsule. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Mga notification at status bar > Magic Capsule > Pagtukoy ng mukha</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Nagbibigay-daan ang OneTap sa tuluy-tuloy na paglilipat ng file sa pagitan ng mga Honor device, pinagsasama ang bilis at saya. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Higit pang koneksyon > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pagganap">
             <feature>• Nilulutas ang minsanang isyu ng paghintu-hinto para mapahusay ang kabuuang pagiging tuluy-tuloy ng device</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stability">
             <feature>• Pinapahusay ang stability ng system</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Panseguridad na patch">
             <feature>• Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Nob 2025) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa mga Panseguridad na update ng Honor, bisitahin ang aming website sa https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Mga Tala" type="end">
             <feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto ang pag-install sa update na ito sa iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update
2. Tuklasin ang higit pang impormasyon sa mga feature ng produkto sa Mga Tip
3. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, makukuha mo ang tulong namin sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng Honor o pagbisita sa customer service center ng Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <imgs>
            </imgs>
</root>