<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="NTH-LGRP1-CHN 5.0.0.13(SP10)"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<cleardata-flag>False</cleardata-flag>
<romsurvey-flag>False</romsurvey-flag>
<notify-level>40</notify-level>
<point-version>False</point-version>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>本次更新优化系统稳定性，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系统】">
<feature>优化系统稳定性。</feature>
</features>

<features module="媒体" id="1">
             <feature title="图库">•  新增清理建议功能，支持重复照片、相似图片、超大视频等自动识别，提供更便捷的清理建议</feature>
         </features><features module="通信社交" id="2">
             <feature title="通信">•  新增 AI 通话功能，不方便接听电话时，支持 AI 自动接听、打字回复，并自动生成 AI 通话纪要</feature>
         </features><features module="系统" id="3">
             <feature title="“收藏空间”升级为“YOYO 记忆”">•  通过 YOYO 对话、三指下滑、应用内收藏同步等多种方式帮您快捷记录信息，YOYO 对话可随时快速查找 (荣耀 AI • 基础服务需更新到最新版本)</feature>
             <feature title="任意门">•  指关节圈选开门新增文字复制功能</feature>
             <feature title="智慧多窗">•  支持更多应用横幅通知下滑进入悬浮窗</feature>
             <feature title="截屏">•  滚动截屏过程中支持手动调整截屏范围</feature>
             <feature title="显示">•  休眠时间新增 30 分钟和 1 小时选项</feature>
             <feature title="锁屏">•  新增锁屏显示步数开关，支持关闭锁屏界面步数显示</feature>
             <feature title="铃声">•  系统铃声和在线铃声新增显性标签分类</feature>
         </features><features module="连接" id="4">
             <feature title="热点">•  个人热点 WLAN 协议新增 Wi-Fi 6(11ax)配置
•  个人热点自动关闭新增“从不”选项，支持个人热点永不关闭</feature>
             <feature title="蓝牙">•  已连接的蓝牙音频设备新增展示蓝牙音频编码</feature>
         </features><features module="安全" id="5">
             <feature title="安全补丁">•  合入安卓 2025 年 8 月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/8</feature>
         </features><features module="【相机】">
<feature>修复暗光长焦部分场景虚化不生效问题。
</feature>
</features><features module="【荣耀分享】">
<feature>修复跨品牌互传部分场景WLAN传输通道被占用问题。</feature>
</features><features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>This update improves the screen display in certain situations.</feature>
</features>
<features module="[Screen]">
<feature>Improves the screen display in certain situations.</feature>
</features>

<features module="Media" id="1">
             <feature title="Gallery">• Cleanup suggestions feature enables automatic identification of duplicate photos, similar images, and oversized videos, providing more convenient cleaning suggestions</feature>
         </features><features module="Communication and Social" id="2">
             <feature title="Communication">• AI Call allows you to select AI auto answer when it is inconvenient for you to answer the call. You can also choose to reply by texting. After the call, the call summary can be found in AI Call Notes</feature>
         </features><features module="System" id="3">
             <feature title="Upgrades Favorites Space to YOYO Memories">• You can quickly record information through various methods such as YOYO conversation, three-finger swipe down gesture, and syncing the content added to favorites within apps. YOYO conversation also allows you to quickly search for information at any time (Ensure that Honor AI Basic Services is updated to the latest version)</feature>
             <feature title="Magic Portal">• After using a knuckle gesture to circle the content and activate Magic Portal, you can copy the text within the circled area and paste it into the desired app via Magic Portal</feature>
             <feature title="Multi-Window">• You can swipe down on banner notifications from more apps to enter floating window mode</feature>
             <feature title="Screenshot">• You can manually adjust the screenshot range while taking a scrolling screenshot</feature>
             <feature title="Display">• You can now choose 30 minutes or 1 hour as the inactivity duration before the device enters Sleep mode</feature>
             <feature title="Lock screen">• Show steps on lock screen toggle allows you to disable the step count display on the lock screen</feature>
             <feature title="Ringtone">• Preset and Online ringtones are now labeled with tags</feature>
         </features><features module="Connect" id="4">
             <feature title="Hotspot">• The personal hotspot Wi-Fi protocol now includes a Wi-Fi 6 (11ax) configuration
• You can select Never to prevent the personal hotspot from turning off automatically, keeping it always on</feature>
             <feature title="Bluetooth">• The connected Bluetooth audio devices now show the Bluetooth audio codec</feature>
         </features><features module="Security" id="5">
             <feature title="Security patch">• Android security patch (Aug 2025) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about Honor Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/8</feature>
         </features><features module="Update notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. This update will not erase your personal data, but we recommend that you back up any important data before updating.
2. For more features, visit Tips.
</feature>
</features></language>

</root>