<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
    <component name="TCPU" version="请自行修改"/>
    <default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
        <language name="en-us" code="1033">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>This update includes the following resource files, which will improve the user experience of the system. Update to enjoy the improvements.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Speech synthesis detection model">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Speech synthesis detection model supports speech synthesis detection in Mandarin Chinese. This model can identify the synthesis risk of the current speech in audio calls.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="am-et" code="1118">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>ይህ ማሻሻያ የሚከተሉትን የመርጃ ፋይሎች ያካትታል፣ ይህም የስርዓቱን የተጠቃሚ ተሞክሮ ያሻሽላል። በማሻሻያዎቹ ለመደሰት ያዘምኑ።</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="የንግግር ማመንጨት ማወቂያ ሞዴል">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>የንግግር ማመንጨት ማወቂያ ሞዴል በመንደሪን ቻይንኛ የንግግር ማመንጨትን ማወቅን ይደግፋል። ይህ ሞዴል በድምጽ ጥሪዎች ውስጥ የአሁኑን ንግግር የማመንጨት ስጋትን መለየት ይችላል።</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>يتضمن هذا التحديث ملفات الموارد التالية، والتي من شأنها تحسين تجربة النظام من قِبل المستخدم. للاستمتاع بالتحسينات، ما عليك سوى التحديث.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="نموذج اكتشاف تركيب الكلام">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>يدعم نموذج اكتشاف تركيب الكلام اكتشاف تركيب الكلام بلغة الماندراين (الصينية). بإمكان هذا النموذج التعرف على مخاطر تركيب الكلام الحالي في المكالمات الصوتية.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="as-in" code="1101">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>এই আপডেটত নিম্নোক্ত সম্পদৰ ফাইলসমূহ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত আছে, যিয়ে ছিষ্টেমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ অভিজ্ঞতা উন্নত কৰিব। উন্নতিসমূহৰ আনন্দ ল\'বলৈ আপডেট কৰক।</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="স্পিচ্চ চিন্থেছিচ চিনাক্তকৰণ মডেল">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>স্পিচ্চ চিন্থেছিচ চিনাক্তকৰণ মডেলে মণ্ডাৰিন চীনাত স্পিচ্চ চিন্থেছিচ চিনাক্তকৰণ সমৰ্থন কৰে। এই মডেলে অডিঅ\' কলসমূহত সাম্প্ৰতিক স্পিচ্চৰ চিন্থেছিচ বিপদাশংকা চিনাক্ত কৰিব পাৰে।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="az-az" code="1068">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Bu yeniləməyə sistemin istifadəçi təcrübəsini yaxşılaşdıracaq aşağıdakı resurs faylları daxildir. Təkmilləşdirmələrdən zövq almaq üçün yeniləyin.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Nitq sintezinin aşkarlanması modeli">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Nitq sintezinin aşkarlanması modeli Mandarin Çin dilində nitq sintezinin aşkarlanmasını dəstəkləyir. Bu model audio zənglərdə cari nitqin sintez edilməsi riskini müəyyən edə bilər.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="jv-id" code="1033">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Panganyaran iki ngatutake file sumber daya ing ngisor iki, sing bakal ngapikake pangalaman pangguna babagan sistem. Anyarake kanggo ngrasakake pangapikan kasebut.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Model deteksi sintesis wicara">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Model deteksi sintesis wicara ndhukung deteksi sintesis wicara ing Basa Mandarin Tiongkok. Model iki bisa ngenali risiko sintesis wicara sing saiki sajrone telpon audio.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Ovo ažuriranje uključuje sledeće datoteke s resursima, što će poboljšati korisničko iskustvo sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u poboljšanjima.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Model otkrivanja sinteze govora">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Model otkrivanja sinteze govora podržava otkrivanje sinteze govora na mandarinskom kineskom. Ovaj model može da prepozna rizik od sinteze trenutnog govora u audio pozivima.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="be-by" code="1059">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Гэта абнаўленне ўключае наступныя файлы рэсурсаў, якія палепшаць уражанні ад выкарыстання сістэмы. Абнавіце, каб атрымаць паляпшэнні.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Мадэль выяўлення сінтэзу маўлення">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Мадэль выяўлення сінтэзу маўлення падтрымлівае выяўленне сінтэзу маўлення на мандарынскім дыялекце кітайскай мовы. Гэта мадэль можа ідэнтыфікаваць рызыку сінтэзу мовы ў бягучых аўдыявыкліках.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Тази актуализация включва следните файлове с ресурси, които ще подобрят работата на потребителите със системата. Актуализирайте, за да се насладите на подобренията.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Модел на засичане на синтез на реч">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Моделът на засичане на синтез на реч поддържа засичане на синтез на реч на китайски Мандарин. Този модел може да идентифицира риска от синтез на текущата реч в аудио обажданията.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="bn-bd" code="2117">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>এই আপডেটে নিম্নলিখিত রিসোর্স ফাইলগুলি অন্তর্ভুক্ত রয়েছে, যা সিস্টেমের ব্যবহারকারীর অভিজ্ঞতাকে উন্নত করবে। উন্নতি উপভোগ করতে আপডেট করুন।</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="স্পিচ সিনথেসিস শনাক্তকরণ মডেল">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>স্পিচ সিনথেসিস শনাক্তকরণ মডেল ম্যান্ডারিন চীনা ভাষায় স্পিচ সিনথেসিস শনাক্তকরণকে সমর্থন করে। এই মডেলটি অডিও কলে বর্তমান স্পিচের সিনথেসিসের ঝুঁকি শনাক্ত করতে পারে।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Ovo ažuriranje uključuje sljedeće datoteke s resursima, što će poboljšati korisničko iskustvo sistema. Ažurirajte da uživate u poboljšanjima.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Model otkrivanja sinteze govora">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Model otkrivanja sinteze govora podržava otkrivanje sinteze govora na mandarinskom kineskom. Ovaj model može prepoznati rizik od sinteze trenutnog govora u audio pozivima.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="ca-es" code="1027">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Aquesta actualització inclou els següents fitxers de recursos, els quals milloraran l\'experiència d\'usuari del sistema. Instal·leu l\'actualització per gaudir de les millores.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Model de detecció de síntesi de veu">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>El model de detecció de síntesi de veu admet la detecció en xinès mandarí. Aquest model pot identificar el risc de síntesi de la veu actual en trucades d\'àudio.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Tato aktualizace obsahuje následující soubory zdrojů, které zlepší uživatelské prostředí systému. Aktualizujte, abyste si mohli užít vylepšení.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Model detekce syntézy řeči">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Model detekce syntézy řeči podporuje detekci syntézy řeči v mandarínské čínštině. Tento model dokáže identifikovat riziko syntézy aktuální řeči v audio hovorech.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="da-dk" code="1030">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Denne opdatering inkluderer følgende ressourcefiler, som forbedrer brugeroplevelsen med systemet. Opdater for at nyde forbedringerne.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Registreringsmodel for talesyntese">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Registreringsmodellen for talesyntese understøtter registrering af talesyntese på mandarin. Denne model kan identificere synteserisikoen for den aktuelle tale i lydopkald.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="de-de" code="1031">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Diese Aktualisierung enthält die folgenden Ressourcendateien, die das Benutzererlebnis mit dem System verbessern. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Modell zur Erkennung der Sprachsynthese">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Das Modell zur Erkennung der Sprachsynthese unterstützt die Erkennung der Sprachsynthese in Chinesisch (Mandarin). Dieses Modell kann das Syntheserisiko der aktuellen Sprache in Sprachanrufen identifizieren.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="el-gr" code="1032">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Αυτή η ενημέρωση περιλαμβάνει τα ακόλουθα αρχεία πόρων, τα οποία θα βελτιώσουν την εμπειρία χρήστη του συστήματος. Πραγματοποιήστε ενημέρωση για να απολαύσετε τις βελτιώσεις.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Μοντέλο ανίχνευσης σύνθεσης ομιλίας">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Το μοντέλο ανίχνευσης σύνθεσης ομιλίας υποστηρίζει την ανίχνευση σύνθεσης ομιλίας στα Μανδαρινικά Κινέζικα. Αυτό το μοντέλο μπορεί να αναγνωρίσει τον κίνδυνο σύνθεσης της τρέχουσας ομιλίας σε ηχητικές κλήσεις.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="en-gb" code="2057">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>This update includes the following resource files, which will improve the user experience of the system. Update to enjoy the improvements.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Speech synthesis detection model">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Speech synthesis detection model supports speech synthesis detection in Mandarin Chinese. This model can identify the synthesis risk of the current speech in audio calls.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="es-es" code="1034">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Esta actualización incluye los siguientes archivos de recursos, que mejorarán la experiencia del usuario del sistema. Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Modelo de detección de síntesis de voz">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>El modelo de detección de síntesis de voz admite la detección de síntesis de voz en chino mandarín. Este modelo puede identificar el riesgo de síntesis del habla actual en llamadas de audio.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="es-us" code="21514">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Esta actualización incluye los siguientes archivos de recursos, que mejorarán la experiencia del usuario en el sistema.  Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Modelo de detección de síntesis de voz">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>El modelo de detección de síntesis de voz admite la detección de síntesis de voz en chino mandarín.  Este modelo puede identificar el riesgo de síntesis de voz actual en llamadas de audio.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="et-ee" code="1061">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>See värskendus sisaldab järgmisi ressursifaile, mis parendavad süsteemi kasutajakogemust. Värskendage täiustuste nautimiseks.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Kõnesünteesi tuvastamise mudel">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Kõnesünteesi tuvastamise mudel toetab kõnesünteesi tuvastamist mandariini hiina keeles. See mudel suudab audiokõnedes tuvastada praeguse kõne sünteesiriski.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="eu-es" code="1069">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Eguneratze honek baliabide-fitxategi hauek ditu, eta sistemaren erabiltzaile-esperientzia hobetzeko balioko dute. Eguneratu hobekuntzez gozatzeko.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Hizketa sintetizatua detektatzeko eredua">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Hizketa sintetizatua detektatzeko ereduak hizketa sintetizatua detektatzeko onartzen du txinera mandarineran. Eredu honek audio-deietan uneko hizketa sintetizatua izateko arriskurik dagoen identifika dezake.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>این به‌روزرسانی شامل فایل‌های منبع زیر است که تجربه کاربر سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد. برای بهره‌مندی از این بهبودها، به‌روزرسانی را انجام دهید.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="مدل شناسایی تولید گفتار">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>مدل شناسایی تولید گفتار از شناسایی تولید گفتار به زبان چینی ماندارین پشتیبانی می‌کند. این مدل می‌تواند خطر صداسازی در مکالمات صوتی در جریان را شناسایی کند.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Tämä päivitys sisältää seuraavat resurssitiedostot, jotka parantavat järjestelmän käyttökokemusta. Päivitä, niin pääset nauttimaan parannuksista.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Puhesynteesin tunnistusmalli">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Puhesynteesin tunnistusmalli tukee puhesynteesin tunnistusta mandariinikiinaksi. Tämä malli voi tunnistaa nykyisen puheen synteesiriskin äänipuheluissa.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Cette mise à jour comprend les fichiers de ressources suivants, qui amélioreront l\'expérience utilisateur du système. Effectuez la mise à jour pour profiter des améliorations.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Modèle de détection de synthèse vocale">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Le modèle de détection de synthèse vocale prend en charge la détection de synthèse vocale en chinois mandarin. Ce modèle permet d\'identifier le risque de synthèse de la parole actuelle dans les appels audio.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="gl-es" code="1110">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Esta actualización inclúe os seguintes ficheiros de recursos que mellorarán a experiencia do usuario no sistema. Actualice para gozar das melloras.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Modelo de detección de síntese de voz">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>O modelo de detección de síntese de voz é compatible coa detección de síntese de voz en chinés mandarín. Este modelo pode identificar o risco de síntese da voz actual nas chamadas de audio.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="gu-in" code="1095">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>આ અપડેટમાં નીચેની સંસાધન ફાઇલો શામેલ છે, જે સિસ્ટમના વપરાશકર્તા અનુભવને સુધારશે. સુધારાઓનો આનંદ માણવા માટે અપડેટ કરો.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="સ્પીચ સિન્થેસિસ ડિટેક્શન મોડેલ">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>સ્પીચ સિન્થેસિસ ડિટેક્શન મોડેલ મેન્ડરિન ચાઇનીઝમાં સ્પીચ સિન્થેસિસ ડિટેક્શનનું સમર્થન કરે છે. આ મોડેલ ઑડિયો કૉલ્સમાં વર્તમાન સ્પીચના સિન્થેસિસ જોખમને ઓળખી શકે છે.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="hi-in" code="1081">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>इस अद्यतन में निम्न संसाधन फ़ाइलें शामिल हैं जिनसे सिस्टम का उपयोगकर्ता अनुभव बेहतर हो जाएगा। सुधारों का फ़ायदा उठाने के लिए अद्यतन करें।</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="बोली संश्लेषण पहचान मॉडल">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>बोली संश्लेषण पहचान मॉडल में मंडारिन चीनी में बोली संश्लेषण पहचान का समर्थन किया जाता है। इस मॉडल से ऑडियो कॉल में वर्तमान बोली के संश्लेषण जोखिम की पहचान हो सकती है।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Ovo ažuriranje uključuje datoteke resursa navedene u nastavku koje će poboljšati korisničko iskustvo upotrebe sustava. Ažurirajte kako biste uživali u poboljšanjima.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Model otkrivanja sinteze govora">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Model otkrivanja sinteze govora podržava otkrivanje sinteze govora na mandarinskom kineskom. Ovaj model može prepoznati rizik sinteze trenutačnog govora u audiopozivima.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Ez a frissítés a következő erőforrásfájlokat tartalmazza, amelyek javítják a rendszer felhasználói élményét. Végezze el a frissítést, hogy élvezhesse a továbbfejlesztéseket.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Beszédszintézis-észlelési modell">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>A beszédszintézis-észlelési modell támogatja a beszédszintézis észlelését kínai mandarin nyelven. Ez a modell képes azonosítani az aktuális beszéd szintéziskockázatát a hanghívásokban.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="in-id" code="1057">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Pembaruan ini menyertakan file sumber daya berikut yang akan meningkatkan pengalaman pengguna sistem. Instal pembaruan ini untuk menikmati berbagai peningkatan.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Model deteksi sintesis suara">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Model deteksi sintesis suara mendukung deteksi sintesis suara dalam bahasa Mandarin (Tionghoa). Model ini dapat mengidentifikasi risiko sintesis suara saat ini dalam panggilan audio.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="it-it" code="1040">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Questo aggiornamento include i seguenti file di risorse, che miglioreranno l\'esperienza utente del sistema. Esegui l\'aggiornamento per usufruire dei miglioramenti.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Modello di rilevamento della sintesi vocale">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Il modello di rilevamento della sintesi vocale supporta il rilevamento della sintesi vocale in cinese mandarino. Questo modello è in grado di identificare il rischio di sintesi del parlato corrente nelle chiamate audio.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="iw-il" code="1037">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>עדכון זה כולל את קובצי המשאבים הבאים, שישפרו את חוויית המשתמש של המערכת. עדכן כדי ליהנות מהשיפורים.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="מודל גילוי סינתזת דיבור">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>מודל גילוי סינתזת דיבור תומך בגילוי סינתזת דיבור בסינית מנדרינית. מודל זה יכול לזהות את הסיכון לסינתזה של הדיבור הנוכחי בשיחות שמע.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="ja-jp" code="1041">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>今回の更新には以下のリソースファイルが含まれます。これによってシステムのユーザー体験が向上します。更新して、改善をお楽しみください。</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="音声合成検出モデル">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>音声合成検出モデルでは、中国標準語での音声合成検出がサポートされています。このモデルは、音声通話での現在の音声の合成リスクを識別できます。</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="ka-ge" code="1079">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>ეს განახლება მოიცავს შემდეგ რესურს-ფაილებს, რომლებიც გააუმჯობესებს სისტემის მუშაობას. განაახლეთ, რომ ისარგებლოთ გაუმჯობესებებით.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="მეტყველების სინთეზის გამოვლენის მოდელი">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>მეტყველების სინთეზის გამოვლენის მოდელს აქვს მეტყველების სინთეზის გამოვლენის მხარდაჭერა მანდარინულ ჩინურზე. ამ მოდელს შეუძლია აუდიოზარებში მიმდინარე მეტყველების სინთეზის რისკის იდენტიფიცირება.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="kk-kz" code="1087">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Бұл жаңарту жүйенің пайдаланушы тәжірибесін жақсартатын келесі ресурс файлдарын қамтиды. Жақсартуларды пайдалану үшін жаңартыңыз.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Сөйлеу синтезін анықтау моделі">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Сөйлеу синтезін анықтау моделі мандарин қытай тілінде сөйлеу синтезін анықтауға қолдау көрсетеді. Бұл модель дыбыстық қоңыраулардағы ағымдағы сөздің синтездеу қаупін анықтай алады.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="km-kh" code="1107">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>ការធ្វេីបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះរួមបញ្ចូលឯកសារធនធានខាងក្រោម ដែលនឹងធ្វើឱ្យប្រសើរឡើងនូវបទពិសោធអ្នកប្រើប្រាស់លេីប្រព័ន្ធ។ ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពដើម្បីរីករាយនឹងការកែលម្អ។</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="គំរូការរកឃើញការសំយោគការនិយាយ">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>គំរូការរកឃើញការសំយោគការនិយាយគាំទ្រការរកឃើញការសំយោគការនិយាយជាភាសាចិនកុកងឺ។ គំរូនេះអាចកំណត់អត្តសញ្ញាណហានិភ័យនៃការសំយោគនៃការនិយាយបច្ចុប្បន្ននៅក្នុងការហៅទូរស័ព្ទជាសំឡេង។</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="kn-in" code="1099">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಈ ಕೆಳಗಿನ ಸಂಪನ್ಮೂಲ ಫೈಲ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಒಳಗೊಂಡಿದ್ದು, ಇದು ಸಿಸ್ಟಂನ ಬಳಕೆದಾರ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ಸುಧಾರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಸುಧಾರಣೆಗಳನ್ನು ಆನಂದಿಸಲು ನವೀಕರಿಸಿ.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="ಮಾತು ಸಂಶ್ಲೇಷಣೆ ಪತ್ತೆ ಮಾದರಿ">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>ಮಾತು ಸಂಶ್ಲೇಷಣೆ ಪತ್ತೆ ಮಾದರಿಯು ಮ್ಯಾಂಡರಿನ್ ಚೈನೀಸ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಮಾತು ಸಂಶ್ಲೇಷಣೆ ಪತ್ತೆಯನ್ನು ಬೆಂಬಲಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಈ ಮಾದರಿಯು ಆಡಿಯೋ ಕರೆಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಪ್ರಸ್ತುತ ಮಾತಿನ ಸಂಶ್ಲೇಷಣೆಯ ಅಪಾಯವನ್ನು ಗುರುತಿಸಬಹುದು.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="ko-kr" code="1042">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>다음 리소스 파일이 이 업데이트에 포함되어 있어 시스템의 사용자 경험을 개선할 수 있습니다. 업데이트하고 개선된 기능을 즐겨보십시오.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="음성 합성 감지 모델">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>음성 합성 감지 모델은 중국어(북경어)의 음성 합성 감지를 지원합니다. 이 모델은 음성 통화에서 현재 음성의 합성 위험을 식별할 수 있습니다.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="lo-la" code="1108">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>ການ​ອັບ​ເດດນີ້​​ລວມ​ມີ​ໄຟ​ລ໌​ຕົ້ນ​ສະ​ບັບ​ຕໍ່​ໄປ​​ນີ້, ເຊິ່ງ​ຈະ​ປັບ​ປຸງ​ປະ​​ສົບ​ການ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້​ຂອງ​ລະ​ບົບ. ອັບ​ເດດ​ເພື່ອ​ມ່ວ​ນ​ຊື່​ນກັບ​ການ​ປັບ​ປຸງ.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="ໂມ​ເດ​ລ​ການກວດ​ຫາການ​ສັງ​ເຄາະສຽງ​ເວົ້າ">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>ໂມ​ເດ​ລ​ການກວດ​ຫາການ​ສັງ​ເຄາະສຽງ​ເວົ້າຮອງ​ຮັບ​ການກວດ​ຫາ​ການ​ສັງ​ເຄາະ​ສຽງ​ເວົ້າ​ໃນ​ຈີນ​ແຜ່ນ​ດິນ​ໃຫຍ່. ໂມ​ເດ​ລ​ນີ້​ສາ​ມາດ​ລະ​ບຸ​ຄວາມ​ສ່ຽງ​ການ​ສັງ​ເຄາະ​ສຽງ​ເວົ້າ​ປັດ​ຈຸ​ບັນ​ໃນ​ການ​ໂທ​ສຽງ.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Į šį atnaujinimą įtraukti toliau nurodyti išteklių failai, kurie pagerina sistemos naudojimo patirtį. Atnaujinkite ir mėgaukitės patobulinimais.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Kalbos sintezės aptikimo modelis">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Kalbos sintezės aptikimo modelis palaiko kalbos sintezės aptikimą mandarinų kalba. Šis modelis gali nustatyti dabartinės kalbos sintezės riziką balso skambučiuose.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Ar šo atjauninājumu ir ietverti tālāk norādītie resursu faili, kas uzlabos sistēmas lietotāja pieredzi. Atjauniniet, lai izbaudītu uzlabojumus.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Runas sintēzes noteikšanas modelis">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Runas sintēzes noteikšanas modelis atbalsta runas sintēzes noteikšanu mandarīnu ķīniešu valodā. Šis modelis var noteikt pašreizējās runas sintēzes risku audio zvanos.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="mai-in" code="1033">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>एहि अपडेट मे निम्नलिखित संसाधन फाइल सभ सम्मिलित अछि, जे सिस्टमक उपयोगकर्ता अनुभव केँ बेसी नीक बनाओत। सुधार सभक आनंद लेबाक लेल अपडेट करू।</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="स्पीच संश्लेषण पहिचान मॉडल">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>स्पीच संश्लेषण पहिचान मॉडल मंदारिन चीनी मे स्पीच संश्लेषण पहिचान केँ सपोर्ट करैत अछि। ई मॉडल ऑडियो कॉल मे वर्तमान स्पीच केर संश्लेषण जोखिम केर पहिचान कए सकैत अछि।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="mi-nz" code="1153">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Kei roto i tēnei whakahoutanga ngā kōnae rauemi e whai ake nei, hei whakapai ake i te wheako kaiwhakamahi o te pūnaha. Whakahoutia kia pai ai te whakapai ake.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Tauira kitenga kōtuinga reo ā-waha">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>E tautoko ana te tauira kitenga kōtuinga reo ā-waha i te kitenga kōtuinga reo ā-waha i te Hainamana Mandarin. Ka taea e tēnei tāutu te tautuhi i te mōrea whakahiato o te kōrero onāianei i roto i ngā waea ororongo.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Ова ажурирање ги вклучува следниве датотеки со ресурси, што може да го подобрат корисничкото искуство со системот. Ажурирајте за да уживате во подобрувањата.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Модел за откривање синтеза на говор">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Моделот за откривање синтеза на говор поддржува откривање синтеза на говор на мандарински кинески јазик. Овој модел може да го открие ризикот од синтеза на постојниот говор во аудиоповици.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="ml-in" code="1100">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിൽ ഇനിപ്പറയുന്ന ഉറവിട ഫയലുകൾ ഉൾപ്പെടുന്നു, ഇത് സിസ്റ്റത്തിന്റെ ഉപയോക്തൃ അനുഭവം മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തും. മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തലുകൾ ആസ്വദിക്കാൻ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="സ്പീച്ച് സിന്തസിസ് കണ്ടെത്തൽ മോഡൽ">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>സ്പീച്ച് സിന്തസിസ് കണ്ടെത്തൽ മോഡൽ മാൻഡരിൻ ചൈനീസിലെ സ്പീച്ച് സിന്തസിസ് കണ്ടെത്തലിനെ പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കുന്നു. ഈ മോഡലിന് ഓഡിയോ കോളുകളിലെ നിലവിലെ സംഭാഷണത്തിന്റെ സിന്തസിസ് അപകടസാധ്യത തിരിച്ചറിയാൻ കഴിയും.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="mn-mn" code="1104">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Энэ шинэчлэлтээр дараах нөөц файлуудыг багтаасан бөгөөд эдгээр нь системийг хэрэглэх хэрэглэгчийн туршлагыг сайжруулна. Шинэчлээд, сайжруулсан хэрэглээг мэдрээрэй.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Нийлэгжүүлсэн яриаг илрүүлэх загвар">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Нийлэгжүүлсэн яриаг илрүүлэх загвар мандарин хятад хэлээр нийлэгжүүлсэн яриаг илрүүлэхийг дэмждэг. Энэ загвар аудио дуудлага хийх үеийн яриаг нийлэгжүүлсэн эсэх эрсдэлийг илрүүлж чадна.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="mr-in" code="1102">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>या अद्यतनामध्ये खालील संसाधन फाइल्सचा समावेश आहे, ज्यामुळे सिस्टमचा वापरकर्ता अनुभव सुधारेल. सुधारणांचा आनंद घेण्यासाठी अद्यतनित करा.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="उच्चार संश्लेषण शोध मॉडेल">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>उच्चार संश्लेषण शोध मॉडेल मंदारिन चीनी भाषेत उच्चार संश्लेषण शोधला सपोर्ट करते. हे मॉडेल ऑडिओ कॉल्समधील वर्तमान भाषणाच्या संश्लेषणाचा धोका ओळखू शकतो.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="ms-my" code="1086">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Kemas kini ini menyertakan fail sumber berikut, yang akan meningkatkan pengalaman pengguna sistem. Kemas kini untuk menikmati penambahbaikan.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Model pengesanan sintesis pertuturan">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Model pengesanan sintesis pertuturan menyokong pengesanan sintesis pertuturan dalam Bahasa Cina Mandarin. Model ini boleh mengenal pasti risiko sintesis pertuturan semasa dalam panggilan audio.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="my-mm" code="1109">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>ဤအပ်ဒိတ်တွင် ဖော်ပြပါ ရင်းမြစ်ဖိုင်များ ပါဝင်ပြီး ၎င်းက စနစ်သုံးစွဲမှု အတွေ့အကြုံကို မြှင့်တင်ပေးပါမည်။ မြှင့်တင်မှုများကို သုံးစွဲရန် အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ပါ။</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="စကားသံအတုလုပ်ခြင်း ရှာဖွေစစ်ဆေးမှု မော်ဒယ်">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>စကားသံအတုလုပ်ခြင်း ရှာဖွေစစ်ဆေးမှု မော်ဒယ်သည် မန်ဒရင်း တရုတ်ဖြင့် စကားသံအတုလုပ်ခြင်းကို ရှာဖွေစစ်ဆေးသည်။ ဤမော်ဒယ်သည် အော်ဒီယိုခေါ်ဆိုမှုများတွင် စကားသံအတုလုပ်ခြင်းကို ခွဲခြားဖော်ထုတ်နိုင်သည်။</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="my-zg" code="1109">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>ဤအပ္ဒိတ္တြင္ ေဖာ္ျပပါ ရင္းျမစ္ဖိုင္မ်ား ပါဝင္ၿပီး ၎က စနစ္သုံးစြဲမႈ အေတြ႕အႀကဳံကို ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးပါမည္။ ျမႇင့္တင္မႈမ်ားကို သုံးစြဲရန္ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ပါ။</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="စကားသံအတုလုပ္ျခင္း ရွာေဖြစစ္ေဆးမႈ ေမာ္ဒယ္">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>စကားသံအတုလုပ္ျခင္း ရွာေဖြစစ္ေဆးမႈ ေမာ္ဒယ္သည္ မန္ဒရင္း တရုတ္ျဖင့္ စကားသံအတုလုပ္ျခင္းကို ရွာေဖြစစ္ေဆးသည္။ ဤေမာ္ဒယ္သည္ ေအာ္ဒီယိုေခၚဆိုမႈမ်ားတြင္ စကားသံအတုလုပ္ျခင္းကို ခြဲျခားေဖာ္ထုတ္ႏိုင္သည္။</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="nb-no" code="1044">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Denne oppdateringen omfatter følgende ressursfiler, som vil forbedre systemets brukeropplevelse. Oppdater for å få forbedringene.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Talesyntesens deteksjonsmodell">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Talesyntesens deteksjonsmodell støtter deteksjon av talesyntese på mandarinkinesisk. Denne modellen kan identifisere synteserisikoen for den gjeldende talen i lydanrop.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="ne-np" code="1121">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>यो अपडेटमा निम्न स्रोत फाइलहरू समावेश गरिएको छ र यसले प्रणालीको प्रयोगकर्ता अनुभव सुधार गर्ने छ । सुधार गरिएका सुविधाहरूको आनन्द लिन अपडेट गर्नुहोस् ।</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="वाचन संश्लेषण पत्ता लगाउने मोडेल">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>वाचन संश्लेषण पत्ता लगाउने मोडेलले मन्दारिन चिनियाँ भाषामा वाचन संश्लेषण पत्ता लगाउने सुविधा उपलब्ध गराउँछ । यो मोडेलले हालको अडियो कलमा वाचन संश्लेषणको जोखिम पहिचान गर्न सक्छ ।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Deze update bevat de volgende bronbestanden, die de gebruikerservaring van het systeem zullen verbeteren. Werk bij om van de verbeteringen te genieten.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Spraaksynthesedetectiemodel">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Spraaksynthesedetectiemodel ondersteunt spraaksynthesedetectie in het Mandarijn-Chinees. Dit model kan het syntheserisico van de huidige spraak in audio-oproepen identificeren.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="or-in" code="1096">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ରେ ନିମ୍ନଲିଖିତ ଉତ୍ସ ଫାଇଲ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରେ, ଯାହା ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ର ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ଅନୁଭୂତିରେ ଉନ୍ନତି ଆଣିବ। ବିକାଶଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଉପଭୋଗ କରିବାକୁ ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="ସ୍ପିଚ୍ ସିନ୍ଥେସିସ୍ ଚିହ୍ନଟକରଣ ମଡେଲ୍">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>ସ୍ପିଚ୍ ସିନ୍ଥେସିସ୍ ଚିହ୍ନଟକରଣ ମଡେଲ୍ ମାଣ୍ଡାରିନ୍ ଚାଇନିଜ୍ ଭାଷାରେ ସ୍ପିଚ୍ ସିନ୍ଥେସିସ୍ ଚିହ୍ନଟକରଣକୁ ସମର୍ଥନ କରେ। ଏହି ମଡେଲ୍ ଅଡିଓ କଲ୍‌ରେ ସମ୍ପ୍ରତି ସ୍ପିଚ୍‌ର ସିନ୍ଥେସିସ୍ ବିପଦ ଆଶଙ୍କାକୁ ଚିହ୍ନଟ କରିପାରିବ।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="pa-in" code="1094">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਹੇਠ ਲਿਖੀਆਂ ਸਰੋਤ ਫ਼ਾਈਲਾਂ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਹਨ, ਜੋ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਨੂੰ ਬਿਹਤਰ ਬਣਾਉਣਗੀਆਂ। ਸੁਧਾਰਾਂ ਦਾ ਆਨੰਦ ਲੈਣ ਲਈ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰੋ।</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="ਬੋਲੀ ਸੰਸ਼ਲੇਸ਼ਣ ਜਾਂਚ ਮਾਡਲ">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>ਬੋਲੀ ਸੰਸ਼ਲੇਸ਼ਣ ਜਾਂਚ ਮਾਡਲ ਮੈਂਡਰਿਨ ਚੀਨੀ ਵਿੱਚ ਬੋਲੀ ਸੰਸ਼ਲੇਸ਼ਣ ਜਾਂਚ ਦਾ ਸਮਰਥਨ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇਹ ਮਾਡਲ ਆਡੀਓ ਕਾਲਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਮੌਜੂਦਾ ਬੋਲੀ ਸੰਬੰਧੀ ਸੰਸ਼ਲੇਸ਼ਣ ਜੋਖਿਮ ਦੀ ਪਛਾਣ ਕਰ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Ta aktualizacja zawiera pliki zasobów, które poprawią komfort obsługi systemu. Zainstaluj tę aktualizację, aby korzystać z ulepszeń.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Model wykrywania syntezy mowy">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Model wykrywania syntezy mowy obsługuje wykrywanie syntezy mowy w języku mandaryńskim. Ten model może identyfikować ryzyko syntezy mowy na bieżąco w połączeniach audio.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="pt-br" code="1046">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Essa atualização inclui os seguintes arquivos de recursos, que melhorarão a experiência de usuário no sistema. Atualize para aproveitar as melhorias.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Modelo de detecção de síntese de fala">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Modelo de detecção de síntese de fala suporta detecção de síntese de fala em chinês mandarim. Este modelo pode identificar o risco de síntese da fala atual em chamadas de áudio.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Esta atualização inclui os seguintes ficheiros de recursos, que irão melhorar a experiência do utilizador do sistema. Atualize para aproveitar as melhorias.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Modelo de deteção de síntese de voz">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>O modelo de deteção de síntese de voz suporta a deteção de síntese de voz em mandarim chinês. Este modelo pode identificar o risco de síntese da fala atual em chamadas de áudio.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Această actualizare include următoarele fișiere de resurse, care vor îmbunătăți experiența de utilizare a sistemului. Actualizați pentru a vă bucura de îmbunătățiri.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Modelul de detectare a sintetizării vocii">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Modelul de detectare a sintetizării vocii acceptă detectarea sintetizării vocii în chineza mandarină. Acest model poate identifica riscul de sintetizare a vocii curente în apelurile audio.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>В это обновление включены следующие файлы ресурсов, повышающие качество обслуживания системы. Установите обновление, чтобы воспользоваться улучшениями.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Модель обнаружения синтеза речи">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Модель обнаружения синтеза речи поддерживает обнаружение синтеза речи на мандаринском диалекте китайского языка. Эта модель может выявлять признаки синтеза речи в текущем аудиовызове.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="si-lk" code="1115">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>මෙම යාවත්කාලයට පද්ධතියේ පරිශීලක අත්දැකීම වැඩිදියුණු කරනු ඇති පහත මූලාශ්‍ර ගොනු ඇතුළත් වේ. වැඩිදියුණු කිරීම් අත්විඳීමට යාවත්කාල කරන්න.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="කථන සංස්ලේෂණය හඳුනාගැනීමේ ආකෘතිය">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>කථන සංස්ලේෂණය හඳුනාගැනීමේ ආකෘතිය මැන්ඩරීන් චීන භාෂාවෙන් කථන සංස්ලේෂණ හඳුනාගැනීමට සහය දක්වයි. මෙම ආකෘතියට ශ්‍රව්‍ය ඇමතුම්වල වර්තමාන කථනයේ සංස්ලේෂණ අවදානම හඳුනාගැනීමට හැකි වේ.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Táto aktualizácia obsahuje nasledujúce zdrojové súbory, ktoré zlepšia používateľskú skúsenosť so systémom. Aktualizujte, aby ste si užili zlepšenia.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Model detekcie syntézy reči">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Model detekcie syntézy reči podporuje detekciu syntézy reči v mandarínskej čínštine. Tento model dokáže identifikovať riziko syntézy aktuálnej reči v hlasových hovoroch.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="sl-si" code="1060">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Ta posodobitev vključuje naslednje datoteke z viri, ki bodo izboljšale uporabniško izkušnjo s sistemom. Izvedite posodobitev in uživajte v izboljšavah.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Model za zaznavanje sinteze govora">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Model za zaznavanje sinteze govora podpira zaznavanje sinteze govora v mandarinščini (kitajščini). Ta model lahko prepozna tveganje za sintezo trenutnega govora v zvočnih klicih.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="sv-se" code="1053">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Den här uppdateringen innehåller följande resursfiler, som kommer att förbättra användarupplevelsen av systemet. Uppdatera för att ta del av förbättringarna.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Modell för detektering av talsyntes">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Modellen för detektering av talsyntes har stöd för detektering av talsyntes på mandarin (kinesiska). Modellen kan identifiera syntetiseringsrisk för det aktuella talet i ljudsamtal.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="sw-tz" code="1089">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Sasisho hili linajumuisha faili za nyenzo ifuatayo, ambazo zitaboresha huduma anayopata mtumiaji wa mfumo. Sasisha ili ufurahie maboresho.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Modeli ya utambuzi wa usemi sanisi">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Modeli ya utambuzi wa usemi sanisi huruhusu utambuzi wa usemi sanisi katika Kichina cha Kimandarini. Modeli hii inaweza kutambua hatari ya usanisi wa usemi wa sasa kwenye upigaji simu wa sauti.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="ta-in" code="1097">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு சிஸ்டத்தின் பயனர் அனுபவத்தை மேம்படுத்தும், பின்வரும் ஆதாரக் கோப்புகளைக் கொண்டுள்ளது. மேம்பாடுகளைப் பெற, புதுப்பிக்கவும்.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="பேச்சுத் தொகுப்புக் கண்டறிதல் மாடல்">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>பேச்சுத் தொகுப்புக் கண்டறிதல் மாடலானது மாண்டரின் சீன மொழியில் பேச்சுத் தொகுப்புக் கண்டறிதலை ஆதரிக்கிறது. இந்த மாடலால் ஆடியோ அழைப்புகளில் நடப்புப் பேச்சில் இருக்கும் செயற்கைத்தன்மை இடரை அடையாளம் காண முடியும்.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="te-in" code="1098">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌లో క్రింది వనరు ఫైల్స్ ఉన్నాయి, ఇవి సిస్టమ్ వినియోగదారు అనుభవాన్ని మెరుగుపరుస్తాయి. మెరుగుదలలను ఆనందించడానికి అప్‌డేట్ చేయండి.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="స్పీచ్ సింథసిస్ గుర్తింపు మోడల్">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>స్పీచ్ సింథసిస్ గుర్తింపు మోడల్ అనేది మాండరిన్ చైనీస్ భాషలోని స్పీచ్ సింథసిస్ గుర్తింపుకు మద్దతు ఇస్తుంది. ఈ మోడల్ ఆడియో కాల్‌ల్లోని ప్రస్తుత ప్రసంగం యొక్క సింథసిస్ ప్రమాదాన్ని గుర్తిస్తుంది.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="th-th" code="1054">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>การอัปเดตนี้รวมไฟล์ทรัพยากรต่อไปนี้ ซึ่งจะปรับปรุงประสบการณ์การใช้งานของผู้ใช้ในระบบ โปรดอัปเดิตเพื่อใช้การปรับปรุงต่างๆ</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="โมเดลการตรวจจับการสังเคราะห์เสียง">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>โมเดลการตรวจจับการสังเคราะห์เสียงรองรับการตรวจจับการสังเคราะห์เสียงในภาษาจีนกลาง โมเดลนี้จะสามารถระบุความเสี่ยงในการสังเคราะห์เสียงพูดในการโทรเสียงที่ดำเนินอยู่ในปัจจุบัน</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="tl-ph" code="1124">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Kasama sa update na ito ang mga sumusunod na file ng mapagkukunan, na magpapaganda sa karanasan ng user sa system. I-update para i-enjoy ang mga pagpapahusay.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Modelo ng pagtukoy ng speech synthesis">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Sinusuportahan ng modelo ng pagtukoy ng speech synthesis ang pagtukoy ng speech synthesis gamit ang Mandarin Chinese. Matutukoy ng modelong ito ang panganib ng synthesis ng kasalukuyang pagsasalita sa mga audio call.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Bu güncelleme, sistemin kullanıcı deneyimini iyileştiren kaynak dosyalarını (aşağıda belirtilmiştir) içermektedir. İyileştirmelerden yararlanmak için güncelleyin.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Konuşma sentezi tespit modeli">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Konuşma sentezi tespit modeli Mandarin Çincesinde konuşma sentezi tespiti desteği sunar. Bu model sesli aramalarda konuşma sırasında mevcut konuşmanın sentezlenmiş olma riskini belirleyebilir.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Це оновлення містить наведені далі файли ресурсів, які покращують взаємодію із системою. Застосуйте оновлення, щоб користуватись удосконаленнями.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Модель виявлення синтезу мовлення">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Модель виявлення синтезу мовлення підтримує мандаринську мову. Вона може виявляти ймовірний синтез мовлення під час аудіовикликів.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>اس اپ ڈیٹ میں درج ذیل وسائل کی فائلز شامل ہیں، جو سسٹم کے صارف کے تجربے کو بہتر بنائے گا۔ بہتری سے لطف اندوز ہونے کے لیے اپ ڈیٹ کریں۔</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="تقریر کی ترکیب کاری کا پتہ لگانے کا ماڈل">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>تقریر کی ترکیب کاری کا پتہ لگانے کا ماڈل مینڈارن چینی زبان میں تقریر کی ترکیب کا پتہ لگانے میں تعاون کرتا ہے۔ یہ ماڈل آڈیو کالز میں موجودہ تقریر کی ترکیب کاری کے خطرے کی شناخت کر سکتا ہے۔</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="ug-cn" code="1152">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>‏بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش تۆۋەندىكى مەنبە ھۆججەتلەرنى يېڭىلاپ، سىستېمىنىڭ ئىشلەتكۈچى تەسىراتىنى يۇقىرى كۆتۈرىدۇ، دەرھال يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="‏ئاۋاز بىرىكتۈرۈشنى تەكشۈرۈش مودېلى">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>‏ئاۋاز بىرىكتۈرۈشنى تەكشۈرۈش مودېلى ئېلان قىلىنغاندىن كېيىن، پۇتۇڭخۇادىكى ئاۋاز بىرىكتۈرۈشنى تەكشۈرۈشنى قوللايدۇ. ئاۋازلىق سۆزلىشىش كۆرۈنۈشلىرىدە بۇ مودېلنى ئىشلىتىپ نۆۋەتتىكى چاقىرىقتىكى ئاۋازنىڭ بىرىكتۈرۈلگەن بولۇش خەۋپىنى تونۇيدۇ.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Bu yangilanish tizim foydalanuvchi taassurotini yaxshilaydigan quyidagi resurs fayllarini oʻz ichiga oladi. Takomillashtirishlardan foydalanish uchun yangilang.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Nutq sintezini aniqlash modeli">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Nutq sintezini aniqlash modeli xitoy mandarin tilida nutq sintezini aniqlashni dastaklaydi. Bu model audio chaqiruvlarda joriy nutqni sintezlash xavfini aniqlay oladi.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>Bản cập nhật này bao gồm các tệp tin tài nguyên sau. Đây là những tài nguyên sẽ cải thiện trải nghiệm người dùng của hệ thống. Hãy cập nhật để trải nghiệm những cải tiến.</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="Mô hình phát hiện tổng hợp giọng nói">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>Mô hình phát hiện tổng hợp giọng nói hỗ trợ phát hiện tổng hợp giọng nói bằng tiếng Quan Thoại. Mô hình này có thể xác định nguy cơ giọng nói hiện tại là giọng nói tổng hợp trong cuộc gọi thoại.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>本次更新如下资源文件，将提升系统的用户体验，建议您立即更新。</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="语音合成检测模型">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>发布语音合成检测模型，支持中文普通话的语音合成检测。在音频通话场景中，会使用该模型来为您识别当前通话语音的合成风险。</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>本次更新了以下資源檔案，將提升系統的用戶體驗，建議您立即更新。</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="語音合成偵測模型">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>發佈語音合成偵測模型，支援中文普通語的語音合成偵測。在音訊通話場景中，會使用該模型來為您識別目前通話語音的合成風險。</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="zh-tw" code="1028">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>本次更新以下資源檔案，將提升系統的使用者經驗，建議您立即更新。</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="語音合成偵測模型">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>發佈語音合成偵測模型，支援中文普通話的語音合成偵測。在音訊通話場景中，會使用此模型為您辨識目前通話語音的合成風險。</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
    <language name="bo-cn" code="1105">
        <features module="" type="header" backgroud="">
            <!-- 引导语 -->
            <feature>ཐེངས་འདིར་གཤམ་གསལ་གྱི་ཐོན་ཁུངས་ཡིག་ཆ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ནས། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་ཉམས་ལེན་མཐོར་འདེགས་གཏོང་། ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་མྱུར་དུ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།</feature>
        </features>
        <!-- 标题 -->
        <features module="སྐད་གདངས་འདྲེས་གྲུབ་ཞིབ་དཔྱད་ཚད་ལེན་མ་དཔེ།">
            <!-- 正文 -->
            <feature>སྐད་གདངས་འདྲེས་གྲུབ་ཞིབ་དཔྱད་ཚད་ལེན་མ་དཔེ་ཁྱབ་སྤེལ་བྱས་ཡོད། རྒྱ་ཡིག་སྤྱི་སྐད་ཀྱི་སྐད་གདངས་འདྲེས་གྲུབ་ཞིབ་དཔྱད་ཚད་ལེན་ལ་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད། སྒྲ་ཟློས་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་ལེན་བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁྲོད་དུ། མ་དཔེ་དེ་བེད་སྤྱད་ནས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་མིག་སྔའི་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་ལེན་གྱི་སྐད་གདངས་འདྲེས་གྲུབ་ཀྱི་ཉེན་ཁ་ངོས་འཛིན་བྱ་སྲིད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="" type="end">
            <feature>zh-CN</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
</root>
