<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version=""/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature></feature>
</features>
<features module="丝滑流畅">
<feature>•  新增 Turbo X 性能引擎平台界面，性能优化效果看得见</feature>
<feature>•  新增侧滑退出/桌面滑动过程中的启动并行响应</feature>
<feature>•  新增抢购功能，抢票快人一步</feature>
<feature>•  优化应用启动退出场景动效曲线，体验更舒适、更流畅</feature>
<feature>•  优化刷视频、看直播、图文浏览流畅体验</feature>
<feature>•  优化相机使用性能，使用过程更流畅</feature>
<feature>•  优化应用安装速度，应用安装更快速</feature>
<feature>•  优化输入法打字体验，打字更流畅</feature>
</features>
<features module="便捷易用">
<feature>•  充电、录屏、日程创建、YOYO打电话、YOYO记忆等接入灵动胶囊，便于查看实时状态、快捷触达</feature>
<feature>•  新增 AI 截屏功能，智能学习使用场景和习惯，自动推荐所需服务，让操作更随心</feature>
<feature>•  新增支持悬浮窗截屏，截屏后可一步选择悬浮窗区域</feature>
<feature>•  截屏编辑后保存支持覆盖原图选项</feature>
<feature>•  支持蓝牙 LHDC 5.0 高清音频编码</feature>
<feature>•  晕动舒缓显示开启后支持圆点颜色自定义、乘车自动开启。体验路径：设置 > 辅助功能 > 晕动舒缓显示</feature>
<feature>•  支持 Android 原生极暗模式（降低白点值）。体验路径：设置 > 辅助功能 > 无障碍 > 极暗</feature>
<feature>•  设置新增语音搜索、模糊搜索功能，搜索更便捷</feature>
<feature>•  新增支持部分银行进行应用分身</feature>
</features>
<features module="UX 焕新">
<feature>•  UX 视觉升级焕新，打造全新 OS 视觉体验</feature>
<feature>•  新增通透模式，提升卡片、文件夹等元素的通透效果，带来极致通透体验。体验路径：设置 > 桌面和个性化 > 桌面设置 > 通透模式开关</feature>
<feature>•  控制中心风格焕新，深色背景强化视觉层级，多彩图标让界面更生动，支持个性化调整，操作更合心意</feature>
<feature>•  最近任务支持全新的堆叠卡片布局，多任务切换更直观，操作更高效。体验路径：设置 > 桌面和个性化 > 最近任务样式</feature>
<feature>•  时钟/图库卡片场景和日程/笔记应用内场景，新增一镜到底动效，实现跨页面转场的丝滑过渡</feature>
<feature>•  新增桌面卡片、控制中心按压位置响应效果</feature>
<feature>•  新增支持桌面底部常驻栏背景板。体验路径：双指捏合进入桌面编辑 > 桌面设置 > 显示桌面底部常驻栏背景板</feature>
<feature>•  优化卡片集翻转效果</feature>
</features>
<features module="玩转桌面">
<feature>•  媒体播控卡片新增进度条调节，可随意调整进度</feature>
<feature>•  控制中心任意位置支持横划切换至通知中心，操作更方便</feature>
<feature>•  控制中心新增关机按钮，关机重启更便捷</feature>
<feature>•  优化状态栏三方应用通知图标显示效果，提升显示一致性</feature>
<feature>•  优化部分应用导航条沉浸式体验</feature>
</features>
<features module="YOYO 记忆">
<feature>•  作为您的专属个人知识库，随心记录、安心管理、贴心使用</feature>
<feature>•  YOYO 记忆全新升级，知乎、小红书等高频应用（需将应用升级到最新版本）收藏可智能提取原文，并支持一键跳转原应用</feature>
<feature>•  新增双重隐私保护机制，使用更安心</feature>
<feature>•  全新列表视图更美观，信息展现与查找更高效</feature>
</features>
<features module="通信社交">
<feature>•  新增通话翻译功能。体验路径：设置 > 荣耀 AI &amp; YOYO > 进入 AI 通话界面 > 点击 AI 通话 > 通话翻译</feature>
<feature>•  来电场景支持配置为横幅通知或全屏显示。体验路径：设置 > 应用 > 拨号服务 > 解锁后来电通知</feature>
</features>
<features module="媒体创作">
<feature>•  相机应用界面焕新，操作更便捷</feature>
<feature>•  影像菜单支持双排显示和滑动翻页。体验路径：相机 > 上滑底部箭头调出影像菜单</feature>
<feature>•  相机新增状态栏自定义功能，可自定义编辑状态栏功能显示。体验路径：相机设置 > 状态栏自定义</feature>
<feature>•  图库视频播放支持帧预览，快速浏览锁定指定帧</feature>
</features>
<features module="荣耀互联">
<feature>•  新增与 iPhone 碰一碰互传文件功能，iOS 上需安装荣耀互联APP (1.1.18111 及以上版本)</feature>
<feature>•  新增与 macOS、Windows 互传功能，在电脑安装“荣耀超级工作台”即可互传图片、视频与文件</feature>
<feature>•  新增支持与 iOS 设备的 OTG 有线克隆，可支持更多数据项</feature>
<feature>•  新增支持与鸿蒙 NEXT 的联系人、图片、视频的换机克隆</feature>
</features>
<features module="安全守护">
<feature>•  新增图片检测功能，可通过“任意门”圈选人脸进行 AI 换脸检测。体验路径：设置 > 安全 > 反诈防护 > AI 换脸/变声检测 > 视频/图片类场景</feature>
<feature>•  新增 AI 通话防诈功能，通话中可检测对方声音是否为 AI 合成或诈骗电话。体验路径：设置 > 安全 > 反诈防护 > AI 换脸/变声检测、AI 诈骗话术检测</feature>
</features>
<features module="稳定可靠">
<feature>•  优化系统稳定性，提高用户整机使用体验</feature>
<feature>•  优化三方头部应用长时间使用的卡顿、卡死问题，提升稳定流畅体验</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项" type="end">
<feature>1. 新版本下载及安装过程会消耗部分电量及轻微发热，属于正常现象
2. 版本安装后重启期间会做部分系统优化，预计花费 1~3 分钟，请耐心等待
3. 升级完成后部分系统优化会在后台自动进行，系统会在后台自动优化，出现少量耗电，轻微发热是正常现象，1 天内即可恢复
4. 因部分第三方应用与 Android 16 不兼容，更新后可能会出现第三方应用无法正常使用的情况 (如闪退、卡顿、耗电等)。建议您在应用市场尝试将该应用更新至最新版本，若仍无法解决问题，请您耐心等待应用更新信息，并及时更新
5. 请务必确保手机有 10 GB 以上的内部存储空间，否则会有升级失败的风险 (查看存储空间方法：设置 > 存储)
6. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份
7. 如果您在使用过程中遇到任何问题，请访问“我的荣耀”应用或访问荣耀官方服务网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us 寻求支持</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature></feature>
</features>
<features module="Smoothness">
<feature>• The new Turbo X performance engine interface makes optimization visible</feature>
<feature>• When you swipe to exit or swipe on the home screen, the system can perform parallel operations</feature>
<feature>• Purchase acceleration helps you get tickets faster than others</feature>
<feature>• Optimizes the animation curves for launching or exiting apps, delivering a more fluid and comfortable experience</feature>
<feature>• Enhances the smoothness of video playback, live streaming, and browsing images and text</feature>
<feature>• Improves the Camera performance for smoother usage</feature>
<feature>• Speeds up app installation</feature>
<feature>• Improves the typing experience with a more responsive keyboard</feature>
</features>
<features module="Convenience">
<feature>• Charging, screen recording, schedule creation, YOYO calls, YOYO Memories, and other features are integrated into Magic Capsule for viewing real-time status and quick access</feature>
<feature>• AI screenshot can intelligently learn from your usage scenarios and habits to automatically recommend the services you need, making operations simpler</feature>
<feature>• You can take a screenshot that includes a floating window and easily select the floating window area in one step</feature>
<feature>• After editing a screenshot, you can save it to replace the original image</feature>
<feature>• Supports Bluetooth LHDC 5.0 high-definition audio codec</feature>
<feature>• Motion Sickness Relief now includes an auto-enable feature during driving, and you can customize the dot color. Try it out by going to: Settings > Accessibility features > Motion Sickness Relief</feature>
<feature>• Supports Android's native extra dim mode, which reduces the white point value. Try it out by going to: Settings > Accessibility features > Accessibility > Extra dim</feature>
<feature>• New voice search and fuzzy search features make searching more convenient</feature>
<feature>• Some bank apps now support App Twin</feature>
</features>
<features module="Refreshed interface">
<feature>• The upgraded interface design delivers a new look for the OS</feature>
<feature>• Transparency mode optimizes the transparency effects of elements such as cards and folders, delivering an exceptional visual experience. Try it out by going to: Settings > Home screen &amp; style > Home screen settings > Enable Transparency mode</feature>
<feature>• The refreshed Control Center includes a dark background to improve visual hierarchy and colorful icons for a more vibrant interface. It also supports personalized adjustments for a better user experience</feature>
<feature>• Recent tasks now feature a new card-stack layout, making it easier and more efficient to switch between tasks. Try it out by going to: Settings > Home screen &amp; style > Recent task style</feature>
<feature>• Long take animation enables smooth transitions across pages for the Clock/Gallery card and Calendar/Notes app</feature>
<feature>• When pressing home screen cards or the Control Center, you can experience responsive effects</feature>
<feature>• The home screen now enables a dock background. Try it out by going to: Pinch with two fingers to access home screen editing > Home screen settings > Show dock background</feature>
<feature>• Optimizes the card set flipping effect</feature>
</features>
<features module="Explore the home screen">
<feature>• The media control card features a progress bar, allowing you to easily adjust the playback</feature>
<feature>• You can swipe horizontally from anywhere in the Control Center to quickly switch to the Notification Center</feature>
<feature>• Control Center now includes a Power off button, making it easier to power off and restart your device</feature>
<feature>• Improves the display of third-party app notification icons in the status bar for a more unified look</feature>
<feature>• Optimizes the immersive experience of the navigation bar in some apps</feature>
</features>
<features module="YOYO Memories">
<feature>• YOYO Memories acts as your exclusive personal knowledge base, allowing you to record freely and manage with ease</feature>
<feature>• The newly upgraded YOYO Memories can intelligently extract content from your collectioins in popular apps like Zhihu and Xiaohongshu (make sure the apps are updated to the latest version). It also allows for one-tap navigation back to the original app</feature>
<feature>• Dual privacy protection makes it more secure to use</feature>
<feature>• The new list view is more visually appealing, with more efficient information display and search</feature>
</features>
<features module="Communication and social">
<feature>• AI Call enables the Call translation feature. Try it out by going to: Settings > Honor AI &amp; YOYO > Enter AI Call interface > Tap AI Call > Call translation</feature>
<feature>• You can set incoming calls to show as either a banner notification or a full-screen display. Try it out by going to: Settings > Apps > Phone Services > Call notification after unlocking</feature>
</features>
<features module="Media creation">
<feature>• The Camera interface has been refreshed for easier use</feature>
<feature>• Imaging menu allows you to view items in two rows and swipe to turn pages. To access the imaging menu, go to Camera and swipe up the bottom arrow</feature>
<feature>• You can customize status bar display by going to: Camera settings > Customize status bar</feature>
<feature>• You can quickly browse videos and easily locate specific frames in Gallery</feature>
</features>
<features module="Honor Connect">
<feature>• Simply tap your device against an iPhone to transfer files. Ensure that the Honor Connect app (v1.1.18111 or later) is installed on the iOS device</feature>
<feature>• Install HONOR Workstation on your macOS or Windows computer to easily transfer images, videos, and files between your Honor device and the computer</feature>
<feature>• OTG wired cloning with iOS devices allows more data items to be transferred</feature>
<feature>• Supports the migration of contacts, images, and videos to HarmonyOS NEXT</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security Guard">
<feature>• Image detection allows you to circle faces via Magic Portal for AI deepfake detection. Try it out by going to: Settings > Security > Scam Protection > AI deepfake &amp; voice cloning detection > Videos/Images</feature>
<feature>• AI Call fraud prevention can detect whether the caller's voice is AI-generated or a scam during the call. Try it out by going to: Settings > Security > Scam Protection > AI deepfake &amp; voice cloning detection > AI scam script detection</feature>
</features>
<features module="Stability and reliability">
<feature>• Improves the system stability to optimize the user experience</feature>
<feature>• Fixes lag and crash issues for popular third-party apps, ensuring a stable and smooth experience</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes" type="end">
<feature>1. The download and installation process of the new version will consume some battery power and cause slight heating, which is normal
2. During the restart after the installation, some system optimizations will be performed, expected to take 1~3 minutes. Please be patient
3. After the upgrade is completed, some system optimizations will automatically proceed in the background. During this period, the device may experience increased power consumption and slight heating. It can be restored to normal within one day
4. Some third-party apps are not compatible with Android 16 and may malfunction after the update (such as crash, lag, abnormal power consumption). Please update your apps to the latest version in App Market. If the problems persist, please wait for the upcoming app updates and update in a timely manner
5. Make sure your phone has more than 10 GB of free storage space. Otherwise, the update may fail (To check your storage space, go to Settings > Storage)
6. This update will not affect your personal data, but it is recommended to back up your data before updating
7. If you encounter any issues during use, please get support by going to My Honor or visiting our website: https://www.Honor.com/cn/contact-us</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
