<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新智慧助手升级为 YOYO 助理，优化智慧视觉的交互操作方式，优化健康使用平板功能以及修复部分场景下健康使用平板统计和管控问题，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="YOYO 助理">
<feature>•  智慧助手升级为 YOYO 助理，新增支持发送图片、文档等交流互动方式和 DeepSeek 深度思考模式。</feature>
</features>
<features module="智慧视觉">
<feature>•  优化智慧视觉的交互操作方式。</feature>
</features>
<features module="健康使用平板">
<feature>•  支持通过家长荣耀账号找回孩子端健康使用平板密码。
•  支持孩子端被卸载应用的使用记录统计。
•  家长端可查看孩子端应用使用实时行为和轨迹数据。
•  健康使用平板统计和管控功能优化。
•  智慧空间和孩子端的绑定流程优化。</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更多精彩功能介绍，请访问“玩机技巧”应用。
3. 如果您在使用过程中遇到任何问题，请访问“我的荣耀”应用或访问荣耀官方服务网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us 寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this update optimizes the interaction methods of Honor Lens. Assistant has been upgraded to YOYO Assistant. Additionally, this update enhances the features of Digital Wellbeing and fixes issues with the statistics and control functions of Digital Wellbeing in some scenarios. Update to enjoy the new features and improvements.</feature>
</features>
<features module="YOYO Assistant">
<feature>• Assistant has been upgraded to YOYO Assistant, now supporting new ways to interact, such as sending images and documents, as well as the DeepSeek deep thinking mode.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Honor Lens">
<feature>• Optimizes the interaction methods of Honor Lens.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Digital Wellbeing">
<feature>• Parents can use their Honor account to recover the child's Digital Wellbeing password.
• Records the usage history of apps that have been uninstalled on the child's device.
• Parents can view real-time app usage behavior and activity history of their child.
• Optimizes the statistics and control functions for Digital Wellbeing.
• Enhances the binding process between AI Space and the child's device.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. This update will not affect your personal data, but it is recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. For more information on the features, please check out the Tips app.
3. If you encounter any issues during use, you can get our support by going to My Honor or visiting our website at https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us.</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
