<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version=""/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新主要针对系统进行了优化，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="界面焕新">
<feature>新增通透模式，提升卡片、文件夹等元素的通透效果，带来极致通透体验。体验路径：设置 >桌面和个性化 > 桌面设置 > 通透模式开关</feature>
</features>
<features module="流畅动效">
<feature>优化多任务界面、控制中心等场景动效体验</feature>
</features>
<features module="振动">
<feature>优化 YOYO 唤醒、输入法、相机变焦等场景振动体验</feature>
</features>
<features module="锁屏">
<feature>优化锁屏数字密码界面</feature>
<feature>新增支持长按锁屏空白区域进入编辑</feature>
</features>
<features module="系统">
<feature>优化系统稳定性</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项" type="end">
<feature>1. 新版本下载及安装过程会消耗部分电量及轻微发热，属于正常现象
2. 版本安装后重启期间会做部分系统优化，预计花费 1~3 分钟，请耐心等待
3. 升级完成后部分系统优化会在后台自动进行，系统会在后台自动优化，出现少量耗电，轻微发热是正常现象，1 天内即可恢复
4. 因部分第三方应用与 Android 16 不兼容，更新后可能会出现第三方应用无法正常使用的情况 (如闪退、卡顿、耗电等)。建议您在应用市场尝试将该应用更新至最新版本，若仍无法解决问题，请您耐心等待应用更新信息，并及时更新
5. 请务必确保手机有 10 GB 以上的内部存储空间，否则会有升级失败的风险 (查看存储空间方法：设置 > 存储)
6. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份
7. 如果您在使用过程中遇到任何问题，请访问“我的荣耀”应用或访问荣耀官方服务网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us 寻求支持</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this update mainly enhances the system performance. Update to enjoy the improvements.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Refreshed interface">
<feature>Transparency mode optimizes the transparency effects of elements such as cards and folders, delivering an exceptional visual experience. Try it out by going to: Settings > Home screen &amp; style > Home screen settings > Enable Transparency mode</feature>
</features>
<features module="Smooth animation">
<feature>Optimizes the user experience by improving animations in Recent tasks interface, Control Center, and other scenarios</feature>
</features>
<features module="Vibration">
<feature>Enhances vibration effects to improve user experience in scenarios such as waking up YOYO, using the keyboard, and zooming in or out with the Camera</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lock screen">
<feature>Optimizes the lock screen PIN interface</feature>
<feature>Long press the blank area of the lock screen to start editing</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Improves the system stability</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes" type="end">
<feature>1. The download and installation process of the new version will consume some battery power and cause slight heating, which is normal
2. During the restart after the installation, some system optimizations will be performed, expected to take 1~3 minutes. Please be patient
3. After the upgrade is completed, some system optimizations will automatically proceed in the background. During this period, the device may experience increased power consumption and slight heating. It can be restored to normal within one day
4. Some third-party apps are not compatible with Android 16 and may malfunction after the update (such as crash, lag, abnormal power consumption). Please update your apps to the latest version in App Market. If the problems persist, please wait for the upcoming app updates and update in a timely manner
5. Make sure your phone has more than 10 GB of free storage space. Otherwise, the update may fail (To check your storage space, go to Settings > Storage)
6. This update will not affect your personal data, but it is recommended to back up your data before updating
7. If you encounter any issues during use, please get support by going to My Honor or visiting our website: https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
