<root>
    <component name="TCPU" version="请自行修改"></component>
    <default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
    <language code="2052" name="zh-cn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新主要针对系统进行了优化，推荐您进行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="动态照片">
             <feature>•  新增支持动态照片锁屏能力。体验路径：设置 > 桌面和个性化 > 锁屏样式 > 动态照片</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="胶片风格水印">
             <feature>•  新增胶片风格水印。体验路径：相机 > 设置 > 水印 > 胶片</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="图库">
             <feature>•  新增清理建议功能，支持重复照片、相似图片、超大视频等自动识别，提供更便捷的清理建议</feature>
             <feature>•  新增智能抠图，支持图片主体抠图移位及背景修改。体验路径：照片 > AI 编辑 > 魔法修图 > 智能抠图</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="智慧视觉">
             <feature>•  长按屏幕文字时，弹出的工具栏新增翻译功能</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="辅助功能">
             <feature>•  支持双击电源键/熄屏状态下双击音量下键打开指定应用</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="荣耀钱包">
             <feature>•  新增门禁卡功能，支持模拟未经加密过的门禁卡</feature>
             <feature>•  新增空白卡功能。体验路径：设置 > 荣耀钱包 > 门禁卡</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安全补丁">
             <feature>•  合入安卓 2025 年 11 月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="更新注意事项" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份
2. 更多精彩功能介绍，请访问“玩机技巧”应用
3. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="en-us">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Dear user, this update mainly enhances the system performance. Update to enjoy the improvements</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Moving Photo">
             <feature>• You can now set a moving photo as the lock screen. Try it out by going to: Settings > Home screen &amp; style > Lock screen style > Moving photo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Film-style watermark">
             <feature>• Camera includes film-style watermarks. Try it out by going to: Camera > Settings > Watermark > FILM</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Gallery">
             <feature>• Cleanup suggestions feature enables automatic identification of duplicate photos, similar images, and oversized videos, providing more convenient cleaning suggestions</feature>
             <feature>• AI Cutout enables you to extract the subject, move it to a new position in the image, and change the background. Try it out by going to: Photos > AI Edit > Magic Retouch > AI Cutout</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• After long-pressing the text on the screen, the pop-up toolbar now includes Translate feature</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Accessibility features">
             <feature>• Double-press the Power button or, when the screen is off, double-press the Volume down button to open a specified app</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• Access card feature supports the simulation of unencrypted access cards</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet includes Blank card feature. Try it out by going to: Settings > Honor Wallet > Access card</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Security patch">
             <feature>• Android security patch (Nov 2025) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about Honor Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating
2. Discover more information on product features in Tips
3. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling Honor service hotline or visiting Honor customer service center</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1118" name="am-ET">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ ይህ ዝማኔ በዋነኛነት የስርዓቱን አፈጻጸም ያሻሽላል። በማሻሻያዎቹ ለመደሰት ያዘምኑ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ተንቀሳቃሽ ፎቶ">
             <feature>• አሁን ተንቀሳቃሽ ፎቶን እንደ የማያ መቆለፊያ ማቀናበር ይችላሉ። ወደዚህ በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > መነሻ ማያ ገጽ እና ቅጥ > የማያ መቆለፊያ ቅጥ > ተንቀሳቃሽ ፎቶ።</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="የፊልም አይነት የጌጥሽልም ቅጥ">
             <feature>• ካሜራ የፊልም አይነት የጌጥሽልም ቅጦችን ያካትታል። ወደዚህ በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ካሜራ > ቅንብሮች > ጌጥሽልም > ፊልም።</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="የሥነ ጥበብ ማዕከል">
             <feature>• የማጽጃ ጥቆማዎች ባህሪው የተባዙ ፎቶዎችን፣ ተመሳሳይ ምስሎች፣ እና መጠናቸው የገዘፈ ቪዲዮዎችን በራስ-ሰር ለይቶ ማወቅን ስራ ያስጀምራል፣ በዚህም ይበልጥ ምቹ የማጽጃ ጥቆማዎችን ያቀርብልዎታል</feature>
             <feature>• ኤአይ ስርጉድ ባለ ጉዳዩን ማውጣትን፣ በምስሉ ላይ ወደ አዲስ ቦታ ማንቀሳቀስን እና ጀርባውን መቀየር ያስችላል። ወደዚህ በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ፎቶዎች > ኤአይ አርትዖት > አስማታዊ ማሳመር > ኤአይ ስርጉድ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ሌንስ">
             <feature>• በማያው ላይ ያለውን ጽሑፍ ከረዥም ጊዜ ከተጫኑ በኋላ ብቅ ባይ የመሳሪያ አሞሌ አሁን የትርጉም ባህሪን ያካትታል</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="የተደራሽነት ባህሪያት">
             <feature>• አንድ የተወሰነ መተግበሪያ ለመክፈት የኃይል አዝራሩን፣ ወይም ደግሞ ማያው ሲጠፋ የድምጽ መቀነሻ አዝራሩን ሁለቴ ይጫኑ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ዋሌት">
             <feature>• የመዳረሻ ካርድ ባህሪ ያልተመሰጠሩ የመዳረሻ ካርዶችን ማስመሰል ይደግፋል</feature>
             <feature>• Honor ዋሌት የባዶ ካርድ ባህሪን ያካትታል። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > Honor ዋሌት > የመዳረሻ ካርድ።</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="የደህንነት መጠገኛ">
             <feature>• የአንድሮይድ የደህንነት መጠገኛ (ኖቬምበር 2025) ለስርዓት ደህንነት ተካትቷል። ስለHonor ደህንነት ዝማኔዎች ተጨማሪ መረጃ ለማግኘት እባክዎ የእኛን ድረ-ገጽ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11 ይጎብኙ</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ማስታወሻዎች" type="end">
             <feature>1. ይህን ዝማኔ መጫን በእርስዎ የግል ውሂብ ላይ ተጽዕኖ አያሳርፍም፣ ነገር ግን አሁንም ከማዘመንዎ በፊት የውሂብዎን መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ ይመከራል
2. በጠቃሚ ምክሮች ውስጥ ስለምርት ባህሪያት ተጨማሪ መረጃ ያግኙ
3. በዝማኔው ጊዜ ማናቸውም ችግሮች ካጋጠሙዎት ወደ የHonor አገልግሎት ቀጥታ መስመር በመደወል ወይም የHonor ደንበኛ አገልግሎት ማዕከልን በመጎብኘት የእኛን እርዳታ ማግኘት ይችላሉ</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="3073" name="ar-eg">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، يحسّن هذا التحديث أداء النظام بشكل أساسي. للاستمتاع بالتحسينات، ما عليك سوى التحديث</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="الصورة المتحركة">
             <feature>• يمكنك الآن تعيين صورة متحركة باعتبارها شاشة قفل. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > الشاشة الرئيسية والنمط > نوع قفل الشاشة > الصورة المتحركة.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="علامة مائية بأسلوب الأفلام">
             <feature>• تتضمن الكاميرا علامات مائية بأسلوب الأفلام. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الكاميرا > الإعدادات > علامة مائية > فيلم.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="المعرض">
             <feature>• بفضل ميزة اقتراحات التنظيف، يُمكنك التعرف تلقائيًا على الصور المكررة والمتشابهة، وكذلك مقاطع الفيديو كبيرة الحجم، ما يوفر لك اقتراحات تنظيف أكثر ذكاء وسهولة</feature>
             <feature>• تتيح لك الميزة "قص ذكي" استخراج الهدف، ونقله إلى موضع جديد في الصورة، وتغيير الخلفية. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الصور > التعديل الذكي > التنقيح السحري > قص ذكي</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="عدسة Honor">
             <feature>• بعد الضغط مطولاً على النص الموجود على الشاشة، يتضمن شريط الأدوات المنبثق الآن ميزة الترجمة</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ميزات إمكانية الوصول">
             <feature>• اضغط مرتين على زر الطاقة، أو عندما تكون الشاشة متوقفة عن التشغيل، اضغط مرتين على زر خفض الصوت لفتح تطبيق معين</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="محفظة Honor">
             <feature>• تدعم ميزة بطاقة الدخول محاكاة بطاقات الدخول غير المشفرة</feature>
             <feature>• تتضمن محفظة Honor ميزة البطاقة الفارغة. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > محفظة Honor > بطاقة الدخول.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="تصحيح الأمان">
             <feature>• تم تضمين تصحيح أمان أندرويد (نوفمبر 2025) لأمان النظام. لمزيد من المعلومات حول تحديثات الأمان في Honor، يرجى زيارة موقعنا على الويب https://www.honor.com/ae-ar/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ملاحظات" type="end">
             <feature>1. لن يؤثر تثبيت هذا التحديث على بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن لا يزال من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية لبياناتك قبل التحديث
2. اكتشف المزيد من المعلومات حول ميزات المنتج في تطبيق التلميحات
3. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيمكنك الحصول على مساعدتنا عن طريق الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة عملاء Honor أو زيارة مركز خدمة عملاء Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1101" name="as-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই আপডেটটোৱে মূলতঃ ছিষ্টেমৰ কাৰ্যদক্ষতা উন্নত কৰে। উন্নতিসমূহৰ আনন্দ ল'বলৈ আপডেট কৰক</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="চলন্ত ফটো">
             <feature>• আপুনি এতিয়া লক স্ক্ৰীণ ৰূপে এখন চলন্ত ফটো ছেট কৰিব পাৰে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াক ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ছেটিংছ > হোম স্ক্ৰীণ আৰু শৈলী > লক স্ক্ৰীণৰ শৈলী > চলন্ত ফটো।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ফিল্ম ষ্টাইল ৱাটাৰমাৰ্ক">
             <feature>• কেমেৰাত ফিল্ম ষ্টাইল ৱাটাৰমাৰ্কসমূহ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত আছে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াক ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: কেমেৰা > ছেটিংছ > ৱাটাৰমাৰ্ক > ফিল্ম।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="গেলাৰী">
             <feature>• পৰিষ্কাৰৰ পৰামৰ্শ ফিচাৰে ডুপ্লিকেট ফটোসমূহ, একেধৰণৰ প্ৰতিচ্ছবিসমূহ আৰু ডাঙৰ আকাৰৰ ভিডিঅ'সমূহৰ স্বয়ংক্ৰিয় চিনাক্তকৰণ সক্ষম কৰে, যিয়ে অধিক সুবিধাজনক পৰিষ্কাৰ কৰাৰ পৰামৰ্শ প্ৰদান কৰে।</feature>
             <feature>• AI কাটআউটে আপোনাক বিষয়বস্তুটো বাহিৰ উলিয়াবলৈ, ইয়াক প্ৰতিচ্ছবিখনত এটা নতুন স্থানলৈ লৈ যাবলৈ আৰু পৃষ্ঠভূমি পৰিৱৰ্তন কৰিবলৈ সক্ষম কৰে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াক ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ফটোসমূহ > AI সম্পাদনা > মেজিক ৰিটাচ্চ্‌ > AI কাটআউট</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• স্ক্ৰীণখনত থকা পাঠত দীঘলীয়াকৈ দবোৱাৰ পাছত প'প-আপ সঁজুলিদণ্ডিকাই এতিয়া অনুবাদ ফিচাৰ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="প্ৰৱেশযোগ্যতা ফিচাৰসমূহ">
             <feature>• এটা নিৰ্দিষ্ট এপ্প্‌ খুলিবলৈ পাৱাৰ বুটামটো দুবাৰ দবাওক বা স্ক্ৰীণখন অফ থকাৰ সময়ত ভলিউম ডাউন বুটামটো দুবাৰ দবওক</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ৱালেট">
             <feature>• এক্সেচ কাৰ্ড ফিচাৰে এনক্ৰিপ্ট নকৰা এক্সেচ কাৰ্ডসমূহৰ চিমুলেচন সমৰ্থন কৰে</feature>
             <feature>• Honor ৱালেটত খালী কাৰ্ড ফিচাৰ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত আছে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াক ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ছেটিংছ > Honor ৱালেট > উপলব্ধ হোৱা কাৰ্ড।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ">
             <feature>• ছিষ্টেমৰ নিৰাপত্তাৰ বাবে Android নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ (নবেম্বৰ 2025) অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হৈছে। Honor নিৰাপত্তা আপডেটৰ বিষয়ে অধিক তথ্যৰ বাবে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি আমাৰ ৱেবছাইট দৰ্শন কৰক: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="টোকাসমূহ" type="end">
             <feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটাত প্ৰভাৱ নপৰিব, কিন্তু আপডেট কৰাৰ পূৰ্বে আপোনাৰ ডাটাৰ বেক আপ ল'বলৈ এতিয়াও পৰামৰ্শ দিয়া হয়
2. আভাসত প্ৰ'ডাক্টৰ ফিচাৰসমূহৰ ওপৰত অধিক তথ্য অনুসন্ধান কৰক
3. আপুনি আপডেটৰ সময়ত কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হ'লে, আপুনি Honor সেৱা হটলাইনত কল কৰি বা Honor গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ গৈ সহায় লাভ কৰিব পাৰে</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1068" name="az-az">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, bu yeniləmə əsasən sistemin performansını artırır. Təkmilləşdirmələrdən yararlanmaq üçün yeniləyin</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Hərəkətli Foto">
             <feature>• İndi hərəkət edən fotonu kilid ekranı kimi təyin edə bilərsiniz. Bura keçməklə sınayın: Parametrlər > Əsas ekran və üslub > Kilid ekranı üslubu > Hərəkət edən foto.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Film üslubunda su nişanı">
             <feature>• Kameraya film üslubunda su nişanları daxildir. Bura keçməklə sınayın: Kamera > Parametrlər > Su nişanı > FİLM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Qalereya">
             <feature>• Təmizləmə təklifləri xüsusiyyəti dublikat fotoların, oxşar şəkillərin və böyük ölçülü videoların avtomatik müəyyən edilməsinə imkan verir və daha rahat təmizləmə təklifləri verir</feature>
             <feature>• AI Kəsim sizə subyekti çıxarmaq, onun yerini şəkildə yeni mövqeyə dəyişmək və arxa fonu dəyişmək imkanı verir. Buraya keçərək sınayın: Şəkillər > AI Redaktə > Sehrli Retuş > AI Kəsim</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Ekrandakı mətnə basıb saxladıqdan sonra açılan alətlər panelinə artıq Tərcümə xüsusiyyəti daxildir</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Xüsusi imkanlar xüsusiyyətləri">
             <feature>• Müəyyən proqramı açmaq üçün Enerji düyməsinə iki dəfə basın və ya ekran sönülü olduqda Səsi azaltma düyməsinə iki dəfə basın</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Pul kisəsi">
             <feature>• Giriş kartı xüsusiyyəti şifrələnməmiş giriş kartlarının simulyasiyasını dəstəkləyir</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Pul kisəsi Boş kart xüsusiyyətini ehtiva edir. Bura keçməklə sınayın: Parametrlər > Honor Pul kisəsi > Giriş kartı.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Təhlükəsizlik paketi">
             <feature>• Sistem təhlükəsizliyi üçün Android təhlükəsizlik paketi (noyabr 2025-ci il) daxil edilib. Honor Təhlükəsizlik yeniləmələri haqqında ətraflı məlumat üçün veb-saytımıza daxil olun: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Qeydlər" type="end">
             <feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınıza təsir etməyəcək, lakin yenə də yeniləməmişdən əvvəl verilənlərin ehtiyat nüsxəsini çıxarmaq tövsiyə olunur
2. İpuclarında məhsul xüsusiyyətləri haqqında daha çox məlumat əldə edin
3. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlə qarşılaşsanız, Honor xidmət qaynar xəttinə zəng etməklə və ya Honor müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə yaxınlaşaraq yardım ala bilərsiniz</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="jv-id">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran iki utamane ningkatake kinerja sistem. Anyarake kanggo ngrasakake pangapikane</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Foto Obah">
             <feature>• Sampeyan saiki bisa netepake foto obah minangka layar kunci. Coba kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Layar ngarep &amp; gaya > Gaya layar kunci > Foto obah.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Watermark gaya film">
             <feature>• Kamera ngatutake watermark gaya film. Coba kanthi mbukak: Kamera > Setelan > Watermark > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galeri">
             <feature>• Fitur Saran reresik mbisakake pangenalan otomatis foto duplikat, gambar sing memper, lan video sing kegedhen saengga menehi saran ngresiki sing luwih gampang</feature>
             <feature>• Kethokan AI mbisakake sampeyan ngekstrak subjek, mindhahake subjek menyang posisi anyar ing gambar, lan ngowahi latar mburi. Coba fitur kuwi kanthi mbukak: Foto > Pangeditan AI > Magic Retouch > Kethokan AI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Sawise menet suwe teks ing layar, wilah alat pop-up saiki ngatutake fitur Pertal</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fitur aksesibilitas">
             <feature>• Menet kaping pindho tombol Daya utawa, nalika layar mati, menet kaping pindho tombol Swara mudhun kanggo mbukak apl tertamtu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Dompet Honor">
             <feature>• Fitur Kertu akses ndhukung simulasi kertu akses sing ora dienkripsi</feature>
             <feature>• Dompet Honor ngatutake fitur Kertu kosong. Coba kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Dompet Honor > Kertu akses.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch keamanan">
             <feature>• Patch keamanan Android (Nov 2025) wis digabungake kanggo keamanan sistem. Kanggo mangerteni informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan panganyaran Keamanan Honor, bukak situs web kita https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Cathetan" type="end">
             <feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mengaruhi data pribadi sampeyan, nanging nggawe serep data dhisik tetep disaranake sadurunge nganyarake
2. Temokake informasi liyane babagan fitur prodhuk ing Tips
3. Yen ana masalah sajrone panganyaran, sampeyan bisa entuk bantuan kita kanthi nelpon hotline layanan Honor utawa nekani pusat layanan pelanggan Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2074" name="sr-rs">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se unapređuju performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u unapređenjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pokretna fotografija">
             <feature>• Sada možete da postavite pokretnu fotografiju kao zaključani ekran. Isprobajte odlaskom u opciju: Podešavanja > Početni ekran i stil > Stil zaključanog ekrana > Pokretna fotografija.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vodeni žig u filmskom stilu">
             <feature>• Kamera uključuje vodene žigove u filmskom stilu. Isprobajte ih odlaskom u opciju: Kamera > Podešavanja > Vodeni žig > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerija">
             <feature>• Funkcija Predlozi za brisanje omogućava automatsko prepoznavanje duplih slika, sličnih slika i prevelikih video zapisa te pruža praktičnije predloge za brisanje</feature>
             <feature>• Isecanje pomoću VI omogućava da izdvojite subjekt, premestite ga na novu poziciju na slici i promenite pozadinu. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići na: Fotografije > AI uređivanje > Čarobno retuširanje > Isecanje pomoću VI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Nakon dugog pritiska na tekst na ekranu, iskačuća alatna traka sada uključuje funkciju Prevedi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkcije pristupačnosti">
             <feature>• Dvaput pritisnite dugme za uključivanje/isključivanje ili, kada je ekran isključen, dvaput pritisnite dugme za smanjenje jačine zvuka da otvorite određenu aplikaciju</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Novčanik">
             <feature>• Funkcija Kartica za pristup podržava simulaciju nešifriranih kartica za pristup</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Novčanik uključuje funkciju Blanko kartice. Isprobajte je odlaskom u opciju: Podešavanja > Honor Novčanik > Kartica za pristup.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezbednosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Android bezbednosna zakrpa (novembar 2025.) je integrisana radi bezbednosti sistema. Za još informacija o Honor bezbednosnim ažuriranjima, posetite naš veb-sajt https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zabeleške" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka pre ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o karakteristikama proizvoda u odeljku Saveti
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete dobiti našu pomoć pozivom dežurne linije kompanije Honor ili posetom centru za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1059" name="be-by">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта абнаўленне ў асноўным паляпшае прадукцыйнасць сістэмы. Каб палепшыць уражанні ад выкарыстання, устанавіце абнаўленне</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Жывое фота">
             <feature>• Цяпер вы можаце ўстанавіць жывое фота ў якасці экрана блакіроўкі. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню«Налады > Галоўны экран і стыль > Стыль экрана блакіроўкі > Жывое фота».</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Вадзяны знак у стылі плёнкі">
             <feature>• Камера цяпер прапануе вадзяныя знакі ў стылі плёнкі. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Камера > Налады > Вадзяны знак > ПЛЁНКА».</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Галерэя">
             <feature>• Функцыя прапаноў па ачыстцы дазваляе аўтаматычна выяўляць дублікаты фота, падобныя выявы і занадта вялікія відэа і прапануе больш зручныя прапановы па ачыстцы</feature>
             <feature>• Функцыя «AI-выразанне» дазваляе вылучыць аб’ект, перамясціць яго ў іншае месца на выяве і змяніць фон. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню: Фатаграфіі > AI-рэдагаванне > Magic Retouch > AI-выразанне</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Цяпер усплывальная панэль інструментаў, якая з’яўляецца пасля доўгага націску на тэкст на экране, змяшчае функцыю перакладу</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Функцыі спецыяльных магчымасцей">
             <feature>• Двойчы націсніце кнопку ўключэння або, калі экран выключаны, двойчы націсніце кнопку памяншэння гучнасці, каб адкрыць пэўную праграму</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Кашалёк Honor">
             <feature>• Функцыя карткі доступу падтрымлівае сімуляцыю незашыфраваных картак доступу</feature>
             <feature>• Кашалёк Honor уключае функцыю «Пустая картка». Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Кашалёк Honor > Картка доступу».</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Выпраўленне сістэмы бяспекі">
             <feature>• Для павышэння бяспекі сістэмы ўключана выпраўленне функцый бяспекі Android (лістапад 2025 г.). Больш інфармацыі аб абнаўленні сістэмы бяспекі Honor можна знайсці на нашым афіцыйным вэб-сайце: https://www.honor.com/by/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Нататкі" type="end">
             <feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не закране вашы асабістыя даныя. Тым не менш рэкамендуецца стварыць рэзервовую копію даных перад абнаўленнем
2. Больш падрабязная інфармацыя аб характарыстыках прадукту даступная ў Падказках
3. Калі вы сутыкняцеся з праблемамі падчас абнаўлення, вы можаце атрымаць нашу дапамогу, патэлефанаваўшы на гарачую лінію службы падтрымкі кліентаў Honor або наведаўшы цэнтр абслугоўвання кліентаў Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1026" name="bg-bg">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Уважаеми потребители, тази актуализация подобрява основно ефективността на системата. Актуализирайте, за да се насладите на подобренията</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Движеща се снимка">
             <feature>• Сега можете да зададете движеща се снимка като заключен екран. Изпробвайте като отидете на: „Настройки > Стил и начален екран > Стил на заключения екран > Движеща се снимка“.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Воден знак във филмов стил">
             <feature>• „Камера“ включва водни знаци във филмов стил. Изпробвайте, като отидете на: „Камера > Настройки > Воден знак > ФИЛМ“.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Галерия">
             <feature>• Функцията за предложения за изчистване позволява автоматичното идентифициране на дублирани снимки, сходни изображения и прекалено големи видеа като предоставя по-удобни предложения за изчистване</feature>
             <feature>• „AI Изрязване“ ви позволява да извлечете обекта, да го преместите на ново място в изображението и да промените фона. Опитайте го, като отидете на: „Снимки > AI редактиране > Магическо ретуширане > AI Изрязване“</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• След дълго натискане върху текста на екрана, изскачащата лента с инструменти вече включва функция „Превод“</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Функции за достъпност">
             <feature>• Натиснете двукратно бутона за захранването или, когато екранът е изключен, натиснете двукратно бутона за намаляване силата на звука, за да отворите определено приложение</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Портфейл">
             <feature>• Функцията „Карта за достъп“ поддържа симулация на нешифровани карти за достъп</feature>
             <feature>• „Honor Портфейл“ включва функцията „Празна карта“. Изпробвайте я като отидете на: „Настройки > Honor Портфейл > Карта за достъп“.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Корекция за сигурност">
             <feature>• Корекцията за сигурност на Android (ноември 2025 г.) е включена за защита на системата. За още информация относно актуализациите за сигурност на Honor посетете нашия уебсайт https://www.honor.com/bg/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Бележки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да се отрази на вашите лични данни, но все пак е препоръчително да архивирате данните си преди актуализиране
2. Открийте повече информация за характеристиките на продукта в „Съвети“
3. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализацията, можете да получите нашата помощ, като се обадите на горещата линия за обслужване на Honor или посетите сервизен център на клиенти на Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2117" name="bn-bd">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই আপডেটটি মূলত সিস্টেমের কর্মক্ষমতা বাড়ায়। উন্নতি উপভোগ করতে আপডেট করুন</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="চলমান ফটো">
             <feature>• আপনি এখন লক স্ক্রিন হিসেবে একটি চলমান ফটো সেট করতে পারেন। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > হোম স্ক্রিন এবং স্টাইল > লক স্ক্রিন স্টাইল > চলমান ফটো।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ফিল্ম-স্টাইলের ওয়াটারমার্ক">
             <feature>• ক্যামেরায় ফিল্ম-স্টাইলের ওয়াটারমার্ক রয়েছে। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: ক্যামেরা > সেটিংস > ওয়াটারমার্ক > ফিল্ম।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="গ্যালারি">
             <feature>• ক্লিনআপ সংক্রান্ত পরামর্শ ফিচারটি ডুপ্লিকেট ফটো, অনুরূপ ছবি এবং বড় আকারের ভিডিওগুলির স্বয়ংক্রিয় শনাক্তকরণ সক্ষম করে আরো সুবিধাজনকভাবে পরিষ্কার করার পরামর্শ প্রদান করে</feature>
             <feature>• AI কাটআউট আপনাকে সাবজেক্টটি এক্সট্র্যাক্ট করতে, সেটিকে ছবিতে কোনো নতুন অবস্থানে সরাতে এবং ব্যাকগ্রাউন্ড পরিবর্তন করতে সক্ষম করে। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: ফটোগুলো > AI সম্পাদনা > ম্যাজিক রিটাচ > AI কাটআউট</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• স্ক্রিনের টেক্সটটি দীর্ঘক্ষণ টিপে রাখার পর, পপ-আপ টুলবারে এখন অনুবাদ ফিচারটি অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="প্রবেশযোগ্যতার বৈশিষ্ট্যগুলি">
             <feature>একটি নির্দিষ্ট অ্যাপ খুলতে পাওয়ার বোতামটি দুবার টিপুন অথবা স্ক্রিন বন্ধ থাকা অবস্থায় ভলিউম কমানোর বোতামটি দুবার টিপুন</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ওয়ালেট">
             <feature>• অ্যাক্সেস কার্ড ফিচারটি এনক্রিপ্ট না করা অ্যাক্সেস কার্ডের সিমুলেশনকে সমর্থন করে</feature>
             <feature>• Honor ওয়ালেটে ফাঁকা কার্ড ফিচারটি অন্তর্ভুক্ত আছে। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > Honor ওয়ালেট > অ্যাক্সেস কার্ড।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ">
             <feature>• সিস্টেমের নিরাপত্তার জন্য Android নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ (নভেম্বর 2025) অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে। Honor-এর নিরাপত্তা আপডেটগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্যের জন্য, আমাদের ওয়েবসাইট দেখুন https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="নোট" type="end">
             <feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে তা আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটাকে প্রভাবিত করবে না, তবুও আপডেট করার আগে আপনার ডেটা ব্যাক আপ করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়
2. পরামর্শ-এ পণ্যের ফিচাতগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্য জানুন
3. আপডেট হওয়ার সময় আপনি কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে Honor সেবা হটলাইনে কল করে বা Honor গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে গিয়ে আমাদের সহায়তা পেতে পারেন</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1105" name="bo-cn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནི་གཙོ་བོ་རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ལ་དམིགས་ནས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུའི་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="འགུལ་པར།">
             <feature>• འགུལ་པར་ཡོལ་ཟྭའི་བྱེད་ནུས་ལ་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད་པ་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ ནས་ཅོག་ངོས་དང་སྒེར་གཤིས་ཅན། དེ་ནས་བརྙན་ཡོལ་ཟྭ་རྒྱག་རྣམ་པ། དེ་ནས་འགུལ་པར།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="སྦྱིན་ཤོག་ཁྱད་ཆོས་ཀྱི་ཆུ་དཔར།">
             <feature>• སྦྱིན་ཤོག་ཁྱད་ཆོས་ཀྱི་ཆུ་དཔར་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། པར་ཆས་ཀྱི་སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་ཆུ་དཔར། དེ་ནས་སྦྱིན་ཤོག</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="པར་མཛོད།">
             <feature>• གཙང་བཤེར་གྲོས་གཞིའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། བསྐྱར་ཟློས་ཀྱི་འདྲ་པར་དང་རིགས་འདྲའི་པར་རིས། བསྐྱར་ཟློས་ཆེན་པོ་སོགས་རང་འགུལ་གྱིས་ངོས་འཛིན་བྱས་ནས་སྔར་བས་སྟབས་བདེ་བའི་གཙང་བཤེར་གྲོས་གཞི་མཁོ་འདོན་བྱེད་པར་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
             <feature>• རིག་ལྡན་པར་གཏུབ་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། པར་རིས་གཙོ་གཟུགས་པར་གཏུབ་སྤོ་སྣུར་དང་རྒྱབ་ལྗོངས་བཟོ་བཅོས་ལ་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། འདྲ་པར།ནས་AI རྩོམ་སྒྲིག དེ་ནས་རྫུ་འཕྲུལ་འདྲ་པར་བཟོ་བཅོས་ དེ་ནས་རིག་ལྡན་པར་གཏུབ།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="རིག་ལྡན་མཐོང་ཚོར།">
             <feature>• བརྙན་ཡོལ་གྱི་ཡི་གེ་ཡུན་རིང་གནོན་སྐབས། འཕར་བའི་ཡོ་བྱད་ཚན་པར་ཡིག་སྒྱུར་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="རམ་འདེགས་ཀྱི་རྩོལ་ནུས་">
             <feature>• གློག་ཁུངས་མཐེབ་ལ་ཉིས་རྡེབ་བྱེད་པའམ་ཡོལ་ཞིའི་རྣམ་པའི་འོག་སྒྲ་ཚད་དམའ་གཏོང་མཐེབ་གཅུས་ཉིས་རྡེབ་བྱེད་པ་ན་ངེས་གཏན་གྱི་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཁ་ཕྱེ་བར་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="རུང་ཡོའོ་དངུལ་ཁུག">
             <feature>• སྒོ་སྲུང་བྱང་བུའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། གསང་རྒྱ་ཅན་མིན་པའི་སྒོ་སྲུང་བྱང་བུ་ལ་ལད་ཟློས་བྱེད་པར་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
             <feature>• བྱང་བུ་སྟོང་པའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་རུང་ཡོའོ་དངུལ་ཁུག དེ་ནས་སྒོ་སྲུང་བྱང་བུ།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ།">
             <feature>• ཨན་སྒྲོའི་ 2025 ལོའི་ཟླ་བ་ 11 པའི་བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདྲེས་འཇུག་བྱས་ཏེ། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་སྟོབས་སྒྱུར་གཏོང་། རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉེན་ཆས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནང་དོན་སྐོར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ། རུང་ཡོའོ་གཞུང་ཕྱོགས་དྲ་ཚིགས་ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/11 ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
             <feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གཞི་གྲངས་སུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་སྔོན་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. དེ་ལས་མང་བའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་ལེགས་པོའི་ངོ་སྤྲོད་ཐད་ཁ་པར་རྩེ་བའི་ལག་རྩལ་གྱི་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱ་རོགས།
3. གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་པའི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད་དུ། གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ། ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་མཁོ་མཁན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་ཕེབས་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་འཚོལ་རོགས།</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="5146" name="bs-ba">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo ažuriranje uglavnom poboljšava performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da uživate u poboljšanjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pokretna fotografija">
             <feature>• Sada možete postaviti pokretnu fotografiju kao zaključani ekran. Isprobajte je odlaskom u opciju: Postavke > Početni ekran i stil > Stil zaključanog ekrana > Pokretna fotografija.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vodeni žig u filmskom stilu">
             <feature>• Fotoaparat uključuje vodene žigove u filmskom stilu. Isprobajte ih odlaskom u opciju: Fotoaparat > Postavke > Vodeni žig > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerija">
             <feature>• Funkcija Prijedlozi za čišćenje omogućava automatsko prepoznavanje dupliciranih slika, sličnih slika i prevelikih videozapisa te pruža praktičnije prijedloge za čišćenje</feature>
             <feature>• AI rezanje vam omogućava da izdvojite subjekat, premjestite ga na novi položaj na slici i promijenite pozadinu. Isprobajte odlaskom u opciju: Fotografije > AI uređivanje > Magično retuširanje > AI rezanje</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Nakon dugog pritiska teksta na ekranu, skočna alatna traka sada uključuje funkciju Prevođenja</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkcije za pristupačnost">
             <feature>• Dvaput pritisnite dugme za uključivanje/isključivanje ili, kada je ekran isključen, dvaput pritisnite dugme za smanjenje jačine zvuka da otvorite određenu aplikaciju</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor novčanik">
             <feature>• Funkcija Pristupne kartice podržava simulaciju nešifriranih pristupnih kartica</feature>
             <feature>• Honor novčanik uključuje funkciju Prazna kartica. Isprobajte je odlaskom u opciju: Postavke > Honor novčanik > Pristupna kartica.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sigurnosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Ugrađena je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (novembar 2025.) radi sigurnosti sistema. Više informacija o Honor sigurnosnim ažuriranjima potražite na našoj web lokaciji https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Bilješke" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja ne utiče na lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o funkcijama proizvoda u Savjetima
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete zatražiti našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati Honor dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetiti Honor servisni centar za korisnike</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1027" name="ca-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització millora principalment el rendiment del sistema. Actualitzeu-la per gaudir de les millores</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Foto en moviment">
             <feature>• Ara podeu establir una foto en moviment com a pantalla de bloqueig. Per provar-ho, aneu a Configuració > Pantalla inicial i estil > Estil de pantalla de bloqueig > Foto en moviment.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Filigrana amb estil cinematogràfic">
             <feature>• La Càmera inclou filigranes d'estil cinematogràfic. Per provar-les, aneu a Càmera > Configuració > Filigrana > PEL·LÍCULA.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galeria">
             <feature>• La funció de Suggeriments de neteja permet la identificació automàtica de fotos duplicades, imatges similars i vídeos de mida excessiva, i ofereix suggeriments de neteja més pràctics</feature>
             <feature>• Retall amb IA us permet extreure el subjecte, desplaçar-lo a una nova posició a la imatge i canviar el fons. Per provar-ho, aneu a: Fotos > Edició amb IA > Retoc màgic > Retall amb IA</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Després de fer una pulsació llarga al text de la pantalla, la barra d'eines emergent ara inclou la funció Traduir</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funcions d'accessibilitat">
             <feature>• Premeu dues vegades el botó d'encesa o, quan la pantalla estigui apagada, premeu dues vegades el botó d'abaixar el volum per obrir una aplicació específica</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Cartera">
             <feature>• La funció de targeta d'accés admet la simulació de targetes d'accés sense xifrar</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Cartera inclou una funció de Targeta en blanc. Per provar-ho, aneu a Configuració > Honor Cartera > Targeta d'accés.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pedaç de seguretat">
             <feature>S'ha incorporat el pedaç de seguretat d'Android (novembre del 2025) per garantir la seguretat del sistema. Per obtenir més informació sobre les actualitzacions de seguretat d'Honor, consulteu el nostre lloc web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. El fet d'instal·lar aquesta actualització no afectarà les vostres dades personals, però es recomana fer una còpia de seguretat de les dades abans d'iniciar l'actualització
2. Descobriu més informació sobre les funcions del producte a Suggeriments
3. Si trobeu algun problema durant l'actualització, per obtenir la nostra ajuda truqueu a la Línia directa d'atenció al client d'Honor o visiteu el Centre d'atenció al client d'Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1029" name="cs-cz">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Vážený uživateli, tato aktualizace především zvyšuje výkon systému. Aktualizujte, abyste si mohli užít vylepšení</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pohyblivé fotografie">
             <feature>• Nyní můžete jako zamčenou obrazovku nastavit pohyblivou fotografii. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce Nastavení > Domovská obrazovka a styl > Styl zámku obrazovky > Pohyblivá fotografie.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vodoznak ve filmovém stylu">
             <feature>• Fotoaparát obsahuje vodoznaky ve filmovém stylu. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce Fotoaparát > Nastavení > Vodoznak > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerie">
             <feature>• Funkce návrhů na čištění umožňuje automatickou identifikaci duplicitních fotografií, podobných obrázků a nadměrně velkých videí a poskytuje tak pohodlnější návrhy na čištění</feature>
             <feature>• Funkce AI Výřez umožňuje vyjmout předmět, přesunout ho na novou pozici v obraze a změnit pozadí. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce Fotografie > AI Úpravy > Magická retuš > AI Výřez</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Po dlouhém stisknutí textu na obrazovce se nyní v rozbalovacím panelu nástrojů zobrazí funkce Přeložit</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkce usnadnění">
             <feature>• Dvakrát stiskněte tlačítko napájení nebo, když je obrazovka vypnutá, dvakrát stiskněte tlačítko snížení hlasitosti a otevřete tak konkrétní aplikaci</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Peněženka">
             <feature>• Funkce přístupové karty podporuje simulaci nešifrovaných přístupových karet.</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Peněženka obsahuje funkci Prázdná karta. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce Nastavení > Honor Peněženka > Přístupová karta.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Oprava zabezpečení">
             <feature>• Do systému byla začleněna bezpečnostní oprava (listopad 2025) pro systém Android pro zajištění bezpečnosti systému. Více informací o bezpečnostních aktualizacích Honor najdete na našem webu https://www.honor.com/cz/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Poznámky" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalace této aktualizace neovlivní vaše osobní data, ale přesto doporučujeme před aktualizací zálohovat data.
2. Další informace o funkcích produktu najdete v aplikaci Tipy.
3. Pokud během aktualizace narazíte na nějaké problémy, zavolejte na informační linku Honor nebo navštivte Centrum služeb zákazníkům Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1030" name="da-dk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Kære bruger. Denne opdatering forbedrer hovedsageligt systemets ydeevne. Opdater for at drage nytte af forbedringerne</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bevægeligt foto">
             <feature>• Du kan nu indstille et bevægeligt foto som låseskærm. Prøv det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Startskærm og stil > Låseskærmstil > Bevægeligt foto.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vandmærke i filmstil">
             <feature>• Kamera inkluderer vandmærker i filmstil. Prøv det ved at gå til: Kamera > Indstillinger > Vandmærke > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galleri">
             <feature>• Funktionen Oprydningsforslag giver mulighed for automatisk identifikation af identiske billeder, lignende billeder og for store videoer, hvilket giver mere praktiske oprydningsforslag</feature>
             <feature>• AI-udskæring giver dig mulighed for at udtrække motivet, flytte det til et nyt sted på billedet og ændre baggrunden. Prøv det ved at gå til: Fotos > AI Redigering > Magisk retouchering > AI-udskæring</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Når du har trykket længe på teksten på skærmen, indeholder pop op-værktøjslinjen nu funktionen Oversæt</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tilgængelighedsfunktioner">
             <feature>• Tryk to gange på tænd/sluk-knappen, eller tryk to gange på lydstyrkeknappen, når skærmen er slukket, for at åbne en bestemt app</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Tegnebog">
             <feature>• Adgangskortfunktion understøtter simulering af ukrypterede adgangskort</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Tegnebog inkluderer funktionen Tomt kort. Prøv det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Honor Tegnebog > Adgangskort.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sikkerhedspatch">
             <feature>• Android sikkerhedspatch (nov 2025) er blevet inkluderet for øget systemsikkerhed. Du kan få flere oplysninger om Honor-sikkerhedsopdateringer på vores websted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Noter" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering påvirker ikke dine personlige data, men vi anbefaler alligevel, at du sikkerhedskopierer dine data inden opdateringen
2. Få flere oplysninger om produktfunktioner i Tips
3. Hvis du oplever problemer under opdateringen, kan du få hjælp ved at ringe til Honors servicehotline eller besøge Honors kundeservicecenter</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1031" name="de-de">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung verbessert hauptsächlich die Systemleistung. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bewegungsfoto">
             <feature>• Sie können jetzt ein Bewegungsfoto als Sperrbildschirm festlegen. Probieren Sie es aus. Gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Startbildschirm und Stil > Sperrbildschirmstil > Bewegungsfoto.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Film-Stil-Wasserzeichen">
             <feature>• Die Kamera enthält Film-Stil-Wasserzeichen. Probieren Sie es aus. Gehen Sie zu: Kamera > Einstellungen > Wasserzeichen > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerie">
             <feature>• Die Funktion Bereinigungsvorschläge ermöglicht die automatische Identifizierung doppelter Fotos, ähnlicher Bilder und übergroßer Videos und stellt praktischere Bereinigungsvorschläge bereit</feature>
             <feature>• Mit KI-Ausschnitt können Sie das Motiv extrahieren, an eine neue Position im Bild verschieben und den Hintergrund ändern. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Fotos > KI-Bearbeitung > Magisches Retuschieren > KI-Ausschnitt</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Nach langem Drücken des Textes auf dem Bildschirm enthält die Pop-up-Symbolleiste jetzt die Funktion Übersetzung</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bedienungshilfen">
             <feature>• Drücken Sie zweimal die Ein-/Aus-Taste oder, wenn der Bildschirm ausgeschaltet ist, zweimal die Leiser-Taste drücken, um eine bestimmte App zu öffnen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• Die Funktion Zugangskarte unterstützt die Simulation unverschlüsselter Zugangskarten</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet enthält die Funktion Blankokarte. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Honor Wallet > Zugangskarte.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sicherheitspatch">
             <feature>• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Nov. 2025) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die Honor Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notizen" type="end">
             <feature>1. Die Installation dieses Updates hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, es wird jedoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen
2. Entdecken Sie weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen in Tipps
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Honor-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein Honor-Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1032" name="el-gr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιώνει κυρίως την απόδοση του συστήματος. Πραγματοποιήστε ενημέρωση για να απολαύσετε τις βελτιώσεις</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Φωτογραφία με κίνηση">
             <feature>• Μπορείτε πλέον να ορίσετε μια φωτογραφία με κίνηση ως οθόνη κλειδώματος. Δοκιμάστε το μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Αρχική οθόνη και στυλ > Στυλ κλειδώματος οθόνης > Φωτογραφία με κίνηση.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Υδατογράφημα σε στυλ ταινίας">
             <feature>• Η Κάμερα περιλαμβάνει υδατογραφήματα σε στυλ ταινίας. Δοκιμάστε το μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Κάμερα > Ρυθμίσεις > Υδατογράφημα > ΤΑΙΝΙΑ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Συλλογή">
             <feature>• Η δυνατότητα Προτάσεων εκκαθάρισης επιτρέπει την αυτόματη αναγνώριση διπλότυπων φωτογραφιών, παρόμοιων εικόνων και βίντεο πολύ μεγάλου μεγέθους, παρέχοντας προτάσεις για πιο εύκολη εκκαθάριση</feature>
             <feature>• Η Αποκοπή AI σας επιτρέπει να εξαγάγετε το θέμα, να το μετακινήσετε σε νέα θέση στην εικόνα και να αλλάξετε το φόντο. Δοκιμάστε το μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Φωτογραφίες > Επεξεργασία με AI > Μαγικό ρετούς > Αποκοπή AI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Αφού πατήσετε παρατεταμένα το κείμενο στην οθόνη, η αναδυόμενη γραμμή εργαλείων περιλαμβάνει πλέον τη δυνατότητα Μετάφρασης</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Δυνατότητες προσβασιμότητας">
             <feature>• Πατήστε δύο φορές το κουμπί λειτουργίας ή, όταν η οθόνη είναι απενεργοποιημένη, πατήστε δύο φορές το κουμπί μείωσης έντασης ήχου για να ανοίξετε μια συγκεκριμένη εφαρμογή</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Πορτοφόλι Honor">
             <feature>• Η δυνατότητα κάρτας πρόσβασης υποστηρίζει την προσομοίωση μη κρυπτογραφημένων καρτών πρόσβασης</feature>
             <feature>• Το Πορτοφόλι Honor περιλαμβάνει τη δυνατότητα «Κενή κάρτα». Δοκιμάστε το μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Πορτοφόλι Honor > Κάρτα πρόσβασης.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφάλειας">
             <feature>• Η ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας Android (Νοέμβριος 2025) ενσωματώθηκε για την ασφάλεια του συστήματος. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις ενημερώσεις της Ασφάλειας Honor, επισκεφθείτε τον ιστότοπό μας https://www.honor.com/gr/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Σημειώσεις" type="end">
             <feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα επηρεάσει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, αλλά ακόμη και έτσι συνιστάται η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας των δεδομένων σας πριν από την ενημέρωση
2. Ανακαλύψτε περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις δυνατότητες του προϊόντος στις Συμβουλές
3. Αν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, μπορείτε να λάβετε τη βοήθειά μας καλώντας την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή εξυπηρέτησης της Honor ή με επίσκεψη σε ένα κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2057" name="en-GB">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Dear user, this update mainly enhances the system performance. Update to enjoy the improvements</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Moving Photo">
             <feature>• You can now set a moving photo as the lock screen. Try it out by going to: Settings > Home screen &amp; style > Lock screen style > Moving photo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Film-style watermark">
             <feature>• Camera includes film-style watermarks. Try it out by going to: Camera > Settings > Watermark > FILM</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Gallery">
             <feature>• Cleanup suggestions feature enables automatic identification of duplicate photos, similar images, and oversized videos, providing more convenient cleaning suggestions</feature>
             <feature>• AI Cutout enables you to extract the subject, move it to a new position in the image, and change the background. Try it out by going to: Photos > AI Edit > Magic Retouch > AI Cutout</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• After long-pressing the text on the screen, the pop-up toolbar now includes Translate feature</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Accessibility features">
             <feature>• Double-press the Power button or, when the screen is off, double-press the Volume down button to open a specified app</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• Access card feature supports the simulation of unencrypted access cards</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet includes Blank card feature. Try it out by going to: Settings > Honor Wallet > Access card</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Security patch">
             <feature>• Android security patch (Nov 2025) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about Honor Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating
2. Discover more information on product features in Tips
3. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling Honor service hotline or visiting Honor customer service centre</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1034" name="es-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado/a usuario/a, esta actualización mejora principalmente el rendimiento del sistema. Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Foto en movimiento">
             <feature>• Ahora puede configurar una foto en movimiento como pantalla de bloqueo. Pruebe la función en: Ajustes > Pantalla principal y estilo > Estilo de pantalla de bloqueo > Foto en movimiento.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Marca de agua estilo película">
             <feature>• Cámara incluye marcas de agua estilo película. Pruébelas en: Cámara > Ajustes > Marca de agua > PELÍCULA.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galería">
             <feature>• La funcionalidad Sugerencias de limpieza permite la identificación automática de fotos duplicadas, imágenes similares y vídeos de gran tamaño, lo que proporciona sugerencias de limpieza más útiles</feature>
             <feature>• Recorte con IA le permite extraer el sujeto, moverlo a una nueva posición en la imagen y cambiar el fondo. Pruébelo en Fotos > Edición con IA > Retoque mágico > Recorte con IA</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Después de mantener pulsado el texto en la pantalla, la barra de herramientas emergente ahora incluye la funcionalidad Traducir</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funciones de accesibilidad">
             <feature>• Pulse dos veces el botón de encendido o, cuando la pantalla esté apagada, pulse dos veces el botón de disminución de volumen para abrir una aplicación específica</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• La funcionalidad de tarjeta de acceso admite la simulación de tarjetas de acceso no cifradas</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet incluye una funcionalidad de tarjeta en blanco. Pruébela en: Ajustes > Honor Wallet > Tarjeta de acceso.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Parche de seguridad">
             <feature>• Se ha incorporado el parche de seguridad de Android (noviembre de 2025) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de Honor, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/es/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar
2. Descubra más información sobre las características de los productos en Sugerencias
3. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, puede obtener nuestra ayuda si llama a la línea de atención al cliente de Honor o si visita el centro de servicios al cliente de Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="21514" name="es-us">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización mejora principalmente el rendimiento del sistema. Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Foto en movimiento">
             <feature>• Ahora puede configurar una foto en movimiento como pantalla de bloqueo. Pruebe la función en: Ajustes > Pantalla principal y estilo > Estilo pantalla bloqueo > Foto en movimiento.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Marca de agua estilo película">
             <feature>• Cámara incluye marcas de agua estilo película. Pruébelas en: Cámara > Ajustes > Marca de agua > PELÍCULA.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galería">
             <feature>• La funcionalidad de sugerencias de limpieza identifica automáticamente fotos duplicadas, imágenes similares y videos muy pesados, ofreciendo recomendaciones para liberar espacio</feature>
             <feature>• Recorte con IA le permite extraer el sujeto, moverlo a una nueva posición en la imagen y cambiar el fondo. Pruebe la función en: Fotos > Edición de IA > Retoque mágico > Recorte con IA</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Lente de Honor">
             <feature>• Después de mantener presionado el texto en la pantalla, la barra de herramientas emergente ahora incluye la funcionalidad Traducir</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funciones de accesibilidad">
             <feature>• Presione dos veces el botón de encendido o, cuando la pantalla esté apagada, presione dos veces el botón de disminución de volumen para abrir una aplicación específica</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• La función Tarjeta de acceso permite simular tarjetas de acceso sin cifrar</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet incluye la función de tarjeta en blanco. Pruebe en: Ajustes > Honor Wallet > Tarjeta de acceso.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Parche de seguridad">
             <feature>• Se incorporó un parche de seguridad de Android (noviembre de 2025) para mejorar la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de Honor, visite nuestro sitio web https://www.honor.com/latam/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de respaldo de sus datos antes de actualizar
2. Descubra más información sobre las funciones del producto en Sugerencias
3. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, puede llamar a la línea de atención al cliente de Honor o visitar el centro de servicios al cliente de Honor para recibir asistencia</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1061" name="et-ee">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hea kasutaja! See värskendus parandab peamiselt süsteemi jõudlust. Värskendage täiustuste nautimiseks</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Liikuv foto">
             <feature>• Nüüd saate lukustuskuvaks määrata liikuva foto. Proovige seda, avades Sätted > Avakuva ja stiil > Lukustuskuva laad > Liikuv foto.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Filmistiilis vesimärk">
             <feature>• Kaamera sisaldab filmistiilis vesimärke. Proovige seda, avades Kaamera > Sätted > Vesimärk > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerii">
             <feature>• Puhastussoovituste funktsioon võimaldab automaatselt tuvastada topeltfotod, sarnased pildid ja ülisuured videoid, pakkudes mugavamaid puhastussoovitusi</feature>
             <feature>• AI-väljalõige võimaldab teil objekti eraldada, selle pildil uude kohta viia ja tausta muuta. Proovige seda, avades Fotod > AI-redigeerimine > Maagiline retušeerimine > AI-väljalõige</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Pärast ekraanil oleva teksti pikka vajutamist kuvatakse hüpiktööriistaribal nüüd ka tõlke funktsioon</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Hõlbustusfunktsioonid">
             <feature>• Topeltvajutage toitenuppu või väljalülitatud ekraani korral helitugevuse vähendamise nuppu, et avada soovitud rakendus</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honori rahakott">
             <feature>• Pääsukaardi funktsioon toetab krüptimata pääsukaartide simuleerimist</feature>
             <feature>• Honori rahakott sisaldab tühja kaardi funktsiooni. Proovige seda, avades Sätted > Honori rahakott > Pääsukaart.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Turvapaik">
             <feature>• Süsteemi turvalisuse tagamiseks rakendati Androidi turvapaik (november 2025). Lisateavet Honori turvavärskenduste kohta leiate meie veebisaidilt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Märkused" type="end">
             <feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei mõjuta teie isiklikke andmeid, aga soovitame ikkagi enne värskendamist andmed varundada
2. Toote funktsioonide kohta leiate lisateavet rakendusest Tips
3. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, saate meilt abi, helistades Honori klienditoe infoliinile või külastades Honori klienditeeninduskeskust</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1069" name="eu-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Erabiltzaile agurgarria: eguneratze honek sistemaren errendimendua hobetzen du nagusiki. Eguneratu hobekuntzez gozatzeko</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Argazki mugikorra">
             <feature>• Orain, argazki mugikor bat blokeatutako pantaila gisa ezar dezakezu. Probatzeko, joan hona: Ezarpenak > Hasierako pantaila eta estiloa > Pantaila-blokeoaren estiloa > Argazki mugikorra.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Film estiloko ur-marka">
             <feature>• Kamerak film-estiloko ur-markak ditu. Probatzeko, joan hona: Kamera > Ezarpenak > Ur-marka > FILMA.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galeria">
             <feature>• Garbiketa-iradokizunen eginbideak argazki bikoiztuen, antzeko argazkien eta tamaina handiko bideoen identifikazio automatikoa gaitzen du, garbiketa-iradokizun egokiagoa emanez</feature>
             <feature>• AA ebakinak subjektua erauzteko, irudian posizio berri batera mugitzeko eta hondoa aldatzeko aukera ematen dizu. Probatu hemen: Argazkiak > AA edizioa > Ukitu magikoa > AA ebakina</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Pantailan testua sakatuta eduki ondoren, tresna-barran Itzuli funtzioa agertuko da</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Erabilerraztasun-eginbideak">
             <feature>• Sakatu bi aldiz Pizteko botoia edo, pantaila itzalita dagoenean, sakatu bi aldiz Bolumena jaisteko botoia zehaztutako aplikazio bat irekitzeko</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Diru-zorroa">
             <feature>• Sartzeko txartelaren eginbideak enkriptatu gabeko sartzeko txartelen simulazioa onartzen du</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Diru-zorroak Txartel hutsa funtzioa barne du. Probatzeko, joan hona: Ezarpenak > Honor Diru-zorroa > Sartzeko txartela.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Segurtasun-adabakia">
             <feature>• Android-en segurtasun-adabakia (2025eko azaroa) gehitu da sistemaren segurtasuna bermatzeko. Honor Segurtasun-eguneratzeei buruzko informazio gehiago lortzeko, ikusi gure gunea: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Oharrak" type="end">
             <feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzeak ez du eraginik izango datu pertsonaletan, baina, eguneratu baino lehen, datuen babeskopia egitea gomendatzen da
2. Ezagutu produktuaren eginbideei buruzko informazio gehiago Aholkuak atalean
3. Eguneratzean arazoren bat baduzu, gure laguntza eska dezakezu Honor-en telefonozko arreta-lineara deituz edo Honor-en bezeroaren zerbitzu-zentrora joanez</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1065" name="fa-ir">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>کاربر گرامی، این به‌روزرسانی به‌طور عمده عملکرد سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد. با انجام این به‌روزرسانی، از این بهبودها بهره‌مند شوید</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="عکس متحرک">
             <feature>‏• اکنون می‌توانید یک عکس متحرک را به‌عنوان صفحۀ قفل تنظیم کنید. آن را با رفتن به این قسمت امتحان کنید: «تنظیمات > صفحۀ اصلی و سبک > سبک صفحۀ قفل > عکس متحرک».</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="واترمارک به سبک فیلم">
             <feature>‏• «دوربین» شامل واترمارک‌هایی به سبک فیلم است. برای امتحان کردن آن به این قسمت بروید: «دوربین > تنظیمات > واترمارک > فیلم».</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="گالری">
             <feature>‏• قابلیت «پیشنهادهای پاکسازی»، امکان شناسایی خودکار عکس‌های تکراری، تصاویر مشابه و ویدیوهای حجیم را فراهم می‌کند و پیشنهادهای پاکسازی راحت‌تر را ارائه می‌دهد</feature>
             <feature>‏• «برش با هوش مصنوعی» به شما امکان می‌دهد سوژه را خارج کنید، آن را به موقعیت جدیدی در تصویر ببرید و پس‌زمینه را تغییر دهید. آن را با رفتن به این قسمت امتحان کنید: عکس‌ها > ویرایش با هوش مصنوعی > روتوش جادویی > برش با هوش مصنوعی</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="لنز Honor">
             <feature>‏• از این پس، بعد از فشار دادن طولانی متن روی صفحۀ نمایش، نوار ابزار بازشونده شامل قابلیت «ترجمه» است</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="امکانات مربوط به قابلیت دسترسی">
             <feature>‏• دکمه «روشن/خاموش» را دو بار فشار دهید، یا زمانی که صفحۀ نمایش خاموش است، دکمه «کاهش صدا» را دو بار فشار دهید تا برنامه مشخصی باز شود</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="کیف پول Honor">
             <feature>‏‏• قابلیت «کارت دسترسی» از شبیه‌سازی کارت‌های دسترسی رمزگذاری‌نشده پشتیبانی می‌کند</feature>
             <feature>‏• «کیف پول Honor» شامل قابلیت «کارت خالی» است. آن را با رفتن به این قسمت امتحان کنید: « تنظیمات > کیف پول Honor > کارت دسترسی».</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="وصلۀ امنیتی">
             <feature>‏• برای حفظ امنیت سیستم، «وصلۀ امنیتی Android (نوامبر ۲۰۲۵)» گنجانده شده است. برای کسب اطلاعات بیشتر دربارۀ به‌روزرسانی‌های «امنیت Honor»، لطفاً به وب‌سایت ما مراجعه کنید: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="یادداشت‌ها" type="end">
             <feature>‏۱. نصب این به‌روزرسانی روی داده‌های شخصی شما تأثیری نخواهد داشت. بااین‌وجود، توصیه می‌شود قبل از به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید
‏۲. اطلاعات بیشتر مربوط به قابلیت‌های محصول را در «نکات» می‌توانید بیابید
‏۳. اگر در طول به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، می‌توانید از طریق تماس با تلفن مستقیم خدمات Honor یا مراجعه به مرکز خدمات مشتریان Honor از ما کمک بگیرید</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1035" name="fi-fi">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä päivitys parantaa ensisijaisesti järjestelmän suorituskykyä. Päivitä, niin pääset nauttimaan parannuksista</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Liikkuva valokuva">
             <feature>• Voit nyt asettaa liikkuvan valokuvan lukitusnäytöksi. Kokeile kohdassa: Asetukset > Aloitusnäyttö ja tyyli > Lukitusnäytön tyyli > Liikkuva valokuva.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Filmityylinen vesileima">
             <feature>• Kamera sisältää filmityyliset vesileimat. Kokeile kohdassa: Kamera > Asetukset > Vesileima > FILMI.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galleria">
             <feature>• Puhdistusehdotukset-ominaisuus mahdollistaa valokuvien kaksoiskappaleiden, samankaltaisten kuvien ja ylisuurten videoiden automaattisen tunnistuksen ja tarjoaa käteviä puhdistusehdotuksia</feature>
             <feature>AI-leikkaus mahdollistaa kohteen poimimisen ja siirtämisen uuteen kohtaan kuvassa sekä taustan vaihtamisen. Voit kokeilla sitä seuraavassa kohdassa: Valokuvat > AI-muokkaus > Magic-retusointi > AI-leikkaus</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Työkalupalkki, joka avautuu, kun näytöllä olevaa tekstiä painetaan pitkään, sisältää nyt Käännä-ominaisuuden</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Helppokäyttöominaisuudet">
             <feature>• Avaa tietty sovellus painamalla Virta-painiketta kaksi kertaa tai, kun näyttö on poissa päältä, painamalla äänenvoimakkuuden vähennyspainiketta kaksi kertaa</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• Kulkukortti-ominaisuus tukee salaamattomien kulkukorttien simulointia</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Walletiin sisältyy Tyhjä kortti -ominaisuus. Voit kokeilla sitä menemällä kohtaan Asetukset > Honor Wallet > Kulkukortti.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Turvallisuuskorjaus">
             <feature>• Android-turvallisuuskorjaus (marraskuu 2025) on lisätty järjestelmän turvallisuutta varten. Lisätietoja Honorin turvallisuuspäivityksistä on saatavilla verkkosivustollamme osoitteessa https://www.honor.com/fi/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Muistiinpanot" type="end">
             <feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei vaikuta henkilökohtaisiin tietoihisi, mutta tietojen varmuuskopiointi ennen päivittämistä on kuitenkin suositeltavaa
2. Lisätietoja tuoteominaisuuksista on Vihjeitä-sovelluksessa
3. Jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia, saat apua soittamalla Honorin palvelunumeroon tai käymällä Honorin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1036" name="fr-fr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour améliore principalement les performances du système. Effectuez la mise à jour pour profiter des améliorations</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Photo dynamique">
             <feature>• Vous pouvez désormais définir une photo dynamique en tant qu'écran verrouillé. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Écran d'accueil et style > Style d'écran verrouillé > Photo dynamique.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Filigrane de style film">
             <feature>• Appareil photo comprend des filigranes de style film. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Appareil photo > Paramètres > Filigrane > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerie">
             <feature>• La fonctionnalité Suggestions de nettoyage permet l'identification automatique des photos en double, des images similaires et des vidéos surdimensionnées, proposant ainsi des suggestions de nettoyage plus pratiques</feature>
             <feature>• Découpe IA vous permet d'extraire le sujet, de le déplacer dans une nouvelle position dans l'image et de modifier l'arrière-plan. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Photos > Modification par IA > Retouche magique > Découpe IA</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Après un appui long sur le texte à l'écran, la barre d'outils contextuelle inclut désormais la fonctionnalité Traduire</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fonctionnalités d'accessibilité">
             <feature>• Appuyez deux fois sur le bouton d'alimentation ou, lorsque l'écran est éteint, appuyez deux fois sur le bouton du volume bas pour ouvrir une application spécifiée</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• La fonction Carte d'accès prend en charge la simulation de cartes d'accès non cryptées</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet comprend la fonctionnalité Carte vierge. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Honor Wallet > Carte d'accès.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Correctif de sécurité">
             <feature>• Un correctif de sécurité Android (novembre 2025) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité Honor, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour
2. Découvrez plus d'informations sur les fonctionnalités du produit dans Astuces
3. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes pendant la mise à jour, vous pouvez obtenir de l'aide en contactant la hotline de service Honor ou en vous rendant dans un centre de services clients Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1110" name="gl-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado usuario, a novidade principal desta actualización é a mellora do rendemento do sistema. Realice a actualización para gozar das melloras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Foto en movemento">
             <feature>• Agora pode establecer unha foto en movemento como a pantalla de bloqueo. Para probalo, vaia a: Configuración > Pantalla de inicio e estilo > Estilo de bloqueo de pantalla > Foto en movemento.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Marca de auga estilo película">
             <feature>• Cámara inclúe marcas de auga estilo película. Para probalo, vaia a: Cámara > Configuración > Marca de auga > PELÍCULA.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galería">
             <feature>• A función de suxestións de limpeza permite identificar automaticamente fotos duplicadas, imaxes similares e vídeos de gran tamaño mediante prácticas suxestións de limpeza</feature>
             <feature>• Recorte con IA permite extraer o punto de interese, movelo a unha nova posición na imaxe e cambiar o fondo. Realice unha proba en Fotos > Edición con IA > Retoque máxico > Recorte con IA</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Despois de premer prolongadamente o texto na pantalla, a barra de ferramentas emerxente agora inclúe a funcionalidade Traducir</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Características de accesibilidade">
             <feature>• Prema dúas veces o botón de acendido ou, coa pantalla apagada, prema dúas veces o botón de baixar o volume para abrir unha determinada aplicación</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Moedeiro Honor">
             <feature>• A funcionalidade Tarxeta de acceso é compatible coa simulación de tarxetas de acceso sen cifrar</feature>
             <feature>• Moedeiro Honor inclúe a funcionalidade Tarxeta en branco. Para probala, vaia a Configuración > Moedeiro Honor > Tarxeta de acceso.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Parche de seguranza">
             <feature>• Incorporárase un parche de seguranza de Android (novembro de 2025) para a seguranza do sistema. Para obter máis información sobre as actualizacións de seguranza de Honor, visite o noso sitio web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalar esta actualización non afectará os seus datos persoais, pero recoméndase que realice unha copia de seguranza dos datos antes da actualización
2. Descubra máis información sobre as funcionalidades do produto en Consellos
3. Se experimenta problemas durante a actualización, pode chamar á liña directa de servizo de Honor ou ir a un centro de servizos ao cliente de Honor para que lle fornezamos axuda</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1095" name="gu-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ અપડેટ મુખ્યત્વે સિસ્ટમની કામગીરીને વધારે છે. સુધારાનો આનંદ માણવા માટે અપડેટ કરો</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ફરતો ફોટો">
             <feature>• તમે હવે ફરતો ફોટો લૉક સ્ક્રીન તરીકે સેટ કરી શકો છો. સેટિંગ્સ > હોમ સ્ક્રીન અને શૈલી > લૉક સ્ક્રીન શૈલી > ફરતો ફોટો પર જઈને તેને અજમાવી જુઓ.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ફિલ્મ-શૈલીનું વૉટરમાર્ક">
             <feature>• કૅમેરામાં ફિલ્મ-શૈલીના વૉટરમાર્કનો સમાવેશ થાય છે. કૅમેરા > સેટિંગ્સ > વૉટરમાર્ક > ફિલ્મ પર જઈને તેને અજમાવી જુઓ.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ગૅલેરી">
             <feature>• ક્લિનઅપ સૂચનો સુવિધા ડુપ્લિકેટ ફોટા, સમાન છબીઓ અને મોટા કદના વિડિઓઝની સ્વચાલિત ઓળખને સક્ષમ કરે છે, જે વધુ અનુકૂળ સફાઈ સૂચનો પ્રદાન કરે છે</feature>
             <feature>• AI કટઆઉટ તમને વિષયને એક્સટ્રેક્ટ કરવા, તેને છબીમાં નવી જગ્યાએ ખસેડવા અને પૃષ્ઠભૂમિ બદલવા માટે સક્ષમ કરે છે. ફોટા > AI સંપાદન > મેજિક રિટચ > AI કટઆઉટપર જઈને તેને અજમાવી જુઓ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• સ્ક્રીન પર ટેક્સ્ટને લાંબા સમય સુધી દબાવી રાખ્યા પછી, પોપ-અપ ટૂલબારમાં હવે અનુવાદ સુવિધા શામેલ છે</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ઍક્સેસિબિલિટી સુવિધાઓ">
             <feature>• ચોક્કસ એપ્લિકેશન ખોલવા માટે પાવર બટનને બે વાર દબાવો અથવા જ્યારે સ્ક્રીન બંધ હોય, ત્યારે વૉલ્યૂમ ઘટાડો બટનને બે વાર દબાવો</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor વૉલેટ">
             <feature>• ઍક્સેસ કાર્ડ સુવિધા એન્ક્રિપ્ટ કરેલ ન હોય તેવા ઍક્સેસ કાર્ડના સિમ્યુલેશનનું સમર્થન કરે છે</feature>
             <feature>Honor વૉલેટમાં ખાલી કાર્ડ સુવિધા શામેલ છે. સેટિંગ્સ > Honor વૉલેટ > ઍક્સેસ કાર્ડ પર જઈને તેમને અજમાવી જુઓ.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="સુરક્ષા પેચ">
             <feature>• Android સુરક્ષા પેચ (નવેમ્બર 2025) સિસ્ટમ સુરક્ષા માટે સામેલ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. Honor સુરક્ષા અપડેટ્સ વિશે વધુ માહિતી માટે, કૃપા કરીને અમારી વેબસાઇટ ની મુલાકાત લો https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="નોંધો" type="end">
             <feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારા વ્યક્તિગત ડેટાને અસર થશે નહીં, પરંતુ અપડેટ કરતા પહેલાં તમારા ડેટાનો બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે
2. ટિપ્સમાં ઉત્પાદન સુવિધાઓ વિશે વધુ માહિતી મેળવો
3. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો તમે Honor સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરીને અથવા Honor ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્રની મુલાકાત લઈને અમારી મદદ મેળવી શકો છો</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1081" name="hi-in">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>नमस्ते उपयोगकर्ता, इस अद्यतन से मुख्य रूप से सिस्टम प्रदर्शन को बढ़ाया जाता है। सुधारों का फ़ायदा उठाने के लिए अद्यतन करें</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="गतिमान फ़ोटो">
             <feature>• अब आप गतिमान फ़ोटो को लॉक स्क्रीन के रूप में सेट कर सकते हैं। यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़माएँ: सेटिंग्स > होम स्क्रीन और शैली > स्क्रीन लॉक शैली > गतिमान फ़ोटो।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="फ़िल्म शैली वाला वाटरमार्क">
             <feature>• कैमरे में फ़िल्म शैली वाले वाटरमार्क शामिल हैं। यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़माएँ: कैमरा > सेटिंग्स > वाटरमार्क > फ़िल्म।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="गैलरी">
             <feature>• क्लीनअप के सुझाव वाली सुविधा से डुप्लिकेट फ़ोटो, मिलती-जुलती छवियों और बड़े साइज़ वाले वीडियो की स्वचालित पहचान सक्षम हो जाती है, ताकि सफ़ाई के अधिक सुविधाजनक सुझाव दिए जा सकें</feature>
             <feature>• AI कटआउट से आपको विषय को अलग करने, उसे छवि में नए स्थान पर ले जाने और पृष्ठभूमि बदलने की सुविधा मिलती है। यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़माएँ: फ़ोटो > AI संपादन > मैजिक रीटच > AI कटआउट</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor लेंस">
             <feature>• स्क्रीन पर मौजूद पाठ पर देर तक दबाने के बाद, पॉप-अप टूलबार में अब अनुवाद सुविधा शामिल हो जाती है</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="पहुँच क्षमता सुविधाएँ">
             <feature>• विशेष ऐप खोलने के लिए पॉवर बटन को दो बार दबाएँ या स्क्रीन बंद होने पर वॉल्यूम डाउन बटन को दो बार दबाएँ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor वॉलेट">
             <feature>• पहुँच कार्ड सुविधा में बिना एन्क्रिप्ट किए गए पहुँच कार्ड के सिमुलेशन का समर्थन किया जाता है</feature>
             <feature>• Honor वॉलेट में ब्लैंक कार्ड सुविधा शामिल है। यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़माएँ: सेटिंग्स > Honor वॉलेट > पहुँच कार्ड।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षा पैच">
             <feature>• सिस्टम की सुरक्षा के लिए Android सुरक्षा पैच (नवंबर, 2025) शामिल किया गया है। Honor सुरक्षा अद्यतनों के बारे में अधिक जानकारी के लिए, हमारी वेबसाइट पर जाएँ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोट्स" type="end">
             <feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपके व्यक्तिगत डेटा पर कोई प्रभाव नहीं पड़ेगा, लेकिन फिर भी अद्यतन करने से पहले अपने डेटा का बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है
2. युक्तियाँ में जाकर उत्पाद की सुविधाओं के बारे में अधिक जानकारी खोजें
3. अगर आपको अद्यतन के दौरान कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो आप Honor सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करके या Honor ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाकर हमारी सहायता पा सकते हैं</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1050" name="hr-hr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim se ažuriranjem uglavnom poboljšavaju performanse sustava. Ažurirajte kako biste uživali u poboljšanjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pokretna fotografija">
             <feature>• Sada možete postaviti pokretnu fotografiju na zaključani zaslon. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Početni zaslon i stil > Stil zaključanog zaslona > Pokretna fotografija.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vodeni žig u filmskom stilu">
             <feature>• Fotoaparat uključuje vodene žigove u filmskom stilu. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Fotoaparat > Postavke > Vodeni žig > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerija">
             <feature>• Značajka Prijedlozi za čišćenje omogućuje automatsko prepoznavanje dupliciranih fotografija, sličnih slika i prevelikih videozapisa te pruža praktičnije prijedloge za čišćenje</feature>
             <feature>• AI isječak omogućuje vam izdvajanje predmeta, njegovo premještanje na novi položaj na slici i promjenu pozadine. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Fotografije > AI uređivanje > Magično retuširanje > AI isječak</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Nakon dugog pritiska teksta na zaslonu, skočna alatna traka sada uključuje značajku prevođenja</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Značajke dostupnosti">
             <feature>• Dvaput pritisnite gumb za uključivanje/isključivanje ili, kada je zaslon isključen, dvaput pritisnuti tipku za smanjivanje glasnoće da biste otvorili određenu aplikaciju</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Novčanik">
             <feature>• Značajka Pristupna kartica podržava simulaciju nešifriranih pristupnih kartica</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Novčanik uključuje značajku Prazna kartica. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Honor Novčanik > Pristupna kartica.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sigurnosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (studeni 2025.) za sigurnost sustava. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima značajke Honor Sigurnost posjetite naše web-mjesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Bilješke" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće utjecati na osobne podatke, ali se svejedno preporučuje izraditi sigurnosnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja
2. Idite u aplikaciju Savjeti kako biste doznali više informacija o značajkama proizvoda
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tijekom ažuriranja, našu pomoć možete dobiti tako da nazovete Honor dežurnu liniju ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1038" name="hu-hu">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez a frissítés elsősorban a rendszerteljesítményt javítja. Végezze el a frissítést, hogy élvezhesse a továbbfejlesztéseket</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Mozgó fénykép">
             <feature>• Mostantól mozgó fényképet is beállíthat zárképernyőként. Próbálja ki itt: Beállítások > Főképernyő és stílus > Képernyőzár stílusa > Mozgó fénykép.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Filmstílusú vízjel">
             <feature>• A Kamera filmstílusú vízjelekkel bővült. Próbálja ki itt: Kamera > Beállítások > Vízjel > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galéria">
             <feature>• A Tisztítási javaslatok funkció a duplikált fényképek, a hasonló képek és a túlméretezett videók automatikus azonosítása révén megfelelőbb tisztítási javaslatokat nyújt</feature>
             <feature>• Az AI-kivágás segítségével kinyerheti a témát, áthelyezheti a kép másik részére, és megváltoztathatja a hátteret. Próbálja ki itt: Fotók > AI-szerkesztés > Mágikus retusálás > AI-kivágás</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• A képernyőn megjelenő szöveg hosszú megnyomása után felugró eszközsor mostantól tartalmazza a Fordítás funkciót</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kisegítő lehetőségek">
             <feature>• Adott alkalmazás megnyitásához nyomja meg duplán a bekapcsológombot, vagy ha a képernyő ki van kapcsolva, nyomja meg duplán a Halkítás gombot</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Tárca">
             <feature>• A Belépőkártya funkció támogatja a titkosítatlan belépőkártyák szimulációját</feature>
             <feature>• A Honor Tárca tartalmazza az Üres kártya funkciót. Próbálja ki itt: Beállítások > Honor Tárca > Belépőkártya.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Biztonsági javítás">
             <feature>• A rendszerbiztonság érdekében a frissítés az Android biztonsági frissítését (2025. november) is tartalmazza. A Honor biztonsági javításaival kapcsolatos további információkért keresse fel weboldalunkat: https://www.honor.com/hu/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Jegyzetek" type="end">
             <feature>1. A jelen frissítés telepítése nem lesz hatással személyes adataira, de a frissítés előtt az adatokról továbbra is ajánlott biztonsági másolatot készíteni
2. A termékfunkciókkal kapcsolatos további információkat a Tippek alkalmazásban tekintheti meg
3. Ha a frissítés során bármilyen problémába ütközik, forduljon hozzánk segítségért a Honor-szerviz forródrótján, vagy látogasson el a Honor ügyfélszolgálati központjába</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1057" name="in-id">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini utamanya meningkatkan kinerja sistem. Instal pembaruan untuk menikmati berbagai peningkatan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Foto Bergerak">
             <feature>• Anda kini dapat mengatur foto bergerak sebagai layar kunci. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Gaya &amp; layar beranda > Gaya kunci layar > Foto bergerak.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tanda air bergaya film">
             <feature>• Kamera menyertakan tanda air bergaya film. Cobalah dengan membuka: Kamera > Pengaturan > Tanda air > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galeri">
             <feature>• Fitur Saran pembersihan memungkinkan identifikasi foto duplikat, gambar serupa, dan video yang terlalu besar secara otomatis, sehingga menyediakan saran pembersihan yang memudahkan</feature>
             <feature>• Potongan AI memungkinkan Anda untuk mengekstrak subjek, memindah posisinya pada gambar, dan mengubah latar belakang. Cobalah dengan membuka: Foto > Edit AI > Perapi Ajaib > Potongan AI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lensa">
             <feature>• Setelah menekan lama pada teks di layar, bilah alat sembul kini menyertakan fitur Terjemahan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fitur aksesibilitas">
             <feature>• Tekan dua kali tombol Daya atau, ketika layar mati, tekan dua kali tombol Perkecil volume untuk membuka aplikasi tertentu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Dompet">
             <feature>• Fitur Kartu akses mendukung simulasi kartu akses tanpa enkripsi</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Dompet menyertakan fitur Kartu kosong. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Honor Dompet > Kartu akses.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Penambal keamanan">
             <feature>• Penambal Keamanan Android (Nov 2025) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan Honor, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Catatan" type="end">
             <feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan untuk mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui
2. Pelajari informasi selengkapnya terkait fitur produk di Kiat
3. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan Honor atau mengunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1040" name="it-it">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento migliora principalmente le prestazioni del sistema. Esegui l'aggiornamento per usufruire dei miglioramenti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Foto in movimento">
             <feature>• Ora è possibile impostare una foto in movimento come schermata di blocco. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Schermata Home e stile > Stile blocco schermo > Foto in movimento.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Filigrana in stile pellicola">
             <feature>• La Fotocamera include filigrane in stile pellicola. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Fotocamera > Impostazioni > Filigrana > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galleria">
             <feature>• La funzione Suggerimenti per la pulizia consente l'identificazione automatica di foto duplicate, immagini simili e video di grandi dimensioni, facilitando la pulizia dello spazio sul dispositivo</feature>
             <feature>• Ritaglio AI consente di estrarre il soggetto, spostarlo in una nuova posizione nell'immagine e modificare lo sfondo. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Foto > Modifica AI > Ritocco magico > Ritaglio AI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Quando si preme a lungo il testo sullo schermo, la barra degli strumenti popup ora include la funzione Traduci</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funzioni accessibilità">
             <feature>• È possibile premere due volte il tasto di accensione o, quando lo schermo è spento, premere due volte il tasto di riduzione del volume per aprire un'app specifica.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• La funzione delle carte di accesso supporta la simulazione delle carte di accesso non crittografate</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet include la funzione Carta vuota. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Honor Wallet > Carta di accesso.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch di sicurezza">
             <feature>• È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (novembre 2025) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza Honor, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Note" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup dei dati prima di procedere
2. Scopri ulteriori informazioni sulle funzioni del prodotto in Suggerimenti
3. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center Honor o visitando un centro servizio clienti Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1037" name="iw-il">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה משפר בעיקר את ביצועי המערכת. עדכן כדי ליהנות מהשיפורים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="תמונה נעה">
             <feature>‏• כעת אפשר להגדיר תמונה נעה בתור מסך הנעילה. כדי לנסות, אפשר לעבור אל: 'הגדרות' > 'מסך הבית וסגנון' > 'סגנון מסך נעילה' > 'תמונה נעה'.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="סימן מים בסגנון סרט">
             <feature>‏• 'מצלמה' כוללת סימני מים בסגנון סרט צילום. כדי לנסות, אפשר לעבור אל: 'מצלמה' > 'הגדרות' > 'סימן מים' > 'סרט'.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="גלריה">
             <feature>‏• תכונת 'הצעות ניקוי' מפעילה זיהוי אוטומטי של תמונות כפולות, תמונות דומות וסרטונים גדולים מדי, ומספקת הצעות ניקוי נוחות יותר</feature>
             <feature>‏• 'תגזירים AI' מאפשר לך לחלץ את הנושא, להזיז אותו למיקום חדש בתמונה ולשנות את הרקע. כדי לנסות, אפשר לעבור אל: 'תמונות' > 'עריכת AI' > 'תיקון קסם' > 'תגזירים AI'</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏Honor Lens">
             <feature>‏• סרגל הכלים המוקפץ כולל כעת את התכונה 'תרגום', שתופיע אחרי לחיצה ארוכה על טקסט במסך</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="תכונות נגישות">
             <feature>‏• לחץ פעמיים על לחצן ההפעלה, או כשהמסך כבוי, לחץ פעמיים על לחצן החלשת עוצמת הקול כדי לפתוח יישום מסוים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏Honor Wallet">
             <feature>‏‏• תכונת כרטיסי הגישה תומכת בהדמיה של כרטיסי גישה לא מוצפנים</feature>
             <feature>‏• ‏‏Honor Wallet כולל את התכונה 'כרטיס ריק'. כדי לנסות, אפשר לעבור אל: 'הגדרות' > ‏‏Honor Wallet > 'כרטיס גישה'.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="תיקון אבטחה">
             <feature>‏• 'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מנוב' 2025) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של Honor', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="הערות" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון
‏2. גלה מידע נוסף על תכונות המוצר ב'טיפים'
‏3. אם תיתקל בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, ניתן לקבל עזרה מאיתנו באמצעות התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של Honor או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1041" name="ja-jp">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ユーザーの皆様、今回の更新では主にシステムのパフォーマンスが強化されます。更新して、改善をお楽しみください</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="動く写真">
             <feature>• 動く写真をロック画面として設定できるようになりました。この機能を試すには、[設定] > [ホーム画面とスタイル] > [ロック画面のスタイル] > [動く写真]に移動してください。</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="フィルムスタイルのウォーターマーク">
             <feature>• カメラにフィルムスタイルのウォーターマークが追加されます。この機能を試すには、[カメラ] > [設定] > [ウォーターマーク] > [フィルム]に移動してください。</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ギャラリー">
             <feature>• クリーンアップ提案機能によって、重複する写真、類似する画像、大容量のビデオを自動的に識別し、より便利なクリーンアップ提案を提供します</feature>
             <feature>• AI切り抜きによって、被写体の抽出、抽出した被写体の画像内の新しい位置への移動、背景の変更が可能になります。[写真] > [AI編集] > [マジックレタッチ] > [AI切り抜き]に移動して試してみてください</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honorレンズ">
             <feature>• 画面上のテキストを長押しすると、ポップアップツールバーに翻訳機能が含まれるようになります</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ユーザー補助機能">
             <feature>• 電源ボタンを2回押すか、画面が消灯状態で音量ダウンボタンを2回押すと、指定のアプリを開くことができます</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• カードキー機能では、暗号化されていないカードキーのシミュレーションがサポートされます</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Walletに銀行カード機能が含まれます。[設定] > [Honor Wallet] > [カードキー]に移動して、試してみてください。</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="セキュリティパッチ">
             <feature>• システムセキュリティのためにAndroidセキュリティパッチ（2025年11月）が組み込まれました。Honorのセキュリティ更新の詳細については、当社のWebサイトをご覧ください：https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="メモ" type="end">
             <feature>1. この更新をインストールしても個人情報への影響はありませんが、更新前に個人情報をバックアップしておくことをおすすめします
2. 製品機能の詳細はヒントアプリで確認してください
3. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、Honorサービスコールセンターにお電話をいただくか、Honorカスタマーサービスセンターにご来店いただき、サポートを受けてください</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1079" name="ka-ge">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ეს განახლება ძირითადად აუმჯობესებს სისტემის ეფექტიანობას. განაახლეთ და ისიამოვნეთ გაუმჯობესებებით</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="მოძრავი ფოტო">
             <feature>• ახლა შეგიძლიათ, ჩაკეტილ ეკრანად მოძრავი ფოტო დააყენოთ. სცადეთ მენიუდან: პარამეტრები > საწყისი ეკრანი და სტილი > ჩაკეტილი ეკრანის სტილი > მოძრავი ფოტო.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ფილმის სტილის წყლის ნიშანი">
             <feature>• კამერა შეიცავს ფილმის სტილის წყლის ნიშანს. სცადეთ მენიუდან: კამერა > პარამეტრები > წყლის ნიშანი > ფილმი.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="გალერეა">
             <feature>• გაწმენდის შემოთავაზებების ფუნქცია იძლევა დუბლირებული ფოტოების, იდენტური სურათებისა და დიდი ზომის ვიდეოების ავტომატური იდენტიფიკაციის საშუალებას, რაც უფრო მოსახერხებელი გაწმენდის შემოთავაზებებს გთავაზობთ</feature>
             <feature>• AI ამონაჭერი საშუალებას გაძლევთ, ამოიღოთ ობიექტი, გადაიტანოთ სურათზე ახალ პოზიციაზე და შეცვალოთ ფონი. სცადეთ მენიუდან: ფოტოები > AI რედაქტირება > ჯადოსნური რეტუში > AI ამონაჭერი</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• ეკრანზე ნაჩვენებ ტექსტზე ხანგრძლივი დაჭერის შემდეგ Pop-up ხელსაწყოთა პანელი ახლა თარგმნის ფუნქციას მოიცავს</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ხელმისაწვდომობის ფუნქციები">
             <feature>• კონკრეტული აპის გასახსნელად ორჯერ დააჭირეთ ჩართვის ღილაკს ან, როცა ეკრანი გამორთულია, ორჯერ დააჭირეთ ხმის დაწევის ღილაკს</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor საფულე">
             <feature>• წვდომის ბარათის ფუნქციას აქვს წვდომის დაუშიფრავი ბარათების სიმულაციის მხარდაჭერა</feature>
             <feature>• Honor საფულე წარმოგიდგენთ ცარიელი ბარათის ფუნქციას. სცადეთ მენიუდან: პარამეტრები > Honor საფულე > წვდომის ბარათი.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="უსაფრთხოების შესწორება">
             <feature>• სისტემის უსაფრთხოებისთვის ჩაირთო Android-ის უსაფრთხოების შესწორება (2025 წლის ნოემბერი). Honor-ის უსაფრთხოების განახლებების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაციისთვის ეწვიეთ ჩვენს ვებსაიტს: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="შენიშვნები" type="end">
             <feature>1. ამ განახლების დაინსტალირება არ იმოქმედებს თქვენს პერსონალურ მონაცემებზე, თუმცა რეკომენდებულია განახლებამდე მონაცემების სარეზერვო ასლის შექმნა
2. გაეცანით დამატებით ინფორმაციას რჩევებში პროდუქტის ფუნქციების შესახებ
3. თუ განახლებისას გარკვეულ პრობლემებს წააწყდით, დახმარებისთვის დარეკეთ Honor-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან ეწვიეთ Honor-ის სერვისცენტრს</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1087" name="kk-kz">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл жаңарту негізінен жүйе өнімділігін жақсартады. Жақсартуларды пайдалану үшін жаңартыңыз</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Қозғалмалы фотосурет">
             <feature>• Енді қозғалмалы фотосуретті құлыптау экраны ретінде орнатуға болады. «Параметрлер» > «Негізгі экран және стиль» > «Құлыптау экраны мәнері» > «Қозғалмалы фотосурет» тармағына өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Таспа стиліндегі су таңбасы">
             <feature>• Камерада таспа стиліндегі су таңбалары бар. Келесіге өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз: «Камера» > «Параметрлер» > «Су таңбасы» > «ТАСПА».</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Галерея">
             <feature>• «Тазалау ұсыныстары» мүмкіндігі дубликат фотосуреттерді, ұқсас кескіндерді және үлкен өлшемді бейнелерді автоматты түрде анықтауға мүмкіндік беріп, тазалауға ыңғайлырақ ұсыныстар береді</feature>
             <feature>• «ЖИ қимасы» нысанды шығарып алуға, оны кескіндегі жаңа орынға жылжытуға және фонды өзгертуге рұқсат етеді. «Фото» > «ЖИ арқылы өңдеу» > «Сиқырлы өңдем» > «ЖИ қимасы» тармағына өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Экрандағы мәтінді ұзақ басқаннан кейін қалқымалы құралдар тақтасында енді «Аудару» мүмкіндігі бар</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Арнайы мүмкіндіктер">
             <feature>• Көрсетілген қолданбаны ашу үшін Қуат түймесін екі рет басыңыз немесе экран өшірулі кезде дыбыс деңгейін төмендету түймесін екі рет басыңыз</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor әмияны">
             <feature>• «Қатынасу картасы» мүмкіндігі шифрланбаған қатынасу карталарының имитациясын қолдайды</feature>
             <feature>• «Honor әмияны» қолданбасында «Бос карта» мүмкіндігі бар. «Параметрлер» > «Honor әмияны» > «Қатынасу картасы» тармағына өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Қауіпсіздік патчы">
             <feature>• Android қауіпсіздік патчы (қараша, 2025) жүйе қауіпсіздігі үшін біріктірілген. Honor қауіпсіздік жаңартулары туралы қосымша ақпарат алу үшін біздің веб-сайтқа кіріңіз: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Ескертпелер" type="end">
             <feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнату жеке деректеріңізге әсер етпейді, бірақ жаңарту алдында деректердің сақтық көшірмесін жасау ұсынылады
2. «Кеңестер» қолданбасында өнім мүмкіндіктері туралы қосымша ақпаратты табыңыз
3. Жаңарту кезінде қандай да бір мәселе орын алса, Honor қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне қоңырау шалу не Honor тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына бару арқылы көмегімізді ала аласыз</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1107" name="km-kh">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះធ្វើឱ្យប្រតិបត្តិការប្រព័ន្ធប្រសើរឡើងជាចម្បង។ ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព ដើម្បីរីករាយនឹងការកែលម្អទាំងនេះ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="រូបថតមានចលនា">
             <feature>•ឥឡូវនេះ អ្នកអាចកំណត់រូបថតមានចលនាជាអេក្រង់ចាក់សោ។ សាកល្បងប្រើដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > រចនាប័ទ្ម និងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម > រចនាប័ទ្មអេក្រង់ជាប់សោ > រូបថតមានចលនា។</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="រូបភាពព្រាលលើផ្ទៃបាតរចនាប័ទ្មហ្វីល">
             <feature>• កាមេរ៉ារួមបញ្ចូលរូបភាពព្រាលលើផ្ទៃបាតរចនាប័ទ្មហ្វីល។ សាកល្បងប្រើដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ កាមេរ៉ា > ការកំណត់ > រូបភាពព្រាលលើផ្ទៃបាត > ហ្វីល។</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="វិចិត្រសាល">
             <feature>• មុខងារណែនាំការសម្អាតអាចឱ្យការកំណត់អត្តសញ្ញាណដោយស្វ័យប្រវត្តិនៃរូបថតស្ទួន រូបភាពស្រដៀងគ្នា និងវីដេអូដែលមានទំហំធំ ដោយផ្ដល់នូវការណែនាំអំពីការសម្អាតកាន់តែងាយស្រួល</feature>
             <feature>• ការកាត់ចេញ AI អនុញ្ញាតឱ្យអ្នកទាញយកវត្ថុ ផ្លាស់ទីវាទៅទីតាំងថ្មីក្នុងរូបភាព និងផ្លាស់ប្តូរផ្ទៃខាងក្រោយ។ សាកល្បងវាដោយចូលទៅកាន់: រូបថត > កែតាម AI > កែលម្អបែបវេទមន្ត > ការកាត់ចេញ AI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• បន្ទាប់ពីចុចយូរលើអត្ថបទនៅលើអេក្រង់ របារឧបករណ៍លេចឡើងឥឡូវនេះរួមបញ្ចូលមុខងារបកប្រែ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="មុខងារភាពងាយស្រួលប្រើប្រាស់">
             <feature>• ចុចពីរដងលើប៊ូតុងថាមពល ឬនៅពេលដែលអេក្រង់បិទ សូមចុចប៊ូតុងកម្រិតសំឡេងចុះពីរដងដើម្បីបើកកម្មវិធីដែលបានបញ្ជាក់</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor កាបូប">
             <feature>• មុខងារកាតចូលប្រើគាំទ្រការក្លែងធ្វើនៃកាតចូលប្រើដែលមិនបានអ៊ិនគ្រីប</feature>
             <feature>• Honor កាបូប​រួមបញ្ចូលមុខងារកាតទទេ។ សាកប្រើវាដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > Honor កាបូប > កាតចូល។</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="បំណះសន្តិសុខ">
             <feature>• បំណះសន្តិសុខ Android (វិច្ឆិកា 2025) ត្រូវបាន​រួមបញ្ចូល​សម្រាប់​សន្តិសុខ​ប្រព័ន្ធ។ សម្រាប់​ព័ត៌មាន​បន្ថែម​អំពី​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​សន្តិសុខ Honor សូមចូលទៅ​គេហទំព័រ​របស់យើង https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់" type="end">
             <feature>1. ការដំឡើងបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះនឹងមិនប៉ះពាល់ដល់ទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួនរបស់អ្នកទេ ប៉ុន្តែសូមណែនាំឱ្យបម្រុងទុកទិន្នន័យរបស់អ្នក មុននឹងធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព
2. ស្វែងយល់បន្ថែមអំពីលក្ខណៈពិសេសផលិតផលនៅក្នុងគន្លឹះ
3. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបប្រទះបញ្ហាណាមួយអំឡុងពេលធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព អ្នកអាចទទួលបានជំនួយរបស់យើងដោយហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សនៃសេវាកម្ម Honor ឬចូលទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌលសេវាកម្មអតិថិជន Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1099" name="kn-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಮುಖ್ಯವಾಗಿ ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಕಾರ್ಯಕ್ಷಮತೆಯನ್ನು ವರ್ಧಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಸುಧಾರಣೆಗಳನ್ನು ಆನಂದಿಸಲು ನವೀಕರಿಸಿ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಚಲಿಸುವ ಫೋಟೋ">
             <feature>• ನೀವು ಈಗ ಚಲಿಸುವ ಫೋಟೋವನ್ನು ಲಾಕ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಆಗಿ ಸೆಟ್ ಮಾಡಬಹುದು. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಮತ್ತು ಶೈಲಿ > ಲಾಕ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಶೈಲಿ > ಚಲಿಸುವ ಫೋಟೋ.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಚಲನಚಿತ್ರ ಶೈಲಿಯ ವಾಟರ್‌ಮಾರ್ಕ್">
             <feature>• ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾವು ಫಿಲ್ಮ್-ಶೈಲಿಯ ವಾಟರ್‌ಮಾರ್ಕ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಒಳಗೊಂಡಿದೆ. ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾ > ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ವಾಟರ್‌ಮಾರ್ಕ್ > ಫಿಲ್ಮ್‌ಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಗ್ಯಾಲರಿ">
             <feature>• ಕ್ಲೀನ್‌ಅಪ್ ಸಲಹೆಗಳ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯವು ನಕಲಿ ಫೋಟೋಗಳು, ಒಂದೇ ರೀತಿಯ ಚಿತ್ರಗಳು ಮತ್ತು ಅತಿ ದೊಡ್ಡ ಗಾತ್ರದ ವೀಡಿಯೊಗಳ ಸ್ವಯಂಚಾಲಿತ ಗುರುತನ್ನು ಸಕ್ರಿಯಗೊಳಿಸುತ್ತದೆ, ಹೆಚ್ಚು ಅನುಕೂಲಕರವಾದ ಕ್ಲೀನಿಂಗ್ ಸಲಹೆಗಳನ್ನು ಒದಗಿಸುತ್ತದೆ</feature>
             <feature>• AI ಕಟ್‌ಔಟ್ ನಿಮಗೆ ವಿಷಯವನ್ನು ಹೊರತೆಗೆಯಲು, ಅದನ್ನು ಚಿತ್ರದಲ್ಲಿ ಹೊಸ ಸ್ಥಾನಕ್ಕೆ ಸರಿಸಲು ಮತ್ತು ಹಿನ್ನೆಲೆಯನ್ನು ಬದಲಾಯಿಸಲು ಅನುವು ಮಾಡಿಕೊಡುತ್ತದೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ: ಫೋಟೋಗಳು > AI ಎಡಿಟ್ > ಮ್ಯಾಜಿಕ್ ರೀಟಚ್ > AI ಕಟ್‍‍ಔಟ್</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಮೇಲಿನ ಪಠ್ಯವನ್ನು ದೀರ್ಘಕಾಲ ಒತ್ತಿದ ನಂತರ, ಪಾಪ್-ಅಪ್ ಟೂಲ್‌ಬಾರ್ ಈಗ ಅನುವಾದ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯವನ್ನು ಒಳಗೊಳ್ಳುತ್ತದೆ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಪ್ರವೇಶಾರ್ಹತೆ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯಗಳು">
             <feature>• ಪವರ್ ಬಟನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಎರಡು ಬಾರಿ ಒತ್ತಿರಿ ಅಥವಾ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಆಫ್ ಆಗಿರುವಾಗ, ನಿರ್ದಿಷ್ಟಪಡಿಸಿದ ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಅನ್ನು ತೆರೆಯಲು ವಾಲ್ಯೂಮ್ ಕಡಿಮೆ ಮಾಡುವ ಬಟನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಎರಡು ಬಾರಿ ಒತ್ತಿರಿ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ವಾಲೆಟ್">
             <feature>• ಆ್ಯಕ್ಸೆಸ್ ಕಾರ್ಡ್ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯವು ಎನ್‌ಕ್ರಿಪ್ಟ್ ಮಾಡದ ಆ್ಯಕ್ಸೆಸ್ ಕಾರ್ಡ್‌ಗಳ ಸಿಮ್ಯುಲೇಶನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಬೆಂಬಲಿಸುತ್ತದೆ</feature>
             <feature>• Honor ವಾಲೆಟ್ ಖಾಲಿ ಕಾರ್ಡ್ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯವನ್ನು ಒಳಗೊಂಡಿದೆ. ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > Honor ವಾಲೆಟ್ > ಆ್ಯಕ್ಸೆಸ್ ಕಾರ್ಡ್‌ ಎಂಬಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ ನೋಡಿ.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್">
             <feature>• ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಭದ್ರತೆಗಾಗಿ Android ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ (ನವೆಂಬರ್ 2025) ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. Honor ಭದ್ರತಾ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಗಾಗಿ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಮ್ಮ ವೆಬ್‌ಸೈಟ್‌ಗೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡಿ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು" type="end">
             <feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾದ ಮೇಲೆ ಪರಿಣಾಮ ಬೀರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೂ ಸಹ ನವೀಕರಿಸುವ ಮೊದಲು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಬ್ಯಾಕ್ ಅಪ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ
2. ಉತ್ಪನ್ನ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಯನ್ನು ಸಲಹೆಗಳು ಎಂಬುದರಲ್ಲಿ ಕಂಡುಕೊಳ್ಳಿ
3. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನಿಮಗೆ ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳು ಎದುರಾದರೆ, ನೀವು Honor ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಅಥವಾ Honor ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ನಮ್ಮ ಸಹಾಯವನ್ನು ಪಡೆಯಬಹುದು</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1042" name="ko-kr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>사용자 여러분, 이번 업데이트는 주로 시스템 성능을 향상시킵니다. 업데이트하고 개선된 기능을 즐겨 보세요</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="움직이는 사진">
             <feature>• 이제 움직이는 사진을 잠금 화면으로 설정할 수 있습니다. 설정 > 홈 화면 및 스타일 > 잠금 화면 스타일 > 움직이는 사진(으)로 이동하여 사용해 보세요.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="필름 스타일 워터마크">
             <feature>• 카메라에 필름 스타일 워터마크가 포함되어 있습니다. 카메라 > 설정 > 워터마크 > 필름으로 이동하여 사용해 보세요.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="갤러리">
             <feature>• 정리 제안 기능이 중복 사진, 비슷한 이미지, 대용량 비디오를 자동으로 파악하여 더욱 편리한 정리 방법을 제공합니다.</feature>
             <feature>• AI 컷아웃 기능을 실행하면 피사체를 추출하고, 이미지 내 새로운 위치로 이동시키며, 배경을 변경할 수 있습니다. 사진 > AI 편집 > 매직 리터치 > AI 컷아웃으로 이동하여 사용해 보세요</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• 화면의 텍스트를 길게 누르면 팝업 도구 막대에 번역 기능이 포함됩니다</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="접근성 기능">
             <feature>• 전원 버튼을 두 번 누르거나, 화면이 꺼져 있을 때 볼륨 다운 버튼을 두 번 눌러 지정된 앱을 열 수 있습니다</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor 전자지갑">
             <feature>• 출입 카드 기능은 암호화되지 않은 출입 카드의 시뮬레이션을 지원합니다</feature>
             <feature>• Honor 전자지갑에 무기명 카드 기능이 추가되었습니다. 설정 > Honor 전자지갑 > 출입 카드로 이동하여 사용해 보세요.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="보안 패치">
             <feature>• 시스템 보안을 위해 Android 보안 패치(2025년 11월)가 통합되었습니다. Honor 보안 업데이트에 대해 자세히 알아보려면 당사 웹사이트(https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11)를 방문하세요.</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="공지" type="end">
             <feature>1. 이 업데이트 설치는 개인 데이터에 영향을 미치지 않지만, 업데이트하기 전에 데이터를 백업하는 것이 좋습니다
2. Tips에서 제품 기능에 대한 자세한 정보를 알아보세요
3. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 Honor 서비스 핫라인으로 전화하거나 Honor 고객 서비스 센터를 방문하여 도움을 받을 수 있습니다</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1108" name="lo-la">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ສະ​ບາຍ​ດີ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​​ນີ້​ຍົກ​ລະ​ດັບ​ປະ​ສິດ​ທິ​ພາບ​ຂອງ​ລະ​ບົບ​ເປັນຫຼັກ. ອັບ​ເດດ​ເພື່ອ​ມ່ວ​ນ​ຊື່​ນກັບ​ການ​ປັບ​ປຸງ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ຮູບ​ເຄື່ອນ​ໄຫວ">
             <feature>• ຕອນ​ນີ້​ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່າຮູບ​ເຄື່ອນ​ໄຫວ​ເປັນ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ລັອກ​ໄດ້ແລ້ວ. ​ລອງໃຊ້ມັນເບິ່ງ​ໄດ້​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການຕັ້ງຄ່າ > ໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ ແລະ ຮູບແບບ > ຮູບແບບໜ້າຈໍລັອກ > ຮູບເຄື່ອນໄຫວ.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ລາຍ​ນ້ຳ​ຮູບ​ແບບ​ຟີມ">
             <feature>• ກ້ອງ​ຖ່າຍ​ຮູບ​ລວມ​ມີລາຍ​ນ້ຳ​ຮູບ​ແບບ​ຟີມ. ​ລອງໃຊ້ມັນເບິ່ງ​ໄດ້​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ກ້ອງ​ຖ່າຍ​ຮູບ > ​ການ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່າ > ​ລາຍ​ນ້ຳ > ​ຟີມ.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ແກ​ເລີ​ຣີ">
             <feature>• ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດຄຳ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ທຳ​ຄວາມ​ສະ​ອາດ​ເປີດ​ໃຊ້​ງານ​ການ​ລະ​ບຸ​ຮູບ​ຖ່າຍ​ທີ່ຊ້ຳ​​ກັນ, ຮູບ​ພາບ​ທີ່​ຄ້າຍ​ຄື​ກັນ ແລະ ວິ​ດີ​ໂອ​ຂະ​ໜາດ​ໃຫຍ່​ເກີນ​ໄປໂດຍ​ອັດ​ຕະ​ໂນ​ມັດ, ເຊິ່ງ​ໃຫ້ຄຳ​ແນະ​ນຳ​​ການທຳ​ຄວາມ​ສະ​ອາດ​ທີ່​ສະ​ດວກ​ສະ​ບາຍ​ຍິ່ງ​ຂຶ້ນ</feature>
             <feature>• ສ່ວນຕັດ​ອອກ AI ໃຫ້​ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ແຍກ​ເປົ້າ​ໝາຍ​ອອກ, ຍ້າຍ​ມັນ​ໄປ​ຫາ​ຕຳ​ແໜ່ງ​ໃໝ່​ໃນ​ຮູບ​ພາບ ແລະ ປ່ຽ​ນ​ພື້ນຫຼັງ. ​ລອງໃຊ້ມັນເບິ່ງ​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ຮູບພາບ > ແກ້ໄຂດ້ວຍ AI > ປັບແຕ່ງເມຈິກ > ສ່ວນຕັດອອກ AI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• ຫຼັງ​ຈາກ​ກົດ​ຂໍ້​ຄວາມ​ໃນ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ຄ້າງ​ໄວ້, ແຖບ​ເຄື່ອງ​ມື​ປັອບ​ອັບ​ຕອນ​ນີ້​ລວມ​ມີ​ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດ​ແປ​ພ​າ​ສາ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ຄຸນສົມບັດ​ການ​ຊ່ວຍ​ເຂົ້າ​ເຖິງ">
             <feature>• ກົດ​ປຸ່ມ​ເປີດ​ປິດເຄື່ອງ​ສອງ​ເທື່ອ​ ຫຼື ເມື່ອ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ປິດ​ຢູ່ ກົດ​ປຸ່ມ​ເອົາ​ສຽງ​ລົງສອງ​ເ​ທື່ອ​ເພື່ອ​ເປີດ​ແອັບ​ທີ່​ລະ​ບຸ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ກະ​ເປົ໋າ​ເງິນ Honor">
             <feature>• ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດ​ບັດ​ເຂົ້າ​ເຖິ​ງ​ຮອງ​ຮັບການ​ຈຳ​ລອງ​ບັດ​ເຂົ້າ​ເຖິງ​ທີ່​ບໍ່​ໄດ້​ໃສ່​ລະ​ຫັດ</feature>
             <feature>• ກະ​ເປົ໋າ​ເງິນ Honor ລວມ​ມີຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດບັດ​ເປົ່າ. ​ລອງໃຊ້ມັນເບິ່ງ​ໄດ້​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການຕັ້ງຄ່າ > ກະເປົ໋າເງິນ Honor > ບັດເຂົ້າເຖິງ.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ">
             <feature>• ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ຂອງ Android (ພະ​ຈິກ 2025) ​ໄດ້ຖືກລວມ​​ເຂົ້າ​ເປັນ​ການ​ຮັກ​ສາ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ລະ​ບົບ. ສຳລັບຂໍ້ມູນເພີ່ມເຕີມກ່ຽວກັບການອັບເດດດ້ານຄວາມປອດໄພຂອງ Honor, ກະລຸນາເຂົ້າໄປ​ທີ່ເວັບໄຊຂອງພວກເຮົາ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ການ​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ສົ່ງ​ຜົນ​ຕໍ່​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ, ແຕ່​ຍັງ​ຄົງ​ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ສຳ​ຮອງ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄວ້ກ່ອນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ
2. ຄົ້ນ​ຫາ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ເພີ່ມ​ເຕີມ​ກ່ຽວ​ກັບ​ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດ​ຜະ​ລິດ​ຕະ​ພັນ​ໃນ​​ເຄັດ​ລັບ
3. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ທ່ານສາມາດຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອຈາກພວກເຮົາໄດ້ ໂດຍການໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນ​ບໍ​ລິ​ການ Honor ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1063" name="lt-lt">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šis naujinys daugiausiai pagerina sistemos našumą. Atnaujinkite ir mėgaukitės patobulinimais.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Videonuotrauka">
             <feature>• Dabar galite nustatyti veideonuotrauką kaip užrakinimo ekraną. Norėdami išbandyti eikite į „Nuostatos > Pradžios ekranas ir stilius > Užrakinimo ekrano stilius > Video nuotrauka“.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Juostelės stiliaus vandens ženklas">
             <feature>• Kameroje yra juostelės stiliaus vandens ženklai. Norėdami išbandyti eikite į „Kamera > Nuostatos > Vandens ženklas > JUOSTELĖ“.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerija">
             <feature>• Valymo pasiūlymų funkcija įjungia automatinį besidubliuojančių nuotraukų, panašių vaizdų ir per didelių vaizdo įrašų aptikimą, todėl teikia patogesnius valymo pasiūlymus</feature>
             <feature>• DI iškirpimo funkcija leidžia ištraukti objektą, perkelti jį į kitą vaizdo vietą ir pakeisti foną. Išbandykite tai nuėję į „Nuotraukos > DI redagavimas > Stebuklingasis retušavimas > DI iškirpimas“</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="„Honor“ objektyvas">
             <feature>• Paspaudus ir palaikius tekstą ekrane, iškylančiojoje priemonių juostoje nuo šiol pateikiama vertimo funkcija</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pritaikymo neįgaliesiems funkcijos">
             <feature>• Dukart paspauskite maitinimo mygtuką arba, kai ekranas išjungtas, dukart paspauskite garsumo mažinimo mygtuką, kad atvertumėte nurodytą programėlę</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="„Honor“ piniginė">
             <feature>• Prieigos kortelės funkcija turi nešifruotų prieigos kortelių imitavimo galimybę</feature>
             <feature>• „Honor“ piniginėje yra funkcija „Tuščia kortelė“. Išbandykite ją nuėję į Nuostatos > „Honor“ piniginė > Prieigos kortelė.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Saugumo pataisa">
             <feature>• Siekiant užtikrinti sistemos saugumą, įtraukta „Android“ saugumo pataisa (2025 m. lapkričio mėn.). Jei reikia daugiau informacijos apie Honor saugumo naujinius, apsilankykite mūsų svetainėje https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Pastabos" type="end">
             <feature>1. Šio naujinio įdiegimas neturės įtakos jūsų asmeniniams duomenims, tačiau prieš atnaujinant rekomenduojama sukurti atsarginę duomenų kopiją
2. Daugiau informacijos apie gaminio funkcijas rasite Patarimuose
3. Jei naujinimo metu kiltų bet kokių problemų, galite kreiptis į mus pagalbos paskambindami „Honor priežiūros karštąja linija arba apsilankydami „Honor“ klientų aptarnavimo centre</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1062" name="lv-lv">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo atjauninājumu galvenokārt ir uzlabota sistēmas veiktspēja. Atjauniniet, lai izbaudītu uzlabojumus</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kustīgs fotoattēls">
             <feature>• Tagad bloķēšanas ekrānam varat iestatīt kustīgu fotoattēlu. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Iestatījumi > Sākuma ekrāns un stils > Ekrāna bloķētāja stils > Kustīgs fotoattēls.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Filmas stila ūdenszīme">
             <feature>• Kamerai ir filmas stila ūdenszīmes. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Kamera > Iestatījumi > Ūdenszīme > FILMA.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerija">
             <feature>• Tīrīšanas ieteikumu funkcija ļauj automātiski identificēt dublētus fotoattēlus, līdzīgus attēlus un pārāk lielus videoklipus, nodrošinot ērtākus tīrīšanas ieteikumus</feature>
             <feature>• AI izgriezums ļauj izvilkt objektu, pārvietot to uz jaunu pozīciju attēlā un mainīt fonu. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Fotoattēli > AI rediģēšana > Magic Retouch > AI izgriezums</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Pēc ilgstošas nospiešanas uz teksta ekrānā uznirstošajā rīkjoslā tagad ir iekļauta funkcija Tulkošana</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pieejamības funkcijas">
             <feature>• Divreiz nospiediet ieslēgšanas/izslēgšanas pogu vai, kad ekrāns ir izslēgts, divreiz nospiediet skaļuma samazināšanas pogu, lai atvērtu norādīto lietotni</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• Piekļuves karšu funkcija atbalsta nešifrētu piekļuves karšu simulāciju</feature>
             <feature>• Lietotnē Honor Wallet ir iekļauta funkcija Tukša karte. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Iestatījumi > Honor Wallet > Piekļuves karte.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Drošības ielāps">
             <feature>• Sistēmas drošībai iekļauts Android drošības ielāps (2025. gada novembris). Lai iegūtu papildinformāciju par Honor drošības atjauninājumiem, lūdzu, apmeklējiet mūsu vietni https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Piezīmes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Šī atjauninājuma instalēšana neietekmēs jūsu personas datus, taču joprojām ir ieteicams pirms atjaunināšanas dublēt datus
2. Lietotnē Padomi atklājiet vairāk par produkta funkcijām
3. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, varat saņemt mūsu palīdzību, zvanot uz Honor klientu apkalpošanas dienesta tālruni vai apmeklējot Honor klientu pakalpojumu centru.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="mai-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, ई अपडेट मुख्य रूप सँ सिस्टमक कार्य-क्षमता केँ वर्धित करैत अछि। सुधार सभक आनंद लेबाक लेल अपडेट करू</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="मूविंग फोटो">
             <feature>• आब अहाँ एकटा मूविंग फोटो केँ लॉक स्क्रीन केर रूप मे सेट कए सकैत छी। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: सेटिंग्स > होम स्क्रीन आ शैली > स्क्रीन लॉक स्टाइल > मूविंग फोटो।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="फिल्म-शैली वाटरमार्क">
             <feature>• कैमरा मे फिल्म-शैली वाटरमार्क सम्मिलित अछि। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: कैमरा > सेटिंग्स > वाटरमार्क > फिल्म।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="गैलरी">
             <feature>• क्लीनअप सुझाव विशेषता डुप्लिकेट फोटो, समान इमेज सभ आ पैघ आकार केर वीडियो सभक स्वचालित पहिचान सक्षम करैत अछि जाहि सँ बेसी सुविधाजनक क्लीनिंग सुझाव प्राप्त होइत अछि</feature>
             <feature>• AI कटआउट अहाँ केँ सब्जेक्ट निकालबाक, एकरा इमेज मे नव स्थिति मे मूव करबाक आओर बैकग्राउंड बदलबाक सुविधा दैत अछि। एहि मे जा कए एकरा सक्षम करू: फोटो सभ > AI संपादन > Magic परिष्करण > AI कटआउट</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• स्क्रीन पर टेक्स्ट केँ देरी धरि दबओलाक बाद, आब पॉप-अप टूलबार मे अनुवाद विशेषता सम्मिलित अछि</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="एक्सेसिबिलिटी फीचर">
             <feature>• कोनो निर्दिष्ट एप केँ खोलबाक लेल पावर बटन केँ दू-बेर दबाउ वा जखन स्क्रीन बंद रहए तखन वॉल्यूम डाउन बटन केँ दू बेर दबाउ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor वॉलेट">
             <feature>• एक्सेस कार्ड विशेषता एन्क्रिप्ट नहि कयल एक्सेस कार्ड केर सिमुलेशन केर सपोर्ट करैत अछि</feature>
             <feature>• Honor वॉलेट मे ब्लैंक कार्ड विशेषता सम्मिलित अछि। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: सेटिंग्स > Honor वॉलेट > एक्सेस कार्ड।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षा पैच">
             <feature>सिस्टमक सुरक्षाक लेल Android सुरक्षा पैच (नवंबर 2025) समाविष्ट कयल गेल अछि। Honor सुरक्षा अपडेट सभक विषय मे आओर जानकारीक लेल, कृपाकए हमरासभक वेबसाइट केँ देखू: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोट्स" type="end">
             <feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा प्रभावित नहि होयत, मुदा तैयो अपडेट करए सँ पहिने अहाँ केँ डेटाक बैकअप लेबाक सुझाव देल जाइत अछि
2. टिप्स मे उत्पाद विशेषता सभ पर आओर जानकारी डिस्‍कवर करू
3. यदि अपडेट केर दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' अहाँ Honor सेवा हॉटलाइन केँ कॉल कए वा Honor सर्विस सेंटर जा कए हमरासभक मदति प्राप्त कए सकैत छी</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1153" name="mi-NZ">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>E te kaiwhakamahi aroha, ko tēnei whakahoutanga e whakarei ake ana i te mahinga pūnaha. Whakahōu ki te oaoa i te whakapai ake</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Whakaahua Nekeneke">
             <feature>• Ka taea ināianei te tatū whakaahua nekeneke hei mata maukati. Whakamātauria mā te haere ki: Ngā Tautuhinga > Mata kāinga &amp; kāhua > Kāhua maukati mata > Whakaahua nekeneke.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tohuwai kāhua kiriata">
             <feature>• Kei roto i te Kāmera ngā tohuwai kāhua kiriata. Whakamātauria mā te haere ki: Kāmera > Ngā tautuhinga > Tohuwai > Kiriata.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Taiwhanga">
             <feature>• Ko te āhuahira tūtohutanga Tahitahi ka whakahohe ki te tautuhi aunoa i ngā whakaahua tārite, ngā atahanga ōrite, me ngā ataata rahi rawa, ā, ka whakarato i ngā tūtohutanga tahitahi kia watea ake ai</feature>
             <feature>• Ka whakahohe te āhuahira Tapahi AI i a koe te tango i te kaupapa, te neke ki tētahi tūnga hou i roto i te atahanga, ā, te huri i te papamuri. Whakamāturia mā te haere ki: Ngā whakaāhua > Whakatika AI > Whakapā anō Tūmatarau > Tapahi AI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Whai muri i te pēhi roa i te kuputuhi i runga i te mata, kei roto ināianei i te paeutauta pahū-ake te āhuahira Whakamāori</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ngā āhuahira urutanga">
             <feature>• Pēhi-rua i te Pātene Hiko rānei, ina whakaweto te mata, te pēhi-rua i te Pātene kahaoro whakararo hei whakatuwhera i tētahi taupānga kua tohua</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Wāreti Honor">
             <feature>• E āhuahira tautoko ana te Kāri urunga i te āhei ki te whakakāhore i ngā kāri urunga kāore i whakamunatia</feature>
             <feature>• Kei roto i te Wāreti Honor te āhuahira Kāri pātea. Whakamātauhia mā te haere ki: Ngā Tautuhinga > Wāreti Honor > Kāri urunga.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Āpure haumarutanga">
             <feature>• Kua whakaurua te pūrei haumarutanga Android (Noema 2025) mō te haumarutanga pūnaha. Mō ētahi anō mōhiohio mō ngā whakahōutanga Haumarutanga Honor, haere koa ki tā mātou paetukutuku https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Ngā Tuhipoka" type="end">
             <feature>1. Mā te tāuta i tēnei whakahōutanga e kore tō raraunga whaiaro e pāngia, engari e taunaki ana kia tāruatia ō raraunga i mua i te whakahōutanga
2. Tūhura mōhiohio ētahi anō mō ngā āhuahira o te hua i Ngā Aki
3. Mēnā ka pāngia koe e ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōutanga, ka taea e koe te tiki āwhina mā te waea atu ki te waeawera ratonga Honor, mā te toro atu rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki a Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1071" name="mk-mk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Почитуван кориснику, ова ажурирање главно ги подобрува перформансите на системот. Ажурирајте за да уживате во подобрувањата</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Подвижна фотографија">
             <feature>• Сега може да поставите подвижна фотографија како екран на заклучен уред. Пробајте преку одење во: Нагодување > Почетен екран и стил > Стил на екран на заклучен уред > Подвижна фотографија.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Воден знак со филмски стил">
             <feature>Камера вклучува водни знаци со филмски стил. Пробајте преку одење во: Камера > Нагодување > Воден знак > ФИЛМ.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Галерија">
             <feature>• Карактеристиката Предлози за чистење овозможува автоматска идентификација на дупликат фотографии, слични слики и видеа со преголема големина, обезбедувајќи попрактични предлози за чистење</feature>
             <feature>• Отсекување со вештачка интелигенција ви овозможува да го извлечете субјектот, да го преместите во нова позиција во сликата, како и да ја смените заднината. Пробајте преку одење во: Фотографии > Уредување со вештачка интелигенција > Магично ретуширање > Отсекување со вештачка интелигенција</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• По долго притискање врз текст на екранот, алатникот во скок-прозорецот сега ја вклучува карактеристиката Преведи</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Карактеристики за пристапност">
             <feature>• Притиснете го двапати копчето за напојување или, кога екранот е исклучен, притиснете го двапати копчето за намалување на јачината на звукот за да отворите специфична апликација</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Паричник од Honor">
             <feature>• Карактеристиката Картичка за пристап го поддржува симулирањето нешифрирани картички за пристап</feature>
             <feature>• Паричник од Honor ја вклучува карактеристиката Празна картичка. Пробајте ја така што ќе отидете во: Нагодување > Паричник од Honor > Картичка за пристап.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Безбедносна крпеница">
             <feature>• Вградена е безбедносна крпеница за Android (ноември 2025) за безбедност на системот. За повеќе информации за ажурирања на безбедноста од Honor, посетете ја нашата веб-локација https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Белешки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да влијае врз вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува да направите резервна копија од податоците пред да ажурирате
2. Откријте повеќе информации за карактеристиките на производот во Совети
3. Ако наидете на какви било проблеми при ажурирањето, може да ја добиете нашата помош со повикување на телефонскиот број на службата на Honor или посета на сервисниот центар за корисници на Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1100" name="ml-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് പ്രധാനമായും സിസ്റ്റം പ്രകടനം മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു. മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തലുകൾ ആസ്വദിക്കാൻ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുക</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ചലിക്കുന്ന ഫോട്ടോ">
             <feature>• നിങ്ങൾക്ക് ഇപ്പോൾ ലോക്ക് സ്‌ക്രീൻ ആയി ഒരു ചലിക്കുന്ന ഫോട്ടോ സജ്ജീകരിക്കാൻ കഴിയും. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്രമീകരണം > ഹോം സ്ക്രീനും ശൈലിയും > ലോക്ക് സ്‌ക്രീൻ ശൈലി > ചലിക്കുന്ന ഫോട്ടോ.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ഫിലിം ശൈലിയിലുള്ള വാട്ടർമാർക്ക്">
             <feature>• ക്യാമറയിൽ ഫിലിം ശൈലിയിലുള്ള വാട്ടർമാർക്കുകൾ ഉൾപ്പെടുന്നു. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്യാമറ > ക്രമീകരണം > വാട്ടർമാർക്ക് > ഫിലിം.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ഗാലറി">
             <feature>• കൂടുതൽ സൗകര്യപ്രദമായ ക്ലീൻ ചെയ്യൽ നിർദ്ദേശങ്ങൾ നൽകുന്നതിനായി, 'ക്ലീനപ്പ് നിർദ്ദേശങ്ങൾ' സവിശേഷത ഡ്യൂപ്ലിക്കേറ്റ് ഫോട്ടോകളും ഒരുപോലുള്ള ഇമേജുകളും അമിതവലുപ്പമുള്ള വീഡിയോകളും സ്വയമേവ തിരിച്ചറിയുന്നത് പ്രവർത്തനസജ്ജമാക്കുന്നു</feature>
             <feature>• സബ്‌ജക്റ്റ് വേർതിരിച്ചെടുത്ത് ഇമേജിലെ ഒരു പുതിയ സ്ഥാനത്തേക്ക് നീക്കാനും പശ്ചാത്തലം മാറ്റാനും 'AI കട്ടൗട്ട്' നിങ്ങളെ പ്രാപ്‌തരാക്കുന്നു. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ഫോട്ടോകൾ > AI എഡിറ്റ് ചെയ്യൽ > മാജിക്ക് റീടച്ച് > AI കട്ടൗട്ട്</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• സ്‌ക്രീനിലെ ടെക്‌സ്‌റ്റിൽ ദീർഘനേരം അമർത്തിക്കഴിഞ്ഞാൽ, ദൃശ്യമാകുന്ന ടൂൾബാറിൽ ഇപ്പോൾ 'വിവർത്തനം ചെയ്യുക' സവിശേഷത ഉൾപ്പെടുന്നു</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ആക്സസബിലിറ്റി സവിശേഷതകൾ">
             <feature>• ഒരു നിർദ്ദിഷ്‌ട ആപ്പ് തുറക്കാൻ, പവർ ബട്ടൺ രണ്ടുതവണ അമർത്തുക, അല്ലെങ്കിൽ സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഓഫായിരിക്കുമ്പോൾ വോളിയം കുറയ്‌ക്കൽ ബട്ടൺ രണ്ടുതവണ അമർത്തുക</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor വാലറ്റ്">
             <feature>• എൻക്രിപ്‌റ്റ് ചെയ്യാത്ത ആക്‌സസ് കാർഡുകളുടെ സിമുലേഷൻ ആക്‌സസ് കാർഡ് സവിശേഷത പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കുന്നു</feature>
             <feature>• Honor വാലറ്റിൽ 'ശൂന്യമായ കാർഡ്' സവിശേഷത ഉൾപ്പെടുന്നു. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്രമീകരണം > Honor വാലറ്റ് > ആക്‌സസ് കാർഡ്.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച്">
             <feature>• സിസ്റ്റം സുരക്ഷയ്‌ക്കായി Android സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് (നവംബർ 2025) ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. Honor സുരക്ഷാ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾക്ക്, ഞങ്ങളുടെ വെബ്‌സൈറ്റ് സന്ദർശിക്കുക: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ ബാധിക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിന് മുമ്പായി നിങ്ങളുടെ ഡാറ്റ ബാക്കപ്പ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു
2. 'നുറുങ്ങുകൾ' എന്നതിൽ ഉൽപ്പന്ന സവിശേഷതകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾ കണ്ടെത്തുക
3. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ നിങ്ങൾക്ക് എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, Honor സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ Honor ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്‌ത് ഞങ്ങളുടെ സഹായം കരസ്ഥമാക്കാവുന്നതാണ്</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1104" name="mn-MN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэ шинэчлэлтээр голчлон системийн гүйцэтгэлийг сайжрууллаа. Шинэчлээд, сайжруулсан хэрэглээг мэдрээрэй</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Хөдөлгөөнт зураг">
             <feature>• Одоо хөдөлгөөнт зургийг түгжээ дэлгэцээр тохируулж болох боллоо. Тохиргоо > Үндсэн дэлгэц, хэв маяг > Түгжээ дэлгэцийн хэв маяг > Хөдөлгөөнт зураг руу очиж туршиж үзнэ үү.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Киноны хэв маягтай усан тэмдэг">
             <feature>• Камер киноны хэв маягтай усан тэмдэгтэй боллоо. Камер > Тохиргоо > Усан тэмдэг > КИНО руу очиж туршиж үзнэ үү.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Галерей">
             <feature>• Цэвэрлэгээний зөвлөмжийн онцлог давхардсан зураг, төстэй зураг, хэт том видео зэргийг автоматаар таних тул цэвэрлэх зөвлөмж илүү хүртээмжтэй боллоо</feature>
             <feature>• Та AI Cutout-г ашиглан зургаас гол дүрийг ялгаж аваад, шинэ байрлал руу зөөж, дэвсгэрийг өөрчлөх боломжтой. Зургууд > AI Засвар > Шидэт засвар > AI Cutout руу очиж туршиж үзнэ үү</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Дэлгэц дээрх бичвэр дээр удаан дарсны дараа гарч ирэх хэрэгслийн мөрд Орчуулах онцлог байдаг боллоо</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Хялбар ашиглалт">
             <feature>• Асаах товчийг хоёр удаа дарах буюу дэлгэц унтраалттай үед дуу суллах товчийг хоёр удаа дарж заасан аппыг нээнэ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Түрийвч">
             <feature>• Нэвтрэх карт онцлог шифрлээгүй нэвтрэх картыг дуурайхыг дэмжинэ</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Түрийвчид Хоосон картын онцлог бий. Тохиргоо > Honor Түрийвч > Нэвтрэх карт руу очиж туршиж үзнэ үү.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Хамгаалалтын нөхөөс">
             <feature>• Системийн хамгаалалтад зориулж Андройд хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг (2025 оны арван нэгдүгээр сар) багтаав. Honor-н хамгаалалтын шинэчлэлтийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэл авах бол манай дараах вебсайтад зочилно уу: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Тэмдэглэл" type="end">
             <feature>1. Энэхүү шинэчлэлтийг суулгахад таны хувийн мэдээлэлд нөлөөлөхгүй ч шинэчлэхээс өмнө өгөгдлөө нөөцлөхийг зөвлөж байна
2. Зөвлөгөө дотроос бүтээгдэхүүний онцлогийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэлтэй танилцана уу
3. Шинэчлэх үед асуудал гарвал Honor-н үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгах буюу Honor-н хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төвд зочилж болно</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1102" name="mr-in">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, हे अद्यतन प्रामुख्याने सिस्टम कार्यप्रदर्शन वाढवते. सुधारणांचा आनंद घेण्यासाठी अद्यतनित करा</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="हलणारे फोटो">
             <feature>• आपण आता लॉक स्क्रीन म्हणून हलणारे फोटो सेट करू शकता. येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पहा: सेटिंग्ज > मुख्य स्क्रीन आणि शैली > लॉक स्‍क्रीन शैली > हलणारे फोटो.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="फिल्म-शैलीतील वॉटरमार्क">
             <feature>• कॅमेरामध्ये फिल्म-शैलीतील वॉटरमार्क समाविष्ट आहेत. येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पहा: कॅमेरा > सेटिंग्ज > वॉटरमार्क > फिल्म.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="गॅलरी">
             <feature>• क्लिनअप सूचना वैशिष्ट्य डुप्लिकेट फोटोज, समान प्रतिमा आणि मोठ्या आकाराच्या व्हिडिओंची स्वयंचलित ओळख सक्षम करते, ज्यामुळे अधिक सोयीस्कर क्लिनिंग सूचना मिळतात</feature>
             <feature>• AI कटआउट आपल्याला विषयवस्तू काढण्याची, प्रतिमेत नवीन स्थानावर हलवण्याची आणि पार्श्वभूमी बदलण्याची परवानगी देतो. येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पहा: फोटो > AI संपादन > मॅजिक रीटच > AI कटआउट</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor लेन्स">
             <feature>• स्क्रीनवरील मजकूर जास्त वेळ दाबल्यानंतर, पॉप-अप टूलबारमध्ये आता भाषांतर वैशिष्ट्य समाविष्ट आहे</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुलभता वैशिष्‍ट्ये">
             <feature>• पॉवर बटण दोनदा दाबा किंवा स्क्रीन बंद असताना, निर्दिष्ट अ‍ॅप उघडण्यासाठी व्हॉल्यूम डाउन बटण दोनदा दाबा</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• प्रवेश कार्ड वैशिष्ट्य एन्क्रिप्ट न केलेल्या प्रवेश कार्ड्सच्या सिम्युलेशनला समर्थन करते</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet मध्ये रिक्त कार्ड वैशिष्ट्य समाविष्ट आहे. येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पहा: सेटिंग्ज > Honor Wallet > प्रवेश कार्ड.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षितता पॅच">
             <feature>• सिस्टम सुरक्षिततेसाठी Android सुरक्षितता पॅच (नोव्हें 2025) समाविष्ट करण्यात आला आहे. Honor सुरक्षितता अद्यतनांबद्दल अधिक माहितीसाठी, कृपया आमच्या वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11 वर जा</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोट्स" type="end">
             <feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्‍थापित केल्याने आपल्या वैयक्तिक डेटावर परिणाम होणार नाही, परंतु तरीही अद्यतनित करण्यापूर्वी आपल्या डेटाचा बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते
2. उत्पादन वैशिष्ट्यांबद्दल अधिक माहिती Tips मध्ये शोधा
3. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, आपण Honor सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करून किंवा Honor ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जाऊन आमची मदत घेऊ शकता</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1086" name="ms-my">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini ini meningkatkan prestasi sistem terutamanya. Kemas kini untuk menikmati penambahbaikan tersebut</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Foto Bergerak">
             <feature>• Anda kini boleh menetapkan foto bergerak sebagai skrin kunci. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Skrin utama &amp; gaya > Gaya skrin kunci > Foto bergerak.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tera air gaya filem">
             <feature>• Kamera menyertakan tera air gaya filem. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Kamera > Tetapan > Tera air > FILEM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galeri">
             <feature>• Ciri cadangan pembersihan membolehkan pengecaman automatik foto pendua, imej serupa dan video bersaiz besar, memberikan cadangan pembersihan yang lebih mudah</feature>
             <feature>• Potongan AI membolehkan anda mengekstrak subjek, mengalihkannya ke kedudukan baharu dalam imej dan menukar latar belakang. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Foto > Edit AI > Kemas Magik > Potongan AI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Selepas menekan lama teks pada skrin, bar alat popup kini menyertakan ciri Terjemah</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kebolehaksesan">
             <feature>• Tekan dua kali butang Kuasa atau, apabila skrin dimatikan, tekan dua kali butang Turun kelantangan untuk membuka aplikasi tertentu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• Ciri kad akses menyokong simulasi kad akses yang tidak disulitkan</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet menyertakan ciri Kad kosong. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Honor Wallet > Kad akses.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tampalan keselamatan">
             <feature>• Tampalan keselamatan Android (Nov 2025) telah dimasukkan untuk tujuan keselamatan sistem. Untuk mendapatkan maklumat lanjut tentang kemas kini Keselamatan Honor, sila lawati laman web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Nota" type="end">
             <feature>1. Memasang kemas kini ini tidak akan menjejaskan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda masih disyorkan agar menyandarkan data sebelum melakukan kemas kini
2. Temui maklumat lanjut tentang ciri produk dalam Tip
3. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, anda boleh mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi talian penting perkhidmatan Honor atau melawati pusat khidmat pelanggan Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1109" name="my-mm">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် စနစ် စွမ်းဆောင်ရည်ကို အဓိက မြှင့်တင်ပေးသည်။ တိုးတက်ကောင်းမွန်အောင်လုပ်ထားသည်များကို သုံးစွဲခံစားရန် အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ရွေ့လျားဓာတ်ပုံ">
             <feature>• ယခုအခါ ရွေ့လျားဓာတ်ပုံကို လော့ခ်မျက်နှာပြင်အဖြစ် သတ်မှတ်နိုင်သည်။ ဖော်ပြပါသို့ သွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ဆက်တင် > ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်နှင့် ပုံစံ > လော့ခ်မျက်နှာပြင် ပုံစံ > ရွေ့လျားဓာတ်ပုံ။</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ရုပ်ရှင်ပုံစံ ရေစာ">
             <feature>• ကင်မရာတွင် ရုပ်ရှင်ပုံစံ ရေစာများ ပါဝင်သည်။ ဖော်ပြပါအတိုင်းသွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ကင်မရာ > ဆက်တင် > ရေစာ > FILM။</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ပုံပြခန်း">
             <feature>• ရှင်းလင်းသင့်သည်များကို အကြံပြုပေးသည့် လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်သည် ထပ်နေသော ဓာတ်ပုံများ၊ ဆင်တူရုပ်ပုံများနှင့် ဆိုဒ်အလွန်ကြီးသော ဗီဒီယိုများကို အော်တို ခွဲခြားဖော်ထုတ်ပေးပြီး ပိုမိုအဆင်ပြေသော ရှင်းလင်းရေး အကြံပြုချက်များကို ပံ့ပိုးပေးသည်</feature>
             <feature>• AI Cutout သုံး၍ အဓိကအရာကို ထုတ်ယူပြီး ပုံထဲရှိ နေရာသစ်တစ်ခုသို့ ပြောင်းရွှေ့ကာ နောက်ခံကို ပြောင်းလဲနိုင်သည်။ ဖော်ပြပါအတိုင်းသွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ပုံများ > AI ဖြင့် တည်းဖြတ် > Magic မွမ်းမံမှု > AI Cutout</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• မျက်နှာပြင်ပေါ်ရှိ စာသားကို ကြာကြာနှိပ်ပြီးနောက် ပေါ့ပ်အပ် တူးလ်ဘားတွင် ယခုအခါ ဘာသာပြန် လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်ကို တွေ့နိုင်ပါသည်</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="အထောက်အကူပြု လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်များ">
             <feature>• ပါဝါခလုတ်ကို နှစ်ချက်နှိပ်၍ သို့မဟုတ် မျက်နှာပြင်ပိတ်ထားချိန်တွင် အသံလျှော့ခလုတ်ကို နှစ်ချက်နှိပ်၍ သတ်မှတ်အက်ပ်တစ်ခုကို ဖွင့်နိုင်သည်</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• ဝင်ရောက်ခွင့်ကတ် လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်သည် ကုဒ်ပြောင်းဝှက်မထားသော ဝင်ရောက်ခွင့်ကတ်များကို တုပနိုင်သည်</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet တွင် ကတ်အလွတ်လုပ်ဆောင်ချက် ပါဝင်သည်။ ဖော်ပြပါအတိုင်းသွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ဆက်တင် > Honor Wallet > ဝင်ရောက်ခွင့်ကတ်။</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ">
             <feature>• စနစ်လုံခြုံရေးအတွက် Android လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့် ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ (နိုဝင်ဘာ 2025) ကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ Honor လုံခြုံရေး အပ်ဒိတ်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို သိရှိရန် ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ ဖော်ပြပါဝက်ဘ်ဆိုဒ်သို့ သွားရောက်ကြည့်ရှုပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="မှတ်ချက်" type="end">
             <feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းက သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာကို ထိခိုက်စေမည်မဟုတ်သော်လည်း အပ်ဒိတ်မလုပ်မီ သင့်ဒေတာကို ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ထားရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်
2. Tips တွင် ကုန်ပစ္စည်း လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို လေ့လာပါ
3. အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်နေစဉ် ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခုနှင့် ကြုံရပါက Honor ဝန်ဆောင်မှု ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ဖုန်းခေါ်၍ သို့မဟုတ် Honor ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားရောက်၍ အကူအညီရယူနိုင်သည်</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1109" name="my-zg">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ စနစ္ စြမ္းေဆာင္ရည္ကို အဓိက ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးသည္။ တိုးတက္ေကာင္းမြန္ေအာင္လုပ္ထားသည္မ်ားကို သုံးစြဲခံစားရန္ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ေ႐ြ႕လ်ားဓာတ္ပုံ">
             <feature>• ယခုအခါ ေ႐ြ႕လ်ားဓာတ္ပုံကို ေလာ့ခ္မ်က္ႏွာျပင္အျဖစ္ သတ္မွတ္ႏိုင္သည္။ ေဖာ္ျပပါသို႔ သြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ဆက္တင္ > ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ႏွင့္ ပုံစံ > ေလာ့ခ္မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ ပုံစံ > ေ႐ြ႕လ်ားဓာတ္ပုံ။</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="႐ုပ္ရွင္ပုံစံ ေရစာ">
             <feature>• ကင္မရာတြင္ ႐ုပ္ရွင္ပုံစံ ေရစာမ်ား ပါဝင္သည္။ ေဖာ္ျပပါအတိုင္းသြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ကင္မရာ > ဆက္တင္ > ေရစာ > FILM။</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ပုံျပခန္း">
             <feature>• ရွင္းလင္းသင့္သည္မ်ားကို အႀကံျပဳေပးသည့္ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္သည္ ထပ္ေနေသာ ဓာတ္ပုံမ်ား၊ ဆင္တူ႐ုပ္ပုံမ်ားႏွင့္ ဆိုဒ္အလြန္ႀကီးေသာ ဗီဒီယိုမ်ားကို ေအာ္တို ခြဲျခားေဖာ္ထုတ္ေပးၿပီး ပိုမိုအဆင္ေျပေသာ ရွင္းလင္းေရး အႀကံျပဳခ်က္မ်ားကို ပံ့ပိုးေပးသည္</feature>
             <feature>• AI Cutout သုံး၍ အဓိကအရာကို ထုတ္ယူၿပီး ပုံထဲရွိ ေနရာသစ္တစ္ခုသို႔ ေျပာင္းေ႐ႊ႕ကာ ေနာက္ခံကို ေျပာင္းလဲႏိုင္သည္။ ေဖာ္ျပပါအတိုင္းသြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ပံုမ်ား > AI ျဖင့္ တည္းျဖတ္ > Magic မြမ္းမံမႈ > AI Cutout</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ေပၚရွိ စာသားကို ၾကာၾကာႏွိပ္ၿပီးေနာက္ ေပါ့ပ္အပ္ တူးလ္ဘားတြင္ ယခုအခါ ဘာသာျပန္ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္ကို ေတြ႕ႏိုင္ပါသည္</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="အေထာက္အကူျပဳ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္မ်ား">
             <feature>• ပါဝါခလုတ္ကို ႏွစ္ခ်က္ႏွိပ္၍ သို႔မဟုတ္ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ပိတ္ထားခ်ိန္တြင္ အသံေလွ်ာ့ခလုတ္ကို ႏွစ္ခ်က္ႏွိပ္၍ သတ္မွတ္အက္ပ္တစ္ခုကို ဖြင့္ႏိုင္သည္</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• ဝင္ေရာက္ခြင့္ကတ္ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္သည္ ကုဒ္ေျပာင္းဝွက္မထားေသာ ဝင္ေရာက္ခြင့္ကတ္မ်ားကို တုပႏိုင္သည္</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet တြင္ ကတ္အလြတ္လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္ ပါဝင္သည္။ ေဖာ္ျပပါအတိုင္းသြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ဆက္တင္ > Honor Wallet > ဝင္ေရာက္ခြင့္ကတ္။</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="လုံျခံဳေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ">
             <feature>• စနစ္လုံၿခဳံေရးအတြက္ Android လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ (ႏိုဝင္ဘာ 2025) ကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ Honor လုံၿခဳံေရး အပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို သိရွိရန္ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ ေဖာ္ျပပါဝက္ဘ္ဆိုဒ္သို႔ သြားေရာက္ၾကည့္ရႈပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="မွတ္ခ်က္" type="end">
             <feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းက သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာကို ထိခိုက္ေစမည္မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း အပ္ဒိတ္မလုပ္မီ သင့္ေဒတာကို ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ထားရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္
2. Tips တြင္ ကုန္ပစၥည္း လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို ေလ့လာပါ
3. အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ေနစဥ္ ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခုႏွင့္ ႀကဳံရပါက Honor ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈ ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ဖုန္းေခၚ၍ သို႔မဟုတ္ Honor ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားေရာက္၍ အကူအညီရယူႏိုင္သည္</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1044" name="nb-no">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Kjære bruker. Denne oppdateringen forbedrer hovedsakelig systemytelsen. Oppdater for å få forbedringene</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Levende bilde">
             <feature>• Du kan nå bruke et levende bilde som låseskjerm. Prøv det ved å gå til Innstillinger > Startskjerm og stil > Låseskjermstil > Levende bilde.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vannmerke i filmstil">
             <feature>• Kamera har vannmerker i filmstil. Prøv det ved å gå til Kamera > Innstillinger > Vannmerke > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galleri">
             <feature>• Funksjonen for Opprydding-forslag muliggjør automatisk identifisering av dupliserte bilder, lignende bilder og store videoer, noe som gir mer hendige oppryddingsforslag</feature>
             <feature>• Med KI-utklipp kan du trekke ut motivet, flytte det til en ny posisjon i bildet og endre bakgrunnen. Prøv funksjonen ved å gå til Bilder > KI-redigering > Magic Retouch > KI-utklipp</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Etter et langt trykk på tekst på skjermen, inkluderer popupverktøylinjen nå Oversett-funksjonen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tilgjengelighetsfunksjoner">
             <feature>• Dobbelttrykk på av/på-knappen eller, når skjermen er slått av, dobbelttrykk på volum ned-knappen for å åpne en bestemt app</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lommebok">
             <feature>• Adgangskort-funksjonen støtter simulering av ukrypterte adgangskort</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Lommebok inkluderer funksjonen Blankt kort. Prøv det ved å gå til Innstillinger > Honor Lommebok > Tilgangskort.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sikkerhetsoppdatering">
             <feature>• Android-sikkerhetsoppdatering (nov 2025) er innlemmet for systemsikkerheten. For mer informasjon om sikkerhetsoppdateringer fra Honor, besøk nettstedet vårt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Merknader" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installeringen av denne oppdateringen påvirker ikke personopplysningene dine, men det anbefales likevel å sikkerhetskopiere dataene dine før du oppdaterer
2. Finn mer informasjon om produktfunksjoner i Tips
3. Hvis det oppstår problemer under oppdateringen, kan du få hjelp ved å ringe Honors kundeservice eller gå til Honors kundeservicesenter</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1121" name="ne-np">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, यो अपडेटले मुख्य गरी प्रणालीको कार्यसम्पादन परिष्कार गर्छ । सुधार गरिएका सुविधाहरूको आनन्द लिन अपडेट गर्नुहोस्</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सर्ने फोटो">
             <feature>• तपाईं अब सर्ने फोटोलाई लक स्क्रिनका रूपमा सेट गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > गृह स्क्रिन र शैली > स्क्रिन लक शैली > सर्ने फोटो.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="चलचित्र शैलीको वाटरमार्क">
             <feature>• क्यामेरामा चलचित्र शैलीको वाटरमार्क समावेश गरिएको छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: क्यामेरा > सेटिङहरू > वाटरमार्क> चलचित्र ।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ग्यालरी">
             <feature>• खाली गर्ने सुझावहरू दिने सुविधाले दोहोरिएका फोटोहरू, मिल्दाजुल्दा फोटोहरू र धेरै ठुलो साइज भएका भिडियोहरू स्वतः पहिचान गरेर खाली गर्ने अझ सहज सुझावहरू प्रदान गर्छ</feature>
             <feature>• तपाईं AI कटआउटका सहायताले सब्जेक्ट एक्स्ट्रयाक्ट गर्न, त्यसलाई सारेर फोटोको नयाँ स्थानमा लैजान र पृष्ठभूमि परिवर्तन गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: फोटोहरू > AI प्रयोग गरी सम्पादन गर्नुहोस् > म्याजिक रिटच > AI कटआउट</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• स्क्रिनमा भएको पाठमा लामो समयसम्म थिचेपछि अब पप-अप टुलबारमा अनुवाद गर्ने सुविधा समावेश हुन्छ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="उपलब्धता सुविधाहरू">
             <feature>• कुनै खास एप खोल्नका निम्ति पावर बटन दुई पटक थिच्नुहोस् वा स्क्रिन अफ भएका बेला भोल्युम डाउन बटन दुई पटक थिच्नुहोस्</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor वालेट">
             <feature>• पहुँच कार्डमा इन्क्रिप्ट नगरिएका पहुँच कार्डहरू सिमुलेसन गर्ने सुविधा उपलब्ध भएको छ</feature>
             <feature>• Honor वालेटमा खाली कार्डको सुविधा समावेश गरिएको छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > Honor वालेट > पहुँच कार्ड.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षा प्याच">
             <feature>• एन्ड्रोइड सुरक्षा प्याच (नोभेम्बर 2025) प्रणाली सुरक्षाका लागि समावेश गरिएको छ । Honor सुरक्षा अपडेटहरूबारे थप जानकारीका लागि कृपया हाम्रो वेबसाइटमा जानुहोस्: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोटहरू" type="end">
             <feature>1. तपाईंले यो एप स्थापना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटामा कुनै प्रभाव नपर्ने भए पनि तपाईंलाई अपडेट गर्नुअघि आफ्नो डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ
2. सुझावहरूमा गई उत्पादनका सुविधाहरूका बारेमा थप जानकारी हेर्नुहोस्
3. अपडेटको क्रममा तपाईंले कुनै समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईं Honor सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गरेर वा Honor ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा गएर हाम्रो मद्दत प्राप्त गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ ।</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1043" name="nl-nl">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Beste gebruiker, deze update verbetert vooral de systeemprestaties. Werk bij om van de verbeteringen te genieten</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Levende foto">
             <feature>• U kunt nu een levende foto instellen als vergrendelscherm. Probeer het uit via: Instellingen > Startscherm en stijl > Vergrendelschermstijl > Levende foto.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Watermerk in filmstijl">
             <feature>• Camera bevat watermerken in filmstijl. Probeer het uit via: Camera > Instellingen > Watermerk > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Foto's">
             <feature>• De functie Opschoonsuggesties maakt automatische identificatie van dubbele foto's, vergelijkbare afbeeldingen en te grote video's mogelijk, voor handigere opschoonsuggesties</feature>
             <feature>• Met AI Uitsnijding kunt u het onderwerp extraheren, naar een nieuwe positie in de afbeelding verplaatsen en de achtergrond wijzigen. Probeer het uit via: Foto's > AI-bewerking > Magische retouche > AI Uitsnijding</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• De pop-upwerkbalk bevat nu de functie Vertalen wanneer u lang op de tekst op het scherm hebt gedrukt</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Toegankelijkheidsfuncties">
             <feature>• Druk tweemaal op de aan/uit-knop of druk tweemaal op de volume lager-knop wanneer het scherm is uitgeschakeld om een specifieke app te openen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• De functie Toegangskaart ondersteunt de simulatie van niet-versleutelde toegangskaarten</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet bevat de functie Lege kaart. Probeer het uit via: Instellingen > Honor Wallet > Toegangskaart.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Beveiligingspatch">
             <feature>• Android-beveiligingspatch (november 2025) is opgenomen voor systeembeveiliging. Voor meer informatie over Honor-beveiligingsupdates kunt u terecht op onze website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notities" type="end">
             <feature>1. Het installeren van deze update heeft geen invloed op uw persoonlijke gegevens, maar het wordt nog steeds aanbevolen om een back-up van uw gegevens te maken voordat u deze update uitvoert
2. Ontdek meer informatie over productfuncties in Tips
3. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, kunt u onze hulp krijgen door de Honor-servicehotline te bellen of naar het Honor-klantenservicecentrum te gaan</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1096" name="or-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ମୁଖ୍ୟତଃ ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ର କାର୍ଯ୍ୟଦକ୍ଷତାକୁ ବଢାଏ। ଉନ୍ନତିଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଉପଭୋଗ କରିବାକୁ ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରନ୍ତୁ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ଚଳମାନ ଫଟୋ">
             <feature>• ଆପଣ ଏବେ ଏକ ଚଳମାନ ଫଟୋକୁ ଲକ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ପରି ସେଟ୍‌ କରିପାରିବେ। ଏଠାକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାକୁ ବ୍ୟବହାର କରି ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ଓ ଷ୍ଟାଇଲ୍ > ଲକ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ଷ୍ଟାଇଲ୍ > ଚଳମାନ ଫଟୋ।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ଫିଲ୍ମ-ଷ୍ଟାଇଲ୍‌ର ୱାଟର୍‌ମାର୍କ">
             <feature>• କ୍ୟାମେରାରେ ଫିଲ୍ମ ଷ୍ଟାଇଲ୍‌ର ୱାଟର୍‌ମାର୍କ ରହିଛି। ଏଠାକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାକୁ ବ୍ୟବହାର କରି ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ: କ୍ୟାମେରା > ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ୱାଟର୍‌ମାର୍କ > ଫିଲ୍ମ।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ଗ୍ୟାଲେରୀ">
             <feature>• କ୍ଲିନ୍‌ ଅପ୍‌ ପରାମର୍ଶଗୁଡ଼ିକର ବିଶେଷତା ଅଧିକ ସୁବିଧାଜନକ କ୍ଲିନ୍‌ ଅପ୍‌ କରିବା ପରାମର୍ଶଗୁଡ଼ିକ ପ୍ରଦାନ କରି ନକଲ ଫଟୋ, ସମାନ ପ୍ରତିଛବି ଏବଂ ବଡ଼ ଭିଡ଼ିଓଗୁଡ଼ିକର ସ୍ୱତଃ ଚିହ୍ନଟକୁ ସକ୍ଷମ କରେ</feature>
             <feature>• AI କଟଆଉଟ୍‌ ଆପଣଙ୍କୁ ବିଷୟ ବାହାର କରିବାକୁ, ପ୍ରତିଛବିରେ ଏକ ନୂତନ ଅବସ୍ଥାନକୁ ସ୍ଥାନାନ୍ତର କରିବାକୁ ଏବଂ ପୃଷ୍ଠପଟ ପରିବର୍ତ୍ତନ କରିବାକୁ ସକ୍ଷମ କରିଥାଏ। ନିମ୍ନଲିଖିତକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାକୁ ବ୍ୟବହାର କରି ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ: ଫଟୋଗୁଡିକ > AI ସମ୍ପାଦନ > ମ୍ୟାଜିକ୍ ରିଟଚ୍ > AI କଟଆଉଟ୍‌</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ଲେନ୍ସ">
             <feature>• ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ରେ ଟେକ୍ସଟ୍‌କୁ ବହୁତ ସମୟ ଧରି ଦବାଇ ରଖିବା ପରେ, ପପ୍-ଅପ୍ ଟୁଲବାର୍‌ରେ ଏବେ ଅନୁବାଦ ବିଶେଷତା ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରେ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ପ୍ରବେଶଯୋଗ୍ୟ ବିଶେଷତା">
             <feature>• ଆପଣ ପାୱାର୍ ବଟନ୍‌କୁ ଦୁଇଥର ଦବାନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ଅଫ୍‌ ଥିବା ସମୟରେ, ଏକ ନିର୍ଦ୍ଦିଷ୍ଟ ଆପ୍ ଖୋଲିବା ପାଇଁ ଭଲ୍ୟୁମ କମାଇବା ବଟନ୍‌କୁ ଦୁଇଥର ଦବାନ୍ତୁ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ୱାଲେଟ୍">
             <feature>• ଆକସେସ୍ କାର୍ଡ୍ ବିଶେଷତା ଏନକ୍ରିପ୍ଟ କରାଯାଇଥିବା ଆକସେସ୍ କାର୍ଡ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକର ସିମୁଲେସନ୍ ସମର୍ଥନ କରେ</feature>
             <feature>• Honor ୱାଲେଟ୍‌ ଶୂନ୍ୟ କାର୍ଡ୍‌ ବିଶେଷତା ମଧ୍ୟ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରେ। ନିମ୍ନୋକ୍ତକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାକୁ ବ୍ୟବହାର କରି ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > Honor ୱାଲେଟ୍‌ > ଆକସେସ୍ କାର୍ଡ୍‌।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌">
             <feature>• Android ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ (ନଭେମ୍ବର 2025) ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପାଇଁ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି। Honor ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ବିଷୟରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି ଆମ ୱେବସାଇଟ୍‌ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11 ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ପ୍ରଭାବିତ ହେବ ନାହିଁ, ତଥାପି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରିବା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡାଟାର ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି
2. ଟିପ୍ସରେ ଉତ୍ପାଦ ବିଶେଷତାଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଉପରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ଆବିଷ୍କାର କରନ୍ତୁ
3. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରିବା ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଆପଣ Honor ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌କୁ କଲ୍‌ କରି କିମ୍ବା Honor ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଇ, ଆମ ସହାୟତା ପାଇପାରିବେ</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1094" name="pa-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਮੁੱਖ ਤੌਰ 'ਤੇ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੀ ਕਾਰਗੁਜ਼ਾਰੀ ਨੂੰ ਬਿਹਤਰ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਸੁਧਾਰਾਂ ਦਾ ਅਨੰਦ ਲੈਣ ਲਈ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰੋ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਚਲ ਚਿੱਤਰ">
             <feature>• ਤੁਸੀਂ ਹੁਣ ਇੱਕ ਚਲ ਚਿੱਤਰ ਨੂੰ ਲੌਕ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਦੇ ਤੌਰ 'ਤੇ ਸੈੱਟ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਅਤੇ ਸ਼ੈਲੀ > ਲੌਕ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਸ਼ੈਲੀ > ਚਲ ਚਿੱਤਰ।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਫ਼ਿਲਮ-ਸ਼ੈਲੀ ਵਾਲਾ ਵਾਟਰਮਾਰਕ">
             <feature>• ਕੈਮਰੇ ਵਿੱਚ ਫ਼ਿਲਮ-ਸ਼ੈਲੀ ਵਾਲੇ ਵਾਟਰਮਾਰਕ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਹਨ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਕੈਮਰਾ > ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਵਾਟਰਮਾਰਕ > ਫ਼ਿਲਮ।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਗੈਲਰੀ">
             <feature>• ਕਲੀਨਅੱਪ ਕਰਨ ਸੰਬੰਧੀ ਸੁਝਾਅ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾ ਡੁਪਲੀਕੇਟ ਫ਼ੋਟੋਆਂ, ਸਮਾਨ ਚਿੱਤਰਾਂ, ਅਤੇ ਵੱਡੇ ਆਕਾਰ ਦੀਆਂ ਵੀਡੀਓ ਦੀ ਸਵੈਚਲਿਤ ਪਛਾਣ ਨੂੰ ਸਮਰੱਥ ਬਣਾਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਨਾਲ ਵਧੇਰੇ ਸੁਵਿਧਾਜਨਕ ਕਲੀਨਅੱਪ ਕਰਨ ਸੰਬੰਧੀ ਸੁਝਾਅ ਮਿਲਦੇ ਹਨ</feature>
             <feature>• AI ਕੱਟਆਉਟ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਵਿਸ਼ੇ ਨੂੰ ਐਕਸਟ੍ਰੈਕਟ ਕਰਨ, ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਚਿੱਤਰ ਵਿੱਚ ਇੱਕ ਨਵੀਂ ਥਾਂ 'ਤੇ ਭੇਜਣ, ਅਤੇ ਬੈਕਗ੍ਰਾਉਂਡ ਬਦਲਣ ਦੇ ਸਮਰੱਥ ਬਣਾਉਂਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਫੋਟੋਆਂ > AI ਸੋਧੋ > ਮੈਜਿਕ ਰੀਟੱਚ > AI ਕੱਟਆਉਟ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ਲੈਂਜ਼">
             <feature>• ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ 'ਤੇ ਟੈਕਸਟ ਨੂੰ ਦੇਰ ਤੱਕ ਦਬਾਉਣ ਤੋਂ ਬਾਅਦ, ਪੌਪ-ਅੱਪ ਟੂਲਬਾਰ ਵਿੱਚ ਹੁਣ ਅਨੁਵਾਦ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਹੈ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਪਹੁੰਚਣਯੋਗਤਾ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾਵਾਂ">
             <feature>• ਕਿਸੇ ਖਾਸ ਐਪ ਨੂੰ ਖੋਲ੍ਹਣ ਲਈ ਪਾਵਰ ਬਟਨ ਨੂੰ ਦੋ ਵਾਰ ਦਬਾਓ ਜਾਂ, ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਬੰਦ ਹੋਣ 'ਤੇ ਆਵਾਜ਼ ਘਟਾਉਣ ਵਾਲੇ ਬਟਨ ਨੂੰ ਦੋ ਵਾਰ ਦਬਾਓ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ਵਾਲੇਟ">
             <feature>• ਐਕਸੈਸ ਕਾਰਡ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾ ਏਨਕ੍ਰਿਪਟ ਨਾ ਕੀਤੇ ਐਕਸੈਸ ਕਾਰਡਾਂ ਦੀ ਨਕਲ ਦਾ ਸਮਰਥਨ ਕਰਦੀ ਹੈ</feature>
             <feature>• Honor ਵਾਲੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਖਾਲੀ ਕਾਰਡ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > Honor ਵਾਲੇਟ > ਐਕਸੈਸ ਕਾਰਡ।</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ">
             <feature>• ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਲਈ Android ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ (ਨਵੰ 2025) ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। Honor ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਲਈ, ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਵੈੱਬਸਾਈਟ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ਨੋਟਸ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ 'ਤੇ ਕੋਈ ਅਸਰ ਨਹੀਂ ਪਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਹਾਲੇ ਵੀ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਦਾ ਬੈਕ ਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ
2. ਸੁਝਾਅ ਐਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਉਤਪਾਦ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾਵਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਦੀ ਖੋਜ ਕਰੋ
3. ਜੇਕਰ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਤੁਸੀਂ Honor ਸੇਵਾ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰ ਕੇ ਜਾਂ Honor ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਮਦਦ ਲੈ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1045" name="pl-pl">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Szanowny użytkowniku, ta aktualizacja w głównej mierze podnosi wydajność systemu. Zainstaluj ją, aby korzystać z ulepszeń</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ruchome zdjęcie">
             <feature>• Możesz już ustawić ruchome zdjęcie jako ekran blokady. Wypróbuj tę funkcję, wybierając kolejno Ustawienia > Ekran główny i styl > Styl ekranu blokady > Ruchome zdjęcie.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Znak wodny w stylu filmowym">
             <feature>• Aparat zawiera znaki wodne w stylu filmowym. Wypróbuj tę funkcję, wybierając kolejno Aparat > Ustawienia > Znak wodny > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galeria">
             <feature>• Funkcja Sugestie oczyszczania umożliwia automatyczną identyfikację duplikatów zdjęć, podobnych obrazów i filmów o zbyt dużym rozmiarze, co ułatwia usuwanie zbędnych plików</feature>
             <feature>• Wycinek AI umożliwia wyodrębnienie obiektu, przeniesienie go w nowe miejsce na zdjęciu i zmianę tła. Wypróbuj tę funkcję, wybierając Zdjęcia > Edycja AI > Magiczny retusz > Wycinek AI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Obiektyw Honor">
             <feature>• Po długim naciśnięciu tekstu na ekranie wyskakujący pasek narzędzi zawiera teraz funkcję tłumaczenia</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkcje ułatwień dostępu">
             <feature>• Naciśnij dwukrotnie przycisk włącznika lub, gdy ekran jest wyłączony, naciśnij dwukrotnie przycisk zmniejszania głośności, aby otworzyć określoną aplikację</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Portfel Honor">
             <feature>• Funkcja karty dostępu umożliwia symulację niezaszyfrowanych kart dostępu</feature>
             <feature>• Portfel Honor ma funkcję Pusta karta. Wypróbuj ją, wybierając Ustawienia > Portfel Honor > Karta dostępu.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Poprawka zabezpieczeń">
             <feature>• Aktualizacja zawiera Poprawkę zabezpieczeń systemu Android (listopad 2025 r.). Więcej informacji o aktualizacjach zabezpieczeń urządzeń Honor można znaleźć w naszej witrynie internetowej: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notatki" type="end">
             <feature>1. Ta aktualizacja nie ma wpływu na Twoje dane osobowe, jednak przed jej zainstalowaniem zaleca się wykonanie kopii zapasowej danych
2. Więcej informacji o funkcjach produktu znajdziesz w Poradach
3. Jeśli podczas aktualizacji napotkasz jakiekolwiek problemy, możesz uzyskać pomoc, dzwoniąc na infolinię serwisu Honor lub odwiedzając punkt serwisowy Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1046" name="pt-br">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Prezado(a) usuário(a), essa atualização aprimora principalmente o desempenho do sistema. Atualize para aproveitar as melhorias</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Foto em movimento">
             <feature>• Agora você pode definir uma foto em movimento como a tela de bloqueio. Experimente acessando: Configurações > Tela inicial e estilo > Estilo de tela de bloqueio > Foto em movimento.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Marca d'água estilo filme">
             <feature>• A Câmera inclui marcas d'água estilo filme. Experimente acessando: Câmera > Configurações > Marca d'água > FILME.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galeria">
             <feature>• O recurso de sugestões de limpeza ativa a identificação automática de fotos duplicadas, imagens semelhantes e vídeos grandes demais, fornecendo sugestões de limpeza mais convenientes</feature>
             <feature>• O Recorte com IA permite que você extraia o objeto, mova-o para uma nova posição na imagem e altere o fundo. Experimente acessando: Fotos > Edição de IA > Retoque mágico > Recorte com IA</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Após pressionar e segurar o texto na tela, a barra de ferramentas pop-up agora inclui o recurso Traduzir</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Recursos de acessibilidade">
             <feature>• Pressione duas vezes o botão de energia ou, quando a tela estiver desligada, pressione duas vezes o botão de abaixar o volume para abrir um aplicativo específico</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Carteira Honor">
             <feature>• O recurso de Cartão de acesso suporta a simulação de cartões de acesso não criptografados</feature>
             <feature>• A Carteira Honor inclui o recurso de Cartão em branco. Experimente acessando: Configurações > Carteira Honor > Cartão de acesso.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch de segurança">
             <feature>• Patch de segurança do Android (novembro de 2025) incorporado para a segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da Honor, visite nosso site: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. A instalação desta atualização não afetará os dados pessoais, mas ainda é recomendável fazer backup dos dados antes de atualizar
2. Descubra mais informações sobre os recursos do produto em Dicas
3. Se você encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, poderá obter nossa ajuda ligando para a Linha de atendimento de serviço da Honor ou acessando a Central de serviços ao cliente da Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2070" name="pt-pt">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Caro utilizador, esta atualização melhora principalmente o desempenho do sistema. Atualize para aproveitar as melhorias</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fotografia dinâmica">
             <feature>• Agora pode definir uma fotografia dinâmica como ecrã de bloqueio. Experimente, acedendo a: Configurações > Ecrã inicial e estilo > Estilo de bloqueio de ecrã > Fotografia dinâmica.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Marca de água estilo película">
             <feature>• A Câmara inclui marcas de água estilo película. Experimente, acedendo a: Câmara > Definições > Marca de água > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galeria">
             <feature>• A funcionalidade de sugestões de limpeza permite a identificação automática de fotos duplicadas, imagens semelhantes e vídeos muito grandes, oferecendo sugestões de limpeza mais convenientes</feature>
             <feature>• O Recorte por IA permite extrair o objeto, movê-lo para uma nova posição na imagem e alterar o fundo. Experimente, acedendo a: Fotografias > AI Edit > Retoque mágico > Recorte por IA</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Após premir longamente o texto no ecrã, a barra de ferramentas pop-up agora inclui a funcionalidade Traduzir</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funcionalidades de acessibilidade">
             <feature>• Toque duas vezes no botão Ligar/Desligar ou, quando o ecrã estiver desligado, toque duas vezes no botão de diminuir o volume para abrir uma aplicação específica</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• A funcionalidade de cartão de acesso suporta a simulação de cartões de acesso não encriptados</feature>
             <feature>• A Honor Wallet inclui a funcionalidade Cartão em branco. Experimente, acedendo a: Configurações > Honor Wallet > Cartão de acesso.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Correção de segurança">
             <feature>• Foi incorporada uma correção de segurança do Android (novembro de 2025) para segurança do sistema. Para mais informações sobre as atualizações de Segurança Honor, visite o nosso website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não afetará os seus dados pessoais, mas ainda assim é recomendável efetuar uma cópia de segurança dos seus dados antes de atualizar
2. Descobrir mais informações sobre as funcionalidades do produto em Sugestões
3. Se encontrar quaisquer problemas durante a atualização, pode obter ajuda ligando para a linha direta de assistência da Honor ou visitando o centro de apoio ao cliente da Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1048" name="ro-ro">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Stimate utilizator, această actualizare îmbunătățește în principal performanța sistemului. Actualizați pentru a beneficia de îmbunătățiri</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fotografie în mișcare">
             <feature>• Acum puteți seta o fotografie în mișcare ca ecran de blocare. Încercați accesând: Setări > Ecran de pornire și stil > Stil blocare ecran > Fotografie în mișcare.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Inscripționare în stilul film">
             <feature>• Camera foto include inscripționări în stilul film. Încercați accesând: Cameră foto > Setări > Inscripționare > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerie">
             <feature>• Funcția Sugestii de curățare permite identificarea automată a fotografiilor duplicate, a imaginilor similare și a videoclipurilor prea mari, oferind sugestii de curățare mai ușor de folosit</feature>
             <feature>• Decupare AI vă permite să extrageți subiectul, să îl mutați într-o nouă poziție în imagine și să schimbați fundalul. Încercați accesând: Fotografii > Editare AI > Retuș magic > Decupare AI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• După apăsarea lungă a textului de pe ecran, bara de instrumente pop-up include acum funcția Traducere</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funcții de accesibilitate">
             <feature>• Apăsați de două ori butonul Pornire sau, când ecranul este stins, apăsați de două ori butonul Reducere volum pentru a deschide o aplicație specificată</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• Funcția Card de acces acceptă simularea cardurilor de acces necriptate</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet include funcția Card gol. Încercați accesând: Setări > Honor Wallet > Card de acces.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Corecție de securitate">
             <feature>• Pentru securitatea sistemului, a fost încorporată o corecție de securitate Android (noiembrie 2025). Pentru mai multe informații despre actualizările de securitate Honor, vă rugăm să vizitați site-ul nostru web: https://www.honor.com/ro/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notițe" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalarea acestei actualizări nu va afecta datele dvs. cu caracter personal, dar este totuși recomandat să faceți o copie de rezervă a datelor înainte de actualizare
2. Descoperiți mai multe informații despre caracteristicile produsului în Sugestii
3. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, puteți solicita ajutorul nostru apelând linia de asistență Honor sau vizitând Centrul de service pentru clienți Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1049" name="ru-ru">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Мы выпустили это обновление, чтобы улучшить производительность системы. Установите его, чтобы оценить изменения</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Живое фото">
             <feature>• Теперь можно установить живое фото в качестве экрана блокировки. Чтобы опробовать эту функцию, перейдите в раздел: «Настройки > Рабочий экран и стиль > Стиль экрана блокировки > Живое фото».</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Стикер в стиле пленки">
             <feature>• Камера включает стикеры в стиле пленки. Чтобы опробовать эту функцию, перейдите в раздел: «Камера > Настройки > Стикеры > ПЛЕНКА».</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Галерея">
             <feature>• Функция предложений по очистке памяти позволяет автоматически находить дублирующие фото, похожие изображения и большие видео, обеспечивая более удобную очистку</feature>
             <feature>• Функция «AI-силуэт» позволяет вырезать объект, переместить его в другое место на изображении и изменить фон. Чтобы опробовать эту функцию, выберите «Фото > AI-редактор > AI-ретушь > AI-силуэт»</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Теперь на панели инструментов, всплывающей после длительного нажатия на текст на экране, появилась функция «Перевести»</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Специальные возможности">
             <feature>• Чтобы открыть указанное приложение, дважды нажмите на кнопку питания или, когда экран выключен, дважды нажмите на кнопку уменьшения громкости</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Кошелек Honor">
             <feature>• Функция «Карта доступа» поддерживает симуляцию незашифрованных карт доступа</feature>
             <feature>• В «Кошелек Honor» добавлена функция «Пустая карта». Чтобы опробовать ее, выберите «Настройки > Кошелек Honor > Карта доступа».</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Исправление безопасности">
             <feature>• В обновление включено исправление безопасности для Android (ноябрь 2025 г.). Чтобы получить подробную информацию об обновлениях безопасности Honor, посетите наш сайт: https://www.honor.com/eurasia/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Заметки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Установка этого обновления не приведет к удалению ваших персональных данных, но мы все равно рекомендуем вам создать резервную копию своих данных перед обновлением
2. Изучите дополнительную информацию о функциях продукта в «Советах»
3. Если во время обновления у вас возникнут проблемы, обратитесь за помощью на горячую линию службы поддержки Honor или в сервисный центр для клиентов Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1115" name="si-lk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, මෙම යාවත්කාලීන කිරීම ප්‍රධාන වශයෙන් පද්ධතියේ කාර්යසාධනය උසස් කරයි. වැඩිදියුණු කිරීම් අත්විඳීමට යාවත්කාල කරන්න</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="චලන ඡායාරූපය">
             <feature>• දැන් ඔබට චලන ඡායාරූපයක් අගුළු තිරය ලෙස සැකසිය හැකි වේ. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: සැකසුම් > මුල් තිරය සහ විලාසය > අගුළු තිර විලාසය > චලන ඡායාරූපය.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="චිත්‍රපට විලාසයේ දිය සලකුණ">
             <feature>• කැමරාවේ චිත්‍රපට විලාසයේ දිය සලකුණු ඇතුළත් වේ. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: කැමරාව > සැකසුම් > දිය සලකුණ > චිත්‍රපටය.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ගැලරිය">
             <feature>• වඩා පහසු පිරිසිදු කිරීමේ යෝජනා සපයමින් පිරිසිදු කිරීමේ යෝජනා විශේෂාංගය අනුපිටපත් ඡායාරූප, සමාන රූප සහ පමණ ඉක්මවා විශාල වූ වීඩියෝ ස්වයංක්‍රීයව හඳුනා ගැනීමේ හැකියාව ලබා දෙයි</feature>
             <feature>• AI කපාගැනීම ඔබට වස්තුව උපුටා ගැනීමට, එය රූපයේ නව පිහිටීමකට ගෙනයාමට සහ පසුබිම වෙනස් කිරීමට හැකියාව ලබා දෙයි. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: ඡායාරූප > AI සංස්කරණය > මැජික් පිරියම් කිරීම > AI කපාගැනීම</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• තිරය මත ඇති පෙළ දීර්ඝ එබීමෙන් පසුව, උත්පතන මෙවලම් තීරුවේ දැන් පරිවර්තනය කිරීමේ විශේෂාංගය ඇතුළත් වේ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ප්‍රවේශ්‍යතා විශේෂාංග">
             <feature>• නිශ්චිත යෙදුමක් විවෘත කිරීමට බලය බොත්තම ද්වි ඔබන්නට හෝ, තිරය අක්‍රියව ඇති විට, හඬ අඩු කිරීමේ බොත්තම ද්වි-ඔබන්න</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• ප්‍රවේශ කාඩ්පත් විශේෂාංගය සංකේතනය නොකළ ප්‍රවේශ කාඩ්පත් අනුකරණයට සහය දක්වයි</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet තුළ හිස් කාඩ්පත විශේෂාංගය ඇතුළත් වේ. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: සැකසුම් > Honor Wallet > ප්‍රවේශ කාඩ්පත.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක">
             <feature>• පද්ධති ආරක්ෂාව සඳහා Android ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක (2025 නොවැ) යොදාගෙන ඇත. Honor ආරක්ෂක යාවත්කාල පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සඳහා, කරුණාකර අපගේ වෙබ් අඩවිය වෙත යන්න https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="සටහන්" type="end">
             <feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්තවලට බල නොපානු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් යාවත්කාල කිරීමට පෙර ඔබගේ දත්ත උපස්ථ කිරීමට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ
2. ඉඟි තුළ නිෂ්පාදන විශේෂාංග පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සොයා ගන්න
3. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේදී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, ඔබට Honor සේවා හොට්ලයින් ඇමතීමෙන් හෝ Honor පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට පිවිසීමෙන් අපගේ උපකාර ලබා ගත හැකි වේ</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1051" name="sk-sk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Vážený používateľ, táto aktualizácia hlavne zvyšuje výkon systému. Aktualizujte, aby ste si užili zlepšenia</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pohyblivá fotografia">
             <feature>• Môžete nastaviť pohyblivú fotografiu ako zamknutú obrazovku. Vyskúšajte to v časti: Nastavenia > Domovská obrazovka a štýl > Štýl obrazovky > Pohyblivá fotografia.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vodotlač vo filmovom štýle">
             <feature>• Fotoaparát obsahuje vodotlače vo filmovom štýle. Vyskúšajte to v časti: Fotoaparát > Nastavenia > Vodotlač > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galéria">
             <feature>• Funkcia Návrhy na vyčistenie umožňuje automatickú identifikáciu duplicitných fotografií, podobných obrázkov a videí s nadmernou veľkosťou, čím poskytuje pohodlnejšie návrhy na vyčistenie</feature>
             <feature>• AI výrez umožňuje vybrať predmet, presunúť ho na nové miesto na obrázku a zmeniť pozadie. Vyskúšajte to v časti: Fotografie > AI úpravy > Magické retušovanie > AI výrez</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Objektív Honor">
             <feature>• Po dlhom stlačení textu na obrazovke sa na rozbaľovacom paneli s nástrojmi zobrazí funkcia Preklad</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkcie uľahčenia prístupu">
             <feature>• Môžete dvakrát stlačiť tlačidlo napájania alebo pri vypnutej obrazovke dvakrát stlačiť tlačidlo zníženia hlasitosti, aby sa otvorila určená aplikácia</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Peňaženka">
             <feature>• Funkcia prístupovej karty podporuje simuláciu nešifrovaných prístupových kariet</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Peňaženka obsahuje funkciu Prázdna karta. Vyskúšajte to v časti: Nastavenia > Honor Peňaženka > Prístupová karta.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezpečnostná oprava">
             <feature>• Súčasťou zabezpečenia systému je bezpečnostná oprava systému Android (z novembra 2025). Ak potrebujete viac informácií o bezpečnostných aktualizáciách spoločnosti Honor, navštívte webovú stránku https://www.honor.com/sk/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Poznámky" type="end">
             <feature>1. Inštalácia tejto aktualizácie neovplyvní vaše osobné údaje, ale aj tak sa odporúča pred aktualizáciou si ich zálohovať
2. Ďalšie informácie o funkciách produktu si pozrite v aplikácii Tipy
3. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytne problém, pomoc môžete získať na zákazníckej linke Honor alebo navštívením Centra služieb zákazníkom Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1060" name="sl-si">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, ta posodobitev izboljša predvsem delovanje sistema. Posodobite, da boste lahko izkoristili izboljšave</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Gibljiva fotografija">
             <feature>• Zdaj lahko za zaklenjeni zaslon nastavite gibljivo fotografijo. Funkcijo lahko preizkusite tako, da izberete: Nastavitve > Začetni zaslon in slog > Slog zaklenjenega zaslona > Gibljiva fotografija.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Filmski vodni žig">
             <feature>• Kamera omogoča filmske vodne žige. Funkcijo lahko preizkusite tako, da izberete: Kamera > Nastavitve > Vodni žig > Film.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerija">
             <feature>• Funkcija predlogov za čiščenje omogoča samodejno prepoznavanje podvojenih fotografij, podobnih slik in prevelikih videoposnetkov, kar zagotavlja bolj priročne predloge za čiščenje</feature>
             <feature>• Izrezovanje z UI omogoča, da izrežete motiv, ga postavite na novo mesto na sliki ter spremenite ozadje. Funkcijo lahko preizkusite tako, da odprete: Fotografije > Urejanje z UI > Čarobna izboljšava > Izrezovanje z UI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Če pritisnete in pridržite besedilo na zaslonu, pojavna orodna vrstica zdaj vključuje funkcijo za prevajanje</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkcije za dostopnost">
             <feature>•Dvakrat pritisnite gumb za vklop/izklop oziroma, ko je zaslon izklopljen, dvakrat pritisnite tipko za znižanje glasnosti, da odprete želeno aplikacijo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Denarnica Honor">
             <feature>• Funkcija dostopne kartice podpira simulacijo nešifriranih dostopnih kartic</feature>
             <feature>• Aplikacija Denarnica Honor ponuja funkcijo za prazne kartice. Preizkusite jo tako, da odprete razdelek Nastavitve > Denarnica Honor > Pristopna kartica.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Varnostni popravek">
             <feature>• Varnostni popravki za Android (november 2025) so vključeni za varnost sistema. Za več informacij o varnostnih posodobitvah Honor obiščite spletno mesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zapiski" type="end">
             <feature>1. Namestitev te posodobitve ne vpliva na vaše osebne podatke, vendar je kljub temu priporočljivo, da podatke pred posodobitvijo varnostno kopirate
2. Več informacij o funkcijah izdelka je na voljo v razdelku Nasveti
3. Če med posodabljanjem pride do težav, lahko pokličete odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom družbe Honor ali obiščete servisni center družbe Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1053" name="sv-se">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Bästa användare, den här uppdateringen förbättrar främst systemets prestanda. Uppdatera för att ta del av förbättringarna</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Rörligt foto">
             <feature>• Du kan nu ange ett rörligt foto som låsskärm. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Startsida och stil > Utseende för låsskärm > Rörligt foto.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vattenstämpel i filmstil">
             <feature>• Kamera omfattar vattenstämplar i filmstil. Prova genom att gå till: Kamera > Inställningar > Vattenstämpel > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galleri">
             <feature>• Funktionen Rensningsförslag möjliggör automatisk identifiering av dubblettfoton, lika bilder och för stora videor, vilket ger mer praktiska rensningsförslag</feature>
             <feature>• Med AI-urklipp kan du extrahera motivet, flytta det till en ny position i bilden och ändra bakgrunden. Prova genom att gå till: Foton > AI-redigering > Magisk retuschering > AI-urklipp</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• När du har tryckt länge på texten på skärmen innehåller nu popup-verktygsfältet funktionen Översätt</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tillgänglighetsfunktioner">
             <feature>• Dubbeltryck på strömknappen eller dubbeltryck på volymknapp ned, när skärmen är av, för att öppna en viss app</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Plånbok">
             <feature>•Funktionen Passerkort stöder simulering av passerkort som inte är krypterade</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Plånbok omfattar funktionen Tomt kort. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Honor Plånbok > Passerkort.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Säkerhetskorrigering">
             <feature>• Säkerhetskorrigering för Android (november 2025) har implementerats för systemsäkerhet. Vill du ha mer information om uppdateringar för Honor Säkerhet går du till vår webbplats https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Noteringar" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installation av den här uppdateringen påverkar inte dina personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du säkerhetskopierar alla data innan du uppdaterar
2. Upptäck mer information om produktfunktioner i Tips
3. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa Honors hotline för service eller besöka Honors kundtjänstcenter för att få hjälp</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1089" name="sw-KE">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, sasisho hili kwa kiasi kikubwa linaboresha utendaji wa mfumo. Sasisha ili ufurahie maboresho</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Picha Inayosonga">
             <feature>• Sasa unaweza kuweka picha inayosonga kama skrini iliyofungwa. Ijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Skrini ya mwanzo na mtindo > Mtindo wa skrini iliyofungwa > Picha inayosonga.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Alama fifi ya mtindo wa filamu">
             <feature>• Kamera inajumuisha alama fifi za mtindo wa filamu. Ijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Kamera > Mipangilio > Alama fifi > FILAMU.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Matunzio">
             <feature>• Kipengele cha mapendekezo ya usafishaji huwezesha utambuzi otomatiki wa picha rudufu, picha zinazofanana na video kubwa kupita kiasi, hivyo basi kukupa mapendekezo yanayokufaa zaidi ya usafishaji</feature>
             <feature>• Madoido ya kuondoa ya AI hukuwezesha kuchopoa mada, kuisogeza hadi sehemu mpya kwenye picha na kubadilisha mandharinyuma. Jaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Picha > Uhariri wa AI > Uboreshaji wa Miujiza > Madoido ya kuondoa ya AI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Baada ya kubofya kwa muda mrefu maandishi yaliyo kwenye skrini, upauzana ibukizi sasa unajumuisha kipengele cha Tafsiri</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vipengele vya zana za walemavu">
             <feature>• Bofya mara mbili Kitufe cha nishati au, skrini ikiwa imezimwa, bofya mara mbili Kitufe cha kupunguza kiwango cha sauti ili ufungue programu iliyoainishwa</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pochi la Honor">
             <feature>• Kipengele cha Kadi ya ufikiaji kinaruhusu uigaji wa kadi za ufikiaji ambazo hazijasimbwa</feature>
             <feature>• Pochi la Honor linajumuisha kipengele cha kadi Tupu. Kijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Pochi la Honor > Kadi ya ufikiaji.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Rekebisho la usalama">
             <feature>• Rekebisho la usalama wa Android (Nov 2025) limejumuishwa kwa ajili ya usalama wa mfumo. Ili kupata maelezo zaidi kuhusu masasisho ya Usalama wa Honor, tafadhali tembelea tovuti yetu: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Madokezo" type="end">
             <feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutaathiri data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado inapendekezwa ili kuweka hifadhi rudufu ya data yako kabla ya kusasisha
2. Gundua maelezo zaidi kwenye vipengele vya bidhaa kwenye Vidokezo
3. Ikiwa utakumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, unaweza kupata msaada wetu kwa kupiga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya Honor au tembelea kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1097" name="ta-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு முதன்மையாக சிஸ்டம் செயல்திறனை மேம்படுத்துகிறது. மேம்பாடுகளைப் பெற, புதுப்பிக்கவும்</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="நகரும் புகைப்படம்">
             <feature>• இப்போது நீங்கள் நகரும் புகைப்படத்தைப் பூட்டுத் திரையாக அமைக்கலாம். இதற்குச் சென்று அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: அமைப்புகள் > முகப்புத் திரை &amp; ஸ்டைல் > பூட்டுத் திரை ஸ்டைல் > நகரும் புகைப்படம்.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ஃபிலிம் ஸ்டைல் வாட்டர்மார்க்">
             <feature>• கேமராவில் ஃபிலிம் ஸ்டைல் வாட்டர்மார்க்குகள் உள்ளன. இதற்குச் சென்று அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: கேமரா > அமைப்புகள் > வாட்டர்மார்க் > ஃபிலிம்.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="கேலரி">
             <feature>• கிளீன்அப் பரிந்துரைகள் அம்சம் நகல் புகைப்படங்கள், ஒத்த படங்கள் மற்றும் பெரிதாக்கப்பட்ட வீடியோக்களைத் தானாக அடையாளம் காண உதவுகிறது, இது மிகவும் வசதியான கிளீன்அப் பரிந்துரைகளை வழங்குகிறது</feature>
             <feature>• AI கட்அவுட் அம்சம் படப்பொருளைப் பிரித்தெடுக்கவும், படத்தில் ஒரு புதிய நிலைக்கு நகர்த்தவும், பின்னணியை மாற்றவும் உதவுகிறது. இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: படங்கள் > AI திருத்தம் > மேஜிக் ரீடச் > AI கட்அவுட்</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• திரையில் உள்ள உரையை நீண்ட நேரம் அழுத்திய பிறகு, பாப்அப் கருவிப்பட்டியில் இப்போது மொழிபெயர்ப்பு அம்சம் சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="அணுகல்திறன் அம்சங்கள்">
             <feature>• பவர் பொத்தானை இருமுறை அழுத்தலாம் அல்லது திரை அணைந்திருக்கும்போது, ஒலியளவைக் குறைக்கும் பொத்தானை இருமுறை அழுத்தி ஒரு குறிப்பிட்ட செயலியைத் திறக்கலாம்</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor வாலட்">
             <feature>• அணுகல் அட்டை அம்சம் குறியாக்கப்படாத அணுகல் அட்டைகளின் உருவகப்படுத்துதலை ஆதரிக்கிறது</feature>
             <feature>• Honor வாலட்டில் வெற்று அட்டை அம்சமும் உள்ளது. இதற்குச் சென்று அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: அமைப்புகள் > Honor வாலட் > அணுகல் அட்டை.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு">
             <feature>• சிஸ்டம் பாதுகாப்பிற்காக Android பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு (நவ 2025) சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. Honor பாதுகாப்புப் புதுப்பிப்புகளைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களுக்கு, எங்கள் வலைத்தளத்தைப் பார்க்கவும்: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="குறிப்புகள்" type="end">
             <feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவைப் பாதிக்காது, எனினும் புதுப்பிப்பதற்கு முன்பு உங்கள் தரவைக் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுப்பது இன்னும் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது
2. உதவிக்குறிப்புகளில் தயாரிப்பு அம்சங்களைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களைக் கண்டறிக
3. புதுப்பிக்கும்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், Honor சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைப்பதன் மூலமோ அல்லது Honor வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்தைப் பார்வையிடுவதன் மூலமோ எங்கள் உதவியைப் பெறலாம்</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1098" name="te-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారుకు, ఈ అప్‌డేట్ ప్రధానంగా సిస్టమ్ పనితీరును మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది. మెరుగుదలలను ఆనందించడానికి అప్‌డేట్ చేయండి</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="కదులుతున్న ఫోటో">
             <feature>• మీరు ఇప్పుడు కదులుతున్న ఫోటోను లాక్ స్క్రీన్ వలె సెట్ చేయవచ్చు. ఇక్కడికి వెళ్ళి దానిని ప్రయత్నించండి: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ &amp; శైలి > లాక్ స్క్రీన్ శైలి > కదులుతున్న ఫోటో.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ఫిల్మ్-శైలి వాటర్‌మార్క్">
             <feature>• కెమెరాలో ఫిల్మ్-శైలి వాటర్‌మార్క్‌లు ఉన్నాయి. ఇక్కడికి వెళ్ళి దానిని ప్రయత్నించండి: కెమెరా > సెట్టింగ్‌లు > వాటర్‌మార్క్ > ఫిల్మ్.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="గ్యాలరీ">
             <feature>• క్లీనప్ సూచనల ఫీచర్ మరింత సౌకర్యవంతమైన క్లీనింగ్ సూచనలను అందించడానికి నకిలీ ఫోటోలు, ఒకేలా ఉన్న చిత్రాలు మరియు అధిక పరిమాణ వీడియోల స్వయంచాలక గుర్తింపును ప్రారంభిస్తుంది</feature>
             <feature>• AI కట్అవుట్ మీరు విషయాన్ని సంగ్రహించి, దానిని చిత్రంలోని కొత్త స్థానానికి తరలించడానికి మరియు నేపథ్యాన్ని మార్చడానికి అనుమతిస్తుంది. ఇక్కడికి వెళ్ళి దానిని ప్రయత్నించండి: ఫోటోలు > AI సవరణ > మేజిక్ రీటచ్ > AI కట్అవుట్</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor లెన్స్">
             <feature>• స్క్రీన్‌లో టెక్స్ట్‌ను నొక్కి, పట్టుకుని తర్వాత, పాప్-అప్ టూల్‌బార్‌లో ఇప్పుడు అనువాదం ఫీచర్ ఉంటుంది</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="యాక్సెసబిలిటీ ఫీచర్‌లు">
             <feature>• పవర్ బటన్‌ను రెండుసార్లు నొక్కండి లేదా స్క్రీన్ ఆఫ్‌లో ఉన్నప్పుడు, నిర్దిష్ట అప్లికేషన్‌ను తెరవడానికి వాల్యూమ్ తగ్గించే బటన్‌ను రెండుసార్లు నొక్కండి</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor వాలెట్">
             <feature>• యాక్సెస్ కార్డ్ ఫీచర్ అన్ఎన్‌క్రిప్ట్ చేసిన యాక్సెస్ కార్డ్‌ల సిమ్యులేషన్‌కు మద్దతు ఇస్తుంది</feature>
             <feature>• Honor వాలెట్‌లో ఖాళీ కార్డ్ ఫీచర్ ఉంటుంది. ఇక్కడికి వెళ్ళి దానిని ప్రయత్నించండి: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > Honor వాలెట్ > యాక్సెస్ కార్డ్.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="భద్రతా ప్యాచ్">
             <feature>• సిస్టమ్ భద్రత కోసం Android భద్రతా ప్యాచ్ (నవం 2025) చేర్చబడింది. Honor భద్రత అప్‌డేట్‌ల గురించి మరింత సమాచారం కోసం, దయచేసి మా వెబ్‌సైట్‌ను సందర్శించండి: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="గమనికలు" type="end">
             <feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్ ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వలన మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటా ప్రభావితం కాదు, కాని అప్‌డేట్ చేయడానికి ముందు మీ డేటాను బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని ఇంకా సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది
2. చిట్కాల్లో ఉత్పత్తి ఫీచర్లపై మరింత సమాచారాన్ని తెలుసుకోండి
3. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో ఏవైనా సమస్యలను ఎదుర్కొంటే, మీరు Honor సర్వీస్ హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేసి లేదా Honor కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రాన్ని సందర్శించి మా సహాయం పొందవచ్చు</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1054" name="th-th">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตครั้งนี้เน้นปรับปรุงประสิทธิภาพระบบเป็นหลัก โปรดอัปเดตเพื่อใช้การปรับปรุง</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ภาพเคลื่อนไหว">
             <feature>• ตอนนี้คุณสามารถตั้งค่าภาพเคลื่อนไหวเป็นหน้าจอล็อคได้แล้ว ลองใช้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > หน้าจอหลักและสไตล์ > รูปแบบหน้าจอล็อค > ภาพเคลื่อนไหว</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ลายน้ำสไตล์ฟิล์ม">
             <feature>• กล้องถ่ายรูปจะมีลายน้ำสไตล์ฟิล์มให้ใช้งาน ลองใช้โดยไปที่: กล้องถ่ายรูป > การตั้งค่า > ลายน้ำ > ฟิล์ม</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="แกลเลอรี">
             <feature>• ฟีเจอร์คำแนะนำการล้างข้อมูลจะช่วยระบุภาพถ่ายซ้ำ รูปภาพที่คล้ายกัน และวิดีโอที่มีขนาดใหญ่เกินโดยอัตโนมัติ ช่วยให้คำแนะนำในการล้างข้อมูลอย่างสะดวกยิ่งขึ้น</feature>
             <feature>• คัทเอาท์ AI ช่วยให้คุณสามารถดึงข้อมูลวัตถุ ย้ายไปยังตำแหน่งใหม่ในรูปภาพ และเปลี่ยนพื้นหลัง ลองใช้โดยไปที่: ภาพถ่าย > การแก้ไขด้วย AI > เมจิกรีทัช > คัทเอาท์ AI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• หลังจากกดที่ข้อความบนหน้าจอค้างไว้ ตอนนี้แถบเครื่องมือจะประกอบไปด้วยฟีเจอร์การแปล</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ฟีเจอร์การเข้าถึง">
             <feature>• กดปุ่มเปิดปิดเครื่องสองครั้ง หรือกดปุ่มลดระดับเสียงลองครั้งเพื่อเปิดแอปที่เฉพาะเจาะจง</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• ฟีเจอร์บัตรเข้าใช้งานรองรับการจำลองบัตรเข้าใช้งานที่ไม่ได้เข้ารหัส</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet จะรวมฟีเจอร์บัตรเปล่า ลองใช้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > Honor Wallet > บัตรเข้าใช้งาน</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="แพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัย">
             <feature>• มีการรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัย Android (พ.ย. 2025) เพื่อความปลอดภัยของระบบ ดูข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับการอัปเดตด้านความปลอดภัยของ Honor ได้โดยไปที่เว็บไซต์ของเรา https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="โน้ต" type="end">
             <feature>1. การติดตั้งการอัปเดตนี้จะไม่ส่งผลต่อข้อมูลส่วนตัว แต่เราขอแนะนำให้คุณสำรองข้อมูลก่อนอัปเดต
2. ค้นพบข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับฟีเจอร์ผลิตภัณฑ์ในเคล็ดลับ
3. หากคุณพบปัญหาใดๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต คุณสามารถรับความช่วยเหลือได้โดยการโทรติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการลูกค้าของ Honor หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1124" name="tl-ph">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Minamahal na user, pangunahing pinapahusay ng update na ito ang performance ng system. I-update para i-enjoy ang mga pagpapahusay</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Gumagalaw na Larawan">
             <feature>• Puwede ka nang magtakda ng gumagalaw na larawan bilang lock screen. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Home screen at estilo > Estilo ng lock ng screen > Gumagalaw na larawan.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Watermark na estilong film">
             <feature>• May mga watermark na estilong film ang Camera. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Camera > Mga Setting > Watermark > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Gallery">
             <feature>• Nagbibigay-daan ang feature na Mga suhestyon sa pag-clean up sa awtomatikong pagtukoy ng mga duplicate na larawan, katulad na larawan, at video na labis ang laki, na nagbibigay ng mga mas magandang suhestyon sa pag-clean up</feature>
             <feature>• Nagbibigay-daan sa iyo ang AI Cutout na i-extract ang subject, dalhin ito sa bagong posisyon sa larawan, at baguhin ang background. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Larawan > AI Edit > Magic Retouch > AI Cutout</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Pagkatapos pindutin nang matagal ang text sa screen, mayroon nang feature na Isalin ang pop-up na toolbar</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Mga feature ng accessibility">
             <feature>• Pindutin nang dalawang beses ang Power button o, kapag naka-off ang screen, pindutin nang dalawang beses ang button na Pagpapahina ng volume para magbukas ng tinukoy na app</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• Sinusuportahan ng feature na access card ang simulation ng mga hindi naka-encrypt na access card</feature>
             <feature>• Kasama sa Honor Wallet ang feature na Blangkong card. Subukan ang mga ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Honor Wallet > Access card.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Panseguridad na patch">
             <feature>• Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Nob 2025) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa mga Panseguridad na update ng Honor, bisitahin ang aming website sa https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Mga Tala" type="end">
             <feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto ang pag-install sa update na ito sa iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update
2. Tuklasin ang higit pang impormasyon sa mga feature ng produkto sa Mga Tip
3. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, makukuha mo ang tulong namin sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng Honor o pagbisita sa customer service center ng Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1055" name="tr-tr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Değerli kullanıcımız, bu güncelleme ile çoğunlukla sistem performansı artırılmıştır. İyileştirmelerin tadını çıkarmak için güncelleyin</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Hareketli Fotoğraf">
             <feature>• Artık hareketli bir fotoğrafı kilit ekranı olarak belirleyebilirsiniz. Şu adımları takip ederek deneyebilirsiniz: Ayarlar > Başlangıç ekranı ve stil > Ekran kilitleme yöntemi > Hareketli fotoğraf.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Film tarzı filigran">
             <feature>• Kamera uygulamasına film tarzı filigranlar eklenmiştir. Şu adımları takip ederek deneyebilirsiniz: Kamera > Ayarlar > Filigran > FİLM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galeri">
             <feature>• Temizlik önerileri özelliği, zaten mevcut olan fotoğrafları, benzer görselleri ve büyük boyutlu videoları otomatik olarak tanımlayarak daha kullanışlı temizlik önerileri sunar</feature>
             <feature>• AI Kesim özelliği görsellerdeki süjeyi çıkarmanıza, yeni konuma taşımanıza ve arka planı değiştirmenize olanak tanır. Şu adımları takip ederek deneyebilirsiniz: Fotoğraflar > AI Düzenleme > Sihirli Rötuş > AI Kesim</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Ekrandaki metne basılı tuttuktan sonra açılan araç çubuğu artık Çeviri özelliğini de içeriyor</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Erişilebilirlik özellikleri">
             <feature>• Belirli bir uygulamayı açmak için Güç düğmesine iki kez basın veya ekran kapalıyken Ses azaltma düğmesine iki kez basın</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Cüzdan">
             <feature>• Giriş kartı özelliğine şifrelenmemiş giriş kartlarını simüle etme desteği eklendi</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Cüzdan'a Boş kart özelliği eklendi. Şu adımları takip ederek deneyebilirsiniz: Ayarlar > Honor Cüzdan > Giriş kartı.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Güvenlik yaması">
             <feature>• Sistem güvenliği için Android güvenlik yamasını (Kasım 2025) içermektedir. Honor Güvenlik güncellemeleri ile ilgili daha fazla bilgi için lütfen web sitemizi ziyaret edin: https://www.honor.com/tr/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notlar" type="end">
             <feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi etkilemeyecektir ancak yine de güncellemeden önce verilerinizi yedeklemeniz önerilir
2. İpuçları bölümünden ürün özellikleri hakkında daha fazla bilgiyi keşfedin
3. Güncelleme sırasında sorunla karşılaşırsanız Honor yardım hattını arayarak veya Honor müşteri hizmetleri merkezini ziyaret ederek yardım alabilirsiniz</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1058" name="uk-ua">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Шановний користувачу! Це оновлення насамперед підвищує продуктивність системи. Установіть його, щоб відчути покращення</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Живе фото">
             <feature>• Тепер можна встановити живе фото як екран блокування. Щоб спробувати, перейдіть до меню Налаштування > Головний екран і стиль > Стиль екрана блокування > Живе фото.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Водяний знак у стилі плівки">
             <feature>• Камера містить водяні знаки в стилі плівки. Щоб спробувати, перейдіть до меню "Камера" > "Налаштування" > "Водяний знак " > "ПЛІВКА".</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Галерея">
             <feature>• Функція "Поради щодо очищення" дає змогу автоматично виявляти дублікати фото, схожі зображення та надто великі відео, надаючи поради для більш зручного очищення місця</feature>
             <feature>• Функція "Ші-вирізання" дає змогу виокремити об’єкт, перемістити його в нове місце на зображенні та змінити фон. Спробуйте її, перейшовши до розділу "Фотографії" > "Інтелектуальне змінення" > "Магічного ретушування" > "ШІ-вирізання"</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Тепер після тривалого натискання тексту на екрані у спливаючій панелі інструментів з'являється функція "Перекласти"</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Функції спеціальних можливостей">
             <feature>• Двічі натисніть кнопку живлення або, коли екран вимкнений, двічі натисніть кнопку зменшення гучності для відкриття зазначеного додатка</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Гаманець Honor">
             <feature>• Функція картки доступу підтримує моделювання незашифрованих карток доступу</feature>
             <feature>• Гаманець Honor дає змогу додати пусту картку. Щоб скористатися цією функцією, виберіть "Налаштування" > "Гаманець Honor" > "Картка доступу".</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Виправлення системи безпеки">
             <feature>• Виправлення безпеки Android від листопада 2025 року впроваджено для посилення безпеки системи. Додаткову інформацію про оновлення для системи безпеки Honor див. на нашому вебсайті https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Нотатки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Установлення цього оновлення не вплине на ваші особисті дані, однак рекомендовано спочатку створити їхні резервні копії
2. Дізнайтеся більше про функції продукту в розділі "Підказки"
3. Якщо під час оновлення у вас виникнуть будь-які проблеми, ви можете отримати нашу допомогу, зателефонувавши на гарячу лінію Honor або відвідавши центр послуг Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1056" name="ur-pk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>محترم صارف، یہ اپ ڈیٹ بنیادی طور پر سسٹم کی کارکردگی کو بڑھاتی ہے۔ بہتریوں سے لطف اندوز ہونے کے لیے اپ ڈیٹ کریں</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="حرکت پذیر تصویر">
             <feature>‏• اب آپ ایک حرکت پذیر تصویر کو لاک اسکرین کے طور پر سیٹ کر سکتے ہیں۔ یہاں جا کر اسے آزمائیں: ترتیبات > ہوم اسکرین اور طرز > لاک اسکرین کی طرز > حرکت پذیر تصویر۔</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="فلمی طرز والا واٹر مارک">
             <feature>‏• کیمرے میں فلمی طرز کے واٹر مارکس شامل ہیں۔ یہاں جا کر اسے آزمائیں: کیمرہ > ترتیبات > واٹر مارک > فلم۔</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="گیلری">
             <feature>‏• صفائی کی تجاویز کی خصوصیت دوہری تصاویر، مماثل تصاویر، اور بڑے سائز کی ویڈیوز کی خود کار شناخت کو فعال کرتی ہے، جو صفائی کی زیادہ آسان تجاویز فراہم کرتی ہے</feature>
             <feature>‏• ‏AI کٹ آؤٹ آپ کو موضوع کو اخذ کرنے، تصویر میں ایک نئی پوزیشن پر لے جانے اور پس منظر کو تبدیل کرنے کے قابل بناتی ہے۔ یہاں جا کر اسے آزمائیں: تصاویر > ‏‏AI ترمیم > میجک ری ٹچ > ‏AI کٹ آؤٹ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏Honor لینز">
             <feature>‏• اسکرین پر متن کو دیر تک دبانے کے بعد، پاپ اپ ٹول بار میں اب ترجمے کی خصوصیت شامل ہے</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="رسائی پذیری کی خصوصیات">
             <feature>‏• مخصوص ایپ کو کھولنے کے لیے پاور بٹن کو دو مرتبہ دبائیں، یا جب اسکرین آف ہو، تو والیوم کم کرنے کے بٹن کو دو مرتبہ دبائیں</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏Honor والیٹ">
             <feature>‏‏• رسائی کا کارڈ کی خصوصیت غیر مرموز کردہ رسائی کے کارڈز کی نقل سازی میں تعاون کرتی ہے</feature>
             <feature>‏• Honor والیٹ میں خالی کارڈ کی خصوصیت شامل ہے۔ یہاں جا کر اسے آزمائیں: ترتیبات > ‏‏Honor والیٹ > رسائی کا کارڈ۔</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="سکیورٹی پیچ">
             <feature>‏• Android سکیورٹی پیچ (نومبر 2025) شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔ Honor سکیورٹی اپ ڈیٹس کے بارے میں مزید معلومات کے لیے، براہ کرم ہماری ویب سائٹ ملاحظہ کریں https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="نوٹس" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا متاثر نہیں ہو گا، لیکن اپ ڈیٹ کرنے سے پہلے اب بھی اپنے ڈیٹا کا بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے
‏2. تجاویز میں پروڈکٹس کی خصوصیات کے بارے میں مزید معلومات دریافت کریں
‏3. اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کوئی مسئلہ درپیش ہوتا ہے، تو آپ Honor سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کر کے یا Honor کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جا کر ہماری مدد حاصل کر سکتے ہیں</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2115" name="uz-uz">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu yangilanish asosan tizim unumdorligini oshiradi. Takomillashtirishlardan foydalanish uchun yangilang</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Animatsiyali surat">
             <feature>• Endi animatsiyali suratni ekran qulfi qilib sozlashingiz mumkin. Bu yerda sinang: Sozlamalar > Bosh ekran va uslub > Ekran qulfi uslubi > Animatsiyali surat.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Film uslubidagi shaffof belgi">
             <feature>• Kamera film uslubidagi shaffof belgilarni oʻz ichiga oladi. Bu yerda sinang: Kamera > Sozlamalar > Shaffof belgi > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galereya">
             <feature>• Tozalash tavsiyalari funksiyasi ikki nusxadagi suratlar, oʻxshash rasmlar va katta hajmli videolarni avtomatik aniqlash imkonini beradi va yanada qulayroq tozalash tavsiyalarini beradi</feature>
             <feature>• AI Kesish sizga subyektni ajratib olish, uni rasmda yangi joyga koʻchirish va fonni almashtirish imkonini beradi. Bu yerda sinang: Suratlar > AI Tahrirlash > Sehrli retush > AI Kesish</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Ekrandagi matn uzoq bosib turilganidan keyin qalqib chiqadigan asboblar paneli endi Tarjima funksiyasini oʻz ichiga oladi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Maxsus imkoniyatlar funksiyalari">
             <feature>• Muayyan ilovani ochish uchun Quvvat tugmasini ikki marta bosing yoki ekran oʻchiqligida Tovushni pasaytirish tugmasini ikki marta bosing</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• Kirish kartasi funksiyasi shifrlanmagan kirish kartalarini simulyatsiyalashni dastaklaydi</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet Toza karta funksiyasini oʻz ichiga oladi. Bu yerda sinang: Sozlamalar > Honor Wallet > Kirish kartasi.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Xavfsizlik tuzatmasi">
             <feature>• Tizim xavfsizligi uchun Android xavfsizlik tuzatmasi (2025-yil, noyabr) kiritildi. Honor Xavfsizlik yangilanishlari haqida batafsil axborot olish uchun veb-saytimizga tashrif buyuring: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Eslatmalar" type="end">
             <feature>1. Bu yangilanishni oʻrnatish shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringizga taʼsir qilmaydi, lekin yangilashdan oldin maʼlumotlaringizni zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi
2. Maslahatlar ilovasida mahsulot xususiyatlari bilan batafsilroq tanishing
3. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, Honor xizmatining tezkor raqamiga telefon qilish yoki Honor mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyurish orqali yordam olishingiz mumkin</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1066" name="vi-vn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật này chủ yếu nâng cao hiệu suất hệ thống. Hãy cập nhật để tận hưởng các cải tiến</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ảnh động">
             <feature>• Bạn hiện có thể đặt ảnh động làm màn hình khóa. Hãy thử bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Phong cách và màn hình chính > Kiểu khóa màn hình > Ảnh động.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Hình chìm mờ kiểu phim">
             <feature>• Máy ảnh bao gồm hình mờ kiểu phim. Hãy thử bằng cách vào: Máy ảnh > Cài đặt > Hình chìm mờ > PHIM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bộ sưu tập">
             <feature>• Tính năng đề xuất dọn dẹp cho phép tự động nhận dạng ảnh trùng lặp, hình ảnh tương tự và video có kích thước lớn, cung cấp các đề xuất dọn dẹp thuận tiện hơn</feature>
             <feature>• AI Cutout cho phép bạn trích xuất chủ thể, di chuyển đến vị trí mới trong ảnh và thay đổi nền. Hãy dùng thử bằng cách vào: Ảnh > AI Sửa > Tự động sửa > AI Cutout</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Sau khi nhấn và giữ văn bản trên màn hình, thanh công cụ bật lên giờ đây có thêm tính năng Dịch</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tính năng Trợ năng">
             <feature>• Nhấn đúp nút Nguồn hoặc, khi màn hình tắt, nhấn đúp nút Giảm âm lượng để mở một ứng dụng cụ thể</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Ví">
             <feature>• Tính năng Thẻ truy cập hỗ trợ mô phỏng thẻ truy cập không được mã hóa</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Ví bao gồm tính năng Thẻ trống. Hãy dùng thử bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Honor Ví > Thẻ truy cập.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bản vá bảo mật">
             <feature>• Bản cập nhật này tích hợp Bản vá bảo mật Android (tháng 11 năm 2025) để bảo mật hệ thống. Để biết thêm thông tin về các Bản cập nhật bảo mật của Honor, vui lòng truy cập trang web của chúng tôi: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Ghi chú" type="end">
             <feature>1. Việc cài đặt bản cập nhật này sẽ không ảnh hưởng đến dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn, nhưng bạn vẫn nên sao lưu dữ liệu trước khi cập nhật
2. Khám phá thêm thông tin về các tính năng sản phẩm trong ứng dụng Mẹo
3. Nếu gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, bạn có thể nhận trợ giúp của chúng tôi bằng cách gọi đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ của Honor hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="3076" name="zh-hk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新主要針對系統進行了優化，建議您進行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="動態相片">
             <feature>• 新增支援動態相片鎖屏能力。體驗路徑：設定 > 主屏幕和個人化 > 鎖屏樣式 > 動態相片。</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="菲林風格浮水印">
             <feature>• 新增菲林風格浮水印。體驗路徑：相機 > 設定 > 浮水印 > 菲林。</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="圖片庫">
             <feature>• 新增清理建議功能，支援重複相片、相似圖片、超大影片等自動識別，提供更便捷的清理建議</feature>
             <feature>• 新增智能退地，支援圖片主體退地移位及背景修改。體驗路徑：相片 > AI 編輯 > 魔法修圖 > 智能退地</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="智能視覺">
             <feature>• 長按屏幕文字時，在彈出的工具欄新增翻譯功能</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="輔助功能">
             <feature>• 支援輕按兩下電源鍵/息屏狀態下輕按兩下遞減音量鍵開啟指定應用程式</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="榮耀錢包">
             <feature>• 新增門卡功能，支援模擬未經加密過的門卡</feature>
             <feature>• 新增空白卡功能。體驗路徑：設定 > 榮耀錢包 > 門卡。</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安全性修補程式">
             <feature>• 整合 Android 2025年11月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需了解有關榮耀軟件安全更新內容的資訊，請瀏覽榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="更新注意事項" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份
2. 更多精彩功能介紹，請瀏覽「玩機技巧」應用程式
3. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線或至榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1028" name="zh-tw">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新主要針對系統進行了最佳化，建議您進行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="動態相片">
             <feature>• 新增支援動態相片鎖定螢幕功能。體驗路徑：設定 > 桌面和個人化 > 鎖定畫面樣式 > 動態相片。</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="膠片風格浮水印">
             <feature>• 新增膠片風格浮水印。體驗路徑：相機 > 設定 > 浮水印 > 膠片。</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="圖片庫">
             <feature>• 新增清理建議功能，支援自動辨識重複相片、相似圖片、超大影片等，提供更便捷的清理建議</feature>
             <feature>• 新增智慧去背，支援圖片主體去背移位及背景變更。體驗路徑：相片 > AI 編輯 > 魔法修圖 > 智慧去背</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="智慧視覺">
             <feature>• 長按螢幕文字時，彈出的工具列新增翻譯功能</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="無障礙功能">
             <feature>• 支援按兩下電源鍵/在螢幕關閉狀態下按兩下降低音量按鈕開啟指定應用程式</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="榮耀錢包">
             <feature>• 新增門禁卡功能，支援模擬未經加密的門禁卡</feature>
             <feature>• 新增空白卡功能。體驗路徑：設定 > 榮耀錢包 > 門禁卡。</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安全性修補程式">
             <feature>• 整合 Android 2025 年 11 月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟體安全更新內容的資訊，請造訪榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="更新注意事項" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份
2. 如需更多精彩功能介紹，請查看「玩機技巧」應用程式
3. 在更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1152" name="ug-cn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا ئاساسلىقى سىستېمىغا قارىتا ئەلالاشتۇرۇش ئېلىپ بېرىلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ھەرىكەتچان رەسىم">
             <feature>‏• ھەرىكەتچان رەسىم ئىشلىتىپ قۇلۇپ ئېكران تەگلىكى تەڭشەش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى. ئىشلىتىش يولى: تەڭشەك > ئۈستەليۈزى ۋە خاسلاشتۇرۇش > قۇلۇپ ئېكران ئۇسلۇبى > ھەرىكەتچان رەسىم.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏پليۇنكا ئۇسلۇبىدىكى سۇ باسما">
             <feature>‏• پىليۇنكا ئۇسلۇبىدىكى سۇباسما يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى. ئىشلىتىش يولى: كامېرا > تەڭشەك > سۇباسما > پىليۇنكا.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏ئامبار">
             <feature>‏• تازىلاش تەكلىپى ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، تەكرار رەسىم، ئوخشىشىدىغان رەسىم، زىيادە چوڭ سىن قاتارلىقلارنى ئۆزلۈكىدىن تونۇپ، تېخىمۇ قولايلىق تازىلاش تەكلىپى بىلەن تەمىنلەيدۇ</feature>
             <feature>‏• رەسىمنى ئاڭلىق قىيىش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، رەسىم ئاساسىي گەۋدىسىنى قىيىپ يۆتكەشكە ۋە ئارقا كۆرۈنۈشىنى ئ‍ۆزگەرتىشكە بولىدۇ. ئىشلىتىش يولى: رەسىم > ‏AI تەھرىرلەش > ‏سېھىرلىك رەسىم تۈزەش > ‏رەسىمنى ئاڭلىق قىيىش</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ئاڭلىق نەزەر">
             <feature>‏• ئېكراندىكى تېكىستنى ئۇزاق بېسىپ تۇرغاندا پەيدا بولغان سەكرەتمە قورالبالداققا تەرجىمە ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ياردەمچى ئىقتىدار">
             <feature>‏• توك مەنبەسى كۇنۇپكىسىنى قوش چېكىش/ئېكران ئۆچۈك چاغدا ئۈنسىزلىتىش كۇنۇپكىسىنى قوش چېكىپ، بەلگىلەنگەن ئەپنى ئېچىشنى قوللايدۇ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏روڭياۋ ھەميانى">
             <feature>‏• ئاچقۇچ كارتا ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، مەخپىيلەشتۈرۈلمىگەن ئاچقۇچ كارتىنى تەقلىد قىلىشنى قوللايدۇ</feature>
             <feature>‏• قۇرۇق كارتا ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى. ئىشلىتىش يولى: تەڭشەك > روڭياۋ ھەميانى > ئاچقۇچ كارتا.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى">
             <feature>‏• ئاندرويدنىڭ 2025-يىل 11-ئايلىق بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، سىستېما بىخەتەرلىكى كۈچەيتىلدى. روڭياۋ يۇمشاق دېتالىنىڭ بىخەتەرلىك يېڭىلاش مەزمۇنىغا ئالاقىدار ئۇچۇرلار ئۈچۈن روڭياۋ ئورگان تەرەپ تور بېكىتى https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/11 نى زىيارەت قىلىڭ.</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="‏يېڭىلاش بىلدۈرگۈسى" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، لېكىن يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتنى زاپاسلاشنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز
‏2. تېخىمۇ كۆپ سەرخىل ئىقتىدارلارنى «ئىشلىتىش كۆرسەتمىسى» ئەپىنى زىيارەت قىلىپ كۆرۈڭ
‏3. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركىسى مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1031" name="de-at">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung verbessert hauptsächlich die Systemleistung. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bewegungsfoto">
             <feature>• Sie können jetzt ein Bewegungsfoto als Sperrbildschirm festlegen. Probieren Sie es aus. Gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Startbildschirm und Stil > Sperrbildschirmstil > Bewegungsfoto.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Film-Stil-Wasserzeichen">
             <feature>• Die Kamera enthält Film-Stil-Wasserzeichen. Probieren Sie es aus. Gehen Sie zu: Kamera > Einstellungen > Wasserzeichen > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerie">
             <feature>• Die Funktion Bereinigungsvorschläge ermöglicht die automatische Identifizierung doppelter Fotos, ähnlicher Bilder und übergroßer Videos und stellt praktischere Bereinigungsvorschläge bereit</feature>
             <feature>• Mit KI-Ausschnitt können Sie das Motiv extrahieren, an eine neue Position im Bild verschieben und den Hintergrund ändern. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Fotos > KI-Bearbeitung > Magisches Retuschieren > KI-Ausschnitt</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Nach langem Drücken des Textes auf dem Bildschirm enthält die Pop-up-Symbolleiste jetzt die Funktion Übersetzung</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bedienungshilfen">
             <feature>• Drücken Sie zweimal die Ein-/Aus-Taste oder, wenn der Bildschirm ausgeschaltet ist, zweimal die Leiser-Taste drücken, um eine bestimmte App zu öffnen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• Die Funktion Zugangskarte unterstützt die Simulation unverschlüsselter Zugangskarten</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet enthält die Funktion Blankokarte. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Honor Wallet > Zugangskarte.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sicherheitspatch">
             <feature>• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Nov. 2025) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die Honor Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notizen" type="end">
             <feature>1. Die Installation dieses Updates hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, es wird jedoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen
2. Entdecken Sie weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen in Tipps
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Honor-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein Honor-Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1031" name="de-ch">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung verbessert hauptsächlich die Systemleistung. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bewegungsfoto">
             <feature>• Sie können jetzt ein Bewegungsfoto als Sperrbildschirm festlegen. Probieren Sie es aus. Gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Startbildschirm und Stil > Sperrbildschirmstil > Bewegungsfoto.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Film-Stil-Wasserzeichen">
             <feature>• Die Kamera enthält Film-Stil-Wasserzeichen. Probieren Sie es aus. Gehen Sie zu: Kamera > Einstellungen > Wasserzeichen > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerie">
             <feature>• Die Funktion Bereinigungsvorschläge ermöglicht die automatische Identifizierung doppelter Fotos, ähnlicher Bilder und übergroßer Videos und stellt praktischere Bereinigungsvorschläge bereit</feature>
             <feature>• Mit KI-Ausschnitt können Sie das Motiv extrahieren, an eine neue Position im Bild verschieben und den Hintergrund ändern. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Fotos > KI-Bearbeitung > Magisches Retuschieren > KI-Ausschnitt</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Nach langem Drücken des Textes auf dem Bildschirm enthält die Pop-up-Symbolleiste jetzt die Funktion Übersetzung</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bedienungshilfen">
             <feature>• Drücken Sie zweimal die Ein-/Aus-Taste oder, wenn der Bildschirm ausgeschaltet ist, zweimal die Leiser-Taste drücken, um eine bestimmte App zu öffnen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• Die Funktion Zugangskarte unterstützt die Simulation unverschlüsselter Zugangskarten</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet enthält die Funktion Blankokarte. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Honor Wallet > Zugangskarte.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sicherheitspatch">
             <feature>• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Nov. 2025) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die Honor Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notizen" type="end">
             <feature>1. Die Installation dieses Updates hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, es wird jedoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen
2. Entdecken Sie weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen in Tipps
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Honor-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein Honor-Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1036" name="fr-ch">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour améliore principalement les performances du système. Effectuez la mise à jour pour profiter des améliorations</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Photo dynamique">
             <feature>• Vous pouvez désormais définir une photo dynamique en tant qu'écran verrouillé. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Écran d'accueil et style > Style d'écran verrouillé > Photo dynamique.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Filigrane de style film">
             <feature>• Appareil photo comprend des filigranes de style film. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Appareil photo > Paramètres > Filigrane > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerie">
             <feature>• La fonctionnalité Suggestions de nettoyage permet l'identification automatique des photos en double, des images similaires et des vidéos surdimensionnées, proposant ainsi des suggestions de nettoyage plus pratiques</feature>
             <feature>• Découpe IA vous permet d'extraire le sujet, de le déplacer dans une nouvelle position dans l'image et de modifier l'arrière-plan. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Photos > Modification par IA > Retouche magique > Découpe IA</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Après un appui long sur le texte à l'écran, la barre d'outils contextuelle inclut désormais la fonctionnalité Traduire</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fonctionnalités d'accessibilité">
             <feature>• Appuyez deux fois sur le bouton d'alimentation ou, lorsque l'écran est éteint, appuyez deux fois sur le bouton du volume bas pour ouvrir une application spécifiée</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• La fonction Carte d'accès prend en charge la simulation de cartes d'accès non cryptées</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet comprend la fonctionnalité Carte vierge. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Honor Wallet > Carte d'accès.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Correctif de sécurité">
             <feature>• Un correctif de sécurité Android (novembre 2025) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité Honor, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour
2. Découvrez plus d'informations sur les fonctionnalités du produit dans Astuces
3. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes pendant la mise à jour, vous pouvez obtenir de l'aide en contactant la hotline de service Honor ou en vous rendant dans un centre de services clients Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1040" name="it-ch">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento migliora principalmente le prestazioni del sistema. Esegui l'aggiornamento per usufruire dei miglioramenti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Foto in movimento">
             <feature>• Ora è possibile impostare una foto in movimento come schermata di blocco. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Schermata Home e stile > Stile blocco schermo > Foto in movimento.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Filigrana in stile pellicola">
             <feature>• La Fotocamera include filigrane in stile pellicola. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Fotocamera > Impostazioni > Filigrana > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galleria">
             <feature>• La funzione Suggerimenti per la pulizia consente l'identificazione automatica di foto duplicate, immagini simili e video di grandi dimensioni, facilitando la pulizia dello spazio sul dispositivo</feature>
             <feature>• Ritaglio AI consente di estrarre il soggetto, spostarlo in una nuova posizione nell'immagine e modificare lo sfondo. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Foto > Modifica AI > Ritocco magico > Ritaglio AI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Quando si preme a lungo il testo sullo schermo, la barra degli strumenti popup ora include la funzione Traduci</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funzioni accessibilità">
             <feature>• È possibile premere due volte il tasto di accensione o, quando lo schermo è spento, premere due volte il tasto di riduzione del volume per aprire un'app specifica.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• La funzione delle carte di accesso supporta la simulazione delle carte di accesso non crittografate</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Wallet include la funzione Carta vuota. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Honor Wallet > Carta di accesso.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch di sicurezza">
             <feature>• È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (novembre 2025) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza Honor, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Note" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup dei dati prima di procedere
2. Scopri ulteriori informazioni sulle funzioni del prodotto in Suggerimenti
3. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center Honor o visitando un centro servizio clienti Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2074" name="sr-ba">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se unapređuju performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u unapređenjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pokretna fotografija">
             <feature>• Sada možete da postavite pokretnu fotografiju kao zaključani ekran. Isprobajte odlaskom u opciju: Podešavanja > Početni ekran i stil > Stil zaključanog ekrana > Pokretna fotografija.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vodeni žig u filmskom stilu">
             <feature>• Kamera uključuje vodene žigove u filmskom stilu. Isprobajte ih odlaskom u opciju: Kamera > Podešavanja > Vodeni žig > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerija">
             <feature>• Funkcija Predlozi za brisanje omogućava automatsko prepoznavanje duplih slika, sličnih slika i prevelikih video zapisa te pruža praktičnije predloge za brisanje</feature>
             <feature>• Isecanje pomoću VI omogućava da izdvojite subjekt, premestite ga na novu poziciju na slici i promenite pozadinu. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići na: Fotografije > AI uređivanje > Čarobno retuširanje > Isecanje pomoću VI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Nakon dugog pritiska na tekst na ekranu, iskačuća alatna traka sada uključuje funkciju Prevedi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkcije pristupačnosti">
             <feature>• Dvaput pritisnite dugme za uključivanje/isključivanje ili, kada je ekran isključen, dvaput pritisnite dugme za smanjenje jačine zvuka da otvorite određenu aplikaciju</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Novčanik">
             <feature>• Funkcija Kartica za pristup podržava simulaciju nešifriranih kartica za pristup</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Novčanik uključuje funkciju Blanko kartice. Isprobajte je odlaskom u opciju: Podešavanja > Honor Novčanik > Kartica za pristup.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezbednosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Android bezbednosna zakrpa (novembar 2025.) je integrisana radi bezbednosti sistema. Za još informacija o Honor bezbednosnim ažuriranjima, posetite naš veb-sajt https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zabeleške" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka pre ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o karakteristikama proizvoda u odeljku Saveti
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete dobiti našu pomoć pozivom dežurne linije kompanije Honor ili posetom centru za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2074" name="sr-me">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se unapređuju performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u unapređenjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pokretna fotografija">
             <feature>• Sada možete da postavite pokretnu fotografiju kao zaključani ekran. Isprobajte odlaskom u opciju: Podešavanja > Početni ekran i stil > Stil zaključanog ekrana > Pokretna fotografija.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vodeni žig u filmskom stilu">
             <feature>• Kamera uključuje vodene žigove u filmskom stilu. Isprobajte ih odlaskom u opciju: Kamera > Podešavanja > Vodeni žig > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galerija">
             <feature>• Funkcija Predlozi za brisanje omogućava automatsko prepoznavanje duplih slika, sličnih slika i prevelikih video zapisa te pruža praktičnije predloge za brisanje</feature>
             <feature>• Isecanje pomoću VI omogućava da izdvojite subjekt, premestite ga na novu poziciju na slici i promenite pozadinu. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići na: Fotografije > AI uređivanje > Čarobno retuširanje > Isecanje pomoću VI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Nakon dugog pritiska na tekst na ekranu, iskačuća alatna traka sada uključuje funkciju Prevedi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Funkcije pristupačnosti">
             <feature>• Dvaput pritisnite dugme za uključivanje/isključivanje ili, kada je ekran isključen, dvaput pritisnite dugme za smanjenje jačine zvuka da otvorite određenu aplikaciju</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Novčanik">
             <feature>• Funkcija Kartica za pristup podržava simulaciju nešifriranih kartica za pristup</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Novčanik uključuje funkciju Blanko kartice. Isprobajte je odlaskom u opciju: Podešavanja > Honor Novčanik > Kartica za pristup.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezbednosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Android bezbednosna zakrpa (novembar 2025.) je integrisana radi bezbednosti sistema. Za još informacija o Honor bezbednosnim ažuriranjima, posetite naš veb-sajt https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zabeleške" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka pre ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o karakteristikama proizvoda u odeljku Saveti
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete dobiti našu pomoć pozivom dežurne linije kompanije Honor ili posetom centru za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1057" name="id-">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini utamanya meningkatkan kinerja sistem. Instal pembaruan untuk menikmati berbagai peningkatan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Foto Bergerak">
             <feature>• Anda kini dapat mengatur foto bergerak sebagai layar kunci. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Gaya &amp; layar beranda > Gaya kunci layar > Foto bergerak.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tanda air bergaya film">
             <feature>• Kamera menyertakan tanda air bergaya film. Cobalah dengan membuka: Kamera > Pengaturan > Tanda air > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Galeri">
             <feature>• Fitur Saran pembersihan memungkinkan identifikasi foto duplikat, gambar serupa, dan video yang terlalu besar secara otomatis, sehingga menyediakan saran pembersihan yang memudahkan</feature>
             <feature>• Potongan AI memungkinkan Anda untuk mengekstrak subjek, memindah posisinya pada gambar, dan mengubah latar belakang. Cobalah dengan membuka: Foto > Edit AI > Perapi Ajaib > Potongan AI</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lensa">
             <feature>• Setelah menekan lama pada teks di layar, bilah alat sembul kini menyertakan fitur Terjemahan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fitur aksesibilitas">
             <feature>• Tekan dua kali tombol Daya atau, ketika layar mati, tekan dua kali tombol Perkecil volume untuk membuka aplikasi tertentu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Dompet">
             <feature>• Fitur Kartu akses mendukung simulasi kartu akses tanpa enkripsi</feature>
             <feature>• Honor Dompet menyertakan fitur Kartu kosong. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Honor Dompet > Kartu akses.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Penambal keamanan">
             <feature>• Penambal Keamanan Android (Nov 2025) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan Honor, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Catatan" type="end">
             <feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan untuk mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui
2. Pelajari informasi selengkapnya terkait fitur produk di Kiat
3. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan Honor atau mengunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1037" name="he-">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה משפר בעיקר את ביצועי המערכת. עדכן כדי ליהנות מהשיפורים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="תמונה נעה">
             <feature>‏• כעת אפשר להגדיר תמונה נעה בתור מסך הנעילה. כדי לנסות, אפשר לעבור אל: 'הגדרות' > 'מסך הבית וסגנון' > 'סגנון מסך נעילה' > 'תמונה נעה'.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="סימן מים בסגנון סרט">
             <feature>‏• 'מצלמה' כוללת סימני מים בסגנון סרט צילום. כדי לנסות, אפשר לעבור אל: 'מצלמה' > 'הגדרות' > 'סימן מים' > 'סרט'.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="גלריה">
             <feature>‏• תכונת 'הצעות ניקוי' מפעילה זיהוי אוטומטי של תמונות כפולות, תמונות דומות וסרטונים גדולים מדי, ומספקת הצעות ניקוי נוחות יותר</feature>
             <feature>‏• 'תגזירים AI' מאפשר לך לחלץ את הנושא, להזיז אותו למיקום חדש בתמונה ולשנות את הרקע. כדי לנסות, אפשר לעבור אל: 'תמונות' > 'עריכת AI' > 'תיקון קסם' > 'תגזירים AI'</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏Honor Lens">
             <feature>‏• סרגל הכלים המוקפץ כולל כעת את התכונה 'תרגום', שתופיע אחרי לחיצה ארוכה על טקסט במסך</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="תכונות נגישות">
             <feature>‏• לחץ פעמיים על לחצן ההפעלה, או כשהמסך כבוי, לחץ פעמיים על לחצן החלשת עוצמת הקול כדי לפתוח יישום מסוים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏Honor Wallet">
             <feature>‏‏• תכונת כרטיסי הגישה תומכת בהדמיה של כרטיסי גישה לא מוצפנים</feature>
             <feature>‏• ‏‏Honor Wallet כולל את התכונה 'כרטיס ריק'. כדי לנסות, אפשר לעבור אל: 'הגדרות' > ‏‏Honor Wallet > 'כרטיס גישה'.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="תיקון אבטחה">
             <feature>‏• 'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מנוב' 2025) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של Honor', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="הערות" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון
‏2. גלה מידע נוסף על תכונות המוצר ב'טיפים'
‏3. אם תיתקל בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, ניתן לקבל עזרה מאיתנו באמצעות התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של Honor או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1124" name="fil-ph">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Minamahal na user, pangunahing pinapahusay ng update na ito ang performance ng system. I-update para i-enjoy ang mga pagpapahusay</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Gumagalaw na Larawan">
             <feature>• Puwede ka nang magtakda ng gumagalaw na larawan bilang lock screen. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Home screen at estilo > Estilo ng lock ng screen > Gumagalaw na larawan.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Watermark na estilong film">
             <feature>• May mga watermark na estilong film ang Camera. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Camera > Mga Setting > Watermark > FILM.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Gallery">
             <feature>• Nagbibigay-daan ang feature na Mga suhestyon sa pag-clean up sa awtomatikong pagtukoy ng mga duplicate na larawan, katulad na larawan, at video na labis ang laki, na nagbibigay ng mga mas magandang suhestyon sa pag-clean up</feature>
             <feature>• Nagbibigay-daan sa iyo ang AI Cutout na i-extract ang subject, dalhin ito sa bagong posisyon sa larawan, at baguhin ang background. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Larawan > AI Edit > Magic Retouch > AI Cutout</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Lens">
             <feature>• Pagkatapos pindutin nang matagal ang text sa screen, mayroon nang feature na Isalin ang pop-up na toolbar</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Mga feature ng accessibility">
             <feature>• Pindutin nang dalawang beses ang Power button o, kapag naka-off ang screen, pindutin nang dalawang beses ang button na Pagpapahina ng volume para magbukas ng tinukoy na app</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Wallet">
             <feature>• Sinusuportahan ng feature na access card ang simulation ng mga hindi naka-encrypt na access card</feature>
             <feature>• Kasama sa Honor Wallet ang feature na Blangkong card. Subukan ang mga ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Honor Wallet > Access card.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Panseguridad na patch">
             <feature>• Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Nob 2025) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa mga Panseguridad na update ng Honor, bisitahin ang aming website sa https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Mga Tala" type="end">
             <feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto ang pag-install sa update na ito sa iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update
2. Tuklasin ang higit pang impormasyon sa mga feature ng produkto sa Mga Tip
3. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, makukuha mo ang tulong namin sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng Honor o pagbisita sa customer service center ng Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <imgs>
            </imgs>
</root>