<root>
    <component name="TCPU" version="请自行修改"></component>
    <default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
    <language code="2052" name="zh-cn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新主要针对系统进行了优化，推荐您进行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="系统">
             <feature>•  新增 Wi-Fi 断开连接、密码显示功能</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="锁屏">
             <feature>•  新增锁屏长时钟。体验路径：设置 > 桌面和个性化 > 自定义 > 点击时钟即可</feature>
             <feature>•  新增视频壁纸，支持最长 10 秒动态效果</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="荣耀互联">
             <feature>•  新增支持荣耀手机与 iPhone 互相共享通知消息</feature>
             <feature>•  新增荣耀手机和 Mac 通知共享功能，Mac 安装最新版“荣耀超级工作台”应用，即可同步消息</feature>
             <feature>•  新增荣耀与 Mac 一碰传功能，Mac 安装最新版“荣耀超级工作台”应用，即可用荣耀手机一碰传图片、视频、文件等内容</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="功耗">
             <feature>•  优化部分场景续航体验</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="稳定性">
             <feature>•  提升系统稳定性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安全补丁">
             <feature>•  合入安卓 2026 年 1 月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="更新注意事项" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份
2. 更多精彩功能介绍，请访问“玩机技巧”应用
3. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="en-us">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Dear user, this update mainly enhances the system performance. Update to enjoy the improvements</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="System">
             <feature>• Supports disconnecting from Wi-Fi and viewing the password</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Lock screen">
             <feature>• The lock screen offers a bigger and stretched clock style. Try it out by going to: Settings > Home screen &amp; style > Custom > Tap the clock to edit</feature>
             <feature>• You can now use videos as the wallpaper, with dynamic effects that play for up to 10 seconds</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor phones and iPhones can now share notification messages with each other</feature>
             <feature>• With the latest HONOR WorkStation installed on your Mac, Connected Notifications allows you to sync notifications to your Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Install the latest version of the HONOR WorkStation on your Mac, then you can use OneTap to transfer images, videos, files, and other content from your Honor phone to your Mac with a single tap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Power consumption">
             <feature>• Optimizes the user experience with battery life in some scenarios</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stability">
             <feature>• Improves the system stability</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Security patch">
             <feature>• Android security patch (Jan 2026) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about Honor Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating
2. Discover more information on product features in Tips
3. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling Honor service hotline or visiting Honor customer service center</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1118" name="am-ET">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ ይህ ዝማኔ በዋነኛነት የስርዓቱን አፈጻጸም ያሻሽላል። በማሻሻያዎቹ ለመደሰት ያዘምኑ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ስርዓት">
             <feature>• ከWi-Fi ጋር ግንኙነት ማቋረጥን እና የይለፍ ቃሉን ማየትን ይደግፋል</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ማያን መቆለፊያ">
             <feature>• የማያ መቆለፊያው የተለቀ እና የተወጠረ የሰዓት ቅጥን ያቀርባል። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > መነሻ ማያ ገጽ እና ቅጥ > ብጁ > ለማርትዕ ሰዓቱን መታ ያድርጉት</feature>
             <feature>• አሁን እስከ 10 ሰከንድ የሚቆይ ተለዋዋጭ ውጤት ባላቸው ቪዲዮዎች እንደ ልጣፍ መጠቀም ይችላሉ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ግንኙነት">
             <feature>• አሁን የHonor ስልኮች እና iPhones የማሳወቂያ መልዕክቶችን እርስ በእርስ መጋራት ይችላሉ</feature>
             <feature>• የቅርብ ጊዜው የHONOR WorkStation በእርስዎ Mac ላይ ሲጫን፣ የተገናኙ ማሳወቂያዎችን ወደ እርስዎ Mac እንዲያቀናጁ ያስችልዎታል</feature>
             <feature>• የቅርብ ጊዜውን የHONOR WorkStation ስሪት በእርስዎ Mac ላይ ይጫኑ፣ ከዚያም ምስሎችን፣ ቪዲዮዎችን፣ ፋይሎችን እና ሌላ ይዘትን ከአ Honor ስልክዎ ወደ ማክዎ በአንድ መታ በማድረግ ለማስተላለፍ OneTap መጠቀም ይችላሉ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="የኃይል ፍጆታ">
             <feature>• በአንዳንድ ሁኔታዎች የባትሪ ዕድሜን በመጠቀም የተጠቃሚውን ተሞክሮ ያሻሽላል</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="መረጋጋት">
             <feature>• የስርዓቱን እርጋታ ያሻሽላል</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="የደህንነት መጠገኛ">
             <feature>• ለስርዓት ደህንነት የአንድሮይድ ደህንነት መጠገኛን (ጃንዋሪ 2026) ተካቷል። ስለHonor ደህንነት ዝማኔዎች ተጨማሪ መረጃ ለማግኘት እባክዎ የእኛን ድር ጣቢያ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1 ይጎብኙ</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ማስታወሻዎች" type="end">
             <feature>1. ይህን ዝማኔ መጫን በእርስዎ የግል ውሂብ ላይ ተጽዕኖ አያሳርፍም፣ ነገር ግን አሁንም ከማዘመንዎ በፊት የውሂብዎን መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ ይመከራል
2. በጠቃሚ ምክሮች ውስጥ ስለምርት ባህሪያት ተጨማሪ መረጃ ያግኙ
3. በዝማኔው ጊዜ ማናቸውም ችግሮች ካጋጠሙዎት ወደ የHonor አገልግሎት ቀጥታ መስመር በመደወል ወይም የHonor ደንበኛ አገልግሎት ማዕከልን በመጎብኘት የእኛን እርዳታ ማግኘት ይችላሉ</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="3073" name="ar-eg">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، يحسّن هذا التحديث أداء النظام بشكل أساسي. للاستمتاع بالتحسينات، ما عليك سوى التحديث</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="النظام">
             <feature>• تدعم هذه الميزة قطع الاتصال بشبكة Wi-Fi وعرض كلمة المرور</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="شاشة القفل">
             <feature>• تقدم شاشة القفل نمط ساعة أكبر وأطول. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > الشاشة الرئيسية والنمط > مخصص > اضغط على الساعة للتعديل</feature>
             <feature>• يمكنك الآن استخدام مقاطع الفيديو كخلفية، مع تأثيرات ديناميكية تعمل لمدة تصل إلى 10 ثوانٍ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="الاتصال من Honor">
             <feature>• بإمكان هواتف Honor وiPhone الآن تبادل رسائل الإشعارات فيما بينها</feature>
             <feature>• مع تثبيت الإصدار الأحدث من محطة العمل من HONOR على جهاز Mac، تسمح لك الإشعارات المتصلة بمزامنة الإشعارات مع جهاز Mac</feature>
             <feature>• قم بتثبيت الإصدار الأحدث من محطة العمل من HONOR على جهاز Mac. بعد ذلك، يمكنك استخدام ميزة ضغطة واحدة لنقل الصور ومقاطع الفيديو والملفات والمحتويات الأخرى من هاتف Honor إلى جهاز Mac بضغطة واحدة</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="استهلاك الطاقة">
             <feature>• يُحسّن تجربة المستخدم فيما يتعلق بعمر البطارية في بعض الحالات</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="الاستقرار">
             <feature>• يحسّن استقرار النظام</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="تصحيح الأمان">
             <feature>• تم تضمين تصحيح أمان أندرويد (يناير 2026) لأمان النظام. لمزيد من المعلومات حول تحديثات الأمان في Honor، يرجى زيارة موقعنا على الويب https://www.honor.com/ae-ar/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ملاحظات" type="end">
             <feature>1. لن يؤثر تثبيت هذا التحديث على بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن لا يزال من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية لبياناتك قبل التحديث
2. اكتشف المزيد من المعلومات حول ميزات المنتج في تطبيق التلميحات
3. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيمكنك الحصول على مساعدتنا عن طريق الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة عملاء Honor أو زيارة مركز خدمة عملاء Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1101" name="as-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই আপডেটটোৱে মূলতঃ ছিষ্টেমৰ কাৰ্যদক্ষতা উন্নত কৰে। উন্নতিসমূহৰ আনন্দ ল'বলৈ আপডেট কৰক</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ছিষ্টেম">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi-ৰ পৰা সংযোগ বিচ্ছিন্ন কৰা আৰু পাছৱৰ্ডটো চোৱা সমৰ্থন কৰে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="লক স্ক্ৰীণ">
             <feature>• লক স্ক্ৰীণে এটা ডাঙৰ আৰু বহল ঘড়ীৰ ষ্টাইল প্ৰদান কৰে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ এইটো ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ছেটিংছ > হোম স্ক্ৰীণ আৰু শৈলী > কাষ্টম > সম্পাদনা কৰিবলৈ ঘড়ীটো টিপক</feature>
             <feature>• আপুনি এতিয়া 10 ছেকেণ্ডলৈকে চলা গতিশীল প্ৰভাৱ থকা ভিডিঅ'সমূহক ৱালপেপাৰ হিচাপে ব্যৱহাৰ কৰিব পাৰে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor সংযোগ">
             <feature>• Honor ফোন আৰু iPhone-এ এতিয়া ইটোৱে সিটোৰ লগত অধিসূচনা বাৰ্তাসমূহ ভাগ-বতৰা কৰিব পাৰে</feature>
             <feature>• আপোনাৰ Mac-ত শেহতীয়া HONOR WorkStation ইনষ্টল কৰি সংযোজিত অধিসূচনাসমূহে আপোনাক আপোনাৰ Mac-ত অধিসূচনাসমূহ ছিংক কৰিবলৈ অনুমতি দিয়ে</feature>
             <feature>• আপোনাৰ Mac-ত HONOR WorkStation-ৰ শেহতীয়া সংস্কৰণটো ইনষ্টল কৰক, তাৰপিছত আপুনি এবাৰ টিপি আপোনাৰ Honor ফোনৰ পৰা আপোনাৰ Mac-ত প্ৰতিচ্ছবিসমূহ, ভিডিঅ'সমূহ, ফাইলসমূহ আৰু অন্য সমল স্থানান্তৰ কৰিবলৈ OneTap ব্যৱহাৰ কৰিব পাৰে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="পাৱাৰ খৰচ">
             <feature>• কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত বেটাৰীৰ জীৱন কালৰ সৈতে থকা অভিজ্ঞতা অনুকূলন কৰে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="স্থিৰতা">
             <feature>• ছিষ্টেমৰ স্থিৰতা উন্নত কৰে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ">
             <feature>• ছিষ্টেমৰ নিৰাপত্তাৰ বাবে Android নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ (জানুৱাৰী 2026) অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হৈছে। Honor নিৰাপত্তা আপডেটৰ বিষয়ে অধিক তথ্যৰ বাবে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি আমাৰ ৱেবছাইট দৰ্শন কৰক: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="টোকাসমূহ" type="end">
             <feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটাত প্ৰভাৱ নপৰিব, কিন্তু আপডেট কৰাৰ পূৰ্বে আপোনাৰ ডাটাৰ বেক আপ ল'বলৈ এতিয়াও পৰামৰ্শ দিয়া হয়
2. আভাসত প্ৰ'ডাক্টৰ ফিচাৰসমূহৰ ওপৰত অধিক তথ্য অনুসন্ধান কৰক
3. আপুনি আপডেটৰ সময়ত কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হ'লে, আপুনি Honor সেৱা হটলাইনত কল কৰি বা Honor গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ গৈ সহায় লাভ কৰিব পাৰে</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1068" name="az-az">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, bu yeniləmə əsasən sistemin performansını artırır. Təkmilləşdirmələrdən yararlanmaq üçün yeniləyin</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistem">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi ilə bağlantının kəsilməsini və parola baxmağı dəstəkləyir</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kilid ekranı">
             <feature>• Kilid ekranı daha böyük və uzadılmış saat üslubu təklif edir. Buraya keçərək sınaqdan keçirin: Parametrlər > Əsas ekran və üslub > Fərdi > Redaktə etmək üçün saata toxunun</feature>
             <feature>• Artıq 10 saniyəyə qədər göstərilən dinamik effektlərlə videoları divar kağızı kimi istifadə edə bilərsiniz</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor telefonları və iPhone-lar artıq bildiriş mesajlarını bir-biri ilə paylaşa bilər</feature>
             <feature>• Mac-də ən son HONOR WorkStation quraşdırıldığı üçün Qoşulmuş Bildirişlər sizə bildirişləri Mac-ə sinxronlaşdırmaq imkanı verir</feature>
             <feature>• HONOR WorkStation-ın ən son versiyasını Mac-də quraşdırın, sonra OneTap-dan istifadə edərək şəkilləri, videoları, faylları və digər məzmunu Honor telefonunuzdan Mac-ə tək toxunuşla ötürə bilərsiniz</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Enerji sərfiyyatı">
             <feature>• Bəzi hallarda batareya ömrü ilə bağlı istifadəçi təcrübəsini optimallaşdırır</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabillik">
             <feature>• Sistemin sabitliyini yaxşılaşdırır</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Təhlükəsizlik paketi">
             <feature>• Sistem təhlükəsizliyi üçün Android təhlükəsizlik paketi (yanvar 2026-cı il) daxil edilib. Honor Təhlükəsizlik yeniləmələri haqqında daha çox məlumat üçün veb-saytımıza daxil olun: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Qeydlər" type="end">
             <feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınıza təsir etməyəcək, lakin yenə də yeniləməmişdən əvvəl verilənlərin ehtiyat nüsxəsini çıxarmaq tövsiyə olunur
2. İpuclarında məhsul xüsusiyyətləri haqqında daha çox məlumat əldə edin
3. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlə qarşılaşsanız, Honor xidmət qaynar xəttinə zəng etməklə və ya Honor müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə yaxınlaşaraq yardım ala bilərsiniz</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="jv-id">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran iki utamane ningkatake kinerja sistem. Anyarake kanggo ngrasakake pangapikane</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistem">
             <feature>• Ndhukung medhot sambungan saka Wi-Fi lan ndeleng sandhi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Layar kunci">
             <feature>• Layar kunci menehi gaya jam sing luwih gedhe lan mulur. Coba kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Layar ngarep &amp; gaya > Kustom > Tutul jam kanggo ngedit</feature>
             <feature>• Sampeyan saiki bisa nggunakake video minangka wallpaper, kanthi efek dhinamis sing muter nganti 10 detik</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Ponsel Honor lan iPhone saiki bisa padha-padha mbage notifikasi</feature>
             <feature>• Kanthi HONOR WorkStation paling anyar diinstal ing Mac, Notifikasi Kasambung nggawe sampeyan bisa nyinkronake notifikasi karo Mac sampeyan</feature>
             <feature>• Instal versi paling anyar HONOR WorkStation ing Mac, banjur sampeyan bisa nggunakake OneTap kanggo nransfer gambar, video, file, lan konten liyane saka ponsel Honor menyang Mac sampeyan kanthi sak tutulan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Panggunaan daya">
             <feature>• Ngoptimalake pangalaman pangguna kanthi durasi baterei ing sawetara skenario</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitas">
             <feature>• Ngapikake stabilitas sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch keamanan">
             <feature>• Patch keamanan Android (Jan 2026) wis digabungake kanggo keamanan sistem. Informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan panganyaran Keamanan Honor bisa dideleng ing situs web kita https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Cathetan" type="end">
             <feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mengaruhi data pribadi sampeyan, nanging nggawe serep data dhisik tetep disaranake sadurunge nganyarake
2. Temokake informasi liyane babagan fitur prodhuk ing Tips
3. Yen ana masalah sajrone panganyaran, sampeyan bisa entuk bantuan kita kanthi nelpon hotline layanan Honor utawa nekani pusat layanan pelanggan Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2074" name="sr-rs">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se unapređuju performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u unapređenjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistem">
             <feature>• Podržava isključivanje sa Wi-Fi mreže i pregled lozinke</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zaključani ekran">
             <feature>• Zaključani ekran nudi veći i rastegnuti stil sata. Isprobajte ga tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Početni ekran i stil > Prilagođeno > Dodirnite sat da biste uredili</feature>
             <feature>• Sada možete da koristite video-zapise kao pozadinu, uz dinamičke efekte koji se reprodukuju do 10 sekundi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Povezivanje">
             <feature>• Honor telefoni i iPhone uređaji sada mogu da dele poruke obaveštenja jedni sa drugima</feature>
             <feature>• Uz najnoviji HONOR WorkStation instaliran na vašem Mac-u, Povezana obaveštenja vam omogućavaju da sinhronizujete obaveštenja sa vašim Mac-om</feature>
             <feature>• Instalirajte najnoviju verziju HONOR WorkStation na Mac, a zatim možete koristiti OneTap za prenos slika, video-zapisa, datoteka i drugog sadržaja sa vašeg Honor telefona na Mac jednim dodirom</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Potrošnja energije">
             <feature>• Optimizuje korisničko iskustvo sa trajanjem baterije u nekim scenarijima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Poboljšava stabilnost sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezbednosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (januar 2026.) je ugrađena zbog bezbednosti sistema. Više informacija o Honor Security ažuriranjima potražite na našem veb-sajtu https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zabeleške" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka pre ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o karakteristikama proizvoda u odeljku Saveti
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete dobiti našu pomoć pozivom dežurne linije kompanije Honor ili posetom centru za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1059" name="be-by">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта абнаўленне ў асноўным паляпшае прадукцыйнасць сістэмы. Каб палепшыць уражанні ад выкарыстання, устанавіце абнаўленне</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Сістэма">
             <feature>• Падтрымлівае адключэнне ад Wi-Fi і прагляд пароля</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Экран блакіроўкі">
             <feature>• Экран блакіроўкі прапануе большы і расцягнуты стыль гадзінніка. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Галоўны экран і стыль > Карыстальніцкае > краніце гадзіннік для рэдагавання»</feature>
             <feature>• Цяпер вы можаце выкарыстоўваць відэа ў якасці шпалер, а дынамічныя эфекты будуць прайгравацца да 10 секунд</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Тэлефоны Honor і iPhone могуць абменьвацца апавяшчэннямі паміж сабой</feature>
             <feature>• Калі ўстанавіць апошнюю версію HONOR WorkStation на Mac, сэрвіс «Падключаныя апавяшчэнні» дазваляюць сінхранізаваць апавяшчэнні з Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Устанавіце апошнюю версію HONOR WorkStation на Mac, пасля чаго вы зможаце выкарыстоўваць OneTap, каб адным дотыкам пераносіць выявы, відэа, файлы і іншае змесціва з тэлефона Honor на Mac</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Энергаспажыванне">
             <feature>• Аптымізуе час работы прылады ад акумулятары ў пэўных сцэнарыях</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Устойлівасць">
             <feature>• Павышана стабільнасць сістэмы</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Выпраўленне сістэмы бяспекі">
             <feature>• Для павышэння бяспекі сістэмы ўключана выпраўленне функцый бяспекі Android (студзень 2026 г.). Больш інфармацыі пра абнаўленне сістэмы бяспекі Honor можна знайсці на нашым вэб-сайце: https://www.honor.com/by/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Нататкі" type="end">
             <feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не закране вашы асабістыя даныя. Тым не менш рэкамендуецца стварыць рэзервовую копію даных перад абнаўленнем
2. Больш падрабязная інфармацыя аб характарыстыках прадукту даступная ў Падказках
3. Калі вы сутыкняцеся з праблемамі падчас абнаўлення, вы можаце атрымаць нашу дапамогу, патэлефанаваўшы на гарачую лінію службы падтрымкі кліентаў Honor або наведаўшы цэнтр абслугоўвання кліентаў Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1026" name="bg-bg">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Уважаеми потребители, тази актуализация подобрява основно ефективността на системата. Актуализирайте, за да се насладите на подобренията</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Система">
             <feature>• Поддържа прекъсване на връзката към Wi-Fi и преглед на паролата</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Заключен екран">
             <feature>• Заключеният екран предлага по-голям и разтегнат стил на часовник. Изпробвайте, като отидете на: „Настройки > Стил и начален екран > Индивидуално“ > Докоснете часовника, за да редактирате</feature>
             <feature>• Вече можете да използвате видеа като тапет с динамични ефекти, които се възпроизвеждат за до 10 секунди</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Телефоните на Honor и телефоните iPhone вече могат да споделят известия помежду си</feature>
             <feature>• С най-новата версия на HONOR WorkStation, инсталирана на вашия Mac, опцията „Свързани известия“ позволява да синхронизирате известията с вашия Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Инсталирайте най-новата версия на HONOR WorkStation на вашия Mac, след което можете да използвате OneTap, за да прехвърляте изображения, видеа, файлове и друго съдържание от вашия телефон Honor към вашия Mac с едно докосване</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Консумация на енергия">
             <feature>• Оптимизира потребителското изживяване с живота на батерията в някои сценарии</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Стабилност">
             <feature>• Подобрява стабилността на системата</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Корекция за сигурност">
             <feature>• Включена е корекция за сигурност на Android (януари 2026 г.) за сигурност на системата. За повече информация относно актуализациите за сигурност на Honor, моля, посетете нашия уебсайт https://www.honor.com/bg/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Бележки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да се отрази на вашите лични данни, но все пак е препоръчително да архивирате данните си преди актуализиране
2. Открийте повече информация за характеристиките на продукта в „Съвети“
3. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализацията, можете да получите нашата помощ, като се обадите на горещата линия за обслужване на Honor или посетите сервизен център на клиенти на Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2117" name="bn-bd">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই আপডেটটি মূলত সিস্টেমের কর্মক্ষমতা বাড়ায়। উন্নতি উপভোগ করতে আপডেট করুন</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="সিস্টেম">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi থেকে সংযোগ বিচ্ছিন্ন করা এবং পাসওয়ার্ড দেখা সমর্থন করে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="লক স্ক্রিন">
             <feature>• লক স্ক্রিনটি আরও বড় এবং প্রসারিত ঘড়ির স্টাইল অফার করে। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > হোম স্ক্রিন এবং স্টাইল > কাস্টম > সম্পাদনা করতে ঘড়িতে ট্যাপ করুন</feature>
             <feature>• আপনি এখন ওয়ালপেপার হিসেবে ভিডিও ব্যবহার করতে পারেন, 10 সেকেন্ড পর্যন্ত চলা ডায়নামিক এফেক্ট সহ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor কানেক্ট">
             <feature>• Honor ফোন এবং iPhone এখন একে অপরের সাথে বিজ্ঞপ্তি বার্তা শেয়ার করতে পারে</feature>
             <feature>• আপনার Mac-এ ইনস্টল করা সর্বশেষ HONOR WorkStation-এর সাহায্যে, সংযুক্ত বিজ্ঞপ্তি আপনাকে আপনার Mac-এ বিজ্ঞপ্তিগুলি সিঙ্ক করতে দেয়</feature>
             <feature>• আপনার Mac-এ HONOR WorkStation-এর সর্বশেষ সংস্করণ ইনস্টল করুন, তারপর আপনি OneTap ব্যবহার করে আপনার Honor ফোন থেকে এক ট্যাপে আপনার Mac-এ ছবি, ভিডিও, ফাইল এবং অন্যান্য কন্টেন্ট স্থানান্তর করতে পারবেন</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="শক্তি খরচ">
             <feature>• কিছু পরিস্থিতিতে ব্যাটারির আয়ুষ্কালের মাধ্যমে ব্যবহারকারীর অভিজ্ঞতা অপ্টিমাইজ করে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="স্থিতিশীলতা">
             <feature>• সিস্টেমের স্থিতিশীলতা উন্নত করে</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ">
             <feature>• সিস্টেমের নিরাপত্তার জন্য Android নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ (জানুয়ারি 2026) যোগ করা হয়েছে। Honor-এর নিরাপত্তা আপডেটগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্যের জন্য, আমাদের ওয়েবসাইট https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1 দেখুন</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="নোট" type="end">
             <feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে তা আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটাকে প্রভাবিত করবে না, তবুও আপডেট করার আগে আপনার ডেটা ব্যাক আপ করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়
2. পরামর্শ-এ পণ্যের ফিচাতগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্য জানুন
3. আপডেট হওয়ার সময় আপনি কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে Honor সেবা হটলাইনে কল করে বা Honor গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে গিয়ে আমাদের সহায়তা পেতে পারেন</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1105" name="bo-cn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནི་གཙོ་བོ་རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ལ་དམིགས་ནས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུའི་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="རྒྱུད་ཁོངས།">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi སྦྲེལ་ལམ་གཅོད་པ། གསང་གྲངས་མངོན་སྟོན་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ཡོལ་ཟྭ།">
             <feature>• ཡོལ་ཟྭ་རིང་བོའི་ཆུ་ཚོད་གསར་སྣོན། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་ཅོག་ངོས་དང་སྒེར་གཤིས་ཅན། དེ་ནས་རང་སྒྲིག དེ་ནས་ཆུ་ཚོད་ལ་རྡེབ་པས་ཆོག</feature>
             <feature>• བརྙན་ཟློས་ཀྱི་ལྡེབ་ཤོག་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཆེས་རིང་ན་སྐར་ཆ་10 ཡི་འགུལ་རྣམ་ཁྱད་ནུས་ལ་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉམ་སྦྲེལ།">
             <feature>• རུང་ཡོའོ་ལག་ཁྱེར་ཁ་པར་དང་ iPhone བར་བརྡ་ཐོ་བརྡ་འཕྲིན་མཉམ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རེས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
             <feature>• རུང་ཡོའོ་ལག་ཁྱེར་ཁ་པར་དང་ Mac བར་བརྡ་ཐོ་མཉམ་སྤྱོད་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། Mac ལ་རུང་ཡོའོ་རིམ་འདས་ལས་སྟེགས་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་པར་གཞི་གསར་བ་སྒྲིག་འཇུག་བྱས་ན་བརྡ་འཕྲིན་གོམ་མཉམ་བྱ་ཆོག</feature>
             <feature>• རུང་ཡོའོ་དང་ Mac ཐུག་ཙམ་གྱིས་སྐུར་བའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། Mac ལ་རུང་ཡོའོ་རིམ་འདས་ལས་སྟེགས་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་པར་གཞི་གསར་བ་སྒྲིག་འཇུག་བྱས་ན། རུང་ཡོའོ་ལག་ཁྱེར་ཁ་པར་བེད་སྤྱད་ནས་པར་རིས་དང་བརྙན་ཟློས། ཡིག་ཆ་སོགས་ཀྱི་ནང་དོན་ཐུག་ཙམ་གྱིས་སྐུར་ཆོག</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ནུས་རྩོལ།">
             <feature>• བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་རྒྱུན་བསྲིང་ཉམས་ལེན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱེད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན།">
             <feature>• རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་ཡོད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ།">
             <feature>• ཨན་སྒྲོའི་ 2026 ལོའི་ཟླ་བ་ 1 པོའི་བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདྲེས་འཇུག་བྱས་ཏེ། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་སྟོབས་སྒྱུར་གཏོང་། རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉེན་ཆས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནང་དོན་སྐོར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ། རུང་ཡོའོ་གཞུང་ཕྱོགས་དྲ་ཚིགས་ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2026/1 ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
             <feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གཞི་གྲངས་སུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་སྔོན་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. དེ་ལས་མང་བའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་ལེགས་པོའི་ངོ་སྤྲོད་ཐད་ཁ་པར་རྩེ་བའི་ལག་རྩལ་གྱི་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱ་རོགས།
3. གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་པའི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད་དུ། གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ། ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་མཁོ་མཁན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་ཕེབས་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་འཚོལ་རོགས།</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="5146" name="bs-ba">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo ažuriranje uglavnom poboljšava performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da uživate u poboljšanjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistem">
             <feature>• Podržava prekid veze s Wi-Fi mrežom i prikaz lozinke</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zaključani ekran">
             <feature>• Zaključani ekran nudi veći i rastegnuti stil sata. Isprobajte funkciju tako što ćete otići na: Postavke > Početni ekran i stil > Prilagođeno > Dodirnite sat za uređivanje</feature>
             <feature>• Sada možete koristiti videozapise kao pozadinu s dinamičnim efektima koji se reproduciraju do 10 sekundi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor povezivanje">
             <feature>• Honor telefoni i iPhone uređaji sada mogu međusobno dijeliti poruke o obavještenjima</feature>
             <feature>• S najnovijom verzijom aplikacije HONOR WorkStation instaliranom na vašem Mac računaru, Povezana obavještavanja vam omogućava sinhronizaciju obavještenja s Mac računarom</feature>
             <feature>• Instalirajte najnoviju verziju aplikacije HONOR WorkStation na svoj Mac, zatim možete koristiti OneTap za prijenos slika, videozapisa, datoteka i drugog sadržaja s Honor telefona na Mac jednim dodirom</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Potrošnja energije">
             <feature>• Optimizira korisničko iskustvo s trajanjem baterije u nekim scenarijima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Poboljšava stabilnost sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sigurnosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Ugrađena je Android sigurnosna ispravka (januar 2026.) radi sistemske sigurnosti. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima sigurnosti uređaja Honor, posjetite našu web stranicu https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Bilješke" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja ne utiče na lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o funkcijama proizvoda u Savjetima
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete zatražiti našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati Honor dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetiti Honor servisni centar za korisnike</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1027" name="ca-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització millora principalment el rendiment del sistema. Actualitzeu-la per gaudir de les millores</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistema">
             <feature>• Admet la desconnexió de la Wi-Fi i la visualització de la contrasenya</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla de bloqueig">
             <feature>• La pantalla de bloqueig ofereix un estil de rellotge més gran i allargat: Per provar-ho, aneu a Configuració > Pantalla inicial i estil > Personalitzada > Tocar el rellotge per editar</feature>
             <feature>• Ara podeu utilitzar vídeos com a fons de pantalla amb efectes dinàmics que es reprodueixen fins a 10 segons</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Els telèfons Honor i els iPhones ara poden compartir missatges de notificació entre si</feature>
             <feature>• Amb la versió més recent d'HONOR WorkStation instal·lada al Mac, Notificacions connectades us permet sincronitzar notificacions amb el Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Instal·leu la versió més recent d'HONOR WorkStation al Mac i podreu utilitzar OneTap per transferir imatges, vídeos, fitxers i altres tipus de contingut del telèfon Honor al Mac amb només un toc</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Consum d'energia">
             <feature>• Optimitza l'experiència d'usuari amb la durada de la bateria en algunes situacions</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilitat">
             <feature>• Millora l'estabilitat del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pedaç de seguretat">
             <feature>• S'ha incorporat el pedaç de seguretat d'Android (gener del 2026) per garantir la seguretat del sistema. Per obtenir més informació sobre les actualitzacions de seguretat d'Honor, consulteu el nostre lloc web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. El fet d'instal·lar aquesta actualització no afectarà les vostres dades personals, però es recomana fer una còpia de seguretat de les dades abans d'iniciar l'actualització
2. Descobriu més informació sobre les funcions del producte a Suggeriments
3. Si trobeu algun problema durant l'actualització, per obtenir la nostra ajuda truqueu a la Línia directa d'atenció al client d'Honor o visiteu el Centre d'atenció al client d'Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1029" name="cs-cz">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Vážený uživateli, tato aktualizace především zvyšuje výkon systému. Aktualizujte, abyste si mohli užít vylepšení</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Systém">
             <feature>• Podporuje odpojení od Wi-Fi a zobrazení hesla</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Obrazovka uzamčení">
             <feature>• Zamčená obrazovka nabízí větší a roztažené hodiny. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce: Nastavení > Domovská obrazovka a styl > Vlastní > Klepnutím na hodiny upravte</feature>
             <feature>• Nyní můžete jako tapetu použít videa s dynamickými efekty, které se přehrávají až 10 sekund</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Telefony Honor a iPhony si nyní mohou navzájem sdílet oznámení</feature>
             <feature>• Pokud máte na svém Macu nainstalovanou nejnovější verzi aplikace HONOR WorkStation, funkce Propojená oznámení vám umožní synchronizovat oznámení s vaším Macem</feature>
             <feature>• Nainstalujte si na svůj Mac nejnovější verzi aplikace HONOR WorkStation a poté můžete pomocí funkce OneTap jediným klepnutím přenášet obrázky, videa, soubory a další obsah ze svého telefonu Honor do Macu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Spotřeba energie">
             <feature>• Optimalizuje uživatelský zážitek s ohledem na výdrž baterie v některých scénářích</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilita">
             <feature>• Vylepšuje stabilitu systému.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Oprava zabezpečení">
             <feature>• Do systému byla začleněna bezpečnostní oprava (leden 2026) pro systém Android, která zajišťuje bezpečnost systému. Více informací o aktualizacích Honor Security najdete na našich webových stránkách https://www.honor.com/cz/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Poznámky" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalace této aktualizace neovlivní vaše osobní data, ale přesto doporučujeme před aktualizací zálohovat data.
2. Další informace o funkcích produktu najdete v aplikaci Tipy.
3. Pokud během aktualizace narazíte na nějaké problémy, zavolejte na informační linku Honor nebo navštivte Centrum služeb zákazníkům Honor.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1030" name="da-dk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Kære bruger. Denne opdatering forbedrer hovedsageligt systemets ydeevne. Opdater for at drage nytte af forbedringerne</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="System">
             <feature>• Understøtter afbrydelse af Wi-Fi-forbindelsen og visning af adgangskoden</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Låseskærm">
             <feature>• Låseskærmen har et større og udstrakt ur. Prøv det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Startskærm og stil > Tilpasset > Tryk på uret for at redigere</feature>
             <feature>• Nu kan du bruge videoer som baggrundsbillede med dynamiske effekter, der afspilles i op til 10 sekunder</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Tilslut">
             <feature>• Nu kan du se notifikationsmeddelelser på både Honor-telefoner og iPhones</feature>
             <feature>• Når du har installeret den nyeste version af HONOR WorkStation på din Mac-computer, giver Tilknyttede meddelelser dig mulighed for at synkronisere meddelelser til din Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Installer den nyeste version af HONOR WorkStation på din Mac-computer, så kan du bruge OneTap til at overføre billeder, videoer, filer og andet indhold fra din Honor-telefon til din Mac med et enkelt tryk</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Strømforbrug">
             <feature>• Optimerer brugeroplevelsen med batterilevetiden i visse scenarier</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitet">
             <feature>• Forbedrer systemstabiliteten</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sikkerhedspatch">
             <feature>• Android-sikkerhedspatch (januar 2026) er blevet integreret af hensyn til systemets sikkerhed. Få flere oplysninger om Honors sikkerhedsopdateringer på vores websted: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Noter" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering påvirker ikke dine personlige data, men vi anbefaler alligevel, at du sikkerhedskopierer dine data inden opdateringen
2. Få flere oplysninger om produktfunktioner i Tips
3. Hvis du oplever problemer under opdateringen, kan du få hjælp ved at ringe til Honors servicehotline eller besøge Honors kundeservicecenter</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1031" name="de-de">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung verbessert hauptsächlich die Systemleistung. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="System">
             <feature>• Unterstützt das Trennen der WLAN-Verbindung und das Anzeigen des Passworts.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bildschirm sperren">
             <feature>• Der Sperrbildschirm bietet einen größeren und gestreckten Uhrstil. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Startbildschirm und Stil > Benutzerdefiniert > Tippen Sie zum Bearbeiten auf die Uhr</feature>
             <feature>• Sie können jetzt Videos als Hintergrund verwenden, mit dynamischen Effekten, die bis zu 10 Sekunden lang abgespielt werden.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor-Telefone und iPhones können jetzt Benachrichtigungsmitteilungen miteinander austauschen.</feature>
             <feature>• Mit der neuesten HONOR WorkStation-Version auf Ihrem Mac können Sie mit geräteübergreifenden Benachrichtigungen die Benachrichtigungen mit Ihrem Mac synchronisieren.</feature>
             <feature>• Installieren Sie die neueste Version von HONOR WorkStation auf Ihrem Mac. Anschließend können Sie mit OneTap Bilder, Videos, Dateien und andere Inhalte mit einem einzigen Tippen von Ihrem Honor-Telefon auf Ihren Mac übertragen.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stromverbrauch">
             <feature>• Optimiert in bestimmten Szenarien die Benutzererfahrung hinsichtlich der Akkulaufzeit.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilität">
             <feature>• Verbessert die Systemstabilität</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sicherheitspatch">
             <feature>• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Jan. 2026) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die Honor Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notizen" type="end">
             <feature>1. Die Installation dieses Updates hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, es wird jedoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen
2. Entdecken Sie weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen in Tipps
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Honor-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein Honor-Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1032" name="el-gr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιώνει κυρίως την απόδοση του συστήματος. Πραγματοποιήστε ενημέρωση για να απολαύσετε τις βελτιώσεις</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Σύστημα">
             <feature>• Υποστηρίζει την αποσύνδεση από το Wi-Fi και την προβολή του κωδικού πρόσβασης</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Κλείδωμα οθόνης">
             <feature>• Η οθόνη κλειδώματος προσφέρει ένα μεγαλύτερο και εκτεταμένο στυλ ρολογιού. Δοκιμάστε αυτή τη λειτουργία μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Αρχική οθόνη και στυλ > Προσαρμοσμένη > Πατήστε το ρολόι για επεξεργασία</feature>
             <feature>• Μπορείτε πλέον να χρησιμοποιείτε τα βίντεο ως ταπετσαρία, με δυναμικά εφέ που αναπαράγονται για έως και 10 δευτερόλεπτα</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Τα τηλέφωνα Honor και τα iPhone μπορούν πλέον να μοιράζονται τα μηνύματα ειδοποιήσεων μεταξύ τους</feature>
             <feature>• Με το πιο πρόσφατο HONOR WorkStation εγκατεστημένο στο Mac σας, οι Συνδεδεμένες ειδοποιήσεις σάς επιτρέπουν να συγχρονίζετε τις ειδοποιήσεις με το Mac σας</feature>
             <feature>• Εγκαταστήστε την πιο πρόσφατη έκδοση του HONOR WorkStation στο Mac σας και, στη συνέχεια, μπορείτε να χρησιμοποιήσετε το OneTap για να μεταφέρετε εικόνες, βίντεο, αρχεία και άλλο περιεχόμενο από το τηλέφωνο Honor σας στο Mac σας με ένα μόνο πάτημα</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Κατανάλωση ενέργειας">
             <feature>• Βελτιστοποιεί την εμπειρία χρήστη με τη διάρκεια ζωής της μπαταρίας σε ορισμένα σενάρια</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Σταθερότητα">
             <feature>• Βελτιώνει τη σταθερότητα του συστήματος</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφάλειας">
             <feature>• Η ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας Android (Ιανουάριος 2026) ενσωματώθηκε για την ασφάλεια του συστήματος. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις ενημερώσεις της Ασφάλειας Honor, επισκεφθείτε τον ιστότοπό μας https://www.honor.com/gr/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Σημειώσεις" type="end">
             <feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα επηρεάσει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, αλλά ακόμη και έτσι συνιστάται η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας των δεδομένων σας πριν από την ενημέρωση
2. Ανακαλύψτε περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις δυνατότητες του προϊόντος στις Συμβουλές
3. Αν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, μπορείτε να λάβετε τη βοήθειά μας καλώντας την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή εξυπηρέτησης της Honor ή με επίσκεψη σε ένα κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2057" name="en-GB">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Dear user, this update mainly enhances the system performance. Update to enjoy the improvements</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="System">
             <feature>• Supports disconnecting from Wi-Fi and viewing the password</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Lock screen">
             <feature>• The lock screen offers a bigger and stretched clock style. Try it out by going to: Settings > Home screen &amp; style > Custom > Tap the clock to edit</feature>
             <feature>• You can now use videos as the wallpaper, with dynamic effects that play for up to 10 seconds</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor phones and iPhones can now share notification messages with each other</feature>
             <feature>• With the latest HONOR WorkStation installed on your Mac, Connected Notifications allows you to sync notifications to your Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Install the latest version of the HONOR WorkStation on your Mac, then you can use OneTap to transfer images, videos, files, and other content from your Honor phone to your Mac with a single tap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Power consumption">
             <feature>• Optimises the user experience with battery life in some scenarios</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stability">
             <feature>• Improves the system stability</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Security patch">
             <feature>• Android security patch (Jan 2026) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about Honor Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating
2. Discover more information on product features in Tips
3. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling Honor service hotline or visiting Honor customer service centre</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1034" name="es-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado/a usuario/a, esta actualización mejora principalmente el rendimiento del sistema. Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistema">
             <feature>• Admite la desconexión de Wi-Fi y la visualización de la contraseña</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla de bloqueo">
             <feature>• La pantalla de bloqueo ofrece un estilo de reloj más grande y alargado. Pruébalo en: Ajustes > Pantalla principal y estilo > Personalizada > Pulse el reloj para editar</feature>
             <feature>• Ahora puede usar vídeos como fondo de pantalla con efectos dinámicos que se reproducen hasta 10 segundos</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Los teléfonos Honor y iPhone ahora pueden compartir mensajes de notificación entre sí</feature>
             <feature>• Con la última versión de HONOR WorkStation instalada en su Mac, Notificaciones conectadas le permite sincronizar las notificaciones con su Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Instale la última versión de HONOR WorkStation en su Mac y, después, podrá usar OneTap para transferir imágenes, vídeos, archivos y otro contenido desde su teléfono Honor a su Mac con un solo toque</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Consumo de energía">
             <feature>• Optimiza la experiencia de usuario con la autonomía de la batería en algunos escenarios</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilidad">
             <feature>• Mejora la estabilidad del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Parche de seguridad">
             <feature>• Se ha incorporado el parche de seguridad de Android (enero de 2026) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de Honor, visite nuestro sitio web https://www.honor.com/es/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar
2. Descubra más información sobre las características de los productos en Sugerencias
3. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, puede obtener nuestra ayuda si llama a la línea de atención al cliente de Honor o si visita el centro de servicios al cliente de Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="21514" name="es-us">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización mejora principalmente el rendimiento del sistema. Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistema">
             <feature>• Admite la desconexión de Wi-Fi y la visualización de la contraseña</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla de bloqueo">
             <feature>• La pantalla de bloqueo ofrece un estilo de reloj más grande y extendido. Pruebe la función en: Ajustes > Pantalla principal y estilo > Personalizada > Toque el reloj para editar</feature>
             <feature>• Ahora puede usar videos como fondo de pantalla, con efectos dinámicos que se reproducen hasta por 10 segundos</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Conecta con Honor">
             <feature>• Los teléfonos Honor y iPhone ahora pueden compartir mensajes de notificación entre sí</feature>
             <feature>• Con la última versión de HONOR WorkStation instalada en su Mac, Notificaciones conectadas le permite sincronizar las notificaciones con su Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Instale la versión más reciente de HONOR WorkStation en su Mac y, a continuación, podrá usar OneTap para transferir imágenes, videos, archivos y otros contenidos desde su teléfono Honor a su Mac con un solo toque</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Consumo de energía">
             <feature>• Optimiza la experiencia del usuario con la duración de la batería en algunos casos</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilidad">
             <feature>• Mejora la estabilidad del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Parche de seguridad">
             <feature>• Se incorporó un parche de seguridad de Android (enero de 2026) para mejorar la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de Honor, visite nuestro sitio web https://www.honor.com/latam/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de respaldo de sus datos antes de actualizar
2. Descubra más información sobre las funciones del producto en Sugerencias
3. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, puede llamar a la línea de atención al cliente de Honor o visitar el centro de servicios al cliente de Honor para recibir asistencia</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1061" name="et-ee">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hea kasutaja! See värskendus parandab peamiselt süsteemi jõudlust. Värskendage täiustuste nautimiseks</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Süsteem">
             <feature>• Toetab Wi-Fi ühenduse katkestamist ja parooli kuvamist</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Lukustuskuva">
             <feature>• Lukustuskuva pakub suuremat ja pikemat kellastiili. Proovige seda, avades Sätted > Avakuva ja stiil > Kohandatud > puudutage kella, et seda muuta</feature>
             <feature>• Nüüd saate kasutada taustapildina videoid, mida esitatakse dünaamiliste efektidega kuni 10 sekundit</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Nüüd saavad Honori telefonid ja iPhone’id omavahel teavitusi jagada</feature>
             <feature>• Kui teie Macis on installitud uusim HONOR WorkStation, võimaldab ühendatud teavituste funktsioon teavitused Maciga sünkroonida</feature>
             <feature>• Installige oma Macis HONOR WorkStationi uusim versioon, misjärel saate OneTapi abil ühe puudutusega pilte, videoid, faile ja muud sisu Honori telefonist oma Maci teisaldada</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Energiakulu">
             <feature>• Optimeerib mõnes olukorras kasutajakogemust ja aku tööiga</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabiilsus">
             <feature>• Parandab süsteemi stabiilsust</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Turvapaik">
             <feature>• Lisati süsteemi turvalisemaks muutev Androidi turvapaik (jaanuar 2026). Lisateabe saamiseks Honori turvavärskenduste kohta külastage meie veebisaiti https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Märkused" type="end">
             <feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei mõjuta teie isiklikke andmeid, aga soovitame ikkagi enne värskendamist andmed varundada
2. Toote funktsioonide kohta leiate lisateavet rakendusest Tips
3. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, saate meilt abi, helistades Honori klienditoe infoliinile või külastades Honori klienditeeninduskeskust</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1069" name="eu-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Erabiltzaile agurgarria: eguneratze honek sistemaren errendimendua hobetzen du nagusiki. Eguneratu hobekuntzez gozatzeko</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistema">
             <feature>• Wifitik deskonektatzea eta pasahitza ikustea onartzen du</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Blokeatutako pantaila">
             <feature>• Blokeatutako pantailak erloju-estilo handiagoa eta luzatuagoa eskaintzen du. Probatzeko, joan hona: Ezarpenak > Hasierako pantaila eta estiloa > Pertsonalizatua > Sakatu editatzeko erlojua</feature>
             <feature>• Bideoak horma-paper gisa erabil ditzakezu, 10 segundora arte erreproduzitzen diren efektu dinamikoekin</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor telefonoek eta iPhone-ek jakinarazpen-mezuak elkarrekin parteka ditzakete orain</feature>
             <feature>• HONOR WorkStation berriena Mac-en instalatuta, jakinarazpenak Mac-ekin sinkronizatzeko aukera ematen dizu Konektatutako jakinarazpenak eginbideak</feature>
             <feature>• Instalatu HONOR WorkStation-en bertsiorik berriena Mac-en, eta gero, OneTap erabil dezakezu irudiak, bideoak, fitxategiak eta bestelako edukia transferitzeko Honor telefonotik Mac-era tekla bakar bat sakatuta</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bateriaren kontsumoa">
             <feature>• Erabiltzaile-esperientzia optimizatzen du egoera batzuetako bateriaren iraupenarekin</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Egonkortasuna">
             <feature>• Sistemaren egonkortasuna hobetu da</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Segurtasun-adabakia">
             <feature>• Android-en segurtasun-adabakia (2026ko urtarrila) gehitu da sistemaren segurtasuna bermatzeko. Honor Segurtasun-eguneratzeei buruzko informazio gehiago lortzeko, ikusi gure webgunea: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Oharrak" type="end">
             <feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzeak ez du eraginik izango datu pertsonaletan, baina, eguneratu baino lehen, datuen babeskopia egitea gomendatzen da
2. Ezagutu produktuaren eginbideei buruzko informazio gehiago Aholkuak atalean
3. Eguneratzean arazoren bat baduzu, gure laguntza eska dezakezu Honor-en telefonozko arreta-lineara deituz edo Honor-en bezeroaren zerbitzu-zentrora joanez</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1065" name="fa-ir">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>کاربر گرامی، این به‌روزرسانی به‌طور عمده عملکرد سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد. با انجام این به‌روزرسانی، از این بهبودها بهره‌مند شوید</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="سیستم">
             <feature>‏• از قطع اتصال از Wi-Fi و مشاهده رمز ورود پشتیبانی می‌شود</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="صفحۀ قفل">
             <feature>‏• صفحهٔ قفل اکنون از سبک ساعت بزرگ‌تر و کشیده‌تر پشتیبانی می‌کند. برای امتحان کردن آن، این مسیر را طی کنید: تنظیمات > صفحۀ اصلی و سبک > سفارشی > روی ساعت ضربه بزنید تا آن را ویرایش کنید</feature>
             <feature>‏• اکنون می‌توانید از ویدیوها به‌عنوان تصاویر زمینه استفاده کنید که با داشتن جلوه‌های پویا، تا ۱۰ ثانیه پخش می‌شوند</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="اتصال Honor">
             <feature>‏• اکنون می‌توان پیام‌های اعلان را در تلفن‌های Honor و iPhone‌ با یکدیگر به اشتراک گذاشت</feature>
             <feature>‏• با نصب جدیدترین نسخه HONOR WorkStation روی Mac، قابلیت «اعلان‌های متصل» به شما امکان می‌دهد اعلان‌ها را با Mac خود همگام‌سازی کنید</feature>
             <feature>‏• جدیدترین نسخه HONOR WorkStation را روی Mac خود نصب کنید، سپس می‌توانید با استفاده از قابلیت «تک‌ضربه» تصاویر، ویدیوها، فایل‌ها و سایر محتوا را با یک ضربه از تلفن Honor خود به Mac منتقل کنید</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="مصرف نیرو">
             <feature>‏• در برخی شرایط تجربه کاربری از عمر باتری را بهبود می‌بخشد</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="پایداری">
             <feature>‏‏• پایداری سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="وصلۀ امنیتی">
             <feature>‏• برای حفظ امنیت سیستم، «وصلۀ امنیتی Android (ژانویه ۲۰۲۶)» گنجانده شده است. برای کسب اطلاعات بیشتر دربارۀ به‌روزرسانی‌های «امنیت Honor»، لطفاً به وب‌سایت ما مراجعه کنید: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="یادداشت‌ها" type="end">
             <feature>‏۱. نصب این به‌روزرسانی روی داده‌های شخصی شما تأثیری نخواهد داشت. بااین‌وجود، توصیه می‌شود قبل از به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید
‏۲. اطلاعات بیشتر مربوط به قابلیت‌های محصول را در «نکات» می‌توانید بیابید
‏۳. اگر در طول به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، می‌توانید از طریق تماس با تلفن مستقیم خدمات Honor یا مراجعه به مرکز خدمات مشتریان Honor از ما کمک بگیرید</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1035" name="fi-fi">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä päivitys parantaa ensisijaisesti järjestelmän suorituskykyä. Päivitä, niin pääset nauttimaan parannuksista</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Järjestelmä">
             <feature>• Tukee Wi-Fi-yhteyden katkaisua ja salasanan katselua</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Lukitusnäyttö">
             <feature>• Lukitusnäyttö tarjoaa suuremman ja venytetyn kellotyylin. Voit kokeilla sitä seuraavassa kohdassa: Asetukset > Aloitusnäyttö ja tyyli > Mukauta > Napauta kelloa sen muokkaamista varten</feature>
             <feature>• Voit nyt käyttää taustakuvana videoita, joiden dynaamiset tehosteet kestävät jopa 10 sekuntia</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor-puhelimet ja iPhonet voivat nyt jakaa ilmoitusviestejä keskenään</feature>
             <feature>• Kun Mac-tietokoneeseesi on asennettu uusin HONOR WorkStation, voit synkronoida ilmoitukset Maciin Yhdistetyt ilmoitukset -ominaisuuden avulla</feature>
             <feature>• Asenna HONOR WorkStationin uusin versio Mac-tietokoneeseesi, niin voit käyttää OneTap-toimintoa ja siirtää kuvia, videoita, tiedostoja ja muuta sisältöä Honor-puhelimesta Maciin yhdellä napautuksella</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Virrankulutus">
             <feature>• Optimoi akun kestoon liittyvän käyttökokemuksen joissakin tilanteissa</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vakaus">
             <feature>• Parantaa järjestelmän vakautta</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Turvallisuuskorjaus">
             <feature>• Android-turvallisuuskorjaus (tammikuu 2026) on lisätty järjestelmän turvallisuutta varten. Lisätietoja Honorin turvallisuuspäivityksistä on saatavilla verkkosivustollamme osoitteessa https://www.honor.com/fi/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Muistiinpanot" type="end">
             <feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei vaikuta henkilökohtaisiin tietoihisi, mutta tietojen varmuuskopiointi ennen päivittämistä on kuitenkin suositeltavaa
2. Lisätietoja tuoteominaisuuksista on Vihjeitä-sovelluksessa
3. Jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia, saat apua soittamalla Honorin palvelunumeroon tai käymällä Honorin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1036" name="fr-fr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour améliore principalement les performances du système. Effectuez la mise à jour pour profiter des améliorations</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Système">
             <feature>• Prend en charge la déconnexion du Wi-Fi et l'affichage du mot de passe</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Écran verrouillé">
             <feature>• L'écran verrouillé propose un style d'horloge agrandi et étiré. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Écran d'accueil et style > Personnalisé > Appuyez sur l'horloge pour la modifier</feature>
             <feature>• Vous pouvez désormais utiliser des vidéos comme fond d'écran, avec des effets dynamiques qui durent jusqu'à 10 secondes</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Les téléphones Honor et les iPhone peuvent désormais partager des messages de notification entre eux</feature>
             <feature>• Avec la dernière version de HONOR WorkStation installée sur votre Mac, Notifications Connectées vous permet de synchroniser les notifications avec votre Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Installez la dernière version de HONOR WorkStation sur votre Mac, puis utilisez OneTap pour transférer des images, des vidéos, des fichiers et d'autres contenus de votre téléphone Honor vers votre Mac d'un simple appui</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Consommation d'énergie">
             <feature>• Optimise l'expérience utilisateur de l'autonomie de la batterie dans certains scénarios</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilité">
             <feature>• Améliore la stabilité du système</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Correctif de sécurité">
             <feature>• Un correctif de sécurité Android (janvier 2026) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité Honor, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour
2. Découvrez plus d'informations sur les fonctionnalités du produit dans Astuces
3. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes pendant la mise à jour, vous pouvez obtenir de l'aide en contactant la hotline de service Honor ou en vous rendant dans un centre de services clients Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1110" name="gl-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado usuario, a novidade principal desta actualización é a mellora do rendemento do sistema. Realice a actualización para gozar das melloras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistema">
             <feature>• Compatible coa desconexión da Wi-Fi e a visualización do contrasinal</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla de bloqueo">
             <feature>• A pantalla de bloqueo ofrece un estilo de reloxo máis grande e alongado. Próbeo facendo o seguinte: Configuración > Pantalla de inicio e estilo > Personalizada > Toque o reloxo para editar</feature>
             <feature>• Xa pode usar vídeos como fondo de escritorio, con efectos dinámicos que se reproducen durante un máximo de 10 segundos</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Conexión de Honor">
             <feature>• Os teléfonos Honor e os iPhones agora poden compartir mensaxes de notificación entre si</feature>
             <feature>• Coa última versión de HONOR WorkStation instalada no seu Mac, Notificacións conectadas permítelle sincronizar as notificacións co seu Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Instala a última versión de HONOR WorkStation no seu Mac e, despois, poderá usar OneTap para transferir imaxes, vídeos, ficheiros e outros contidos do seu teléfono Honor ao seu Mac cun só toque</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Consumo de enerxía">
             <feature>• Optimiza a experiencia do usuario coa duración da batería nalgúns casos</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilidade">
             <feature>• Mellora a estabilidade do sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Parche de seguranza">
             <feature>• Incorporouse o parche de seguranza de Android (xaneiro de 2026) para maior seguridade do sistema. Para obter máis información sobre as actualizacións de seguridade de Honor, visite o noso sitio web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalar esta actualización non afectará os seus datos persoais, pero recoméndase que realice unha copia de seguranza dos datos antes da actualización
2. Descubra máis información sobre as funcionalidades do produto en Consellos
3. Se experimenta problemas durante a actualización, pode chamar á liña directa de servizo de Honor ou ir a un centro de servizos ao cliente de Honor para que lle fornezamos axuda</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1095" name="gu-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ અપડેટ મુખ્યત્વે સિસ્ટમની કામગીરીને વધારે છે. સુધારાનો આનંદ માણવા માટે અપડેટ કરો</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="સિસ્ટમ">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi થી ડિસ્કનેક્ટ થવાનું અને પાસવર્ડ જોવાનું સમર્થન કરે છે</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="લૉક સ્ક્રીન">
             <feature>• લૉક સ્ક્રીન એક મોટી અને ખેંચાયેલી ઘડિયાળ શૈલી પ્રદાન કરે છે. અહીં જઈને તેને અજમાવી જુઓ: સેટિંગ્સ > હોમ સ્ક્રીન અને શૈલી > કસ્ટમ કરો > સંપાદિત કરવા માટે ઘડિયાળ પર ટૅપ કરો</feature>
             <feature>• હવે તમે ડાયનેમિક પ્રભાવ સાથેના વિડિઓઝનો ઉપયોગ વૉલપેપર તરીકે કરી શકો છો, જે 10 સેકંડ સુધી ચાલે છે</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor કનેક્ટ">
             <feature>• Honor ફોન અને iPhone હવે એકબીજા સાથે સૂચના સંદેશા શેર કરી શકે છે</feature>
             <feature>• તમારા Mac પર ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરેલા નવીનતમ HONOR WorkStation સાથે, કનેક્ટ થયેલ સૂચનાઓ તમને તમારા Mac પર સૂચનાઓ સિંક કરવાની અનુમતિ આપે છે</feature>
             <feature>• તમારા Mac પર HONOR WorkStation નું નવીનતમ સંસ્કરણ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરો, પછી તમે તમારા Honor ફોનમાંથી છબીઓ, વિડિઓઝ, ફાઇલો અને અન્ય સામગ્રીને એક જ ટૅપથી તમારા Mac પર ટ્રાન્સફર કરવા માટે OneTap નો ઉપયોગ કરી શકો છો</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="પાવર વપરાશ">
             <feature>• કેટલીક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં બૅટરી આવરદા સાથે વપરાશકર્તા અનુભવને ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="સ્થિરતા">
             <feature>• સિસ્ટમની સ્થિરતામાં સુધારો કરે છે</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="સુરક્ષા પેચ">
             <feature>• Android સુરક્ષા પેચ (જાન્યુઆરી 2026) સિસ્ટમ સુરક્ષા માટે સામેલ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. Honor સુરક્ષા અપડેટ્સ વિશે વધુ માહિતી માટે, કૃપા કરીને અમારી વેબસાઇટ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1 ની મુલાકાત લો</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="નોંધો" type="end">
             <feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારા વ્યક્તિગત ડેટાને અસર થશે નહીં, પરંતુ અપડેટ કરતા પહેલાં તમારા ડેટાનો બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે
2. ટિપ્સમાં ઉત્પાદન સુવિધાઓ વિશે વધુ માહિતી મેળવો
3. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો તમે Honor સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરીને અથવા Honor ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્રની મુલાકાત લઈને અમારી મદદ મેળવી શકો છો</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1081" name="hi-in">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>नमस्ते उपयोगकर्ता, इस अद्यतन से मुख्य रूप से सिस्टम प्रदर्शन को बढ़ाया जाता है। सुधारों का फ़ायदा उठाने के लिए अद्यतन करें</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सिस्टम">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi से डिस्कनेक्ट करने और पासवर्ड देखने का समर्थन किया जाता है</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्क्रीन लॉक करें">
             <feature>• लॉक स्क्रीन में अधिक बड़ी और स्ट्रेच की हुई घड़ी शैली दी जाती है। यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़माएँ: सेटिंग्स > होम स्क्रीन और शैली > कस्टम > संपादित करने के लिए घड़ी पर टैप करें</feature>
             <feature>• अधिकतम 10 सेकंड तक चलने वाले डायनामिक प्रभावों के साथ, आप अब वीडियो का उपयोग वॉलपेपर के रूप में कर सकते हैं</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor फ़ोन और iPhone अब एक-दूसरे के साथ अधिसूचना संदेश साझा कर सकते हैं</feature>
             <feature>• आपके Mac पर नवीनतम HONOR WorkStation स्थापित होने पर, कनेक्टेड अधिसूचना से आपको अधिसूचनाओं को अपने Mac से सिंक करने की अनुमति मिलती है</feature>
             <feature>• अपने Mac पर HONOR WorkStation का नवीनतम संस्करण स्थापित करें, उसके बाद आप अपने Honor फ़ोन से छवियों, वीडियो, फ़ाइलों और अन्य सामग्री को एक ही टैप में अपने Mac पर ट्रांसफ़र करने के लिए OneTap का उपयोग कर सकते हैं</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="पॉवर उपभोग">
             <feature>• कुछ स्थितियों में बैटरी लाइफ़ से उपयोगकर्ता अनुभव को ऑप्टिमाइज़ किया जाता है</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्थिरता">
             <feature>• सिस्टम स्थिरता में सुधार किया जाता है</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षा पैच">
             <feature>• सिस्टम की सुरक्षा के लिए Android सुरक्षा पैच (जनवरी, 2026) शामिल किया गया है। Honor सुरक्षा अद्यतनों के बारे में अधिक जानकारी के लिए, कृपया हमारी वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1 पर जाएँ</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोट्स" type="end">
             <feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपके व्यक्तिगत डेटा पर कोई प्रभाव नहीं पड़ेगा, लेकिन फिर भी अद्यतन करने से पहले अपने डेटा का बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है
2. युक्तियाँ में जाकर उत्पाद की सुविधाओं के बारे में अधिक जानकारी खोजें
3. अगर आपको अद्यतन के दौरान कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो आप Honor सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करके या Honor ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाकर हमारी सहायता पा सकते हैं</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1050" name="hr-hr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim se ažuriranjem uglavnom poboljšavaju performanse sustava. Ažurirajte kako biste uživali u poboljšanjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sustav">
             <feature>• Podržava isključivanje s Wi-Fi mreže i pregled lozinke</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zaključani zaslon">
             <feature>• Zaključani zaslon pruža stil većeg i rastegnutog sata. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Početni zaslon i stil > Prilagođeno > Dodirnite sat za uređivanje</feature>
             <feature>• Sada možete za pozadinu upotrebljavati videozapise uz dinamičke efekte koji se reproduciraju do 10 sekundi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Povezivanje">
             <feature>• Telefoni Honor i uređaji iPhone sada mogu međusobno dijeliti poruke s obavijestima</feature>
             <feature>• S najnovijom verzijom HONOR WorkStation instaliranom na vašem Macu, značajka Povezanih obavijesti omogućuje vam sinkronizaciju obavijesti s vašim Macom</feature>
             <feature>• Instalirajte najnoviju verziju HONOR WorkStationa na svoj Mac kako biste mogli koristiti OneTap za prijenos slika, videozapisa, datoteka i ostalog sadržaja s Honor telefona na Mac jednim dodirom</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Potrošnja energije">
             <feature>• Optimizira korisničko iskustvo s trajanjem baterije u nekim scenarijima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Poboljšava se stabilnost sustava</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sigurnosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (siječanj 2026.) za sigurnost sustava. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima značajke Honor Sigurnost posjetite naše web-mjesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Bilješke" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće utjecati na osobne podatke, ali se svejedno preporučuje izraditi sigurnosnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja
2. Idite u aplikaciju Savjeti kako biste doznali više informacija o značajkama proizvoda
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tijekom ažuriranja, našu pomoć možete dobiti tako da nazovete Honor dežurnu liniju ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1038" name="hu-hu">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez a frissítés elsősorban a rendszerteljesítményt javítja. Végezze el a frissítést, hogy élvezhesse a továbbfejlesztéseket</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Rendszer">
             <feature>• Támogatja a Wi-Fi-ről való leválasztást, és a jelszó megtekintését</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zárképernyő">
             <feature>• A zárképernyő nagyobb, megnyújtott órastílust kínál. Próbálja ki itt: Beállítások > Főképernyő és stílus > Egyéni > Érintse meg az órát a szerkesztéshez</feature>
             <feature>• Mostantól videókat is használhat háttérképként, dinamikus effektusokkal, akár 10 másodperces lejátszási idővel</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• A Honor telefonok és az iPhone készülékek mostantól megoszthatják egymással az értesítési üzeneteket</feature>
             <feature>• Ha Mac készülékére telepítette a HONOR WorkStation legfrissebb verzióját, a Csatlakoztatott értesítések segítségével az értesítéseket szinkronizálhatja a Mac készülékével</feature>
             <feature>• Telepítse a HONOR WorkStation legfrissebb verzióját a Mac készülékére, és azt követően a OneTap használatával egyetlen érintéssel vihet át képeket, videókat, fájlokat és más tartalmat Honor telefonjáról a Mac készülékére</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Energiafogyasztás">
             <feature>• Optimalizálja az üzemidővel kapcsolatos felhasználói élményt bizonyos helyzetekben</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitás">
             <feature>• Javítja a rendszer stabilitását</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Biztonsági javítás">
             <feature>• A rendszer biztonsága érdekében beépítésre került az Android biztonsági javítása (2026. január). A Honor biztonsági frissítéseivel kapcsolatos további információkért látogasson el webhelyünkre a következő címen: https://www.honor.com/hu/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Jegyzetek" type="end">
             <feature>1. A jelen frissítés telepítése nem lesz hatással személyes adataira, de a frissítés előtt az adatokról továbbra is ajánlott biztonsági másolatot készíteni
2. A termékfunkciókkal kapcsolatos további információkat a Tippek alkalmazásban tekintheti meg
3. Ha a frissítés során bármilyen problémába ütközik, forduljon hozzánk segítségért a Honor-szerviz forródrótján, vagy látogasson el a Honor ügyfélszolgálati központjába</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1057" name="in-id">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini utamanya meningkatkan kinerja sistem. Instal pembaruan untuk menikmati berbagai peningkatan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistem">
             <feature>• Mendukung pemutusan dari Wi-Fi dan menampilkan kata sandi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Layar kunci">
             <feature>• Layar kunci menawarkan gaya jam yang lebih besar dan direntangkan. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Gaya &amp; layar beranda > Khusus > Ketuk jam untuk mengedit</feature>
             <feature>• Anda kini dapat menggunakan video sebagai wallpaper, dengan efek dinamis yang diputar hingga 10 detik</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Koneksi">
             <feature>• Ponsel Honor dan iPhone kini dapat membagikan pesan notifikasi ke satu sama lain</feature>
             <feature>• Dengan HONOR WorkStation terbaru yang diinstal di Mac Anda, Notifikasi Terhubung memungkinkan Anda untuk menyinkronkan notifikasi ke Mac Anda</feature>
             <feature>• Instal versi terbaru HONOR WorkStation di Mac Anda, lalu Anda dapat menggunakan OneTap untuk mentransfer gambar, video, file, dan konten lainnya dari ponsel Honor ke Mac Anda dengan sekali ketuk</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Konsumsi daya">
             <feature>• Mengoptimalkan pengalaman pengguna usia baterai di skenario tertentu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitas">
             <feature>• Meningkatkan stabilitas sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Penambal keamanan">
             <feature>• Patch keamanan Android (Januari 2026) telah diterapkan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan Honor, kunjungi situs web kami di https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Catatan" type="end">
             <feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan untuk mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui
2. Pelajari informasi selengkapnya terkait fitur produk di Kiat
3. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan Honor atau mengunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1040" name="it-it">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento migliora principalmente le prestazioni del sistema. Esegui l'aggiornamento per usufruire dei miglioramenti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistema">
             <feature>• È supportata la disconnessione dal Wi-Fi e la visualizzazione della password</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Blocca schermo">
             <feature>• La schermata di blocco presenta uno stile orologio più grande e allungato. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Schermata Home e stile > Personalizzato > Tocca l'orologio per modificare</feature>
             <feature>• Ora puoi usare i video come sfondo, con effetti dinamici che durano fino a 10 secondi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• I telefoni Honor e gli iPhone possono ora condividere tra loro i messaggi di notifica</feature>
             <feature>• Una volta installata la versione più recente di HONOR WorkStation sul Mac, potrai sincronizzare le notifiche sul Mac grazie a Notifiche connesse</feature>
             <feature>• Installa la versione più recente di HONOR WorkStation sul Mac e potrai usare OneTap per trasferire immagini, video, file e altri contenuti dal tuo telefono Honor al Mac con un solo tocco</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Consumo di energia">
             <feature>• Viene ottimizzata la durata della batteria per una migliore esperienza utente in alcuni scenari</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilità">
             <feature>• Viene migliorata la stabilità del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch di sicurezza">
             <feature>• È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (gennaio 2026) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza Honor, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Note" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup dei dati prima di procedere
2. Scopri ulteriori informazioni sulle funzioni del prodotto in Suggerimenti
3. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center Honor o visitando un centro servizio clienti Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1037" name="iw-il">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה משפר בעיקר את ביצועי המערכת. עדכן כדי ליהנות מהשיפורים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="מערכת">
             <feature>‏• תומך בניתוק מ-Wi-Fi ובהצגת הסיסמה</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="מסך נעילה">
             <feature>‏• מסך הנעילה מאפשר סגנון שעון מוגדל ומתוח. כדי לנסות זאת, אפשר לעבור אל: הגדרות > מסך הבית וסגנון > מותאם אישית > להקיש על השעון כדי לערוך אותו</feature>
             <feature>‏• עכשיו אפשר להגדיר סרטונים בתור טפט, עם אפקטים דינמיים שפועלים למשך 10 שניות לכל היותר</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏Honor Connect">
             <feature>‏• טלפונים של Honor והתקני iPhone יכולים כעת לשתף זה עם זה התראות על הודעות</feature>
             <feature>‏• עם התקנת הגרסה העדכנית ביותר של HONOR WorkStation ב-Mac שברשותך, 'התראה מחוברת' תאפשר לך לסנכרן התראות עם אותו Mac</feature>
             <feature>‏• התקן את הגרסה העדכנית ביותר של HONOR WorkStation ב-Mac שברשותך, ולאחר מכן תוכל להשתמש ב-OneTap כדי להעביר בהקשה אחת תמונות, סרטונים, קבצים ותוכן אחר מטלפון Honor שברשותך לאותו Mac</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏צריכת חשמל">
             <feature>‏• ממטב את חוויית המשתמש עם חיי הסוללה בתרחישים מסוימים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="יציבות">
             <feature>‏‏• משפר את יציבות המערכת</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="תיקון אבטחה">
             <feature>‏• 'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מינו' 2026) נכלל למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של Honor', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="הערות" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון
‏2. גלה מידע נוסף על תכונות המוצר ב'טיפים'
‏3. אם תיתקל בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, ניתן לקבל עזרה מאיתנו באמצעות התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של Honor או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1041" name="ja-jp">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ユーザーの皆様、今回の更新では主にシステムのパフォーマンスが強化されます。更新して、改善をお楽しみください</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="システム">
             <feature>• Wi-Fiの切断とパスワードの表示をサポートします</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ロック画面">
             <feature>• ロック画面では、より大きく引き延ばされた時計スタイルが提供されます。この機能を試すには、[設定] > [ホーム画面とスタイル] > [カスタム]に移動して、時計をタップして編集してください</feature>
             <feature>• ビデオを壁紙として使用できるようになり、ダイナミック効果が最大10秒再生されます</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honorコネクト">
             <feature>• Honor携帯電話とiPhone間で通知メッセージを共有できるようになりました</feature>
             <feature>• Macに最新バージョンのHONOR WorkStationをインストールすると、コネクト通知によりMacと通知を同期させることができます</feature>
             <feature>• Macに最新バージョンのHONOR WorkStationをインストールすると、OneTapを使用して、画像、ビデオ、ファイル、その他のコンテンツをHonor携帯電話からMacにワンタップで転送できます</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="消費電力">
             <feature>• 一部のシナリオにおいてバッテリー寿命におけるユーザー体験を最適化します</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安定性">
             <feature>• システムの安定性が改善します</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="セキュリティパッチ">
             <feature>• システムセキュリティのためにAndroidセキュリティパッチ（2026年1月）が組み込まれました。Honorのセキュリティ更新の詳細については、当社のWebサイトをご覧ください：https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="メモ" type="end">
             <feature>1. この更新をインストールしても個人情報への影響はありませんが、更新前に個人情報をバックアップしておくことをおすすめします
2. 製品機能の詳細はヒントアプリで確認してください
3. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、Honorサービスコールセンターにお電話をいただくか、Honorカスタマーサービスセンターにご来店いただき、サポートを受けてください</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1079" name="ka-ge">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ეს განახლება ძირითადად აუმჯობესებს სისტემის ეფექტიანობას. განაახლეთ და ისიამოვნეთ გაუმჯობესებებით</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="სისტემა">
             <feature>• მხარს უჭერს Wi-Fi-დან გათიშვას და პაროლის ნახვას</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ჩაკეტილი ეკრანი">
             <feature>• დაბლოკვის ეკრანი გთავაზობთ უფრო დიდ და გაწელილ საათის სტილს. სცადეთ შემდეგ ბმულზე გადასვლით: პარამეტრები > საწყისი ეკრანი და სტილი > მორგებული > შეეხეთ საათს რედაქტირებისთვის</feature>
             <feature>• ახლა შეგიძლიათ გამოიყენოთ ვიდეოები ფონად, დინამიური ეფექტებით, რომლებიც 10 წამამდე გრძელდება</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor კავშირი">
             <feature>• Honor ტელეფონებსა და iPhone-ებს ახლა შეუძლიათ ერთმანეთთან შეტყობინებების გაზიარება</feature>
             <feature>• თქვენს Mac-ზე დაინსტალირებული უახლესი HONOR WorkStation-ის წყალობით, დაკავშირებული შეტყობინებები საშუალებას გაძლევთ, შეტყობინებების თქვენს Mac-თან სინქრონიზაცია მოახდინოთ</feature>
             <feature>• დააინსტალირეთ HONOR WorkStation-ის უახლესი ვერსია თქვენს Mac-ზე, შემდეგ კი OneTap-ის გამოყენებით შეგიძლიათ ერთი შეხებით გადაიტანოთ სურათები, ვიდეოები, ფაილები და სხვა კონტენტი თქვენი Honor ტელეფონიდან Mac-ზე</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ენერგიის მოხმარება">
             <feature>• ზოგიერთ სცენარში ახდენს მომხმარებლის გამოცდილების ოპტიმიზებას კვების ელემენტის ხანგრძლივობით</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="სტაბილურობა">
             <feature>• აუმჯობესებს სისტემის სტაბილურობას</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="უსაფრთხოების შესწორება">
             <feature>• სისტემის უსაფრთხოებისთვის დანერგილია Android-ის უსაფრთხოების პატჩი (2026 წლის იანვარი). Honor Security-ის განახლებების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაციისთვის, გთხოვთ, ეწვიოთ ჩვენს ვებსაიტს https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="შენიშვნები" type="end">
             <feature>1. ამ განახლების დაინსტალირება არ იმოქმედებს თქვენს პერსონალურ მონაცემებზე, თუმცა რეკომენდებულია განახლებამდე მონაცემების სარეზერვო ასლის შექმნა
2. გაეცანით დამატებით ინფორმაციას რჩევებში პროდუქტის ფუნქციების შესახებ
3. თუ განახლებისას გარკვეულ პრობლემებს წააწყდით, დახმარებისთვის დარეკეთ Honor-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან ეწვიეთ Honor-ის სერვისცენტრს</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1087" name="kk-kz">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл жаңарту негізінен жүйе өнімділігін жақсартады. Жақсартуларды пайдалану үшін жаңартыңыз</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Жүйе">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi желісінен ажыратуды және құпиясөзді көруді қолдайды</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Құлыптау экраны">
             <feature>• Құлыптау экраны үлкенірек және созылған сағат стилін ұсынады. «Параметрлер» > «Негізгі экран және стиль» > «Теңшелетін» > «Өңдейтін сағатты түртіңіз» тармағына өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз</feature>
             <feature>• Енді сіз бейнелерді 10 секундқа дейін ойнатылатын динамикалық әсерлері бар тұсқағаз ретінде пайдалана аласыз</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Қосылу">
             <feature>• Honor телефондары мен iPhone-дар енді хабарландыру хабарламаларын бір-бірімен бөлісе алады</feature>
             <feature>• Mac-ке орнатылған соңғы HONOR WorkStation нұсқасымен «Қосылған хабарландырулар» мүмкіндігі хабарландыруларды Mac-пен синхрондауына рұқсат етеді</feature>
             <feature>• Mac-ке HONOR WorkStation соңғы нұсқасын орнатып, OneTap көмегімен кескіндерді, бейнелерді, файлдарды және басқа мазмұнды Honor телефоныңыздан Mac-ке бір рет түрту арқылы тасымалдауға болады</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Қуат тұтыну">
             <feature>• Кейбір жағдайларда батареяның қызмет көрсету мерзімін оңтайландырады</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Тұрақтылық">
             <feature>• Жүйе тұрақтылығын жақсартады</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Қауіпсіздік патчы">
             <feature>• Android қауіпсіздік патчы (қаңтар, 2026) жүйе қауіпсіздігі үшін біріктірілген. Honor қауіпсіздік жаңартулары туралы қосымша ақпарат алу үшін біздің веб-сайтқа кіріңіз: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Ескертпелер" type="end">
             <feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнату жеке деректеріңізге әсер етпейді, бірақ жаңарту алдында деректердің сақтық көшірмесін жасау ұсынылады
2. «Кеңестер» қолданбасында өнім мүмкіндіктері туралы қосымша ақпаратты табыңыз
3. Жаңарту кезінде қандай да бір мәселе орын алса, Honor қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне қоңырау шалу не Honor тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына бару арқылы көмегімізді ала аласыз</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1107" name="km-kh">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះធ្វើឱ្យប្រតិបត្តិការប្រព័ន្ធប្រសើរឡើងជាចម្បង។ ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព ដើម្បីរីករាយនឹងការកែលម្អទាំងនេះ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ប្រព័ន្ធ">
             <feature>• អាចប្រើការផ្ដាច់ពី Wi-Fi និងការមើលពាក្យសម្ងាត់</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="អេក្រង់ជាប់សោ">
             <feature>• អេក្រង់ចាក់សោផ្ដល់ជូននូវរចនាបថនាឡិកាធំជាង និងលាតសន្ធឹង។ សាកល្បងប្រើដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > រចនាប័ទ្ម និងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម > តាមតម្រូវការ > ប៉ះនាឡិកាដើម្បីកែ</feature>
             <feature>• ឥឡូវ អ្នកអាចប្រើវីដេអូជារូបផ្ទៃអេក្រង់ ដែលមានបែបផែនឌីណាមិកដែលលេងរហូតដល់ 10 វិនាទី</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• ឥឡូវ ទូរស័ព្ទ Honor និង iPhone អាចចែករំលែកសារជូនដំណឹងជាមួយគ្នាទៅវិញទៅមក</feature>
             <feature>• ដោយបានដំឡើង HONOR WorkStation ចុងក្រោយបំផុតនៅលើ Mac របស់អ្នក ការជូនដំណឹងតភ្ជាប់អនុញ្ញាតឱ្យអ្នកធ្វើសមកាលកម្មការជូនដំណឹងទៅ Mac របស់អ្នក</feature>
             <feature>• ដំឡើងកំណែចុងក្រោយបំផុតនៃ HONOR WorkStation នៅលើ Mac របស់អ្នក បន្ទាប់មក អ្នកអាចប្រើប្រាស់ OneTap ដើម្បីផ្ទេររូបភាព វីដេអូ ឯកសារ និងខ្លឹមសារផ្សេងទៀតពីទូរស័ព្ទ Honor របស់អ្នកទៅ Mac របស់អ្នកត្រឹមមួយប៉ះ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ការប្រើប្រាស់ថាមពល">
             <feature>• ធ្វើឱ្យបទពិសោធអ្នកប្រើអាយុកាលថ្មប្រសើរឡើងក្នុងសេណារីយោមួយចំនួន</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ស្ថិរភាព">
             <feature>• កែលម្អស្ថិរភាពប្រព័ន្ធ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="បំណះសន្តិសុខ">
             <feature>• បំណះសន្តិសុខ Android (មករា 2026) ត្រូវបាន​រួមបញ្ចូល​សម្រាប់​សន្តិសុខ​ប្រព័ន្ធ។ សម្រាប់​ព័ត៌មាន​បន្ថែម​អំពី​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​សន្តិសុខ Honor សូមចូលទៅ​គេហទំព័រ​របស់យើង https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់" type="end">
             <feature>1. ការដំឡើងបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះនឹងមិនប៉ះពាល់ដល់ទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួនរបស់អ្នកទេ ប៉ុន្តែសូមណែនាំឱ្យបម្រុងទុកទិន្នន័យរបស់អ្នក មុននឹងធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព
2. ស្វែងយល់បន្ថែមអំពីលក្ខណៈពិសេសផលិតផលនៅក្នុងគន្លឹះ
3. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបប្រទះបញ្ហាណាមួយអំឡុងពេលធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព អ្នកអាចទទួលបានជំនួយរបស់យើងដោយហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សនៃសេវាកម្ម Honor ឬចូលទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌលសេវាកម្មអតិថិជន Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1099" name="kn-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಮುಖ್ಯವಾಗಿ ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಕಾರ್ಯಕ್ಷಮತೆಯನ್ನು ವರ್ಧಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಸುಧಾರಣೆಗಳನ್ನು ಆನಂದಿಸಲು ನವೀಕರಿಸಿ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi ಸಂಪರ್ಕ ಕಡಿತಗೊಳಿಸುವುದು ಮತ್ತು ಗುಪ್ತಪದ ವೀಕ್ಷಿಸುವುದನ್ನು ಬೆಂಬಲಿಸುತ್ತದೆ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಲಾಕ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್">
             <feature>• ಲಾಕ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ದೊಡ್ಡದಾದ ಮತ್ತು ವಿಸ್ತರಿಸಲಾದ ಗಡಿಯಾರ ಶೈಲಿಯನ್ನು ನೀಡುತ್ತದೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ ನೋಡಿ: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಮತ್ತು ಶೈಲಿ > ಕಸ್ಟಮ್ > ಎಡಿಟ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಗಡಿಯಾರವನ್ನು ಟ್ಯಾಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ</feature>
             <feature>• 10 ಸೆಕೆಂಡುಗಳವರೆಗೆ ಪ್ಲೇ ಆಗುವ ಡೈನಾಮಿಕ್ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್‌ಗಳ ಮೂಲಕ, ನೀವು ಈಗ ವೀಡಿಯೊಗಳನ್ನು ವಾಲ್‌ಪೇಪರ್‌ ಆಗಿ ಬಳಸಬಹುದು</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ಕನೆಕ್ಟ್">
             <feature>• Honor ಫೋನ್‌ಗಳು ಮತ್ತು iPhone ಗಳು ಈಗ ಪರಸ್ಪರ ಅಧಿಸೂಚನೆ ಸಂದೇಶಗಳನ್ನು ಹಂಚಿಕೊಳ್ಳಬಹುದು</feature>
             <feature>• ನಿಮ್ಮ Mac ನಲ್ಲಿ ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸಲಾದ ಇತ್ತೀಚಿನ HONOR ವರ್ಕ್‌ಸ್ಟೇಷನ್‌ನ ಮೂಲಕ, ಕನೆಕ್ಟ್ ಆಗಿರುವ ಅಧಿಸೂಚನೆಗಳು ನಿಮ್ಮ Mac ಗೆ ಅಧಿಸೂಚನೆಗಳನ್ನು ಸಿಂಕ್ ಮಾಡಲು ನಿಮಗೆ ಅನುಮತಿಸುತ್ತದೆ</feature>
             <feature>• ನಿಮ್ಮ Mac ನಲ್ಲಿ HONOR ವರ್ಕ್‌ಸ್ಟೇಷನ್‍‍ನ ಇತ್ತೀಚಿನ ಆವೃತ್ತಿಯನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸಿ, ನಂತರ ನೀವು OneTap ಬಳಸಿ ನಿಮ್ಮ Honor ಫೋನ್‌ನಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ Mac ಗೆ ಒಂದೇ ಟ್ಯಾಪ್ ಮೂಲಕ ಚಿತ್ರಗಳು, ವೀಡಿಯೊಗಳು, ಫೈಲ್‌ಗಳು ಹಾಗೂ ಇತರ ವಿಷಯವನ್ನು ವರ್ಗಾಯಿಸಬಹುದು</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಪವರ್ ಬಳಕೆ">
             <feature>• ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಬ್ಯಾಟರಿ ಬಾಳಿಕೆಯ ಜೊತೆಗೆ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಸ್ಥಿರತೆ">
             <feature>• ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಸ್ಥಿರತೆಯನ್ನು ಸುಧಾರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್">
             <feature>• ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಭದ್ರತೆಗಾಗಿ Android ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ (ಜನವರಿ 2026) ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. Honor ಭದ್ರತಾ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಗಾಗಿ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಮ್ಮ ವೆಬ್‌ಸೈಟ್‌ಗೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡಿ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು" type="end">
             <feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾದ ಮೇಲೆ ಪರಿಣಾಮ ಬೀರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೂ ಸಹ ನವೀಕರಿಸುವ ಮೊದಲು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಬ್ಯಾಕ್ ಅಪ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ
2. ಉತ್ಪನ್ನ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಯನ್ನು ಸಲಹೆಗಳು ಎಂಬುದರಲ್ಲಿ ಕಂಡುಕೊಳ್ಳಿ
3. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನಿಮಗೆ ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳು ಎದುರಾದರೆ, ನೀವು Honor ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಅಥವಾ Honor ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ನಮ್ಮ ಸಹಾಯವನ್ನು ಪಡೆಯಬಹುದು</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1042" name="ko-kr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>사용자 여러분, 이번 업데이트는 주로 시스템 성능을 향상시킵니다. 업데이트하고 개선된 기능을 즐겨 보세요</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="시스템">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi의 연결 해제와 암호 확인을 지원합니다</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="잠금 화면">
             <feature>• 잠금 화면이 더 크고 늘어난 시계 스타일을 제공합니다. 설정 > 홈 화면 및 스타일 > 사용자 설정으로 이동한 다음 > 편집할 시계를 탭하여 사용해 보세요</feature>
             <feature>• 이제 최대 10초 동안 재생되는 동적 효과와 함께 비디오를 배경화면으로 사용할 수 있습니다</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor 커넥트">
             <feature>• 이제 Honor 휴대폰과 iPhone이 서로 알림 메시지를 공유할 수 있습니다</feature>
             <feature>• Mac에 최신 HONOR 워크스테이션을 설치하면 커넥티드 알림을 통해 알림을 Mac과 동기화할 수 있습니다</feature>
             <feature>• Mac에 최신 버전의 HONOR 워크스테이션을 설치하면 OneTap을 사용하여 Honor 휴대폰에서 Mac으로 이미지, 비디오, 파일 및 기타 콘텐츠를 탭 한 번으로 전송할 수 있습니다</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="소비 전력">
             <feature>• 일부 시나리오에서 배터리 수명으로 사용자 경험을 최적화합니다</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="안정성">
             <feature>• 시스템 안정성이 개선되었습니다</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="보안 패치">
             <feature>• 시스템 보안을 위해 Android 보안 패치(2026년 1월)가 통합되었습니다. Honor 보안 업데이트에 대해 자세히 알아보려면 당사 웹사이트(https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1)를 방문하세요</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="공지" type="end">
             <feature>1. 이 업데이트 설치는 개인 데이터에 영향을 미치지 않지만, 업데이트하기 전에 데이터를 백업하는 것이 좋습니다
2. Tips에서 제품 기능에 대한 자세한 정보를 알아보세요
3. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 Honor 서비스 핫라인으로 전화하거나 Honor 고객 서비스 센터를 방문하여 도움을 받을 수 있습니다</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1108" name="lo-la">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ສະ​ບາຍ​ດີ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​​ນີ້​ຍົກ​ລະ​ດັບ​ປະ​ສິດ​ທິ​ພາບ​ຂອງ​ລະ​ບົບ​ເປັນຫຼັກ. ອັບ​ເດດ​ເພື່ອ​ມ່ວ​ນ​ຊື່​ນກັບ​ການ​ປັບ​ປຸງ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="​ລະບົບ">
             <feature>• ຮອງ​ຮັບ​ການຕັດ​ການ​ເຊື່ອມ​ຕໍ່​ຈາກ Wi-Fi ແລະ ການ​ເບິ່ງ​ລະ​ຫັດ​ຜ່ານ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ໜ້າຈໍລັອກ">
             <feature>• ໜ້າ​ຈໍລັອກສະ​ເໜີ​ໃຫ້​ຮູບ​ແບບ​ໂມງ​ທີ່​ໃຫຍ່​ຂຶ້ນ ແລະ ຍືດ​ອອກ. ​ລອງໃຊ້ມັນເບິ່ງ​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການຕັ້ງຄ່າ > ໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ ແລະ ຮູບແບບ > ກຳນົດເອງ > ແຕະ​ໂມງ​ເພື່ອ​ແກ້​ໄຂ</feature>
             <feature>• ຕອນ​ນີ້​ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ໃຊ້​ວິ​ດີ​ໂອ​ເປັນ​ພາບ​ພື້ນຫຼັງ​ໄດ້​, ພ້ອມ​ເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ໄດ​ນາ​ມິກ​ທີ່ຫຼິ້ນ​ເປັນ​ເວ​ລາ​ເຖິງ 10 ວິ​ນາ​ທີ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• ຕອນ​ນີ້​ໂທລະສັບ Honor ແລະ iPhone ສາ​ມາດ​ແຊ​ຣ໌​ຂໍ້​ຄວາມ​ການ​ແຈ້ງ​ເຕືອນລະ​ຫວ່າງ​ກັນ​ໄດ້​ແລ້ວ</feature>
             <feature>• ເມື່ອ​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ HONOR WorkStation ໃໝ່​ຫຼ້າ​ສຸດ​ໃນ Mac ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ແລ້ວ, ການແຈ້ງເຕືອນທີ່ເຊື່ອມຕໍ່ແລ້ວອະ​ນຸ​ຍາດ​ໃຫ້​ທ່ານ​ຊິງ​​ຄ໌​ການ​ແຈ້ງ​ເຕືອນ​ກັບ Mac ຂອງ​ທ່ານ</feature>
             <feature>• ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ​ເວີ​ຊັນ​ໃໝ່ຫຼ້າ​ສຸດ​​ຂອງ HONOR WorkStation ໃນ Mac ຂອງ​ທ່ານ, ຈາກນັ້ນ​ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ໃຊ້ OneTap ເພື່ອ​ໂອນ​ຮູບ​ພາບ, ວິດີໂອ, ໄຟ​ລ໌ ແລະ ເນື້ອ​ຫາ​ອື່ນໆ​ຈາກ​ໂທ​ລະ​ສັບ Honor ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄປ​ຫາ Mac ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄດ້​ດ້ວຍ​ການ​ແຕະ​ພຽງ​ຄັ້ງ​ດຽວ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="​ການ​ໃຊ້​ພະ​ລັງ​ງານ">
             <feature>• ປັບປະ​ສົບ​ການຜູ້​​ໃຊ້​ກັບອາຍຸແບັດເຕີຣີໃນບາງສະພາບການ​ໃຫ້ເໝາະສົມ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ຄວາມສະ​ຖຽນ">
             <feature>• ປັບປຸງຄວາມສະຖຽນຂອງລະບົບ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ">
             <feature>• ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ຂອງ Android (ມັງ​ກອນ 2026) ​ໄດ້ຖືກລວມ​​ເຂົ້າ​ເປັນ​ການ​ຮັກ​ສາ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ລະ​ບົບ. ສຳລັບຂໍ້ມູນເພີ່ມເຕີມກ່ຽວກັບການອັບເດດດ້ານຄວາມປອດໄພຂອງ Honor, ກະລຸນາເຂົ້າໄປ​ທີ່ເວັບໄຊທ໌ຂອງພວກເຮົາ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ການ​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ສົ່ງ​ຜົນ​ຕໍ່​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ, ແຕ່​ຍັງ​ຄົງ​ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ສຳ​ຮອງ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄວ້ກ່ອນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ
2. ຄົ້ນ​ຫາ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ເພີ່ມ​ເຕີມ​ກ່ຽວ​ກັບ​ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດ​ຜະ​ລິດ​ຕະ​ພັນ​ໃນ​​ເຄັດ​ລັບ
3. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ທ່ານສາມາດຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອຈາກພວກເຮົາໄດ້ ໂດຍການໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນ​ບໍ​ລິ​ການ Honor ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1063" name="lt-lt">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šis naujinys daugiausiai pagerina sistemos našumą. Atnaujinkite ir mėgaukitės patobulinimais.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistema">
             <feature>• Palaiko atsijungimą nuo „Wi-Fi“ ir slaptažodžio peržiūrą</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Užrakinimo ekranas">
             <feature>• Užrakinimo ekrane rodomas didesnis, ištempto stiliaus laikrodis. Išbandykite jį, nuėję į „Nuostatos > Pradžios ekranas ir stilius > Tinkintas >“. Palieskite laikrodį, kad jį suredaguotumėte</feature>
             <feature>• Dabar galite naudoti vaizdo įrašus kaip ekrano foną su iki 10 sekundžių trukmės dinaminiais efektais</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="„Honor Connect“">
             <feature>• „Honor“ ir „iPhone“ telefonai dabar gali bendrinti pranešimus tarpusavyje</feature>
             <feature>• Įdiegę naujausią programos „HONOR WorkStation“ versiją į „Mac“ kompiuterį, naudodamiesi funkcija Prijungtieji pranešimai galite sinchronizuoti pranešimus su „Mac“ kompiuteriu</feature>
             <feature>• Įdiekite naujausią „HONOR WorkStation“ versiją savo „Mac“ kompiuteryje, tada naudodami „OneTap“ galėsite vienu palietimu persiųsti vaizdus, vaizdo įrašus, failus ir kitą turinį iš „Honor“ telefono į „Mac“ kompiuterį</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Energijos sąnaudos">
             <feature>• Optimizuoja naudotojo patirtį, atsižvelgiant į akumuliatoriaus veikimo trukmę tam tikrais atvejais</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilumas">
             <feature>• Pagerinamas sistemos stabilumas</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Saugumo pataisa">
             <feature>• Sistemos saugumui užtikrinti įdiegta „Android“ saugumo pataisa (2026 m. sausio mėn.). Daugiau informacijos apie „Honor“ saugumo naujinius rasite mūsų svetainėje https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Pastabos" type="end">
             <feature>1. Šio naujinio įdiegimas neturės įtakos jūsų asmeniniams duomenims, tačiau prieš atnaujinant rekomenduojama sukurti atsarginę duomenų kopiją
2. Daugiau informacijos apie gaminio funkcijas rasite Patarimuose
3. Jei naujinimo metu kiltų bet kokių problemų, galite kreiptis į mus pagalbos paskambindami „Honor priežiūros karštąja linija arba apsilankydami „Honor“ klientų aptarnavimo centre</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1062" name="lv-lv">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo atjauninājumu galvenokārt ir uzlabota sistēmas veiktspēja. Atjauniniet, lai izbaudītu uzlabojumus</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistēma">
             <feature>• Atbalsta atvienošanos no Wi-Fi un paroles apskati</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bloķēšanas ekrāns">
             <feature>• Bloķēšanas ekrānā ir pieejams lielāks un izstiepts pulksteņa stils. Izmēģiniet to, atverot Iestatījumi > Sākuma ekrāns un stils > Pielāgoti > Pieskarieties pulkstenim, lai rediģētu</feature>
             <feature>• Tagad varat izmantot video kā fonu ar dinamiskiem efektiem, kas tiek atskaņoti līdz 10 sekundēm</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor un iPhone tālruņi tagad var savstarpēji apmainīties ar paziņojumu ziņām</feature>
             <feature>• Ja uz jūsu Mac datora ir instalēta jaunākā HONOR WorkStation versija, funkcija Sinhronizētie paziņojumi ļauj sinhronizēt paziņojumus ar jūsu Mac datoru</feature>
             <feature>• Instalējiet jaunāko HONOR WorkStation versiju savā Mac datorā, tad ar vienu pieskārienu OneTap pieskarieties, lai pārsūtītu attēlus, video, failus un citu saturu no Honor tālruņa uz Mac datoru</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Enerģijas patēriņš">
             <feature>• Optimizē lietošanas iespējas ar akumulatora darbības laiku dažos scenārijos</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitāte">
             <feature>• Uzlabo sistēmas stabilitāti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Drošības ielāps">
             <feature>• Sistēmas drošībai iekļauts Android drošības ielāps (2026. gada janvāris). Lai iegūtu papildinformāciju par Honor drošības atjauninājumiem, lūdzu, apmeklējiet mūsu vietni https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Piezīmes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Šī atjauninājuma instalēšana neietekmēs jūsu personas datus, taču joprojām ir ieteicams pirms atjaunināšanas dublēt datus
2. Lietotnē Padomi atklājiet vairāk par produkta funkcijām
3. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, varat saņemt mūsu palīdzību, zvanot uz Honor klientu apkalpošanas dienesta tālruni vai apmeklējot Honor klientu pakalpojumu centru.</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="mai-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, ई अपडेट मुख्य रूप सँ सिस्टमक कार्य-क्षमता केँ वर्धित करैत अछि। सुधार सभक आनंद लेबाक लेल अपडेट करू</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सिस्टम">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi सँ डिस्कनेक्ट करब आ पासवर्ड देखब केँ सपोर्ट करैत अछि</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="लॉक स्क्रीन">
             <feature>• लॉक स्क्रीन एकटा पैघ आ पसरल घड़ी शैली प्रदान करैत अछि। एहि मे जा एकरा आजमाउ: सेटिंग्स > होम स्क्रीन आ शैली > अनुकूलन > संपादित करबाक लेल घड़ी केँ टैप करू</feature>
             <feature>• आब अहाँ गतिशील प्रभाव सभ संग जे 10 सेकंड धरि चलैत अछि, वीडियो सभ केँ वॉलपेपर केर रूप में उपयोग कए सकैत छी</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor कनेक्ट">
             <feature>• आब Honor फोन आ iPhone सभ आपस मे अधिसूचना संदेश सभ साझा कए सकैत अछि</feature>
             <feature>• अहाँक Mac पर नवीनतम HONOR WorkStation इंस्टॉल भेला पर, कनेक्ट कयल अधिसूचना सभ अहाँ केँ अधिसूचना सभ केँ अपन Mac संग सिंक्रोनाइज करबाक सुविधा दैत अछि</feature>
             <feature>• अपन Mac पर HONOR WorkStation केर नवीनतम वर्जन इंस्टॉल करू, तकर बाद अहाँ OneTap केर उपयोग कए अपन Honor फोन सँ इमेज, वीडियो, फाइल सभ आ दोसर कंटेंट एकहि टैप मे अपन Mac पर ट्रांसफर कए सकैत छी</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="पावर खपत">
             <feature>•किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे बैटरीक आयु संग उपयोगकर्ताक अनुभव केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्थिरता">
             <feature>• सिस्टमक स्थिरता मे सुधार करैत अछि</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षा पैच">
             <feature>• सिस्टमक सुरक्षाक लेल Android सुरक्षा पैच (जनवरी 2026) समाविष्ट कयल गेल अछि। Honor सुरक्षा अपडेट सभक विषय मे आओर जानकारीक लेल, कृपाकए हमरासभक वेबसाइट केँ देखू: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोट्स" type="end">
             <feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा प्रभावित नहि होयत, मुदा तैयो अपडेट करए सँ पहिने अहाँ केँ डेटाक बैकअप लेबाक सुझाव देल जाइत अछि
2. टिप्स मे उत्पाद विशेषता सभ पर आओर जानकारी डिस्‍कवर करू
3. यदि अपडेट केर दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' अहाँ Honor सेवा हॉटलाइन केँ कॉल कए वा Honor सर्विस सेंटर जा कए हमरासभक मदति प्राप्त कए सकैत छी</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1153" name="mi-NZ">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>E te kaiwhakamahi aroha, ko tēnei whakahoutanga e whakarei ake ana i te mahinga pūnaha. Whakahōu ki te oaoa i te whakapai ake</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pūnaha">
             <feature>• Ka tautoko i te momotu i te Wi-Fi me te tiro i te kupuhipa</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Mata maukati">
             <feature>• Ka whakarato te mata maukati i tētahi kāhua karaka nui, roa hoki. Whakamātauria mā te haere ki: Ngā Tautuhinga > Mata kāinga &amp; kāhua > Ritenga ake > Pato ki te karaka hei whakatika</feature>
             <feature>• Ka taea inaianei te whakamahi i ngā ataata hei pepapātū, me ngā pānga ā-ōkawa ka purei mō te 10 hekona te roa</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tūhono Honor">
             <feature>• Ka taea e ngā waea Honor me ngā iPhone te tiri i ngā karere whakamōhiotanga ki a rātau tētahi atu</feature>
             <feature>• Ki te HONOR WorkStation hou tāuta i runga i tō Mac, Whakamōhiotanga Tūhono tukua ki a koe te tukutahi whakamōhiotanga ki tō Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Tāuta i te putanga hou o te HONOR WorkStation i runga i tō Mac, ka taea e koe te whakamahi i OneTap ki te whakawhiti ngā atahanga, ngā ataata, ngā kōnae, me tētahi atu ihirangi i tō waea Honor ki tō Mac ki te pato kotahi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Whakapetonga hiko">
             <feature>• Arotau ake i te wheako kaiwhakamahi ki te ora pūhiko i roto i ētahi tauari</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pūmautanga">
             <feature>• Ka whakapai ake i te pūmautanga o te pūnaha</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Āpure haumarutanga">
             <feature>• Kua whakaurua te pūrei haumarutanga Android (Hānuere 2026) mō te haumarutanga pūnaha. Mō ētahi anō mōhiohio mō ngā whakahōutanga Haumarutanga Honor, haere koa ki tā mātou paetukutuku https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Ngā Tuhipoka" type="end">
             <feature>1. Mā te tāuta i tēnei whakahōutanga e kore tō raraunga whaiaro e pāngia, engari e taunaki ana kia tāruatia ō raraunga i mua i te whakahōutanga
2. Tūhura mōhiohio ētahi anō mō ngā āhuahira o te hua i Ngā Aki
3. Mēnā ka pāngia koe e ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōutanga, ka taea e koe te tiki āwhina mā te waea atu ki te waeawera ratonga Honor, mā te toro atu rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki a Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1071" name="mk-mk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Почитуван кориснику, ова ажурирање главно ги подобрува перформансите на системот. Ажурирајте за да уживате во подобрувањата</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Систем">
             <feature>• Поддржува исклучување од Wi-Fi и прегледување на лозинката</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Екран на заклучен уред">
             <feature>• Заклучениот екран нуди поголем и проширен стил на часовник. Пробајте го така што ќе отидете во: Нагодување > Почетен екран и стил > Приспособено > Допрете го часовникот за да уредите</feature>
             <feature>• Сега може да користите видеа како заднина, со динамички ефекти што се емитуваат до 10 секунди</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Поврзување од Honor">
             <feature>• Телефоните Honor и iPhone сега можат да споделуваат пораки за известувања едни со други</feature>
             <feature>• Со најновата HONOR WorkStation инсталирана на вашиот Mac, Поврзани известувања ви овозможува да ги синхронизирате известувањата со вашиот Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Инсталирајте ја најновата верзија на HONOR WorkStation на вашиот Mac, а потоа можете да користите OneTap за пренос на слики, видеа, датотеки и друга содржина од вашиот Honor телефон на вашиот Mac со еден допир</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Потрошувачка на енергија">
             <feature>• Го оптимизира корисничкото искуство со траењето на батеријата во некои сценарија</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Стабилност">
             <feature>• Ја подобрува стабилноста на системот</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Безбедносна крпеница">
             <feature>• Вградена е безбедносна закрпа за Андроид (јануари 2026 година) за безбедноста на системот. За повеќе информации за ажурирањата за безбедност на Honor, посетете ја нашата веб-страница https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Белешки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да влијае врз вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува да направите резервна копија од податоците пред да ажурирате
2. Откријте повеќе информации за карактеристиките на производот во Совети
3. Ако наидете на какви било проблеми при ажурирањето, може да ја добиете нашата помош со повикување на телефонскиот број на службата на Honor или посета на сервисниот центар за корисници на Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1100" name="ml-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് പ്രധാനമായും സിസ്റ്റം പ്രകടനം മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു. മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തലുകൾ ആസ്വദിക്കാൻ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുക</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="സിസ്റ്റം">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi യിൽ നിന്ന് ഡിസ്‌കണക്റ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിനെയും പാസ്‌വേഡ് കാണുന്നതിനെയും പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കുന്നു</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ലോക്ക് സ്‌ക്രീൻ">
             <feature>• ലോക്ക് സ്‌ക്രീൻ വലുതും വിശാലവുമായ ഒരു ക്ലോക്ക് ശൈലി നൽകുന്നു. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്രമീകരണം > ഹോം സ്ക്രീനും ശൈലിയും > കസ്റ്റം > എഡിറ്റ് ചെയ്യാൻ ക്ലോക്കിൽ ടാപ്പ് ചെയ്യുക</feature>
             <feature>• നിങ്ങൾക്ക് ഇപ്പോൾ വീഡിയോകൾ 10 സെക്കന്റ് വരെ പ്ലേ ചെയ്യുന്ന ചലനാത്മക ഇഫക്റ്റുകൾ ഉള്ള വാൾപേപ്പറായി ഉപയോഗിക്കാവുന്നതാണ്</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor ഫോണുകൾക്കും iPhone-കൾക്കും ഇപ്പോൾ പരസ്‌പരം നോട്ടിഫിക്കേഷൻ മെസേജുകൾ പങ്കിടാൻ കഴിയും</feature>
             <feature>• നിങ്ങളുടെ Mac-ൽ ഏറ്റവും പുതിയ HONOR WorkStation ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്‌താൽ, നിങ്ങളുടെ Mac-ൽ നോട്ടിഫിക്കേഷനുകൾ സമന്വയിപ്പിക്കാൻ 'കണക്റ്റ് ചെയ്‌തിരിക്കുന്ന നോട്ടിഫിക്കേഷൻ' നിങ്ങളെ അനുവദിക്കുന്നു</feature>
             <feature>• നിങ്ങളുടെ Mac-ൽ HONOR WorkStation-ന്റെ ഏറ്റവും പുതിയ പതിപ്പ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്‌ത് കഴിഞ്ഞാൽ, നിങ്ങൾക്ക് OneTap ഉപയോഗിച്ച് വെറുമൊരു ടാപ്പിൽ നിങ്ങളുടെ Honor ഫോണിൽ നിന്ന് നിങ്ങളുടെ Mac-ലേക്ക് ഇമേജുകളും വീഡിയോകളും ഫയലുകളും മറ്റ് ഉള്ളടക്കവും കൈമാറാൻ കഴിയും</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="വൈദ്യുതി ഉപഭോഗം">
             <feature>• ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിൽ ബാറ്ററി ആയുസുമായി ബന്ധപ്പെട്ട ഉപയോക്തൃ അനുഭവം ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുന്നു</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="സ്ഥിരത">
             <feature>• സിസ്റ്റം സ്ഥിരത മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച്">
             <feature>• സിസ്റ്റം സുരക്ഷയ്‌ക്കായി Android സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് (ജനുവരി 2026) ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. Honor സുരക്ഷാ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾക്ക്, ഞങ്ങളുടെ വെബ്‌സൈറ്റ് സന്ദർശിക്കുക: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ ബാധിക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിന് മുമ്പായി നിങ്ങളുടെ ഡാറ്റ ബാക്കപ്പ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു
2. 'നുറുങ്ങുകൾ' എന്നതിൽ ഉൽപ്പന്ന സവിശേഷതകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾ കണ്ടെത്തുക
3. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ നിങ്ങൾക്ക് എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, Honor സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ Honor ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്‌ത് ഞങ്ങളുടെ സഹായം കരസ്ഥമാക്കാവുന്നതാണ്</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1104" name="mn-MN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэ шинэчлэлтээр голчлон системийн гүйцэтгэлийг сайжрууллаа. Шинэчлээд, сайжруулсан хэрэглээг мэдрээрэй</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Систем">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi-н холболтыг тасалж, нууц үг харахыг дэмжинэ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Түгжээ дэлгэц">
             <feature>• Түгжээ дэлгэц дээр цагны илүү том, сунгасан хэв маяг ашиглах боломжтой боллоо. Тохиргоо > Үндсэн дэлгэц, хэв маяг > Тусгай > Цаг дээр товшиж засах хэсгээс туршина уу</feature>
             <feature>• Одоо видеог 10 секунд хүртэл тоглуулж болох динамик эффект бүхий арын зураг болгох боломжтой боллоо</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor утас ба iPhone хоорондоо мэдэгдлийн зурвас хуваалцах боломжтой боллоо</feature>
             <feature>• Та Mac компьютер дээрээ HONOR WorkStation-ын хамгийн сүүлийн хувилбарыг суулгаснаас Холбоотой мэдэгдлийг ашиглан Mac компьютертой мэдэгдлээ синхрончлох боломжтой</feature>
             <feature>• Mac компьютер дээрээ HONOR WorkStation-ын хамгийн сүүлийн хувилбарыг суулгаад OneTap-г ашиглан Honor утаснаасаа ганц товшилтоор зураг, видео, файл, бусад контентыг Mac компьютер луугаа шилжүүлээрэй</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Эрчим хүчний хэрэглээ">
             <feature>• Зарим тохиолдол дахь хэрэглэгчийн батарейн ашиглалтын хэрэглээг оновчлов</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Тогтвортой байдал">
             <feature>• Системийн тогтвортой байдлыг сайжруулсан</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Хамгаалалтын нөхөөс">
             <feature>• Системийн хамгаалалтад зориулж Андройд хамгаалалтын нөхөн засварыг (2026 оны нэгдүгээр сар) оруулав. Honor-н хамгаалалтын шинэчлэлтийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэл авах бол манай дараах вебсайтаар зочилно уу: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Тэмдэглэл" type="end">
             <feature>1. Энэхүү шинэчлэлтийг суулгахад таны хувийн мэдээлэлд нөлөөлөхгүй ч шинэчлэхээс өмнө өгөгдлөө нөөцлөхийг зөвлөж байна
2. Зөвлөгөө дотроос бүтээгдэхүүний онцлогийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэлтэй танилцана уу
3. Шинэчлэх үед асуудал гарвал Honor-н үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгах буюу Honor-н хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төвд зочилж болно</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1102" name="mr-in">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, हे अद्यतन प्रामुख्याने सिस्टम कार्यप्रदर्शन वाढवते. सुधारणांचा आनंद घेण्यासाठी अद्यतनित करा</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सिस्टम">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi वरून डिस्कनेक्ट करणे आणि संकेतशब्द पाहणे याला समर्थन देते</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="लॉक स्क्रीन">
             <feature>• लॉक स्क्रीन एक मोठी आणि ताणलेली घड्याळ शैली देते. येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पहा: सेटिंग्ज > मुख्य स्क्रीन आणि शैली > सानुकूल > संपादित करण्यासाठी घड्याळावर टॅप करा</feature>
             <feature>• आता आपण वॉलपेपर म्हणून व्हिडिओज वापरू शकता, ज्यात 10 सेकंदांपर्यंत चालणारे डायनॅमिक प्रभाव असतील</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor कनेक्ट">
             <feature>• आता Honor फोन्स आणि iPhones एकमेकांशी सूचना संदेश सामायिक करू शकतात</feature>
             <feature>• आपल्या Mac वर नवीनतम HONOR वर्कस्टेशन स्थापित केल्यामुळे, कनेक्ट केलेल्या सूचना आपल्याला आपल्या Macवर सूचना सिंक्रोनाइझ करण्याची अनुमती देते</feature>
             <feature>• आपल्या Mac वर HONOR वर्कस्टेशनची नवीनतम आवृत्ती स्थापित करा, त्यानंतर आपण OneTap वापरून आपल्या Honor फोनवरून प्रतिमा, व्हिडिओ, फाइल्स आणि इतर सामग्री एकाच टॅपमध्ये आपल्या Mac वर स्थानांतरित करू शकता</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="पॉवर वापर">
             <feature>• काही परिस्थितींमध्ये बॅटरी लाइफसह वापरकर्त्याचा अनुभव ऑप्टिमाइझ करते</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्थिरता">
             <feature>• सिस्टम स्थिरता सुधारते</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षितता पॅच">
             <feature>• सिस्टम सुरक्षिततेसाठी Android सुरक्षितता पॅच (जाने 2026) समाविष्ट करण्यात आला आहे. Honor सुरक्षितता अद्यतनांबद्दलच्या अधिक माहितीसाठी, कृपया आमच्या वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1 वर जा</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोट्स" type="end">
             <feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्‍थापित केल्याने आपल्या वैयक्तिक डेटावर परिणाम होणार नाही, परंतु तरीही अद्यतनित करण्यापूर्वी आपल्या डेटाचा बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते
2. उत्पादन वैशिष्ट्यांबद्दल अधिक माहिती Tips मध्ये शोधा
3. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, आपण Honor सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करून किंवा Honor ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जाऊन आमची मदत घेऊ शकता</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1086" name="ms-my">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini ini meningkatkan prestasi sistem terutamanya. Kemas kini untuk menikmati penambahbaikan tersebut</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistem">
             <feature>• Menyokong pemutusan sambungan daripada Wi-Fi dan melihat kata laluan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Skrin kunci">
             <feature>• Skrin kunci menawarkan gaya jam yang lebih besar dan memanjang. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Skrin utama &amp; gaya > Tersuai > Ketik jam untuk mengedit</feature>
             <feature>• Anda kini boleh menggunakan video sebagai hias latar, dengan kesan dinamik yang dimainkan sehingga 10 saat</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Telefon Honor dan iPhone kini boleh berkongsi mesej pemberitahuan antara satu sama lain</feature>
             <feature>• Dengan HONOR WorkStation terkini yang dipasang pada Mac anda, Pemberitahuan Bersambung membolehkan anda menyegerakkan pemberitahuan ke Mac anda</feature>
             <feature>• Pasang versi terkini HONOR WorkStation pada Mac anda, kemudian anda boleh menggunakan OneTap untuk memindahkan imej, video, fail dan kandungan lain daripada telefon Honor anda ke Mac anda dengan satu ketikan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Penggunaan kuasa">
             <feature>• Mengoptimumkan pengalaman pengguna dengan hayat bateri dalam beberapa senario</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kestabilan">
             <feature>• Meningkatkan kestabilan sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tampalan keselamatan">
             <feature>• Tampalan keselamatan Android (Jan 2026) telah dimasukkan untuk tujuan keselamatan sistem. Untuk mendapatkan maklumat lanjut tentang kemas kini Keselamatan Honor, sila lawati laman web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Nota" type="end">
             <feature>1. Memasang kemas kini ini tidak akan menjejaskan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda masih disyorkan agar menyandarkan data sebelum melakukan kemas kini
2. Temui maklumat lanjut tentang ciri produk dalam Tip
3. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, anda boleh mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi talian penting perkhidmatan Honor atau melawati pusat khidmat pelanggan Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1109" name="my-mm">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် စနစ် စွမ်းဆောင်ရည်ကို အဓိက မြှင့်တင်ပေးသည်။ တိုးတက်ကောင်းမွန်အောင်လုပ်ထားသည်များကို သုံးစွဲခံစားရန် အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="စနစ်">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi နှင့် ချိတ်ဆက်မှုဖြုတ်ခြင်းနှင့် စကားဝှက်ကြည့်ခြင်းတို့ကို ပံ့ပိုးပေးပါသည်</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="လော့ခ်မျက်နှာပြင်">
             <feature>• လော့ခ်မျက်နှာပြင်သည် ပိုမိုကြီးမားကျယ်ပြန့်သော နာရီစတိုင်ကို ပေးအပ်သည်။ ဖော်ပြပါအတိုင်းသွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ဆက်တင် > ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်နှင့် ပုံစံ > စိတ်ကြိုက် > နာရီကိုနှိပ်ပြီး တည်းဖြတ်ရန်</feature>
             <feature>• ယခုအခါ သင်သည် ဗီဒီယိုများကို နောက်ခံပုံအဖြစ် အသုံးပြုနိုင်ပြီး ရွေ့လျား အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်များကို 10 စက္ကန့်ကြာ ပြသပေးသည်</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ချိတ်ဆက်မှု">
             <feature>• ယခုအခါ Honor ဖုန်းနှင့် iPhone များသည် အသိပေး အချက်ပြမှု မက်ဆေ့ချ်များကို အချင်းချင်း မျှဝေနိုင်ပါပြီ</feature>
             <feature>• သင်၏ Mac တွင် နောက်ဆုံးထွက် HONOR WorkStation ကို ထည့်သွင်းထားပါက ချိတ်ဆက်ထားသည့် အသိပေး အချက်ပြမှုများကို အသုံးပြု၍ အသိပေး အချက်ပြမှုများကို သင်၏ Mac သို့ ချိန်ကိုက်နိုင်သည်</feature>
             <feature>• သင်၏ Mac တွင် HONOR WorkStation နောက်ဆုံးထွက် Version ကို ထည့်သွင်းပြီးနောက် တစ်ချက်နှိပ် လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်ကို အသုံးပြု၍ ရုပ်ပုံများ၊ ဗီဒီယိုများ၊ ဖိုင်များနှင့် အခြားအကြောင်းအရာများကို တစ်ချက်နှိပ်ရုံဖြင့် သင်၏ Honor ဖုန်းမှ Mac သို့ လွှဲပြောင်းနိုင်ပါသည်</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ပါဝါ သုံးစွဲမှု">
             <feature>• အချို့သော အခြေ‌အနေများတွင် ဘက်ထရီသက်တမ်းဆိုင်ရာ သုံးစွဲသူအတွေ့အကြုံကို အကောင်းဆုံး မြှင့်တင်လိုက်ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="တည်ငြိမ်မှု">
             <feature>• စနစ် ပိုမိုတည်ငြိမ်စေရန် မြှင့်တင်ပေးသည်</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ">
             <feature>• စနစ်လုံခြုံရေးအတွက် Android လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ (ဇန်နဝါရီ 2026) ကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ Honor လုံခြုံရေး အပ်ဒိတ်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို သိရှိရန် ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ ဖော်ပြပါဝက်ဘ်ဆိုဒ်သို့ သွားရောက်ကြည့်ရှုပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="မှတ်ချက်" type="end">
             <feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းက သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာကို ထိခိုက်စေမည်မဟုတ်သော်လည်း အပ်ဒိတ်မလုပ်မီ သင့်ဒေတာကို ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ထားရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်
2. Tips တွင် ကုန်ပစ္စည်း လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို လေ့လာပါ
3. အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်နေစဉ် ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခုနှင့် ကြုံရပါက Honor ဝန်ဆောင်မှု ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ဖုန်းခေါ်၍ သို့မဟုတ် Honor ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားရောက်၍ အကူအညီရယူနိုင်သည်</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1109" name="my-zg">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ စနစ္ စြမ္းေဆာင္ရည္ကို အဓိက ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးသည္။ တိုးတက္ေကာင္းမြန္ေအာင္လုပ္ထားသည္မ်ားကို သုံးစြဲခံစားရန္ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="စနစ္">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi ႏွင့္ ခ်ိတ္ဆက္မႈျဖဳတ္ျခင္းႏွင့္ စကားဝွက္ၾကည့္ျခင္းတို႔ကို ပံ့ပိုးေပးပါသည္</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ေလာ့ခ္မ်က္ႏွာျပင္">
             <feature>• ေလာ့ခ္မ်က္ႏွာျပင္သည္ ပိုမိုႀကီးမားက်ယ္ျပန႔္ေသာ နာရီစတိုင္ကို ေပးအပ္သည္။ ေဖာ္ျပပါအတိုင္းသြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ဆက္တင္ > ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ႏွင့္ ပုံစံ > စိတ္ၾကိဳက္ > နာရီကိုႏွိပ္ၿပီး တည္းျဖတ္ရန္</feature>
             <feature>• ယခုအခါ သင္သည္ ဗီဒီယိုမ်ားကို ေနာက္ခံပုံအျဖစ္ အသုံးျပဳႏိုင္ၿပီး ေ႐ြ႕လ်ား အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္မ်ားကို 10 စကၠန႔္ၾကာ ျပသေပးသည္</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ခ်ိတ္ဆက္မႈ">
             <feature>• ယခုအခါ Honor ဖုန္းႏွင့္ iPhone မ်ားသည္ အသိေပး အခ်က္ျပမႈ မက္ေဆ့ခ်္မ်ားကို အခ်င္းခ်င္း မွ်ေဝႏိုင္ပါၿပီ</feature>
             <feature>• သင္၏ Mac တြင္ ေနာက္ဆုံးထြက္ HONOR WorkStation ကို ထည့္သြင္းထားပါက ခ်ိတ္ဆက္ထားသည့္ အသိေပး အခ်က္ျပမႈမ်ားကို အသုံးျပဳ၍ အသိေပး အခ်က္ျပမႈမ်ားကို သင္၏ Mac သို႔ ခ်ိန္ကိုက္ႏိုင္သည္</feature>
             <feature>• သင္၏ Mac တြင္ HONOR WorkStation ေနာက္ဆုံးထြက္ Version ကို ထည့္သြင္းၿပီးေနာက္ တစ္ခ်က္ႏွိပ္ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္ကို အသုံးျပဳ၍ ႐ုပ္ပုံမ်ား၊ ဗီဒီယိုမ်ား၊ ဖိုင္မ်ားႏွင့္ အျခားအေၾကာင္းအရာမ်ားကို တစ္ခ်က္ႏွိပ္႐ုံျဖင့္ သင္၏ Honor ဖုန္းမွ Mac သို႔ လႊဲေျပာင္းႏိုင္ပါသည္</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ပါဝါ သုံးစြဲမႈ">
             <feature>• အခ်ိဳ႕ေသာ အေျခ‌အေနမ်ားတြင္ ဘက္ထရီသက္တမ္းဆိုင္ရာ သုံးစြဲသူအေတြ႕အႀကဳံကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ျမႇင့္တင္လိုက္ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="တည္ၿငိမ္မႈ">
             <feature>• စနစ္ ပိုမိုတည္ၿငိမ္ေစရန္ ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးသည္</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="လုံျခံဳေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ">
             <feature>• စနစ္လုံၿခဳံေရးအတြက္ Android လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ (ဇန္နဝါရီ 2026) ကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ Honor လုံၿခဳံေရး အပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို သိရွိရန္ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ ေဖာ္ျပပါဝက္ဘ္ဆိုဒ္သို႔ သြားေရာက္ၾကည့္ရႈပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="မွတ္ခ်က္" type="end">
             <feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းက သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာကို ထိခိုက္ေစမည္မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း အပ္ဒိတ္မလုပ္မီ သင့္ေဒတာကို ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ထားရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္
2. Tips တြင္ ကုန္ပစၥည္း လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို ေလ့လာပါ
3. အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ေနစဥ္ ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခုႏွင့္ ႀကဳံရပါက Honor ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈ ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ဖုန္းေခၚ၍ သို႔မဟုတ္ Honor ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားေရာက္၍ အကူအညီရယူႏိုင္သည္</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1044" name="nb-no">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Kjære bruker. Denne oppdateringen forbedrer hovedsakelig systemytelsen. Oppdater for å få forbedringene</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="System">
             <feature>• Støtter frakobling fra Wi-Fi og visning av passordet</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Låseskjerm">
             <feature>• Låseskjermen tilbyr en større og strukket klokkestil. Prøv den ved å gå til: Innstillinger > Startskjerm og stil > Egendefinert > Trykk på klokken for å redigere den</feature>
             <feature>• Du kan nå bruke videoer som bakgrunn, med dynamiske effekter som spilles av i opptil 10 sekunder</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Tilkobling">
             <feature>• Honor-telefoner og iPhoner kan nå dele varslingsmeldinger med hverandre</feature>
             <feature>• Med den nyeste versjonen av HONOR WorkStation installert på Macen, kan du bruke Tilkoblede varslinger til å synkronisere varslinger til Macen</feature>
             <feature>• Installer den nyeste versjonen av HONOR WorkStation på Macen, deretter kan du bruke OneTap til å overføre bilder, videoer, filer og annet innhold fra Honor-telefonen til Macen med ett enkelt trykk</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Batteribruk">
             <feature>• Optimerer brukeropplevelsen med batterilevetid i enkelte tilfeller</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitet">
             <feature>• Gjør systemet mer stabilt</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sikkerhetsoppdatering">
             <feature>• Android-sikkerhetsoppdatering (januar 2026) er integrert for systemsikkerhet. Hvis du vil ha mer informasjon om Honor-sikkerhetsoppdateringer, kan du gå til nettstedet vårt: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Merknader" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installeringen av denne oppdateringen påvirker ikke personopplysningene dine, men det anbefales likevel å sikkerhetskopiere dataene dine før du oppdaterer
2. Finn mer informasjon om produktfunksjoner i Tips
3. Hvis det oppstår problemer under oppdateringen, kan du få hjelp ved å ringe Honors kundeservice eller gå til Honors kundeservicesenter</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1121" name="ne-np">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, यो अपडेटले मुख्य गरी प्रणालीको कार्यसम्पादन परिष्कार गर्छ । सुधार गरिएका सुविधाहरूको आनन्द लिन अपडेट गर्नुहोस्</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="प्रणाली">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi बाट डिस्कनेक्ट गर्ने र पासवर्ड हेर्ने सुविधा उपलब्ध गराउँछ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="लक स्क्रिन">
             <feature>• लक स्क्रिनमा घडीका अझ ठुला र तन्काइएका शैलीहरू उपलब्ध छन् । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > गृह स्क्रिन र शैली > अनुकूलन > सम्पादन गर्न घडीमा ट्याप गर्नुहोस्</feature>
             <feature>• तपाईं अब 10 सेकेन्डसम्म प्ले हुने गतिशील प्रभावहरू प्रयोग गरी भिडियोहरूलाई वालपेपरका रूपमा प्रयोग गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor फोनहरू र iPhone हरू अब एक-आपसमा सूचनाका म्यासेजहरू सेयर गर्न सक्छन्</feature>
             <feature>• Mac मा HONOR WorkStation को नवीनतम संस्करण इन्स्टल गरेपछि तपाईं जडान गरिएका सूचनाहरूका सहायताले Mac मा सूचनाहरू समक्रमण गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ</feature>
             <feature>आफ्नो Mac मा HONOR WorkStation को नवीनतम संस्करण स्थापना गर्नुहोस्। त्यसपछि तपाईं आफ्नो Honor फोनमा भएका फोटो, भिडियो, फाइलहरू र अन्य सामग्री एक ट्याप गरेकै भरमा Mac मा ट्रान्स्फर गर्न OneTap प्रयोग गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="पावर खपत">
             <feature>• केही परिदृश्यहरूमा ब्याट्री जीवनको साथ प्रयोगकर्ता अनुभवलाई अनुकूलित गर्दछ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="स्थिरता">
             <feature>• प्रणालीको स्थिरता सुधार गर्छ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="सुरक्षा प्याच">
             <feature>• एन्ड्रोइड सुरक्षा प्याच (जनवरी 2026) प्रणाली सुरक्षाका लागि समावेश गरिएको छ । Honor सुरक्षा अपडेटहरूबारे थप जानकारीका लागि कृपया हाम्रो वेबसाइटमा जानुहोस्: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="नोटहरू" type="end">
             <feature>1. तपाईंले यो एप स्थापना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटामा कुनै प्रभाव नपर्ने भए पनि तपाईंलाई अपडेट गर्नुअघि आफ्नो डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ
2. सुझावहरूमा गई उत्पादनका सुविधाहरूका बारेमा थप जानकारी हेर्नुहोस्
3. अपडेटको क्रममा तपाईंले कुनै समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईं Honor सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गरेर वा Honor ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा गएर हाम्रो मद्दत प्राप्त गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ ।</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1043" name="nl-nl">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Beste gebruiker, deze update verbetert vooral de systeemprestaties. Werk bij om van de verbeteringen te genieten</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Systeem">
             <feature>• Ondersteunt het verbreken van de wifiverbinding en het bekijken van het wachtwoord</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Vergrendelscherm">
             <feature>• Het vergrendelscherm biedt een grotere en uitgerekte klokstijl. Probeer het uit via: Instellingen > Startscherm en stijl > Aangepast > Tik op de klok om te bewerken</feature>
             <feature>• U kunt nu video's als achtergrond gebruiken, met dynamische effecten die tot 10 seconden kunnen worden afgespeeld</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor-telefoons en iPhones kunnen nu meldingsberichten met elkaar delen</feature>
             <feature>• Als het nieuwste HONOR WorkStation op uw Mac is geïnstalleerd, zorgt Verbonden meldingen ervoor dat u meldingen kunt synchroniseren met uw Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Installeer de nieuwste versie van het HONOR WorkStation op uw Mac, dan kunt u OneTap gebruiken om met één tik afbeeldingen, video's, bestanden en andere inhoud van uw Honor-telefoon naar uw Mac over te dragen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Energieverbruik">
             <feature>• Optimaliseert de gebruikerservaring met de levensduur van de batterij in bepaalde scenario's</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabiliteit">
             <feature>• Verbetert de systeemstabiliteit</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Beveiligingspatch">
             <feature>• Er is een Android-beveiligingspatch (januari 2026) opgenomen voor systeembeveiliging. Voor meer informatie over Honor-beveiligingsupdates kunt u terecht op onze website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notities" type="end">
             <feature>1. Het installeren van deze update heeft geen invloed op uw persoonlijke gegevens, maar het wordt nog steeds aanbevolen om een back-up van uw gegevens te maken voordat u deze update uitvoert
2. Ontdek meer informatie over productfuncties in Tips
3. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, kunt u onze hulp krijgen door de Honor-servicehotline te bellen of naar het Honor-klantenservicecentrum te gaan</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1096" name="or-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ମୁଖ୍ୟତଃ ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ର କାର୍ଯ୍ୟଦକ୍ଷତାକୁ ବଢାଏ। ଉନ୍ନତିଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଉପଭୋଗ କରିବାକୁ ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରନ୍ତୁ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌">
             <feature>• Wi-Fiରୁ ବିଚ୍ଛିନ୍ନ ହେବା ଏବଂ ପାସୱାର୍ଡ ଦେଖିବା ସମର୍ଥନ କରେ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ଲକ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍">
             <feature>• ଲକ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ଏକ ବଡ଼ ଏବଂ ବିସ୍ତାରିତ ଘଣ୍ଟା ଶୈଳୀ ପ୍ରଦାନ କରେ। ଏଠାକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାକୁ ବ୍ୟବହାର କରି ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ଓ ଷ୍ଟାଇଲ୍ > କଷ୍ଟମ୍ > ସମ୍ପାଦନ କରିବାକୁ ଘଣ୍ଟାକୁ ଟାପ୍ କରନ୍ତୁ</feature>
             <feature>• ଆପଣ ଏବେ ଭିଡ଼ିଓଗୁଡ଼ିକୁ ୱାଲପେପର ଭାବରେ ଡାଇନାମିକ୍ ଇଫେକ୍ଟ ସହିତ ବ୍ୟବହାର କରିପାରିବେ, ଯାହା 10 ସେକେଣ୍ଡ ପର୍ଯ୍ୟନ୍ତ ଚାଲିଥାଏ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ସଂଯୋଗ">
             <feature>• Honor ଫୋନ୍ ଏବଂ iPhones ଏବେ ପରସ୍ପର ସହିତ ବିଜ୍ଞପ୍ତି ମେସେଜଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଶେୟାର କରିପାରିବେ</feature>
             <feature>• ଆପଣଙ୍କର Macରେ ନୂବୀନତମ HONOR WorkStation ସଂସ୍ଥାପିତ ହେବା ସହିତ, ସଂଯୋଜିତ ବିଜ୍ଞପ୍ତିଗୁଡିକ ଆପଣଙ୍କୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କର Macରେ ବିଜ୍ଞପ୍ତିଗୁଡିକୁ ସିଙ୍କ୍ କରିବାକୁ ଅନୁମତି ଦିଏ</feature>
             <feature>• ଆପଣଙ୍କ Macରେ HONOR WorkStationର ନବୀନତମ ସଂସ୍କରଣ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରନ୍ତୁ, ତାପରେ ଆପଣ OneTap ବ୍ୟବହାର କରି ଆପଣଙ୍କ Honor ଫୋନ୍‌ରୁ ଗୋଟିଏ ଟାପ୍‌ରେ ଆପଣଙ୍କ Macକୁ ପ୍ରତିଛବି, ଭିଡ଼ିଓ, ଫାଇଲ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଏବଂ ଅନ୍ୟାନ୍ୟ ବିଷୟବସ୍ତୁ ଟ୍ରାନ୍ସଫର କରିପାରିବେ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ପାୱାର୍ ଖର୍ଚ୍ଚ">
             <feature>• କିଛି ପରିସ୍ଥିତିରେ ବ୍ୟାଟେରୀ ଲାଇଫ୍ ସହିତ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ଅଭିଜ୍ଞତାକୁ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍ କରେ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ସ୍ଥିରତା">
             <feature>• ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ ସ୍ଥିରତା ଉନ୍ନତ କରେ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌">
             <feature>• Android ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ (ଜନୁୟାରୀ 2026) ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପାଇଁ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି। Honor ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ବିଷୟରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି ଆମ ୱେବସାଇଟ୍‌ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1 ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ପ୍ରଭାବିତ ହେବ ନାହିଁ, ତଥାପି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରିବା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡାଟାର ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି
2. ଟିପ୍ସରେ ଉତ୍ପାଦ ବିଶେଷତାଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଉପରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ଆବିଷ୍କାର କରନ୍ତୁ
3. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରିବା ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଆପଣ Honor ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌କୁ କଲ୍‌ କରି କିମ୍ବା Honor ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଇ, ଆମ ସହାୟତା ପାଇପାରିବେ</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1094" name="pa-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਮੁੱਖ ਤੌਰ 'ਤੇ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੀ ਕਾਰਗੁਜ਼ਾਰੀ ਨੂੰ ਬਿਹਤਰ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਸੁਧਾਰਾਂ ਦਾ ਅਨੰਦ ਲੈਣ ਲਈ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰੋ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਸਿਸਟਮ">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi ਤੋਂ ਡਿਸਕਨੈਕਟ ਕਰਨ ਅਤੇ ਪਾਸਵਰਡ ਵੇਖਣ ਦਾ ਸਮਰਥਨ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਲੌਕ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ">
             <feature>• ਲੌਕ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਘੜੀ ਦੀ ਵੱਡੀ ਅਤੇ ਫੈਲੀ ਹੋਈ ਸ਼ੈਲੀ ਪੇਸ਼ ਕਰਦੀ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ। ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਅਤੇ ਸ਼ੈਲੀ > ਕਸਟਮ > ਸੋਧ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਘੜੀ 'ਤੇ ਟੈਪ ਕਰੋ</feature>
             <feature>• ਹੁਣ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਵੀਡੀਓ ਨੂੰ ਵਾਲਪੇਪਰ ਵਜੋਂ ਵਰਤ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ, ਜਿਸ ਵਿੱਚ ਡਾਇਨਾਮਿਕ ਇਫੈਕਟ 10 ਸਕਿੰਟ ਤੱਕ ਚੱਲਦੇ ਹਨ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor ਕਨੈਕਟ">
             <feature>• Honor ਫ਼ੋਨ ਅਤੇ iPhones ਹੁਣ ਇੱਕ-ਦੂਜੇ ਨਾਲ ਸੂਚਨਾ ਸੁਨੇਹੇ ਸਾਂਝੇ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੇ ਹਨ</feature>
             <feature>• ਤੁਹਾਡੇ Mac 'ਤੇ ਨਵੀਨਤਮ HONOR ਵਰਕਸਟੇਸ਼ਨ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਹੋਣ 'ਤੇ, ਕਨੈਕਟ ਕੀਤੀਆਂ ਸੂਚਨਾਵਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਤੁਹਾਡੀਆਂ ਸੂਚਨਾਵਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ Mac ਨਾਲ ਸਿੰਕ ਕਰਨ ਦੀ ਇਜਾਜ਼ਤ ਦਿੰਦੀਆਂ ਹਨ</feature>
             <feature>• ਆਪਣੇ Mac ਉੱਤੇ HONOR ਵਰਕਸਟੇਸ਼ਨ ਦਾ ਨਵੀਨਤਮ ਸੰਸਕਰਣ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰੋ, ਫਿਰ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਆਪਣੇ Honor ਫ਼ੋਨ ਤੋਂ ਆਪਣੇ Mac 'ਤੇ ਚਿੱਤਰਾਂ, ਵੀਡੀਓ, ਫ਼ਾਈਲਾਂ, ਅਤੇ ਹੋਰ ਸਮੱਗਰੀ ਨੂੰ ਇੱਕ ਟੈਪ ਨਾਲ ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ OneTap ਨੂੰ ਵਰਤ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਪਾਵਰ ਖਪਤ">
             <feature>• ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਬੈਟਰੀ ਸਮਰੱਥਾ ਦੇ ਨਾਲ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਉਂਦਾ ਹੈ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਸਥਿਰਤਾ">
             <feature>• ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੀ ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੁਧਾਰ ਕਰਦੀ ਹੈ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ">
             <feature>• ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਲਈ Android ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ (ਜਨ 2026) ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। Honor ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਲਈ, ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਵੈੱਬਸਾਈਟ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ਨੋਟਸ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ 'ਤੇ ਕੋਈ ਅਸਰ ਨਹੀਂ ਪਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਹਾਲੇ ਵੀ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਦਾ ਬੈਕ ਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ
2. ਸੁਝਾਅ ਐਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਉਤਪਾਦ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾਵਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਦੀ ਖੋਜ ਕਰੋ
3. ਜੇਕਰ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਤੁਸੀਂ Honor ਸੇਵਾ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰ ਕੇ ਜਾਂ Honor ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਮਦਦ ਲੈ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1045" name="pl-pl">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Szanowny użytkowniku, ta aktualizacja w głównej mierze podnosi wydajność systemu. Zainstaluj ją, aby korzystać z ulepszeń</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="System">
             <feature>• Obsługuje rozłączanie z siecią Wi-Fi i wyświetlanie hasła</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ekran blokady">
             <feature>• Teraz zegar na ekranie blokady może być większy i rozciągnięty. Wypróbuj go, wybierając Ustawienia > Ekran główny i styl > Niestandardowe, a następnie dotknij zegara, aby go edytować</feature>
             <feature>• Teraz możesz używać filmów jako tapet z dynamicznymi efektami odtwarzanymi maksymalnie 10 sekund</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Połączenie Honor">
             <feature>• Telefony Honor i iPhone'y mogą teraz udostępniać wiadomości powiadomień między sobą</feature>
             <feature>• Gdy zainstalujesz najnowszą wersję HONOR WorkStation na komputerze Mac, Połączone powiadomienia umożliwią synchronizowanie powiadomień z komputerem Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Zainstaluj najnowszą wersję HONOR WorkStation na komputerze Mac, aby używać OneTap do transferowania obrazów, filmów i innej zawartości z telefonu Honor na komputer Mac jednym dotknięciem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zużycie energii">
             <feature>• Optymalizuje komfort użytkowania poprzez czas pracy baterii w określonych sytuacjach</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilność">
             <feature>• Poprawiono stabilność systemu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Poprawka zabezpieczeń">
             <feature>• Aktualizacja zawiera Poprawkę zabezpieczeń systemu Android (styczeń 2026 r.). Więcej informacji o aktualizacjach zabezpieczeń urządzeń Honor można znaleźć w naszej witrynie internetowej: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notatki" type="end">
             <feature>1. Ta aktualizacja nie ma wpływu na Twoje dane osobowe, jednak przed jej zainstalowaniem zaleca się wykonanie kopii zapasowej danych
2. Więcej informacji o funkcjach produktu znajdziesz w Poradach
3. Jeśli podczas aktualizacji napotkasz jakiekolwiek problemy, możesz uzyskać pomoc, dzwoniąc na infolinię serwisu Honor lub odwiedzając punkt serwisowy Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1046" name="pt-br">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Prezado(a) usuário(a), essa atualização aprimora principalmente o desempenho do sistema. Atualize para aproveitar as melhorias</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistema">
             <feature>• Suporta a desconexão do Wi-Fi e a visualização da senha</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tela de bloqueio">
             <feature>• A tela de bloqueio oferece um estilo de relógio maior e alongado. Experimente acessando: Configurações > Tela inicial e estilo > Personalizado > Toque no relógio para editar</feature>
             <feature>• Agora você pode usar vídeos como o papel de parede, com efeitos dinâmicos que são reproduzidos por até 10 segundos</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Os telefones Honor e os iPhones agora podem compartilhar mensagens de notificação entre eles</feature>
             <feature>• Com o HONOR WorkStation mais recente instalado em seu Mac, as Notificações conectadas permitem que você sincronize as notificações com seu Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Instale a versão mais recente do HONOR WorkStation em seu Mac e você poderá usar o OneTap para transferir imagens, vídeos, arquivos e outro conteúdo de seu telefone Honor para seu Mac com um único toque</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Consumo de energia">
             <feature>• Otimiza a experiência do usuário em relação à duração da bateria em alguns cenários</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilidade">
             <feature>• Melhora a estabilidade do sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch de segurança">
             <feature>• Patch de segurança do Android (janeiro de 2026) incorporado para a segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da Honor, visite nosso site: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. A instalação desta atualização não afetará os dados pessoais, mas ainda é recomendável fazer backup dos dados antes de atualizar
2. Descubra mais informações sobre os recursos do produto em Dicas
3. Se você encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, poderá obter nossa ajuda ligando para a Linha de atendimento de serviço da Honor ou acessando a Central de serviços ao cliente da Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2070" name="pt-pt">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Caro utilizador, esta atualização melhora principalmente o desempenho do sistema. Atualize para aproveitar as melhorias</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistema">
             <feature>• Suporta desligar do Wi-Fi e ver a palavra-passe</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ecrã de bloqueio">
             <feature>• O ecrã de bloqueio oferece um estilo de relógio maior e alongado. Experimente-o, acedendo a: Definições > Ecrã inicial e estilo > Personalizado > Tocar no relógio para editar</feature>
             <feature>• Agora pode usar vídeos como papel de parede, com efeitos dinâmicos que são reproduzidos durante e até 10 segundos</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Os telefones Honor e iPhones agora podem partilhar mensagens de notificação entre si</feature>
             <feature>• Com a versão mais recente da HONOR WorkStation instalada no seu Mac, as Notificações ligadas permitem-lhe sincronizar notificações com o seu Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Instale a versão mais recente da HONOR WorkStation no seu Mac e, de seguida, utilize o OneTap para transferir imagens, vídeos, ficheiros e outros conteúdos do seu telefone Honor para o seu Mac com um único toque</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Consumo de energia">
             <feature>• Otimiza a experiência do utilizador com a duração da bateria em alguns cenários</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Estabilidade">
             <feature>• Melhora a estabilidade do sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Correção de segurança">
             <feature>• A correção de segurança do Android (janeiro de 2026) foi incorporada para a segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da Honor, visite o nosso website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não afetará os seus dados pessoais, mas ainda assim é recomendável efetuar uma cópia de segurança dos seus dados antes de atualizar
2. Descobrir mais informações sobre as funcionalidades do produto em Sugestões
3. Se encontrar quaisquer problemas durante a atualização, pode obter ajuda ligando para a linha direta de assistência da Honor ou visitando o centro de apoio ao cliente da Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1048" name="ro-ro">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Stimate utilizator, această actualizare îmbunătățește în principal performanța sistemului. Actualizați pentru a beneficia de îmbunătățiri</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistem">
             <feature>• Acceptă deconectarea de la Wi-Fi și vizualizarea parolei</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ecran de blocare">
             <feature>• Ecranul de blocare oferă un stil de ceas mai mare și mai extins. Încercați mergând la: Setări > Ecran de pornire și stil > Personalizat > Atingeți ceasul pentru editare</feature>
             <feature>• Acum puteți utiliza videoclipuri ca fundal, cu efecte dinamice redate timp de până la 10 secunde</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Conectare Honor">
             <feature>• Telefoanele Honor și iPhone pot acum să partajeze mesaje de notificare între ele</feature>
             <feature>• Cu cea mai recentă versiune de HONOR WorkStation instalată pe Mac, funcția Notificări conectate vă permite să sincronizați notificările cu dispozitivul dvs. Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Instalați cea mai recentă versiune a aplicației HONOR WorkStation pe Mac, apoi puteți utiliza OneTap pentru a transfera imagini, videoclipuri, fișiere și alt conținut de pe telefonul Honor pe Mac cu o singură atingere</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Consum de energie">
             <feature>• Optimizează experiența de utilizare legată de autonomia bateriei în unele scenarii</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitate">
             <feature>• Îmbunătățește stabilitatea sistemului</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Corecție de securitate">
             <feature>• Corecția de securitate Android (ianuarie 2026) a fost inclusă pentru securitatea sistemului. Pentru mai multe informații despre actualizările de securitate Honor, vizitați site-ul nostru web: https://www.honor.com/ro/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notițe" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalarea acestei actualizări nu va afecta datele dvs. cu caracter personal, dar este totuși recomandat să faceți o copie de rezervă a datelor înainte de actualizare
2. Descoperiți mai multe informații despre caracteristicile produsului în Sugestii
3. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, puteți solicita ajutorul nostru apelând linia de asistență Honor sau vizitând Centrul de service pentru clienți Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1049" name="ru-ru">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Мы выпустили это обновление, чтобы улучшить производительность системы. Установите его, чтобы оценить изменения</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Система">
             <feature>• Поддерживает отключение от Wi-Fi и просмотр пароля</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Экран блокировки">
             <feature>• Экран блокировки теперь поддерживает увеличенный и растянутый стиль часов. Чтобы опробовать эту функцию, выберите «Настройки > Рабочий экран и стиль > Пользовательское изображение» и нажмите на часы, чтобы их отредактировать</feature>
             <feature>• Теперь вы можете использовать видео в качестве обоев, с динамическими эффектами, которые воспроизводятся до 10 секунд</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Телефоны Honor и iPhone теперь могут обмениваться уведомлениями друг с другом</feature>
             <feature>• С установленной последней версией HONOR WorkStation на вашем Mac функция «Подключенные уведомления» позволяет синхронизировать уведомления с вашим Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Установите последнюю версию HONOR WorkStation на ваш Mac, затем вы сможете использовать OneTap для передачи изображений, видео, файлов и другого контента с вашего телефона Honor на ваш Mac одним касанием</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Энергопотребление">
             <feature>• Оптимизирует пользовательский опыт при работе от аккумулятора в некоторых сценариях</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Стабильность">
             <feature>• Повышает стабильность системы</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Исправление безопасности">
             <feature>• В обновление включено исправление безопасности для Android (январь 2026 г.). Чтобы получить подробную информацию об обновлениях безопасности Honor, посетите наш сайт: https://www.honor.com/ru/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Заметки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Установка этого обновления не приведет к удалению ваших персональных данных, но мы все равно рекомендуем вам создать резервную копию своих данных перед обновлением
2. Изучите дополнительную информацию о функциях продукта в «Советах»
3. Если во время обновления у вас возникнут проблемы, обратитесь за помощью на горячую линию службы поддержки Honor или в сервисный центр для клиентов Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1115" name="si-lk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, මෙම යාවත්කාලීන කිරීම ප්‍රධාන වශයෙන් පද්ධතියේ කාර්යසාධනය උසස් කරයි. වැඩිදියුණු කිරීම් අත්විඳීමට යාවත්කාල කරන්න</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="පද්ධතිය">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi වෙතින් විසන්ධි කිරීමට සහ මුරපදය බැලීමට සහය දක්වයි</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="අගුළු තිරය">
             <feature>• අගුළු තිරය වඩා විශාල හා දිගු කළ ඔරලෝසු විලාසයක් ලබා දෙයි. මෙය වෙත ගොස් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: සැකසුම් > මුල් තිරය සහ විලාසය > අභිමත > සංස්කරණය කිරීමට ඔරලෝසුව තට්ටු කරන්න</feature>
             <feature>• දැන් ඔබට තත්පර 10 ක් දක්වා කාලයක් තිස්සේ ධාවනය වන ගතික ප්‍රයෝග සමගින්, වෝල්පේපරය ලෙස වීඩියෝ භාවිත කළ හැකි වේ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor දුරකථන සහ iPhone වලට දැන් එකිනෙක සමගින් දැනුම්දීම් පණිවුඩ හුවමාරු කරගත හැකි වේ</feature>
             <feature>• ඔබගේ Mac පරිගණකයේ නවතම HONOR WorkStation ස්ථාපනය කර තබා ගැනීමෙන්, සම්බන්ධිත දැනුම්දීම් මගින් ඔබට ඔබගේ Mac පරිගණකයට දැනුම්දීම් සමමුහුර්ත කිරීමට ඉඩ දෙයි</feature>
             <feature>• ඔබගේ Mac යන්ත්‍රයේ HONOR WorkStation හි නවතම අනුවාදය ස්ථාපනය කරන්න, ඉන්පසු ඔබට ඔබගේ Honor දුරකථනයෙන් රූප, වීඩියෝ, ගොනු සහ වෙනත් අන්තර්ගතය ඔබගේ Mac වෙත එක් තට්ටු කිරීමකින් මාරු කිරීමට OneTap භාවිත කළ හැකි වේ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="බල පරිභෝජනය">
             <feature>• සමහර අවස්ථාවල දී බැටරි ආයු කාලය සමගින් පරිශීලක අත්දැකීම ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ස්ථායීතාවය">
             <feature>• පද්ධතියේ ස්ථායිතාව වැඩිදියුණු කරයි</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක">
             <feature>• පද්ධති ආරක්ෂාව සඳහා Android ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක (2026 ජන) යොදාගෙන ඇත. Honor ආරක්ෂක යාවත්කාල පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සඳහා, කරුණාකර අපගේ වෙබ් අඩවියට යන්න https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="සටහන්" type="end">
             <feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්තවලට බල නොපානු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් යාවත්කාල කිරීමට පෙර ඔබගේ දත්ත උපස්ථ කිරීමට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ
2. ඉඟි තුළ නිෂ්පාදන විශේෂාංග පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සොයා ගන්න
3. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේදී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, ඔබට Honor සේවා හොට්ලයින් ඇමතීමෙන් හෝ Honor පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට පිවිසීමෙන් අපගේ උපකාර ලබා ගත හැකි වේ</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1051" name="sk-sk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Vážený používateľ, táto aktualizácia hlavne zvyšuje výkon systému. Aktualizujte, aby ste si užili zlepšenia</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Systém">
             <feature>• Podporuje odpojenie od siete Wi-Fi a zobrazenie hesla</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zamknutá obrazovka">
             <feature>• Zamknutá obrazovka ponúka štýl väčších a roztiahnutých hodín. Vyskúšajte to v časti: Nastavenia > Domovská obrazovka a štýl > Vlastné > ťuknutím na hodiny ich upravte</feature>
             <feature>• Teraz môžete ako tapetu používať videá s dynamickými efektmi, ktoré sa môžu prehrávať až 10 sekúnd</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pripojenie Honor">
             <feature>• Teraz môžete zdieľať upozornenia medzi telefónmi Honor a iPhone</feature>
             <feature>• S najnovšou verziou HONOR WorkStation nainštalovanou na vašom počítači Mac vám funkcia Pripojené upozornenia umožňuje synchronizovať upozornenia s vaším počítačom Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Nainštalujte si najnovšiu verziu aplikácie HONOR WorkStation do počítača Mac a potom môžete pomocou aplikácie OneTap jediným kliknutím prenášať obrázky, videá, súbory a ďalší obsah z telefónu Honor do počítača Mac</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Spotreba energie">
             <feature>• Optimalizuje používateľskú skúsenosť s výdržou batérie v niektorých situáciách</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilita">
             <feature>• Zlepšuje stabilitu systému</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezpečnostná oprava">
             <feature>• Súčasťou zabezpečenia systému je bezpečnostná oprava systému Android (z januára 2026). Ďalšie informácie o bezpečnostných aktualizáciách spoločnosti Honor nájdete na webovej stránke https://www.honor.com/sk/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Poznámky" type="end">
             <feature>1. Inštalácia tejto aktualizácie neovplyvní vaše osobné údaje, ale aj tak sa odporúča pred aktualizáciou si ich zálohovať
2. Ďalšie informácie o funkciách produktu si pozrite v aplikácii Tipy
3. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytne problém, pomoc môžete získať na zákazníckej linke Honor alebo navštívením Centra služieb zákazníkom Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1060" name="sl-si">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, ta posodobitev izboljša predvsem delovanje sistema. Posodobite, da boste lahko izkoristili izboljšave</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistem">
             <feature>• Podpira prekinitev povezave z omrežjem Wi‑Fi in ogled gesla</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zaklenjen zaslon">
             <feature>• Zaklenjeni zaslon zagotavlja večji, raztegnjen slog ure. Preizkusite ga tako, da odprete: Nastavitve > Začetni zaslon in slog > Po meri > Dotaknite se ure za urejanje</feature>
             <feature>• Videoposnetke lahko zdaj uporabite kot ozadje z dinamičnimi učinki, ki se predvajajo do 10 sekund</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor povezovanje">
             <feature>• Telefoni Honor in iPhone lahko zdaj med seboj delijo obvestila</feature>
             <feature>• Z najnovejšo različico HONOR WorkStation, nameščeno v računalniku Mac, vam funkcija Povezana obvestila omogoča sinhronizacijo obvestil z računalnikom Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Namestite najnovejšo različico HONOR WorkStation v računalnik Mac, nato pa uporabite OneTap za prenos slik, videoposnetkov, datotek in druge vsebine iz vašega telefona Honor v računalnik Mac z enim dotikom</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Poraba energije">
             <feature>• Optimizira uporabniško izkušnjo in čas delovanja baterije v določenih scenarijih</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Izboljša stabilnost sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Varnostni popravek">
             <feature>• Varnostni popravek za Android (januar 2026) je bil vključen za izboljšanje varnosti sistema. Za več informacij o varnostnih posodobitvah Honor obiščite spletno mesto: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zapiski" type="end">
             <feature>1. Namestitev te posodobitve ne vpliva na vaše osebne podatke, vendar je kljub temu priporočljivo, da podatke pred posodobitvijo varnostno kopirate
2. Več informacij o funkcijah izdelka je na voljo v razdelku Nasveti
3. Če med posodabljanjem pride do težav, lahko pokličete odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom družbe Honor ali obiščete servisni center družbe Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1053" name="sv-se">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Bästa användare, den här uppdateringen förbättrar främst systemets prestanda. Uppdatera för att ta del av förbättringarna</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="System">
             <feature>• Stöder frånkoppling från Wi-Fi och visning av lösenordet</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Låsskärm">
             <feature>• Låsskärmen erbjuder en större och utsträckt klockstil. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Startsida och stil > Anpassad > Tryck på klockan för att redigera</feature>
             <feature>• Nu kan du använda videor som bakgrundsbild med dynamiska effekter som spelas upp i upp till 10 sekunder</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Anslut">
             <feature>• Aviseringsmeddelanden kan nu delas mellan Honor-telefoner och iPhones</feature>
             <feature>• Med den senaste versionen av HONOR WorkStation installerad på din Mac kan du synkronisera aviseringar till Mac med Anslutna aviseringar</feature>
             <feature>• Installera den senaste versionen av HONOR WorkStation på din Mac, så kan du använda OneTap för att överföra bilder, videor, filer och annat innehåll från Honor-telefonen till Mac med ett enda tryck</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Energiförbrukning">
             <feature>• Optimerar användarupplevelsen med batteritid i vissa scenarier</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitet">
             <feature>• Förbättrar systemets stabilitet</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Säkerhetskorrigering">
             <feature>• Android-säkerhetskorrigeringen (januari 2026) har implementerats för systemsäkerhet. Vill du ha mer information om säkerhetsuppdateringar för Honor går du till vår webbplats https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Noteringar" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installation av den här uppdateringen påverkar inte dina personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du säkerhetskopierar alla data innan du uppdaterar
2. Upptäck mer information om produktfunktioner i Tips
3. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa Honors hotline för service eller besöka Honors kundtjänstcenter för att få hjälp</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1089" name="sw-TZ">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, sasisho hili kwa kiasi kikubwa linaboresha utendaji wa mfumo. Sasisha ili ufurahie maboresho</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Mfumo">
             <feature>• Inaruhusu kutenganisha kutoka kwenye Wi-Fi na kutazama nenosiri</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Skrini iliyofungwa">
             <feature>• Skrini iliyofungwa hutoa mtindo mkubwa na uliopanuliwa wa saa. Ujaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Skrini ya mwanzo na mtindo > Maalum > Gusa saa ili uhariri</feature>
             <feature>• Unaweza sasa kutumia video kama pazia, kwa athari nyumbulifu ambazo zinachezwa hadi sekunde 10</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Simu za Honor na iPhone zinaweza kushirikishana jumbe za taarifa kwa sasa</feature>
             <feature>• Ukiwa na HONOR WorkStation ya hivi karibuni imesakinishwa kwenye Mac yako, Taarifa Zilizounganishwa inakuruhusu kulandanisha taarifa kwenye Mac yako</feature>
             <feature>• Sakinisha toleo la hivi karibuni la HONOR WorkStation kwenye Mac yako, kisha unaweza kutumia OneTap ili kuhamisha picha, video, mafaili na maudhui mengine kutoka kwenye simu yako ya Honor kwenye Mac yako kwa mguso mmoja</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Utumiaji nishati">
             <feature>• Huboresha huduma anayopata mtumiaji kwa maisha ya betri katika baadhi ya matukio</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Uthabiti">
             <feature>• Linaboresha uthabiti wa mfumo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Rekebisho la usalama">
             <feature>• Rekebisho la usalama wa Android (Jan 2026) limejumuishwa kwa ajili ya usalama wa mfumo. Ili kupata maelezo zaidi kuhusu masasisho ya Usalama wa Honor, tafadhali tembelea tovuti yetu: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Madokezo" type="end">
             <feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutaathiri data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado inapendekezwa ili kuweka hifadhi rudufu ya data yako kabla ya kusasisha
2. Gundua maelezo zaidi kwenye vipengele vya bidhaa kwenye Vidokezo
3. Ikiwa utakumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, unaweza kupata msaada wetu kwa kupiga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya Honor au tembelea kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1097" name="ta-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு முதன்மையாக சிஸ்டம் செயல்திறனை மேம்படுத்துகிறது. மேம்பாடுகளைப் பெற, புதுப்பிக்கவும்</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="சிஸ்டம்">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi இலிருந்து துண்டிப்பதற்கும் கடவுச்சொல்லைப் பார்ப்பதற்கும் இது ஆதரவளிக்கிறது</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="பூட்டுத் திரை">
             <feature>• பூட்டுத் திரை பெரிய மற்றும் அகண்ட கடிகார ஸ்டைலை வழங்குகிறது. இங்குச் சென்று அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: அமைப்புகள் > முகப்புத் திரை &amp; ஸ்டைல் > தனிப்பயன் > கடிகாரத்தைத் தட்டித் திருத்தவும்</feature>
             <feature>• 10 வினாடிகள் வரை இயங்கும் டைனாமிக் விளைவுகளுடன் வீடியோக்களை இப்போது நீங்கள் சுவர்சித்திரமாகப் பயன்படுத்தலாம்</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• இப்போது Honor ஃபோன்களாலும் iPhoneகளாலும் ஒன்றுக்கொன்று அறிவிப்புச் செய்திகளைப் பகிர்ந்துகொள்ள முடியும்</feature>
             <feature>• உங்கள் Mac-இல் சமீபத்திய HONOR WorkStation நிறுவப்பட்டிருந்தால், இணைக்கப்பட்ட அறிவிப்புகள் அறிவிப்புகளை உங்கள் Mac உடன் ஒத்திசைக்க உங்களை அனுமதிக்கிறது</feature>
             <feature>• உங்கள் Mac-இல் HONOR WorkStation-இன் சமீபத்திய பதிப்பை நிறுவிய பிறகு, ஒரே ஒரு தட்டல் மூலம் உங்கள் Honor ஃபோனில் இருந்து படங்கள், வீடியோக்கள், கோப்புகள் மற்றும் பிற உள்ளடக்கத்தை உங்கள் Mac-க்குப் பரிமாற்ற OneTap-ஐப் பயன்படுத்தலாம்</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="மின் நுகர்வு">
             <feature>• சில சூழ்நிலைகளில் பேட்டரி ஆயுளுடனான பயனர் அனுபவத்தை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="நிலைத்தன்மை">
             <feature>• சிஸ்டம் நிலைத்தன்மையை மேம்படுத்துகிறது</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு">
             <feature>• சிஸ்டம் பாதுகாப்பிற்கு Android பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு (ஜன 2026) சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. Honor பாதுகாப்புப் புதுப்பிப்புகளைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களுக்கு, எங்கள் வலைத்தளத்தைப் பார்க்கவும்: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="குறிப்புகள்" type="end">
             <feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவைப் பாதிக்காது, எனினும் புதுப்பிப்பதற்கு முன்பு உங்கள் தரவைக் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுப்பது இன்னும் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது
2. உதவிக்குறிப்புகளில் தயாரிப்பு அம்சங்களைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களைக் கண்டறிக
3. புதுப்பிக்கும்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், Honor சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைப்பதன் மூலமோ அல்லது Honor வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்தைப் பார்வையிடுவதன் மூலமோ எங்கள் உதவியைப் பெறலாம்</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1098" name="te-IN">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారుకు, ఈ అప్‌డేట్ ప్రధానంగా సిస్టమ్ పనితీరును మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది. మెరుగుదలలను ఆనందించడానికి అప్‌డేట్ చేయండి</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="సిస్టమ్">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi నుండి డిస్‌కనెక్ట్ చేయడానికి మరియు పాస్‌వర్డ్‌ను చూడటానికి మద్దతు ఇస్తుంది</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="లాక్ స్క్రీన్">
             <feature>• లాక్ స్క్రీన్ పెద్దదిగా మరియు సాగదీయబడిన గడియార శైలిని అందిస్తుంది. ఇక్కడికి వెళ్లి దానిని ప్రయత్నించండి: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ &amp; శైలి > అనుకూలం > సవరించడానికి గడియారాన్ని ట్యాప్ చేయండి</feature>
             <feature>• ఇప్పుడు మీరు వీడియోలను వాల్‌పేపర్‌గా ఉపయోగించవచ్చు, ఇవి 10 సెకన్ల వరకు ప్లే అయ్యే డైనమిక్ ఎఫెక్ట్‌లతో వస్తాయి</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor కనెక్ట్">
             <feature>• Honor ఫోన్‌లు మరియు iPhoneలు ఇప్పుడు ఒకదానితో ఒకటి నోటిఫికేషన్ సందేశాలను భాగస్వామ్యం చేసుకోగలవు</feature>
             <feature>• మీ Macలో ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయబడిన తాజా HONOR WorkStationతో, కనెక్ట్ చేయబడిన నోటిఫికేషన్‌లు మీ Macకు నోటిఫికేషన్‌లను సమకాలీకరించడానికి మిమ్మల్ని అనుమతిస్తాయి</feature>
             <feature>• మీ Macలో HONOR WorkStation యొక్క తాజా సంస్కరణను ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయండి, ఆ తర్వాత మీరు OneTapను ఉపయోగించి మీ Honor ఫోన్‌ నుండి చిత్రాలు, వీడియోలు, ఫైల్స్ మరియు ఇతర కంటెంట్‌ను కేవలం ఒక్క ట్యాప్‌తో మీ Macకు బదిలీ చేయవచ్చు</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="పవర్ వాడకం">
             <feature>• కొన్ని సందర్భాల్లో బ్యాటరీ లైఫ్‌తో పాటు వినియోగదారు అనుభవాన్ని కూడా ఇది ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="స్థిరత్వం">
             <feature>• సిస్టమ్ స్థిరత్వాన్ని మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="భద్రతా ప్యాచ్">
             <feature>• సిస్టమ్ భద్రత కోసం Android భద్రతా ప్యాచ్ (జన 2026) చేర్చబడింది. Honor భద్రత అప్‌డేట్‌ల గురించి మరింత సమాచారం కోసం, దయచేసి మా వెబ్‌సైట్‌ను సందర్శించండి: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="గమనికలు" type="end">
             <feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్ ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వలన మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటా ప్రభావితం కాదు, కాని అప్‌డేట్ చేయడానికి ముందు మీ డేటాను బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని ఇంకా సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది
2. చిట్కాల్లో ఉత్పత్తి ఫీచర్లపై మరింత సమాచారాన్ని తెలుసుకోండి
3. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో ఏవైనా సమస్యలను ఎదుర్కొంటే, మీరు Honor సర్వీస్ హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేసి లేదా Honor కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రాన్ని సందర్శించి మా సహాయం పొందవచ్చు</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1054" name="th-th">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตครั้งนี้เน้นปรับปรุงประสิทธิภาพระบบเป็นหลัก โปรดอัปเดตเพื่อใช้การปรับปรุง</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ระบบ">
             <feature>• รองรับการยกเลิกการเชื่อมต่อจาก Wi-Fi และการดูรหัสผ่าน</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="หน้าจอล็อค">
             <feature>• หน้าจอล็อคมีสไตล์นาฬิกาที่มีขนาดใหญ่และขยายออกยิ่งขึ้น ลองใช้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > หน้าจอหลักและสไตล์ > กำหนดเอง > แตะนาฬิกาเพื่อแก้ไข</feature>
             <feature>• ตอนนี้คุณสามารถใช้วิดีโอเป็นพื้นหลังได้แล้ว โดยมีเอฟเฟ็กต์แบบไดนามิกที่เล่นได้นานสุด 10 วินาที</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• ตอนนี้โทรศัพท์ Honor และ iPhone สามารถแชร์ข้อความการแจ้งเตือนถึงกันและกันได้แล้ว</feature>
             <feature>• เมื่อติดตั้ง HONOR WorkStation เวอร์ชันล่าสุดบน Mac แล้ว การแจ้งเตือนที่เชื่อมต่อจะช่วยให้คุณสามารถซิงค์การแจ้งเตือนไปยัง Mac ได้</feature>
             <feature>• ติดตั้ง HONOR WorkStation เวอร์ชันล่าสุดบน Mac จากนั้นคุณสามารถใช้ OneTap เพื่อถ่ายโอนรูปภาพ วิดีโอ ไฟล์ และเนื้อหาอื่นๆ จากโทรศัพท์ Honor ไปยัง Mac ได้ด้วยการแตะครั้งเดียว</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="การใช้พลังงาน">
             <feature>• ปรับปรุงประสบการณ์การใช้งานของผู้ใช้เกี่ยวกับอายุการใช้งานแบตเตอรี่ในบางสถานการณ์</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ความเสถียร">
             <feature>• ปรับปรุงความเสถียรของระบบ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="แพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัย">
             <feature>• มีการรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัย Android (ม.ค. 2026) เพื่อความปลอดภัยของระบบ ดูข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับการอัปเดตความปลอดภัยของ Honor ได้ในเว็บไซต์ของเรา https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="โน้ต" type="end">
             <feature>1. การติดตั้งการอัปเดตนี้จะไม่ส่งผลต่อข้อมูลส่วนตัว แต่เราขอแนะนำให้คุณสำรองข้อมูลก่อนอัปเดต
2. ค้นพบข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับฟีเจอร์ผลิตภัณฑ์ในเคล็ดลับ
3. หากคุณพบปัญหาใดๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต คุณสามารถรับความช่วยเหลือได้โดยการโทรติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการลูกค้าของ Honor หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1124" name="tl-ph">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Minamahal na user, pangunahing pinapahusay ng update na ito ang performance ng system. I-update para i-enjoy ang mga pagpapahusay</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="System">
             <feature>• Sinusuportahan ang pagdiskonekta mula sa Wi-Fi at pagtingin sa password</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Lock screen">
             <feature>• Nag-aalok ang lock screen ng mas malaki at mas mahabang estilo ng orasan. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Home screen at estilo > Custom > I-tap ang orasan para i-edit ito</feature>
             <feature>• Puwede mo nang gamitin ang mga video bilang wallpaper, kung saan nagpe-play ang mga dynamic na effect hanggang sa 10 segundo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Puwede nang magbahagi ang mga telepono ng Honor at iPhone ng mga mensaheng notification sa isa't isa</feature>
             <feature>• Dahil naka-install sa iyong Mac ang HONOR WorkStation, nagbibigay-daan sa iyo ang Mga Nakakonektang Notification na i-sync ang mga notification sa iyong Mac</feature>
             <feature>• I-install ang pinakabagong bersyon ng HONOR WorkStation sa iyong Mac, pagkatapos ay puwede mong gamitin ang OneTap para maglipat ng mga larawan, video, file, at iba pang content mula sa iyong telepono ng Honor patungo sa iyong Mac sa isang tap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pagkonsumo ng power">
             <feature>• Ino-optimize ang karanasan ng user sa tagal ng baterya sa ilang sitwasyon</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stability">
             <feature>• Pinapahusay ang stability ng system</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Panseguridad na patch">
             <feature>• Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Ene 2026) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng Honor, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Mga Tala" type="end">
             <feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto ang pag-install sa update na ito sa iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update
2. Tuklasin ang higit pang impormasyon sa mga feature ng produkto sa Mga Tip
3. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, makukuha mo ang tulong namin sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng Honor o pagbisita sa customer service center ng Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1055" name="tr-tr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Değerli kullanıcımız, bu güncelleme ile çoğunlukla sistem performansı artırılmıştır. İyileştirmelerin tadını çıkarmak için güncelleyin</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistem">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi bağlantısını kesip şifreyi görüntüleme desteği eklendi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kilit ekranı">
             <feature>• Kilit ekranına daha büyük ve uzatılmış bir saat stili eklendi. Şu adımları takip ederek deneyebilirsiniz: Ayarlar > Başlangıç ekranı ve stil > Özel > Düzenlemek için saate dokunun</feature>
             <feature>• Artık en fazla 10 saniye süren dinamik efektli videoları duvar kağıdı olarak kullanabilirsiniz</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor telefonlar ve iPhone'lar artık bildirim mesajlarını birbirleriyle paylaşabilecek</feature>
             <feature>• Mac'inizde en güncel HONOR WorkStation yüklüyken Bağlı Bildirimler aracılığıyla bildirimleri Mac'inizle senkronize edebilirsiniz</feature>
             <feature>• HONOR WorkStation'ın en son sürümünü Mac'inize yükleyin, ardından OneTap'i kullanarak görselleri, videoları, dosyaları ve diğer içerikleri Honor telefonunuzdan Mac'inize tek dokunuşla aktarın</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Güç tüketimi">
             <feature>• Bazı senaryolarda pil ömrü ile ilgili kullanıcı deneyimi optimize edildi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Kararlılık">
             <feature>• Sistem kararlılığı iyileştirildi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Güvenlik yaması">
             <feature>• Sistem güvenliği için Android güvenlik yaması (Ocak 2026) entegre edilmiştir. Honor Güvenlik güncellemeleri hakkında daha fazla bilgi için lütfen https://www.honor.com/tr/support/bulletin/2026/1 web sitemizi ziyaret edin</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notlar" type="end">
             <feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi etkilemeyecektir ancak yine de güncellemeden önce verilerinizi yedeklemeniz önerilir
2. İpuçları bölümünden ürün özellikleri hakkında daha fazla bilgiyi keşfedin
3. Güncelleme sırasında sorunla karşılaşırsanız Honor yardım hattını arayarak veya Honor müşteri hizmetleri merkezini ziyaret ederek yardım alabilirsiniz</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1058" name="uk-ua">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Шановний користувачу! Це оновлення насамперед підвищує продуктивність системи. Установіть його, щоб відчути покращення</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Система">
             <feature>• Підтримує відключення від мережі Wi-Fi та перегляд пароля</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Екран блокування">
             <feature>• На екрані блокування можна встановити годинник у збільшеному й розтягненому вигляді. Щоб спробувати, виберіть "Налаштування" > "Головний екран і стиль" > "Користувацьке", потім торкніться годинника для редагування</feature>
             <feature>• Тепер можна використовувати відео як фоновий малюнок із динамічними ефектами тривалістю до 10 секунд</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Сполучення Honor">
             <feature>• Телефони Honor та iPhone тепер можуть обмінюватися сповіщеннями між собою</feature>
             <feature>• Після встановлення найновішої версії HONOR WorkStation на Mac ви зможете синхронізувати сповіщення з Mac за допомогою функції "Сполучені сповіщення"</feature>
             <feature>• Установіть найновішу версію HONOR WorkStation на свій Mac, щоб передавати зображення, відео, файли та інший вміст із вашого телефона Honor на Mac одним дотиком у OneTap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Споживання енергії">
             <feature>• Оптимізує взаємодію користувача щодо терміну служби акумулятора в певних сценаріях</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Стабільність">
             <feature>• Покращено стабільність роботи системи</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Виправлення системи безпеки">
             <feature>• Виправлення для системи безпеки Android (січень 2026 року) впроваджено для посилення безпеки системи. Додаткова інформація про оновлення системи безпеки Honor наводиться на нашому вебсайті https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Нотатки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Установлення цього оновлення не вплине на ваші особисті дані, однак рекомендовано спочатку створити їхні резервні копії
2. Дізнайтеся більше про функції продукту в розділі "Підказки"
3. Якщо під час оновлення у вас виникнуть будь-які проблеми, ви можете отримати нашу допомогу, зателефонувавши на гарячу лінію Honor або відвідавши центр послуг Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1056" name="ur-pk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>محترم صارف، یہ اپ ڈیٹ بنیادی طور پر سسٹم کی کارکردگی کو بڑھاتی ہے۔ بہتریوں سے لطف اندوز ہونے کے لیے اپ ڈیٹ کریں</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="سسٹم">
             <feature>‏• Wi-Fi سے منقطع ہونے اور پاس ورڈ دیکھنے میں تعاون کرتی ہے</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="لاک اسکرین">
             <feature>‏• لاک اسکرین ایک بڑی اور پھیلی ہوئی گھڑی کا انداز پیش کرتی ہے۔ یہاں جا کر اسے آزمائیں: ترتیبات > ہوم اسکرین اور طرز > حسب ضرورت > ترمیم کرنے کے لیے گھڑی پر ٹیپ کریں</feature>
             <feature>‏• اب آپ 10 سیکنڈ تک چلنے والے ڈائنیمک اثرات کے ساتھ، ویڈیوز کو وال پیپر کے طور پر استعمال کر سکتے ہیں</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏Honor Connect">
             <feature>‏• Honor فونز اور iPhones اب ایک دوسرے کے ساتھ اطلاعاتی پیغامات شیئر کر سکتے ہیں</feature>
             <feature>‏• آپ کے Mac پر جدید ترین HONOR WorkStation انسٹال ہونے کے ساتھ، مربوط اطلاعات آپ کو اپنے Mac پر اطلاعات کو سنک کرنے کی اجازت دیتی ہیں</feature>
             <feature>‏• اپنے Mac پر HONOR WorkStation کا تازہ ترین ورژن انسٹال کریں، پھر آپ اپنے Honor فون سے تصاویر، ویڈیوز، فائلز اور دیگر مواد کو ایک ہی ٹیپ کے ساتھ اپنے Mac پر منتقل کرنے کے لیے OneTap کو استعمال کر سکتے ہیں</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏بجلی کی کھپت">
             <feature>‏• کچھ منظرناموں میں بیٹری لائف کے ساتھ صارف کے تجربے کو بہتر بناتی ہے</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="استحکام">
             <feature>‏‏• سسٹم کے استحکام کو بہتر بناتی ہے</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="سکیورٹی پیچ">
             <feature>‏• ‏Android سکیورٹی پیچ (جنوری 2026) شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔ Honor سکیورٹی اپ ڈیٹس کے بارے میں مزید معلومات کے لیے، براہ کرم ہماری ویب سائٹ ملاحظہ کریں https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="نوٹس" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا متاثر نہیں ہو گا، لیکن اپ ڈیٹ کرنے سے پہلے اب بھی اپنے ڈیٹا کا بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے
‏2. تجاویز میں پروڈکٹس کی خصوصیات کے بارے میں مزید معلومات دریافت کریں
‏3. اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کوئی مسئلہ درپیش ہوتا ہے، تو آپ Honor سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کر کے یا Honor کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جا کر ہماری مدد حاصل کر سکتے ہیں</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2115" name="uz-uz">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu yangilanish asosan tizim unumdorligini oshiradi. Takomillashtirishlardan foydalanish uchun yangilang</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tizim">
             <feature>• Wi-Fi tarmoqdan aloqani uzishni va parolni koʻrishni dastaklaydi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ekranni qulflash">
             <feature>• Ekran qulfi kattaroq va choʻzilgan soat uslubini taklif qiladi. Bu yerda sinang: Sozlamalar > Bosh ekran va uslub > Maxsus > Tahrirlash uchun soatni bosish</feature>
             <feature>• Endi 10 soniyagacha ijro etiladigan dinamik effektlar bilan videolardan fon rasmi sifatida foydalanishingiz mumkin</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor telefonlari va iPhone qurilmalari endi bildirishnoma xabarlarini bir-biriga ulashishi mumkin</feature>
             <feature>• HONOR WorkStation ilovasining eng oxirgi versiyasi Mac kompyuteringizga oʻrnatilsa, Ulangan bildirishnomalar funksiyasi bildirishnomalarni Mac kompyuteringizga sinxronlash imkonini beradi</feature>
             <feature>• HONOR WorkStation ilovasining eng oxirgi versiyasini Mac kompyuteringizga oʻrnating, keyin OneTap funksiyasidan foydalanib rasmlar, videolar, fayllar va boshqa kontentni Honor telefoningizdan Mac kompyuteringizga bir marta bosib uzatishingiz mumkin</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Quvvat sarfi">
             <feature>• Ayrim holatlarda batareyaning xizmat muddatini yaxshilash orqali foydalanuvchi taassurotini optimallaydi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Barqarorlik">
             <feature>• Tizim barqarorligi yaxshilandi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Xavfsizlik tuzatmasi">
             <feature>• Tizim xavfsizligini kuchaytirish uchun Android xavfsizlik tuzatmasi (2026-yil, yanvar) kiritildi. Honor xavfsizlik yangilanishlari haqida batafsil axborot olish uchun veb-saytimizga tashrif buyuring: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Eslatmalar" type="end">
             <feature>1. Bu yangilanishni oʻrnatish shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringizga taʼsir qilmaydi, lekin yangilashdan oldin maʼlumotlaringizni zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi
2. Maslahatlar ilovasida mahsulot xususiyatlari bilan batafsilroq tanishing
3. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, Honor xizmatining tezkor raqamiga telefon qilish yoki Honor mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyurish orqali yordam olishingiz mumkin</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1066" name="vi-vn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật này chủ yếu nâng cao hiệu suất hệ thống. Hãy cập nhật để tận hưởng các cải tiến</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Hệ thống">
             <feature>• Hỗ trợ ngắt kết nối Wi-Fi và xem mật khẩu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Màn hình khóa">
             <feature>• Màn hình khóa cung cấp kiểu đồng hồ lớn hơn và trải rộng hơn. Hãy dùng thử bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Phong cách và màn hình chính > Tùy chỉnh > Chạm vào đồng hồ để sửa</feature>
             <feature>• Giờ đây, bạn có thể sử dụng video làm hình nền, với hiệu ứng động phát trong tối đa 10 giây</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Điện thoại Honor và iPhone giờ đây có thể chia sẻ thông báo với nhau</feature>
             <feature>• Với HONOR WorkStation phiên bản mới nhất được cài đặt trên máy Mac, tính năng Thông báo được kết nối cho phép bạn đồng bộ thông báo với máy Mac của mình</feature>
             <feature>• Cài đặt phiên bản HONOR WorkStation mới nhất trên máy Mac của bạn, sau đó bạn có thể sử dụng OneTap để truyền hình ảnh, video, tệp tin và nội dung khác từ điện thoại Honor sang máy Mac chỉ bằng một thao tác chạm</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tiêu thụ pin">
             <feature>• Tối ưu hóa trải nghiệm người dùng với thời lượng pin trong một số trường hợp</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Độ ổn định">
             <feature>• Cải thiện độ ổn định của hệ thống</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bản vá bảo mật">
             <feature>• Bản cập nhật này tích hợp Bản vá bảo mật Android (tháng 1 năm 2026) để bảo mật hệ thống. Để biết thêm thông tin về các Bản cập nhật bảo mật của Honor, vui lòng truy cập trang web của chúng tôi https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Ghi chú" type="end">
             <feature>1. Việc cài đặt bản cập nhật này sẽ không ảnh hưởng đến dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn, nhưng bạn vẫn nên sao lưu dữ liệu trước khi cập nhật
2. Khám phá thêm thông tin về các tính năng sản phẩm trong ứng dụng Mẹo
3. Nếu gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, bạn có thể nhận trợ giúp của chúng tôi bằng cách gọi đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ của Honor hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="3076" name="zh-hk">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新主要針對系統進行了優化，建議您進行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="系統">
             <feature>• 新增 Wi-Fi 中斷連線和密碼顯示功能</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="鎖屏">
             <feature>• 新增鎖屏長時鐘。體驗路徑：設定 > 主屏幕和個人化 > 自訂 > 輕觸時鐘即可</feature>
             <feature>• 新增視訊桌布，支援最長 10 秒動態效果</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="榮耀互聯">
             <feature>• 新增支援榮耀手機與 iPhone 互相分享通知訊息</feature>
             <feature>• 新增榮耀手機和 Mac 通知分享功能，Mac 安裝最新版「榮耀超級工作台」應用程式，即可同步訊息</feature>
             <feature>• 新增榮耀與 Mac 一拍即傳功能，Mac 安裝最新版「榮耀超級工作台」應用程式，即可用榮耀手機一拍即傳圖片、影片、檔案等內容</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="功耗">
             <feature>• 優化部分場景的續航體驗</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="穩定性">
             <feature>• 提升系統穩定性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安全性修補程式">
             <feature>• 整合 Android 2026年1月安全修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟件安全更新內容的資訊，請瀏覽榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="更新注意事項" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份
2. 更多精彩功能介紹，請瀏覽「玩機技巧」應用程式
3. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線或至榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1028" name="zh-tw">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新主要針對系統進行了最佳化，建議您進行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="系統">
             <feature>• 新增 Wi-Fi 中斷連線、密碼顯示功能</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="鎖定螢幕">
             <feature>•  新增鎖定螢幕長時鐘。體驗路徑：設定 > 桌面和個人化 > 自訂 > 輕觸時鐘即可</feature>
             <feature>• 新增影片桌布，支援最長 10 秒動態效果</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="榮耀互聯">
             <feature>• 新增支援榮耀手機與 iPhone 互相共享通知訊息</feature>
             <feature>• 新增榮耀手機和 Mac 通知共享功能，在 Mac 上安裝最新版「榮耀超級工作台」應用程式，即可同步訊息</feature>
             <feature>• 新增榮耀與 Mac 一碰傳功能，在 Mac 上安裝最新版「榮耀超級工作台」應用程式，即可使用榮耀手機一碰傳圖片、影片、檔案等內容</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="電力消耗">
             <feature>• 最佳化在部分場景下的續航體驗</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="穩定性">
             <feature>• 提升系統穩定性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安全性修補程式">
             <feature>• 整合 Android 2026 年 1 月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟體安全更新內容的資訊，請造訪榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="更新注意事項" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份
2. 如需更多精彩功能介紹，請查看「玩機技巧」應用程式
3. 在更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1152" name="ug-cn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا ئاساسلىقى سىستېمىغا قارىتا ئەلالاشتۇرۇش ئېلىپ بېرىلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏سىستېما">
             <feature>‏• Wi-Fi نى ئۈزۈپ ئ‍ۇلاش، مەخپىي نومۇرنى كۆرسىتىش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏قۇلۇپ ئېكرانى">
             <feature>‏•  قۇلۇپ ئېكران ئۇزۇن سائىتى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى. ئىشلىتىش يولى: تەڭشەك > ئۈستەليۈزى ۋە خاسلاشتۇرۇش > ئىختىيارىي > سائەتنى چەكسىڭىزلا بولىدۇ</feature>
             <feature>‏• سىن تەگلىكى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، ئۇزۇن بولغاندا 10 سېكۇنتلۇق ھەرىكەت ئۈنۈمىنى قوللايدۇ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="روڭياۋ ئۇلاش">
             <feature>‏• روڭياۋ يانفونى بىلەن iPhone ئارىسىدا ئۇقتۇرۇش ئۇچۇرىنى ئورتاقلىشىشنى قوللايدىغان بولدى</feature>
             <feature>‏• روڭياۋ يانفونى بىلەن Mac ئۇقتۇرۇش ئورتاقلىشىش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، Mac كە ئەڭ يېڭى نەشرىدىكى «روڭياۋ دەرىجىدىن تاشقىرى خىزمەت سۇپىسى» ئەپىنى قاچىلىسىڭىز، ئۇچۇرلارنى ماسقەدەملەشكە بولىدۇ</feature>
             <feature>‏‏• روڭياۋ بىلەن Mac ئارىسىدا تەگكۈزۈپ يوللاش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، Mac كە ئەڭ يېڭى نەشرىدىكى «روڭياۋ دەرىجىدىن تاشقىرى خىزمەت سۇپىسى» ئەپىنى قاچىلىسىڭىز، روڭياۋ يانفونى بىلەن تەگكۈزۈپلا رەسىم، سىن، ھۆججەت قاتارلىق مەزمۇنلارنى يوللاشقا بولىدۇ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏سەرپىيات">
             <feature>‏• بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى توك ساقلاش تەسىراتى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏مۇقىملىق">
             <feature>‏• سىستېمىنىڭ مۇقىملىقى يۇقىرى كۆتۈرۈلدى</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى">
             <feature>‏• ئاندرويدنىڭ 2026-يىل 1-ئايلىق بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، سىستېما بىخەتەرلىكى كۈچەيتىلدى. روڭياۋ يۇمشاق دېتالىنىڭ بىخەتەرلىك يېڭىلاش مەزمۇنىغا ئالاقىدار ئۇچۇرلار ئۈچۈن روڭياۋ ئورگان تەرەپ تور بېكىتىنى زىيارەت قىلىڭ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="‏يېڭىلاش بىلدۈرگۈسى" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، لېكىن يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتنى زاپاسلاشنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز
‏2. تېخىمۇ كۆپ سەرخىل ئىقتىدارلارنى «ئىشلىتىش كۆرسەتمىسى» ئەپىنى زىيارەت قىلىپ كۆرۈڭ
‏3. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركىسى مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1031" name="de-at">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung verbessert hauptsächlich die Systemleistung. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="System">
             <feature>• Unterstützt das Trennen der WLAN-Verbindung und das Anzeigen des Passworts.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bildschirm sperren">
             <feature>• Der Sperrbildschirm bietet einen größeren und gestreckten Uhrstil. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Startbildschirm und Stil > Benutzerdefiniert > Tippen Sie zum Bearbeiten auf die Uhr</feature>
             <feature>• Sie können jetzt Videos als Hintergrund verwenden, mit dynamischen Effekten, die bis zu 10 Sekunden lang abgespielt werden.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor-Telefone und iPhones können jetzt Benachrichtigungsmitteilungen miteinander austauschen.</feature>
             <feature>• Mit der neuesten HONOR WorkStation-Version auf Ihrem Mac können Sie mit geräteübergreifenden Benachrichtigungen die Benachrichtigungen mit Ihrem Mac synchronisieren.</feature>
             <feature>• Installieren Sie die neueste Version von HONOR WorkStation auf Ihrem Mac. Anschließend können Sie mit OneTap Bilder, Videos, Dateien und andere Inhalte mit einem einzigen Tippen von Ihrem Honor-Telefon auf Ihren Mac übertragen.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stromverbrauch">
             <feature>• Optimiert in bestimmten Szenarien die Benutzererfahrung hinsichtlich der Akkulaufzeit.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilität">
             <feature>• Verbessert die Systemstabilität</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sicherheitspatch">
             <feature>• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Jan. 2026) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die Honor Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notizen" type="end">
             <feature>1. Die Installation dieses Updates hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, es wird jedoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen
2. Entdecken Sie weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen in Tipps
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Honor-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein Honor-Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1031" name="de-ch">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung verbessert hauptsächlich die Systemleistung. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="System">
             <feature>• Unterstützt das Trennen der WLAN-Verbindung und das Anzeigen des Passworts.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bildschirm sperren">
             <feature>• Der Sperrbildschirm bietet einen größeren und gestreckten Uhrstil. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Startbildschirm und Stil > Benutzerdefiniert > Tippen Sie zum Bearbeiten auf die Uhr</feature>
             <feature>• Sie können jetzt Videos als Hintergrund verwenden, mit dynamischen Effekten, die bis zu 10 Sekunden lang abgespielt werden.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Honor-Telefone und iPhones können jetzt Benachrichtigungsmitteilungen miteinander austauschen.</feature>
             <feature>• Mit der neuesten HONOR WorkStation-Version auf Ihrem Mac können Sie mit geräteübergreifenden Benachrichtigungen die Benachrichtigungen mit Ihrem Mac synchronisieren.</feature>
             <feature>• Installieren Sie die neueste Version von HONOR WorkStation auf Ihrem Mac. Anschließend können Sie mit OneTap Bilder, Videos, Dateien und andere Inhalte mit einem einzigen Tippen von Ihrem Honor-Telefon auf Ihren Mac übertragen.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stromverbrauch">
             <feature>• Optimiert in bestimmten Szenarien die Benutzererfahrung hinsichtlich der Akkulaufzeit.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilität">
             <feature>• Verbessert die Systemstabilität</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sicherheitspatch">
             <feature>• Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Jan. 2026) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die Honor Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notizen" type="end">
             <feature>1. Die Installation dieses Updates hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, es wird jedoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen
2. Entdecken Sie weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen in Tipps
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Honor-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein Honor-Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1036" name="fr-ch">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour améliore principalement les performances du système. Effectuez la mise à jour pour profiter des améliorations</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Système">
             <feature>• Prend en charge la déconnexion du Wi-Fi et l'affichage du mot de passe</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Écran verrouillé">
             <feature>• L'écran verrouillé propose un style d'horloge agrandi et étiré. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Écran d'accueil et style > Personnalisé > Appuyez sur l'horloge pour la modifier</feature>
             <feature>• Vous pouvez désormais utiliser des vidéos comme fond d'écran, avec des effets dynamiques qui durent jusqu'à 10 secondes</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Les téléphones Honor et les iPhone peuvent désormais partager des messages de notification entre eux</feature>
             <feature>• Avec la dernière version de HONOR WorkStation installée sur votre Mac, Notifications Connectées vous permet de synchroniser les notifications avec votre Mac</feature>
             <feature>• Installez la dernière version de HONOR WorkStation sur votre Mac, puis utilisez OneTap pour transférer des images, des vidéos, des fichiers et d'autres contenus de votre téléphone Honor vers votre Mac d'un simple appui</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Consommation d'énergie">
             <feature>• Optimise l'expérience utilisateur de l'autonomie de la batterie dans certains scénarios</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilité">
             <feature>• Améliore la stabilité du système</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Correctif de sécurité">
             <feature>• Un correctif de sécurité Android (janvier 2026) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité Honor, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour
2. Découvrez plus d'informations sur les fonctionnalités du produit dans Astuces
3. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes pendant la mise à jour, vous pouvez obtenir de l'aide en contactant la hotline de service Honor ou en vous rendant dans un centre de services clients Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1040" name="it-ch">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento migliora principalmente le prestazioni del sistema. Esegui l'aggiornamento per usufruire dei miglioramenti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistema">
             <feature>• È supportata la disconnessione dal Wi-Fi e la visualizzazione della password</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Blocca schermo">
             <feature>• La schermata di blocco presenta uno stile orologio più grande e allungato. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Schermata Home e stile > Personalizzato > Tocca l'orologio per modificare</feature>
             <feature>• Ora puoi usare i video come sfondo, con effetti dinamici che durano fino a 10 secondi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• I telefoni Honor e gli iPhone possono ora condividere tra loro i messaggi di notifica</feature>
             <feature>• Una volta installata la versione più recente di HONOR WorkStation sul Mac, potrai sincronizzare le notifiche sul Mac grazie a Notifiche connesse</feature>
             <feature>• Installa la versione più recente di HONOR WorkStation sul Mac e potrai usare OneTap per trasferire immagini, video, file e altri contenuti dal tuo telefono Honor al Mac con un solo tocco</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Consumo di energia">
             <feature>• Viene ottimizzata la durata della batteria per una migliore esperienza utente in alcuni scenari</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilità">
             <feature>• Viene migliorata la stabilità del sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Patch di sicurezza">
             <feature>• È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (gennaio 2026) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza Honor, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Note" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup dei dati prima di procedere
2. Scopri ulteriori informazioni sulle funzioni del prodotto in Suggerimenti
3. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center Honor o visitando un centro servizio clienti Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2074" name="sr-ba">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se unapređuju performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u unapređenjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistem">
             <feature>• Podržava isključivanje sa Wi-Fi mreže i pregled lozinke</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zaključani ekran">
             <feature>• Zaključani ekran nudi veći i rastegnuti stil sata. Isprobajte ga tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Početni ekran i stil > Prilagođeno > Dodirnite sat da biste uredili</feature>
             <feature>• Sada možete da koristite video-zapise kao pozadinu, uz dinamičke efekte koji se reprodukuju do 10 sekundi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Povezivanje">
             <feature>• Honor telefoni i iPhone uređaji sada mogu da dele poruke obaveštenja jedni sa drugima</feature>
             <feature>• Uz najnoviji HONOR WorkStation instaliran na vašem Mac-u, Povezana obaveštenja vam omogućavaju da sinhronizujete obaveštenja sa vašim Mac-om</feature>
             <feature>• Instalirajte najnoviju verziju HONOR WorkStation na Mac, a zatim možete koristiti OneTap za prenos slika, video-zapisa, datoteka i drugog sadržaja sa vašeg Honor telefona na Mac jednim dodirom</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Potrošnja energije">
             <feature>• Optimizuje korisničko iskustvo sa trajanjem baterije u nekim scenarijima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Poboljšava stabilnost sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezbednosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (januar 2026.) je ugrađena zbog bezbednosti sistema. Više informacija o Honor Security ažuriranjima potražite na našem veb-sajtu https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zabeleške" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka pre ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o karakteristikama proizvoda u odeljku Saveti
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete dobiti našu pomoć pozivom dežurne linije kompanije Honor ili posetom centru za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2074" name="sr-me">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se unapređuju performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u unapređenjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistem">
             <feature>• Podržava isključivanje sa Wi-Fi mreže i pregled lozinke</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Zaključani ekran">
             <feature>• Zaključani ekran nudi veći i rastegnuti stil sata. Isprobajte ga tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Početni ekran i stil > Prilagođeno > Dodirnite sat da biste uredili</feature>
             <feature>• Sada možete da koristite video-zapise kao pozadinu, uz dinamičke efekte koji se reprodukuju do 10 sekundi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Povezivanje">
             <feature>• Honor telefoni i iPhone uređaji sada mogu da dele poruke obaveštenja jedni sa drugima</feature>
             <feature>• Uz najnoviji HONOR WorkStation instaliran na vašem Mac-u, Povezana obaveštenja vam omogućavaju da sinhronizujete obaveštenja sa vašim Mac-om</feature>
             <feature>• Instalirajte najnoviju verziju HONOR WorkStation na Mac, a zatim možete koristiti OneTap za prenos slika, video-zapisa, datoteka i drugog sadržaja sa vašeg Honor telefona na Mac jednim dodirom</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Potrošnja energije">
             <feature>• Optimizuje korisničko iskustvo sa trajanjem baterije u nekim scenarijima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilnost">
             <feature>• Poboljšava stabilnost sistema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bezbednosna zakrpa">
             <feature>• Bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (januar 2026.) je ugrađena zbog bezbednosti sistema. Više informacija o Honor Security ažuriranjima potražite na našem veb-sajtu https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Zabeleške" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka pre ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o karakteristikama proizvoda u odeljku Saveti
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete dobiti našu pomoć pozivom dežurne linije kompanije Honor ili posetom centru za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1057" name="id-">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini utamanya meningkatkan kinerja sistem. Instal pembaruan untuk menikmati berbagai peningkatan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sistem">
             <feature>• Mendukung pemutusan dari Wi-Fi dan menampilkan kata sandi</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Layar kunci">
             <feature>• Layar kunci menawarkan gaya jam yang lebih besar dan direntangkan. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Gaya &amp; layar beranda > Khusus > Ketuk jam untuk mengedit</feature>
             <feature>• Anda kini dapat menggunakan video sebagai wallpaper, dengan efek dinamis yang diputar hingga 10 detik</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Koneksi">
             <feature>• Ponsel Honor dan iPhone kini dapat membagikan pesan notifikasi ke satu sama lain</feature>
             <feature>• Dengan HONOR WorkStation terbaru yang diinstal di Mac Anda, Notifikasi Terhubung memungkinkan Anda untuk menyinkronkan notifikasi ke Mac Anda</feature>
             <feature>• Instal versi terbaru HONOR WorkStation di Mac Anda, lalu Anda dapat menggunakan OneTap untuk mentransfer gambar, video, file, dan konten lainnya dari ponsel Honor ke Mac Anda dengan sekali ketuk</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Konsumsi daya">
             <feature>• Mengoptimalkan pengalaman pengguna usia baterai di skenario tertentu</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stabilitas">
             <feature>• Meningkatkan stabilitas sistem</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Penambal keamanan">
             <feature>• Patch keamanan Android (Januari 2026) telah diterapkan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan Honor, kunjungi situs web kami di https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Catatan" type="end">
             <feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan untuk mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui
2. Pelajari informasi selengkapnya terkait fitur produk di Kiat
3. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan Honor atau mengunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1037" name="he-">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה משפר בעיקר את ביצועי המערכת. עדכן כדי ליהנות מהשיפורים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="מערכת">
             <feature>‏• תומך בניתוק מ-Wi-Fi ובהצגת הסיסמה</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="מסך נעילה">
             <feature>‏• מסך הנעילה מאפשר סגנון שעון מוגדל ומתוח. כדי לנסות זאת, אפשר לעבור אל: הגדרות > מסך הבית וסגנון > מותאם אישית > להקיש על השעון כדי לערוך אותו</feature>
             <feature>‏• עכשיו אפשר להגדיר סרטונים בתור טפט, עם אפקטים דינמיים שפועלים למשך 10 שניות לכל היותר</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏‏Honor Connect">
             <feature>‏• טלפונים של Honor והתקני iPhone יכולים כעת לשתף זה עם זה התראות על הודעות</feature>
             <feature>‏• עם התקנת הגרסה העדכנית ביותר של HONOR WorkStation ב-Mac שברשותך, 'התראה מחוברת' תאפשר לך לסנכרן התראות עם אותו Mac</feature>
             <feature>‏• התקן את הגרסה העדכנית ביותר של HONOR WorkStation ב-Mac שברשותך, ולאחר מכן תוכל להשתמש ב-OneTap כדי להעביר בהקשה אחת תמונות, סרטונים, קבצים ותוכן אחר מטלפון Honor שברשותך לאותו Mac</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏צריכת חשמל">
             <feature>‏• ממטב את חוויית המשתמש עם חיי הסוללה בתרחישים מסוימים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="יציבות">
             <feature>‏‏• משפר את יציבות המערכת</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="תיקון אבטחה">
             <feature>‏• 'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מינו' 2026) נכלל למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של Honor', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="הערות" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון
‏2. גלה מידע נוסף על תכונות המוצר ב'טיפים'
‏3. אם תיתקל בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, ניתן לקבל עזרה מאיתנו באמצעות התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של Honor או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1124" name="fil-ph">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Minamahal na user, pangunahing pinapahusay ng update na ito ang performance ng system. I-update para i-enjoy ang mga pagpapahusay</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="System">
             <feature>• Sinusuportahan ang pagdiskonekta mula sa Wi-Fi at pagtingin sa password</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Lock screen">
             <feature>• Nag-aalok ang lock screen ng mas malaki at mas mahabang estilo ng orasan. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Home screen at estilo > Custom > I-tap ang orasan para i-edit ito</feature>
             <feature>• Puwede mo nang gamitin ang mga video bilang wallpaper, kung saan nagpe-play ang mga dynamic na effect hanggang sa 10 segundo</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Puwede nang magbahagi ang mga telepono ng Honor at iPhone ng mga mensaheng notification sa isa't isa</feature>
             <feature>• Dahil naka-install sa iyong Mac ang HONOR WorkStation, nagbibigay-daan sa iyo ang Mga Nakakonektang Notification na i-sync ang mga notification sa iyong Mac</feature>
             <feature>• I-install ang pinakabagong bersyon ng HONOR WorkStation sa iyong Mac, pagkatapos ay puwede mong gamitin ang OneTap para maglipat ng mga larawan, video, file, at iba pang content mula sa iyong telepono ng Honor patungo sa iyong Mac sa isang tap</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pagkonsumo ng power">
             <feature>• Ino-optimize ang karanasan ng user sa tagal ng baterya sa ilang sitwasyon</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stability">
             <feature>• Pinapahusay ang stability ng system</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Panseguridad na patch">
             <feature>• Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Ene 2026) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng Honor, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2026/1</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Mga Tala" type="end">
             <feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto ang pag-install sa update na ito sa iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update
2. Tuklasin ang higit pang impormasyon sa mga feature ng produkto sa Mga Tip
3. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, makukuha mo ang tulong namin sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng Honor o pagbisita sa customer service center ng Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <imgs>
            </imgs>
</root>