<root>
    <component name="TCPU" version="请自行修改"></component>
    <default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
    <language code="2052" name="zh-cn">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新主要针对系统进行了优化，推荐您进行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="桌面">
            <feature>•  新增通透模式，提升卡片、文件夹等元素的通透效果，带来极致通透体验。体验路径：设置 > 桌面和个性化 > 桌面设置 > 通透模式</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="荣耀钱包">
            <feature>•  新增门禁卡功能，支持模拟未经加密过的门禁卡</feature>
			<feature>•  新增空白卡功能。体验路径：设置 > 荣耀钱包 > 门禁卡</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="更新注意事项" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份
2. 更多精彩功能介绍，请访问“玩机技巧”应用
3. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="en-us">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Dear user, this update mainly enhances the system performance. Update to enjoy the improvements</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Home screen">
            <feature>• Transparency mode optimizes the transparency effects of elements such as cards and folders, delivering an exceptional visual experience. Try it out by going to: Settings > Home screen &amp; style > Home screen settings > Transparency mode</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• Access card feature supports the simulation of unencrypted access cards</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Wallet includes Blank card feature. Try it out by going to: Settings > Honor Wallet > Access card</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating
2. Discover more information on product features in Tips
3. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling Honor service hotline or visiting Honor customer service center</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1118" name="am-ET">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ ይህ ዝማኔ በዋነኛነት የስርዓቱን አፈጻጸም ያሻሽላል። በማሻሻያዎቹ ለመደሰት ያዘምኑ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="መነሻ ገጽ">
            <feature>• የግልጽነት ሁነታው እንደ ካርዶች እና አቃፊዎች ያሉ የክፍለ-አካላት የግልጽነት ተጽዕኖዎችን ያተባል፣ በዚህም ልዩ የሆነ ምስላዊ ተሞክሮን ያቀርባል። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > መነሻ ማያ ገጽ እና ቅጥ > የመነሻ ማያ ቅንብሮች > የግልጽነት ሁነታ</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor ዋሌት">
            <feature>• የመዳረሻ ካርድ ባህሪ ያልተመሰጠሩ የመዳረሻ ካርዶችን ማስመሰል ይደግፋል</feature>
			<feature>• የHonor ዋሌት ባዶ ካርድ ባህሪን ያካትታል። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > Honor ዋሌት > የመዳረሻ ካርድ</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="ማስታወሻዎች" type="end">
             <feature>1. ይህን ዝማኔ መጫን በእርስዎ የግል ውሂብ ላይ ተጽዕኖ አያሳርፍም፣ ነገር ግን አሁንም ከማዘመንዎ በፊት የውሂብዎን መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ ይመከራል
2. በጠቃሚ ምክሮች ውስጥ ስለምርት ባህሪያት ተጨማሪ መረጃ ያግኙ
3. በዝማኔው ጊዜ ማናቸውም ችግሮች ካጋጠሙዎት ወደ የHonor አገልግሎት ቀጥታ መስመር በመደወል ወይም የHonor ደንበኛ አገልግሎት ማዕከልን በመጎብኘት የእኛን እርዳታ ማግኘት ይችላሉ</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="3073" name="ar-eg">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، يحسّن هذا التحديث أداء النظام بشكل أساسي. للاستمتاع بالتحسينات، ما عليك سوى التحديث</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="الشاشة الرئيسية">
            <feature>• يحسّن وضع الشفافية تأثيرات الشفافية على عناصر مثل البطاقات والمجلدات، مما يؤدي إلى تقديم تجربة بصرية استثنائية. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > الشاشة الرئيسية والنمط > إعدادات الشاشة الرئيسية > وضع الشفافية</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="محفظة Honor">
            <feature>• تدعم ميزة بطاقة الدخول محاكاة بطاقات الدخول غير المشفرة</feature>
			<feature>• تتضمن محفظة Honor ميزة البطاقة الفارغة. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > محفظة Honor > بطاقة الدخول</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="ملاحظات" type="end">
             <feature>1. لن يؤثر تثبيت هذا التحديث على بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن لا يزال من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية لبياناتك قبل التحديث
2. اكتشف المزيد من المعلومات حول ميزات المنتج في تطبيق التلميحات
3. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيمكنك الحصول على مساعدتنا عن طريق الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة عملاء Honor أو زيارة مركز خدمة عملاء Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1101" name="as-IN">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই আপডেটটোৱে মূলতঃ ছিষ্টেমৰ কাৰ্যদক্ষতা উন্নত কৰে। উন্নতিসমূহৰ আনন্দ ল'বলৈ আপডেট কৰক</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="হোম স্ক্ৰীণ">
            <feature>• স্বচ্ছতা মোডে কাৰ্ড আৰু ফ'ল্ডাৰৰ দৰে উপাদানসমূহৰ স্বচ্ছতা প্ৰভাৱ অনুকূলন কৰে, যিয়ে এক ব্যতিক্ৰমী দৃশ্যমান অভিজ্ঞতা প্ৰদান কৰে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ এইটো ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ছেটিংছ > হোম স্ক্ৰীণ আৰু শৈলী > হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ ছেটিংছ > স্বচ্ছতা মোড</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor ৱালেট">
            <feature>• এক্সেচ কাৰ্ড ফিচাৰে এনক্ৰিপ্ট নকৰা এক্সেচ কাৰ্ডসমূহৰ চিমুলেচন সমৰ্থন কৰে</feature>
			<feature>• Honor ৱালেটত খালী কাৰ্ডৰ ফিচাৰ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত আছে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ এইটো ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: ছেটিংছ > Honor ৱালেট > এক্সেচ কাৰ্ড</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="টোকাসমূহ" type="end">
             <feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটাত প্ৰভাৱ নপৰিব, কিন্তু আপডেট কৰাৰ পূৰ্বে আপোনাৰ ডাটাৰ বেক আপ ল'বলৈ এতিয়াও পৰামৰ্শ দিয়া হয়
2. আভাসত প্ৰ'ডাক্টৰ ফিচাৰসমূহৰ ওপৰত অধিক তথ্য অনুসন্ধান কৰক
3. আপুনি আপডেটৰ সময়ত কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হ'লে, আপুনি Honor সেৱা হটলাইনত কল কৰি বা Honor গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ গৈ সহায় লাভ কৰিব পাৰে</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1068" name="az-az">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, bu yeniləmə əsasən sistemin performansını artırır. Təkmilləşdirmələrdən yararlanmaq üçün yeniləyin</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Əsas ekran">
            <feature>• Şəffaflıq rejimi kartlar və qovluqlar kimi elementlərin şəffaflıq effektlərini optimallaşdıraraq müstəsna vizual təcrübə təqdim edir. Buraya keçərək sınaqdan keçirin: Parametrlər > Əsas ekran və üslub > Əsas ekran parametrləri > Şəffaflıq rejimi</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Pul kisəsi">
            <feature>• Giriş kartı xüsusiyyəti şifrələnməmiş giriş kartlarının simulyasiyasını dəstəkləyir</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Pul kisəsinə Boş kart xüsusiyyəti daxildir. Buraya keçərək sınayın: Parametrlər > Honor Pul kisəsi > Giriş kartı</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Qeydlər" type="end">
             <feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınıza təsir etməyəcək, lakin yenə də yeniləməmişdən əvvəl verilənlərin ehtiyat nüsxəsini çıxarmaq tövsiyə olunur
2. İpuclarında məhsul xüsusiyyətləri haqqında daha çox məlumat əldə edin
3. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlə qarşılaşsanız, Honor xidmət qaynar xəttinə zəng etməklə və ya Honor müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə yaxınlaşaraq yardım ala bilərsiniz</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="jv-id">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran iki utamane ningkatake kinerja sistem. Anyarake kanggo ngrasakake pangapikane</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Layar ngarep">
            <feature>• Mode transparansi ngoptimalake efek transparansi unsur, kayata kertu lan folder saengga menehi pangalaman visual sing apik banget. Coba kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Layar ngarep &amp; gaya > Setelan layar ngarep > Mode transparansi</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Dompet Honor">
            <feature>• Fitur Kertu akses ndhukung simulasi kertu akses sing ora dienkripsi</feature>
			<feature>• Dompet Honor ngatutake fitur Kertu kosong. Coba kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Dompet Honor > Kertu akses</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Cathetan" type="end">
             <feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mengaruhi data pribadi sampeyan, nanging nggawe serep data dhisik tetep disaranake sadurunge nganyarake
2. Temokake informasi liyane babagan fitur prodhuk ing Tips
3. Yen ana masalah sajrone panganyaran, sampeyan bisa entuk bantuan kita kanthi nelpon hotline layanan Honor utawa nekani pusat layanan pelanggan Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2074" name="sr-rs">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se unapređuju performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u unapređenjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Početni ekran">
            <feature>• Režim providnosti optimizuje efekte providnosti elemenata kao što su kartice i fascikle, pružajući izuzetno vizuelno iskustvo. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Početni ekran i stil > Podešavanja početnog ekrana > Režim providnosti</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Novčanik">
            <feature>• Funkcija Kartica za pristup podržava simulaciju nešifriranih kartica za pristup</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Novčanik obuhvata funkciju Prazna kartica. Isprobajte je tako što ćete otići na sledeću lokaciju: Podešavanja > Honor Novčanik > Kartica za pristup</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Zabeleške" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka pre ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o karakteristikama proizvoda u odeljku Saveti
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete dobiti našu pomoć pozivom dežurne linije kompanije Honor ili posetom centru za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1059" name="be-by">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта абнаўленне ў асноўным паляпшае прадукцыйнасць сістэмы. Каб палепшыць уражанні ад выкарыстання, устанавіце абнаўленне</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Галоўны экран">
            <feature>• Рэжым празрыстасці аптымізуе эфекты празрыстасці элементаў, такіх як карткі і папкі, што забяспечвае ўнікальны візуальны досвед. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Галоўны экран і стыль > Налады галоўнага экрана > Рэжым празрыстасці»</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Кашалёк Honor">
            <feature>• Функцыя карткі доступу падтрымлівае сімуляцыю незашыфраваных картак доступу</feature>
			<feature>• Кашалёк Honor уключае функцыю «Пустая картка». Каб паспрабаваць яе, прайдзіце ў меню Налады > Кашалёк Honor > Картка доступу</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Нататкі" type="end">
             <feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не закране вашы асабістыя даныя. Тым не менш рэкамендуецца стварыць рэзервовую копію даных перад абнаўленнем
2. Больш падрабязная інфармацыя аб характарыстыках прадукту даступная ў Падказках
3. Калі вы сутыкняцеся з праблемамі падчас абнаўлення, вы можаце атрымаць нашу дапамогу, патэлефанаваўшы на гарачую лінію службы падтрымкі кліентаў Honor або наведаўшы цэнтр абслугоўвання кліентаў Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1026" name="bg-bg">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Уважаеми потребители, тази актуализация подобрява основно ефективността на системата. Актуализирайте, за да се насладите на подобренията</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Начален екран">
            <feature>• Режимът на прозрачност оптимизира ефектите на прозрачност на елементи като карти и папки, осигурявайки изключително визуално изживяване. Изпробвайте, като отидете на: „Настройки > Стил и начален екран > Настройки на началния екран > Режим на прозрачност“</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Портфейл">
            <feature>• Функцията „Карта за достъп“ поддържа симулация на нешифровани карти за достъп</feature>
			<feature>• „Honor Портфейл“ включва функция „Празна карта“. Изпробвайте, като отидете на: „Настройки > Honor Портфейл > Карта за достъп“</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Бележки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да се отрази на вашите лични данни, но все пак е препоръчително да архивирате данните си преди актуализиране
2. Открийте повече информация за характеристиките на продукта в „Съвети“
3. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализацията, можете да получите нашата помощ, като се обадите на горещата линия за обслужване на Honor или посетите сервизен център на клиенти на Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2117" name="bn-bd">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই আপডেটটি মূলত সিস্টেমের কর্মক্ষমতা বাড়ায়। উন্নতি উপভোগ করতে আপডেট করুন</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="হোম স্ক্রিন">
            <feature>• স্বচ্ছতা মোড কার্ড এবং ফোল্ডারের মতো জিনিসগুলির ট্রান্সপারেন্সি এফেক্টগুলিকে অপ্টিমাইজ করে একটি ব্যতিক্রমী ভিজ্যুয়াল অভিজ্ঞতা প্রদান করে। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > হোম স্ক্রিন এবং স্টাইল > হোম স্ক্রিন সেটিংস > স্বচ্ছতা মোড</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor ওয়ালেট">
            <feature>• অ্যাক্সেস কার্ড ফিচারটি এনক্রিপ্ট না করা অ্যাক্সেস কার্ডের সিমুলেশনকে সমর্থন করে</feature>
			<feature>• Honor ওয়ালেটে ফাঁকা কার্ড ফিচারটি অন্তর্ভুক্ত আছে। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > Honor ওয়ালেট > অ্যাক্সেস কার্ড</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="নোট" type="end">
             <feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে তা আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটাকে প্রভাবিত করবে না, তবুও আপডেট করার আগে আপনার ডেটা ব্যাক আপ করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়
2. পরামর্শ-এ পণ্যের ফিচাতগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্য জানুন
3. আপডেট হওয়ার সময় আপনি কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে Honor সেবা হটলাইনে কল করে বা Honor গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে গিয়ে আমাদের সহায়তা পেতে পারেন</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1105" name="bo-cn">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནི་གཙོ་བོ་རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ལ་དམིགས་ནས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུའི་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ཅོག་ངོས།">
            <feature>• དྭངས་གསལ་རྣམ་པ་གསར་སྣོན། བྱང་བུ་དང་ཡིག་ཆ་སོགས་གཞི་རྒྱུའི་དྭངས་གསལ་ཁྱད་ནུས་མཐོར་འདེགས་གཏོང་ཆེད། དྭངས་གསལ་ཉམས་ལེན་མཐར་སོན་ཁྱེར་ཡོང་། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་ཅོག་ངོས་དང་སྒེར་གཤིས་ཅན། དེ་ནས་ཅོག་ངོས་སྒྲིག་འགོད། དེ་ནས་དྭངས་གསལ་རྣམ་པ།</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="རུང་ཡོའོ་དངུལ་ཁུག">
            <feature>• སྒོ་སྲུང་བྱང་བུའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། གསང་རྒྱ་ཅན་མིན་པའི་སྒོ་སྲུང་བྱང་བུ་ལ་ལད་ཟློས་བྱེད་པར་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
			<feature>• བྱང་བུ་སྟོང་པའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་རུང་ཡོའོ་དངུལ་ཁུག དེ་ནས་སྒོ་སྲུང་བྱང་བུ།</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
             <feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གཞི་གྲངས་སུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་སྔོན་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. དེ་ལས་མང་བའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་ལེགས་པོའི་ངོ་སྤྲོད་ཐད་ཁ་པར་རྩེ་བའི་ལག་རྩལ་གྱི་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱ་རོགས།
3. གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་པའི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད་དུ། གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ། ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་མཁོ་མཁན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་ཕེབས་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་འཚོལ་རོགས།</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="5146" name="bs-ba">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo ažuriranje uglavnom poboljšava performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da uživate u poboljšanjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Početni ekran">
            <feature>• Način providnosti optimizira efekte providnosti elemenata kao što su kartice i fascikle, pružajući izuzetno vizuelno iskustvo. Isprobajte funkciju tako što ćete otići na: Postavke > Početni ekran i stil > Postavke početnog ekrana > Način providnosti</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor novčanik">
            <feature>• Funkcija Pristupne kartice podržava simulaciju nešifriranih pristupnih kartica</feature>
			<feature>• Honor novčanik uključuje funkciju Prazna kartica. Isprobajte funkciju tako što ćete otići na: Postavke > Honor novčanik > Pristupna kartica</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Bilješke" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja ne utiče na lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o funkcijama proizvoda u Savjetima
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete zatražiti našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati Honor dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetiti Honor servisni centar za korisnike</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1027" name="ca-es">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització millora principalment el rendiment del sistema. Actualitzeu-la per gaudir de les millores</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla inicial">
            <feature>• El Mode de transparència optimitza els efectes de transparència d'elements com ara targetes i carpetes, la qual cosa ofereix una experiència visual excepcional. Per provar-ho, aneu a Configuració > Pantalla inicial i estil > Configuració de la pantalla inicial > Mode de transparència</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Cartera">
            <feature>• La funció de targeta d'accés admet la simulació de targetes d'accés sense xifrar</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Cartera inclou la funció Targeta en blanc. Per provar-la, aneu a Configuració > Honor Cartera > Targeta d'accés</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. El fet d'instal·lar aquesta actualització no afectarà les vostres dades personals, però es recomana fer una còpia de seguretat de les dades abans d'iniciar l'actualització
2. Descobriu més informació sobre les funcions del producte a Suggeriments
3. Si trobeu algun problema durant l'actualització, per obtenir la nostra ajuda truqueu a la Línia directa d'atenció al client d'Honor o visiteu el Centre d'atenció al client d'Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1029" name="cs-cz">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Vážený uživateli, tato aktualizace především zvyšuje výkon systému. Aktualizujte, abyste si mohli užít vylepšení</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Domovská obrazovka">
            <feature>• Režim průhlednosti optimalizuje efekty průhlednosti prvků, jako jsou karty a složky, a poskytuje tak výjimečný vizuální zážitek. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce Nastavení > Domovská obrazovka a styl > Nastavení domovské obrazovky > Režim průhlednosti</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Peněženka">
            <feature>• Funkce přístupové karty podporuje simulaci nešifrovaných přístupových karet.</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Peněženka obsahuje funkci Prázdná karta. Vyzkoušejte ji v nabídce Nastavení > Honor Peněženka > Přístupová karta</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Poznámky" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalace této aktualizace neovlivní vaše osobní data, ale přesto doporučujeme před aktualizací zálohovat data.
2. Další informace o funkcích produktu najdete v aplikaci Tipy.
3. Pokud během aktualizace narazíte na nějaké problémy, zavolejte na informační linku Honor nebo navštivte Centrum služeb zákazníkům Honor.</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1030" name="da-dk">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Kære bruger. Denne opdatering forbedrer hovedsageligt systemets ydeevne. Opdater for at drage nytte af forbedringerne</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Startskærm">
            <feature>• Gennemsigtighedstilstand optimerer gennemsigtighedseffekterne for elementer såsom kort og mapper og giver en enestående visuel oplevelse. Prøv det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Startskærm og stil > Indstillinger for startskærm > Gennemsigtighedstilstand</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Tegnebog">
            <feature>• Adgangskortfunktion understøtter simulering af ukrypterede adgangskort</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Tegnebog indeholder en Blank kort-funktion. Prøv den ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Honor Tegnebog > Adgangskort</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Noter" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering påvirker ikke dine personlige data, men vi anbefaler alligevel, at du sikkerhedskopierer dine data inden opdateringen
2. Få flere oplysninger om produktfunktioner i Tips
3. Hvis du oplever problemer under opdateringen, kan du få hjælp ved at ringe til Honors servicehotline eller besøge Honors kundeservicecenter</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1031" name="de-de">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung verbessert hauptsächlich die Systemleistung. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Startbildschirm">
            <feature>• Der Transparenzmodus optimiert die Transparenzeffekte von Elementen wie Karten und Ordnern und sorgt so für ein außergewöhnliches Anzeigeerlebnis. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Startbildschirm und Stil > Startbildschirmeinstellungen > Transparenzmodus</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• Die Funktion Zugangskarte unterstützt die Simulation unverschlüsselter Zugangskarten</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Wallet enthält die Funktion Blankokarte. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Honor Wallet > Zugangskarte</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notizen" type="end">
             <feature>1. Die Installation dieses Updates hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, es wird jedoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen
2. Entdecken Sie weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen in Tipps
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Honor-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein Honor-Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1032" name="el-gr">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιώνει κυρίως την απόδοση του συστήματος. Πραγματοποιήστε ενημέρωση για να απολαύσετε τις βελτιώσεις</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Αρχική οθόνη">
            <feature>• Η Λειτουργία διαφάνειας βελτιστοποιεί τα εφέ διαφάνειας στοιχείων όπως κάρτες και φάκελοι, προσφέροντας μια εξαιρετική οπτική εμπειρία. Δοκιμάστε αυτή τη λειτουργία μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Αρχική οθόνη και στυλ > Ρυθμίσεις αρχικής οθόνης > Λειτουργία διαφάνειας</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Πορτοφόλι Honor">
            <feature>• Η δυνατότητα κάρτας πρόσβασης υποστηρίζει την προσομοίωση μη κρυπτογραφημένων καρτών πρόσβασης</feature>
			<feature>• Το Πορτοφόλι Honor περιλαμβάνει τη δυνατότητα «Κενή κάρτα». Δοκιμάστε αυτή τη λειτουργία μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Πορτοφόλι Honor > Κάρτα πρόσβασης</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Σημειώσεις" type="end">
             <feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα επηρεάσει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, αλλά ακόμη και έτσι συνιστάται η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας των δεδομένων σας πριν από την ενημέρωση
2. Ανακαλύψτε περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις δυνατότητες του προϊόντος στις Συμβουλές
3. Αν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, μπορείτε να λάβετε τη βοήθειά μας καλώντας την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή εξυπηρέτησης της Honor ή με επίσκεψη σε ένα κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2057" name="en-GB">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Dear user, this update mainly enhances the system performance. Update to enjoy the improvements</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Home screen">
            <feature>• Transparency mode optimizes the transparency effects of elements such as cards and folders, delivering an exceptional visual experience. Try it out by going to: Settings > Home screen &amp; style > Home screen settings > Transparency mode</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• Access card feature supports the simulation of unencrypted access cards</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Wallet includes Blank card feature. Try it out by going to: Settings > Honor Wallet > Access card</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating
2. Discover more information on product features in Tips
3. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling Honor service hotline or visiting Honor customer service centre</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1034" name="es-es">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado/a usuario/a, esta actualización mejora principalmente el rendimiento del sistema. Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla principal">
            <feature>• El modo de transparencia optimiza los efectos de transparencia de elementos como tarjetas y carpetas, lo que ofrece una experiencia visual excepcional. Pruébelo en Ajustes > Pantalla principal y estilo > Ajustes pantalla principal > Modo de transparencia</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• La funcionalidad de tarjeta de acceso admite la simulación de tarjetas de acceso no cifradas</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Wallet incluye una función de tarjeta en blanco. Pruébela en: Ajustes > Honor Wallet > Tarjeta de acceso</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar
2. Descubra más información sobre las características de los productos en Sugerencias
3. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, puede obtener nuestra ayuda si llama a la línea de atención al cliente de Honor o si visita el centro de servicios al cliente de Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="21514" name="es-us">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización mejora principalmente el rendimiento del sistema. Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla principal">
            <feature>• El Modo transparente optimiza los efectos de transparencia de elementos como tarjetas y carpetas, ofreciendo una experiencia visual excepcional. Pruebe la función en: Ajustes > Pantalla principal y estilo > Ajustes de pantalla principal > Modo transparente</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• La función Tarjeta de acceso permite simular tarjetas de acceso sin cifrar</feature>
			<feature>• Billetera de Honor incluye la función de tarjeta en blanco. Puede probar esta opción si va a: Ajustes > Billetera de Honor > Tarjeta de acceso</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de respaldo de sus datos antes de actualizar
2. Descubra más información sobre las funciones del producto en Sugerencias
3. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, puede llamar a la línea de atención al cliente de Honor o visitar el centro de servicios al cliente de Honor para recibir asistencia</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1061" name="et-ee">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hea kasutaja! See värskendus parandab peamiselt süsteemi jõudlust. Värskendage täiustuste nautimiseks</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Avakuva">
            <feature>• Läbipaistvusrežiim optimeerib elementide, nagu kaartide ja kaustade läbipaistvuse efekte, pakkudes erakordset visuaalset kogemust. Proovige seda, avades Sätted > Avakuva ja stiil > Avakuva sätted > Läbipaistvusrežiim</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honori rahakott">
            <feature>• Pääsukaardi funktsioon toetab krüptimata pääsukaartide simuleerimist</feature>
			<feature>• Honori rahakott sisaldab tühja kaardi funktsiooni. Proovige seda, avades Sätted > Honori rahakott > Pääsukaart</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Märkused" type="end">
             <feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei mõjuta teie isiklikke andmeid, aga soovitame ikkagi enne värskendamist andmed varundada
2. Toote funktsioonide kohta leiate lisateavet rakendusest Tips
3. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, saate meilt abi, helistades Honori klienditoe infoliinile või külastades Honori klienditeeninduskeskust</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1069" name="eu-es">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Erabiltzaile agurgarria: eguneratze honek sistemaren errendimendua hobetzen du nagusiki. Eguneratu hobekuntzez gozatzeko</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Hasierako pantaila">
            <feature>• Gardentasun moduak txartelen, karpeten eta antzeko elementuen gardentasun-efektuak optimizatzen ditu, ikusizko esperientzia bikaina emanez. Probatzeko, joan hona: Ezarpenak > Hasierako pantaila eta estiloa > Hasierako pantailako ezarpenak > Gardentasun modua</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Diru-zorroa">
            <feature>• Sartzeko txartelaren eginbideak enkriptatu gabeko sartzeko txartelen simulazioa onartzen du</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Diru-zorroak Txartel hutsa eginbidea du. Probatzeko, joan hona: Ezarpenak > Honor Diru-zorroa > Sartzeko txartela</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Oharrak" type="end">
             <feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzeak ez du eraginik izango datu pertsonaletan, baina, eguneratu baino lehen, datuen babeskopia egitea gomendatzen da
2. Ezagutu produktuaren eginbideei buruzko informazio gehiago Aholkuak atalean
3. Eguneratzean arazoren bat baduzu, gure laguntza eska dezakezu Honor-en telefonozko arreta-lineara deituz edo Honor-en bezeroaren zerbitzu-zentrora joanez</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1065" name="fa-ir">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>کاربر گرامی، این به‌روزرسانی به‌طور عمده عملکرد سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد. با انجام این به‌روزرسانی، از این بهبودها بهره‌مند شوید</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏صفحۀ اصلی">
            <feature>‏• حالت شفافیت، جلوه‌های شفاف عناصر مختلف مانند کارت‌ها و پوشه‌ها را بهینه می‌کند و تجربهٔ بصری منحصربه‌فردی ارائه می‌دهد. برای امتحان کردن آن، این مسیر را طی کنید: تنظیمات > صفحۀ اصلی و سبک > تنظیمات صفحۀ اصلی > حالت شفافیت</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="کیف پول Honor">
            <feature>‏‏• قابلیت «کارت دسترسی» از شبیه‌سازی کارت‌های دسترسی رمزگذاری‌نشده پشتیبانی می‌کند</feature>
			<feature>‏• «کیف پول Honor» شامل قابلیت «کارت خالی» است. آن را با طی کردن این مسیر امتحان کنید: تنظیمات > کیف پول Honor > کارت دسترسی</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="یادداشت‌ها" type="end">
             <feature>‏۱. نصب این به‌روزرسانی روی داده‌های شخصی شما تأثیری نخواهد داشت. بااین‌وجود، توصیه می‌شود قبل از به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید
‏۲. اطلاعات بیشتر مربوط به قابلیت‌های محصول را در «نکات» می‌توانید بیابید
‏۳. اگر در طول به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، می‌توانید از طریق تماس با تلفن مستقیم خدمات Honor یا مراجعه به مرکز خدمات مشتریان Honor از ما کمک بگیرید</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1035" name="fi-fi">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä päivitys parantaa ensisijaisesti järjestelmän suorituskykyä. Päivitä, niin pääset nauttimaan parannuksista</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Aloitusnäyttö">
            <feature>• Läpinäkyvyystila optimoi korttien ja kansioiden kaltaisten elementtien läpinäkyvyystehosteet tarjoten poikkeuksellisen visuaalisen kokemuksen. Voit kokeilla sitä seuraavassa kohdassa: Asetukset > Aloitusnäyttö ja tyyli > Aloitusnäytön asetukset > Läpinäkyvyystila</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• Kulkukortti-ominaisuus tukee salaamattomien kulkukorttien simulointia</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Walletiin sisältyy Tyhjä kortti -ominaisuus. Voit kokeilla sitä seuraavassa kohdassa: Asetukset > Honor Wallet > Kulkukortti</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Muistiinpanot" type="end">
             <feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei vaikuta henkilökohtaisiin tietoihisi, mutta tietojen varmuuskopiointi ennen päivittämistä on kuitenkin suositeltavaa
2. Lisätietoja tuoteominaisuuksista on Vihjeitä-sovelluksessa
3. Jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia, saat apua soittamalla Honorin palvelunumeroon tai käymällä Honorin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1036" name="fr-fr">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour améliore principalement les performances du système. Effectuez la mise à jour pour profiter des améliorations</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Écran d'accueil">
            <feature>• Le mode transparence optimise les effets de transparence d'éléments tels que les cartes et les dossiers, procurant une expérience visuelle exceptionnelle. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Écran d'accueil et style > Paramètres de l'écran d'accueil > Mode transparence</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• La fonction Carte d'accès prend en charge la simulation de cartes d'accès non cryptées</feature>
			<feature>• Portefeuille Honor comprend la fonctionnalité Carte vierge. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Portefeuille Honor > Carte d'accès</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour
2. Découvrez plus d'informations sur les fonctionnalités du produit dans Astuces
3. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes pendant la mise à jour, vous pouvez obtenir de l'aide en contactant la hotline de service Honor ou en vous rendant dans un centre de services clients Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1110" name="gl-es">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado usuario, a novidade principal desta actualización é a mellora do rendemento do sistema. Realice a actualización para gozar das melloras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pantalla de inicio">
            <feature>• O modo de transparencia optimiza os efectos de transparencia de elementos como tarxetas e carpetas, o que ofrece unha experiencia visual excepcional. Próbeo facendo o seguinte: Configuración > Pantalla de inicio e estilo > Configuración da pantalla de inicio > Modo de transparencia</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Moedeiro Honor">
            <feature>• A funcionalidade Tarxeta de acceso é compatible coa simulación de tarxetas de acceso sen cifrar</feature>
			<feature>• Moedeiro Honor inclúe a funcionalidade Tarxeta en branco. Próbea facendo o seguinte: Configuración > Moedeiro Honor > Tarxeta de acceso</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalar esta actualización non afectará os seus datos persoais, pero recoméndase que realice unha copia de seguranza dos datos antes da actualización
2. Descubra máis información sobre as funcionalidades do produto en Consellos
3. Se experimenta problemas durante a actualización, pode chamar á liña directa de servizo de Honor ou ir a un centro de servizos ao cliente de Honor para que lle fornezamos axuda</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1095" name="gu-IN">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ અપડેટ મુખ્યત્વે સિસ્ટમની કામગીરીને વધારે છે. સુધારાનો આનંદ માણવા માટે અપડેટ કરો</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="હોમ સ્ક્રીન">
            <feature>• પારદર્શિતા મોડ કાર્ડ્સ અને ફોલ્ડર્સ જેવા તત્વોના પારદર્શિતા પ્રભાવોને ઑપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે, જે એક અસાધારણ દ્રશ્ય અનુભવ પ્રદાન કરે છે. અહીં જઈને તેને અજમાવી જુઓ: સેટિંગ્સ > હોમ સ્ક્રીન અને શૈલી > હોમ સ્ક્રીન સેટિંગ > પારદર્શિતા મોડ</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor વૉલેટ">
            <feature>• ઍક્સેસ કાર્ડ સુવિધા એન્ક્રિપ્ટ કરેલ ન હોય તેવા ઍક્સેસ કાર્ડના સિમ્યુલેશનનું સમર્થન કરે છે</feature>
			<feature>• Honor વૉલેટમાં ખાલી કાર્ડની સુવિધા શામેલ છે. સેટિંગ્સ > Honor વૉલેટ > ઍક્સેસ કાર્ડ પર જઈને તેને અજમાવી જુઓ</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="નોંધો" type="end">
             <feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારા વ્યક્તિગત ડેટાને અસર થશે નહીં, પરંતુ અપડેટ કરતા પહેલાં તમારા ડેટાનો બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે
2. ટિપ્સમાં ઉત્પાદન સુવિધાઓ વિશે વધુ માહિતી મેળવો
3. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો તમે Honor સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરીને અથવા Honor ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્રની મુલાકાત લઈને અમારી મદદ મેળવી શકો છો</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1081" name="hi-in">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>नमस्ते उपयोगकर्ता, इस अद्यतन से मुख्य रूप से सिस्टम प्रदर्शन को बढ़ाया जाता है। सुधारों का फ़ायदा उठाने के लिए अद्यतन करें</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="होम स्क्रीन">
            <feature>• पारदर्शिता मोड से, कार्ड और फ़ोल्डर जैसे तत्वों के पारदर्शिता प्रभावों को अनुकूलित किया जाता है जिससे असाधारण विज़ुअल अनुभव प्राप्त होता है। यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़माएँ: सेटिंग्स > होम स्क्रीन और शैली > होम स्क्रीन सेटिंग्स > पारदर्शिता मोड</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor वॉलेट">
            <feature>• पहुँच कार्ड सुविधा में बिना एन्क्रिप्ट किए गए पहुँच कार्ड के सिमुलेशन का समर्थन किया जाता है</feature>
			<feature>• Honor वॉलेट में ब्लैंक कार्ड सुविधा शामिल है। यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़माएँ: सेटिंग्स > Honor वॉलेट > पहुँच कार्ड</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="नोट्स" type="end">
             <feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपके व्यक्तिगत डेटा पर कोई प्रभाव नहीं पड़ेगा, लेकिन फिर भी अद्यतन करने से पहले अपने डेटा का बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है
2. युक्तियाँ में जाकर उत्पाद की सुविधाओं के बारे में अधिक जानकारी खोजें
3. अगर आपको अद्यतन के दौरान कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो आप Honor सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करके या Honor ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाकर हमारी सहायता पा सकते हैं</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1050" name="hr-hr">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim se ažuriranjem uglavnom poboljšavaju performanse sustava. Ažurirajte kako biste uživali u poboljšanjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Početni zaslon">
            <feature>• Način transparentnosti optimizira efekte transparentnosti elemenata poput kartica i mapa za iznimno vizualno iskustvo. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Početni zaslon i stil > Postavke početnog zaslona > Način transparentnosti</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Novčanik">
            <feature>• Značajka Pristupna kartica podržava simulaciju nešifriranih pristupnih kartica</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Novčanik uključuje značajku Prazna kartica. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Honor Novčanik > Pristupna kartica</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Bilješke" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće utjecati na osobne podatke, ali se svejedno preporučuje izraditi sigurnosnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja
2. Idite u aplikaciju Savjeti kako biste doznali više informacija o značajkama proizvoda
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tijekom ažuriranja, našu pomoć možete dobiti tako da nazovete Honor dežurnu liniju ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1038" name="hu-hu">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez a frissítés elsősorban a rendszerteljesítményt javítja. Végezze el a frissítést, hogy élvezhesse a továbbfejlesztéseket</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Főképernyő">
            <feature>• Az Áttetszőség mód optimalizálja az olyan elemek, mint a kártyák és mappák átlátszósági hatásait, kivételes vizuális élményt nyújtva. Próbálja ki itt: Beállítások > Főképernyő és stílus > Főképernyő-beállítások > Áttetszőség mód</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Tárca">
            <feature>• A Belépőkártya funkció támogatja a titkosítatlan belépőkártyák szimulációját</feature>
			<feature>• A Honor Tárca tartalmazza az Üres kártya funkciót. Próbálja ki itt: Beállítások > Honor Tárca > Belépőkártya</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Jegyzetek" type="end">
             <feature>1. A jelen frissítés telepítése nem lesz hatással személyes adataira, de a frissítés előtt az adatokról továbbra is ajánlott biztonsági másolatot készíteni
2. A termékfunkciókkal kapcsolatos további információkat a Tippek alkalmazásban tekintheti meg
3. Ha a frissítés során bármilyen problémába ütközik, forduljon hozzánk segítségért a Honor-szerviz forródrótján, vagy látogasson el a Honor ügyfélszolgálati központjába</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1057" name="in-id">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini utamanya meningkatkan kinerja sistem. Instal pembaruan untuk menikmati berbagai peningkatan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Layar beranda">
            <feature>• Mode transparansi mengoptimalkan efek tembus pandang pada elemen seperti kartu dan folder sehingga menghadirkan pengalaman visual yang menakjubkan. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Gaya &amp; layar beranda > Pengaturan layar beranda > Mode transparansi</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Dompet">
            <feature>• Fitur Kartu akses mendukung simulasi kartu akses tanpa enkripsi</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Dompet menyertakan fitur Kartu kosong. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Honor Dompet > Kartu akses</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Catatan" type="end">
             <feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan untuk mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui
2. Pelajari informasi selengkapnya terkait fitur produk di Kiat
3. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan Honor atau mengunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1040" name="it-it">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento migliora principalmente le prestazioni del sistema. Esegui l'aggiornamento per usufruire dei miglioramenti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Schermata Home">
            <feature>• La modalità trasparenza ottimizza gli effetti di trasparenza di elementi quali schede e cartelle, offrendo un'esperienza visiva eccezionale. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Schermata Home e stile > Impostazioni schermata Home > Modalità trasparenza</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• La funzione delle carte di accesso supporta la simulazione delle carte di accesso non crittografate</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Wallet include la funzione Carta vuota. Per provarla, vai in: Impostazioni > Honor Wallet > Carta di accesso</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Note" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup dei dati prima di procedere
2. Scopri ulteriori informazioni sulle funzioni del prodotto in Suggerimenti
3. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center Honor o visitando un centro servizio clienti Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1037" name="iw-il">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה משפר בעיקר את ביצועי המערכת. עדכן כדי ליהנות מהשיפורים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="מסך הבית">
            <feature>‏• מצב 'שקיפות' ממטב את אפקטי השקיפות של אלמנטים כמו כרטיסים ותיקיות, לחוויה חזותית יוצאת מן הכלל. כדי לנסות אותו, אפשר לעבור אל: הגדרות > מסך הבית וסגנון > הגדרות מסך הבית > מצב 'שקיפות'</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="‏‏Honor Wallet">
            <feature>‏‏• תכונת כרטיסי הגישה תומכת בהדמיה של כרטיסי גישה לא מוצפנים</feature>
			<feature>‏• Honor Wallet כולל את התכונה 'כרטיס ריק'. כדי לנסות, אפשר לעבור אל: הגדרות > ‏‏Honor Wallet > כרטיס גישה</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="הערות" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון
‏2. גלה מידע נוסף על תכונות המוצר ב'טיפים'
‏3. אם תיתקל בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, ניתן לקבל עזרה מאיתנו באמצעות התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של Honor או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1041" name="ja-jp">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ユーザーの皆様、今回の更新では主にシステムのパフォーマンスが強化されます。更新して、改善をお楽しみください</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ホーム画面">
            <feature>• 透明モードでは、カードやフォルダなどの要素の透明効果が最適化され、非常に優れた視覚体験が実現します。この機能を試すには、[設定] > [ホーム画面とスタイル] > [ホーム画面設定] > [透明モード]に移動してください</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• カードキー機能では、暗号化されていないカードキーのシミュレーションがサポートされます</feature>
			<feature>• Honorウォレットに空のカード機能が含まれます。この機能を試すには、設定 > Honorウォレット > カードキーに移動してください</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="メモ" type="end">
             <feature>1. この更新をインストールしても個人情報への影響はありませんが、更新前に個人情報をバックアップしておくことをおすすめします
2. 製品機能の詳細はヒントアプリで確認してください
3. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、Honorサービスコールセンターにお電話をいただくか、Honorカスタマーサービスセンターにご来店いただき、サポートを受けてください</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1079" name="ka-ge">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ეს განახლება ძირითადად აუმჯობესებს სისტემის ეფექტიანობას. განაახლეთ და ისიამოვნეთ გაუმჯობესებებით</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="საწყისი ეკრანი">
            <feature>• გამჭვირვალობის რეჟიმი ოპტიმიზაციას უკეთებს ისეთი ელემენტების გამჭვირვალობის ეფექტებს, როგორიცაა ბარათები და საქაღალდეები, რაც განსაკუთრებულ ვიზუალურ გამოცდილებას უზრუნველყოფს. სცადეთ ეს შემდეგზე გადასვლით: პარამეტრები > საწყისი ეკრანი და სტილი > საწყისი ეკრანის პარამეტრები > გამჭვირვალობის რეჟიმი</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor საფულე">
            <feature>• წვდომის ბარათის ფუნქციას აქვს წვდომის დაუშიფრავი ბარათების სიმულაციის მხარდაჭერა</feature>
			<feature>• Honor საფულეს აქვს ცარიელი ბარათის ფუნქცია. სცადეთ ის შემდეგზე გადასვლით: პარამეტრები > Honor საფულე > წვდომის ბარათი</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="შენიშვნები" type="end">
             <feature>1. ამ განახლების დაინსტალირება არ იმოქმედებს თქვენს პერსონალურ მონაცემებზე, თუმცა რეკომენდებულია განახლებამდე მონაცემების სარეზერვო ასლის შექმნა
2. გაეცანით დამატებით ინფორმაციას რჩევებში პროდუქტის ფუნქციების შესახებ
3. თუ განახლებისას გარკვეულ პრობლემებს წააწყდით, დახმარებისთვის დარეკეთ Honor-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან ეწვიეთ Honor-ის სერვისცენტრს</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1087" name="kk-kz">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл жаңарту негізінен жүйе өнімділігін жақсартады. Жақсартуларды пайдалану үшін жаңартыңыз</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Негізгі экран">
            <feature>• Мөлдірлік режимі карталар мен қалталар сияқты элементтердің мөлдірлік әсерлерін оңтайландырады, ерекше визуалды тәжірибе береді. «Параметрлер» > «Негізгі экран және стиль» > «Негізгі экран параметрлері» > «Мөлдірлік режимі» тармағына өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor әмияны">
            <feature>• «Қатынасу картасы» мүмкіндігі шифрланбаған қатынасу карталарының имитациясын қолдайды</feature>
			<feature>• «Honor әмияны» қолданбасында «Бос карта» мүмкіндігі бар. «Параметрлер» > «Honor әмияны» > «Қатынасу картасы» тармағына өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Ескертпелер" type="end">
             <feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнату жеке деректеріңізге әсер етпейді, бірақ жаңарту алдында деректердің сақтық көшірмесін жасау ұсынылады
2. «Кеңестер» қолданбасында өнім мүмкіндіктері туралы қосымша ақпаратты табыңыз
3. Жаңарту кезінде қандай да бір мәселе орын алса, Honor қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне қоңырау шалу не Honor тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына бару арқылы көмегімізді ала аласыз</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1107" name="km-kh">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះធ្វើឱ្យប្រតិបត្តិការប្រព័ន្ធប្រសើរឡើងជាចម្បង។ ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព ដើម្បីរីករាយនឹងការកែលម្អទាំងនេះ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="អេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម">
            <feature>• ម៉ូដថ្លាធ្វើឱ្យប្រសើរឡើងនូវបែបផែនថ្លានៃធាតុដូចជាកាត និងថតឯកសារ ដោយផ្ដល់នូវបទពិសោធមើលឃើញដ៏ល្អឥតខ្ចោះ។ សាកល្បងប្រើដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ការកំណត់ > រចនាប័ទ្ម និងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម > ការកំណត់អេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម > ម៉ូដថ្លា</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor កាបូប">
            <feature>• មុខងារកាតចូលប្រើគាំទ្រការក្លែងធ្វើនៃកាតចូលប្រើដែលមិនបានអ៊ិនគ្រីប</feature>
			<feature>• Honor កាបូបរួមបញ្ចូលមុខងារកាតទទេ។ សាកល្បងវាដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > Honor កាបូប > កាតចូល</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់" type="end">
             <feature>1. ការដំឡើងបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះនឹងមិនប៉ះពាល់ដល់ទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួនរបស់អ្នកទេ ប៉ុន្តែសូមណែនាំឱ្យបម្រុងទុកទិន្នន័យរបស់អ្នក មុននឹងធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព
2. ស្វែងយល់បន្ថែមអំពីលក្ខណៈពិសេសផលិតផលនៅក្នុងគន្លឹះ
3. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបប្រទះបញ្ហាណាមួយអំឡុងពេលធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព អ្នកអាចទទួលបានជំនួយរបស់យើងដោយហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សនៃសេវាកម្ម Honor ឬចូលទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌលសេវាកម្មអតិថិជន Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1099" name="kn-IN">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಮುಖ್ಯವಾಗಿ ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಕಾರ್ಯಕ್ಷಮತೆಯನ್ನು ವರ್ಧಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಸುಧಾರಣೆಗಳನ್ನು ಆನಂದಿಸಲು ನವೀಕರಿಸಿ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್">
            <feature>• ಕಾರ್ಡ್‌ಗಳು ಮತ್ತು ಫೋಲ್ಡರ್‌ಗಳಂತಹ ಎಲಿಮೆಂಟ್‌ಗಳ ಪಾರದರ್ಶಕತೆ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಪಾರದರ್ಶಕತೆ ಮೋಡ್ ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ, ಇದು ಅಸಾಧಾರಣ ದೃಶ್ಯ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ನೀಡುತ್ತದೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ ನೋಡಿ: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಮತ್ತು ಶೈಲಿ > ಹೋಮ್‌ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಪಾರದರ್ಶಕತೆ ಮೋಡ್</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor ವಾಲೆಟ್">
            <feature>• ಆ್ಯಕ್ಸೆಸ್ ಕಾರ್ಡ್ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯವು ಎನ್‌ಕ್ರಿಪ್ಟ್ ಮಾಡದ ಆ್ಯಕ್ಸೆಸ್ ಕಾರ್ಡ್‌ಗಳ ಸಿಮ್ಯುಲೇಶನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಬೆಂಬಲಿಸುತ್ತದೆ</feature>
			<feature>• Honor ವಾಲೆಟ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಖಾಲಿ ಕಾರ್ಡ್ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯವಿದೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ ನೋಡಿ: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > Honor ವಾಲೆಟ್ > ಆ್ಯಕ್ಸೆಸ್ ಕಾರ್ಡ್‌</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು" type="end">
             <feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾದ ಮೇಲೆ ಪರಿಣಾಮ ಬೀರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೂ ಸಹ ನವೀಕರಿಸುವ ಮೊದಲು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಬ್ಯಾಕ್ ಅಪ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ
2. ಉತ್ಪನ್ನ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಯನ್ನು ಸಲಹೆಗಳು ಎಂಬುದರಲ್ಲಿ ಕಂಡುಕೊಳ್ಳಿ
3. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನಿಮಗೆ ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳು ಎದುರಾದರೆ, ನೀವು Honor ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಅಥವಾ Honor ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ನಮ್ಮ ಸಹಾಯವನ್ನು ಪಡೆಯಬಹುದು</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1042" name="ko-kr">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>사용자 여러분, 이번 업데이트는 주로 시스템 성능을 향상시킵니다. 업데이트하고 개선된 기능을 즐겨 보세요</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="홈 화면">
            <feature>• 투명 모드는 카드, 폴더와 같은 요소의 투명 효과를 최적화하여 뛰어난 시각적 경험을 제공합니다. 설정 > 홈 화면 및 스타일 > 홈 화면 설정 > 투명 모드로 이동하여 사용해 보세요</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor 전자지갑">
            <feature>• 출입 카드 기능은 암호화되지 않은 출입 카드의 시뮬레이션을 지원합니다</feature>
			<feature>• Honor 전자지갑에 무기명 카드 기능이 추가되었습니다. 설정 > Honor 전자지갑 > 출입 카드로 이동하여 사용해 보세요</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="공지" type="end">
             <feature>1. 이 업데이트 설치는 개인 데이터에 영향을 미치지 않지만, 업데이트하기 전에 데이터를 백업하는 것이 좋습니다
2. Tips에서 제품 기능에 대한 자세한 정보를 알아보세요
3. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 Honor 서비스 핫라인으로 전화하거나 Honor 고객 서비스 센터를 방문하여 도움을 받을 수 있습니다</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1108" name="lo-la">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ສະ​ບາຍ​ດີ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​​ນີ້​ຍົກ​ລະ​ດັບ​ປະ​ສິດ​ທິ​ພາບ​ຂອງ​ລະ​ບົບ​ເປັນຫຼັກ. ອັບ​ເດດ​ເພື່ອ​ມ່ວ​ນ​ຊື່​ນກັບ​ການ​ປັບ​ປຸງ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ">
            <feature>• ໂໝດ​ຄວາມ​ໂປ່ງ​ໃສປັບ​ເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ຄວາມ​ໂປ່ງ​ໃ​ສ​ຂອງ​ອົງ​ປະ​ກອບ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ ເຊັ່ນ: ​ບັດ ແລະ ໂຟ​ລ​ເດີ, ເຊິ່ງ​ໃຫ້​ປະ​ສົບ​ການ​ພາບພິ​ເສດ. ​ລອງໃຊ້ມັນເບິ່ງ​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການຕັ້ງຄ່າ > ໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ ແລະ ຮູບແບບ > ການຕັ້ງຄ່າໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ > ໂໝດຄວາມໂປ່ງໃສ</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="ກະ​ເປົ໋າ​ເງິນ Honor">
            <feature>• ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດ​ບັດ​ເຂົ້າ​ເຖິ​ງ​ຮອງ​ຮັບການ​ຈຳ​ລອງ​ບັດ​ເຂົ້າ​ເຖິງ​ທີ່​ບໍ່​ໄດ້​ໃສ່​ລະ​ຫັດ</feature>
			<feature>• ກະ​ເປົ໋າ​ເງິນ Honor ລວມ​ມີຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດບັດ​ເປົ່າ. ​ລອງໃຊ້ມັນເບິ່ງ​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການຕັ້ງຄ່າ > ກະເປົ໋າເງິນ Honor > ບັດເຂົ້າເຖິງ</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ການ​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ສົ່ງ​ຜົນ​ຕໍ່​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ, ແຕ່​ຍັງ​ຄົງ​ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ສຳ​ຮອງ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄວ້ກ່ອນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ
2. ຄົ້ນ​ຫາ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ເພີ່ມ​ເຕີມ​ກ່ຽວ​ກັບ​ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດ​ຜະ​ລິດ​ຕະ​ພັນ​ໃນ​​ເຄັດ​ລັບ
3. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ທ່ານສາມາດຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອຈາກພວກເຮົາໄດ້ ໂດຍການໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນ​ບໍ​ລິ​ການ Honor ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1063" name="lt-lt">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šis naujinys daugiausiai pagerina sistemos našumą. Atnaujinkite ir mėgaukitės patobulinimais.</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Pradžios ekranas">
            <feature>• Skaidrumo režimas optimizuoja kortelių, aplankų ir kitų elementų skaidrumo efektus, užtikrinant išskirtinę vizualinę patirtį. Išbandykite jį nuėję į „Nuostatos > Pradžios ekranas ir stilius > Pradžios ekrano nuostatos > Skaidrumo režimas“</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="„Honor“ piniginė">
            <feature>• Prieigos kortelės funkcija turi nešifruotų prieigos kortelių imitavimo galimybę</feature>
			<feature>• „Honor“ piniginė turi tuščios kortelės funkciją. Išbandykite ją nuėję į „Nuostatos > „Honor“ piniginė > Prieigos kortelė“</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Pastabos" type="end">
             <feature>1. Šio naujinio įdiegimas neturės įtakos jūsų asmeniniams duomenims, tačiau prieš atnaujinant rekomenduojama sukurti atsarginę duomenų kopiją
2. Daugiau informacijos apie gaminio funkcijas rasite Patarimuose
3. Jei naujinimo metu kiltų bet kokių problemų, galite kreiptis į mus pagalbos paskambindami „Honor priežiūros karštąja linija arba apsilankydami „Honor“ klientų aptarnavimo centre</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1062" name="lv-lv">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo atjauninājumu galvenokārt ir uzlabota sistēmas veiktspēja. Atjauniniet, lai izbaudītu uzlabojumus</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Sākuma ekrāns">
            <feature>• Caurspīdīguma režīms optimizē tādu elementu kā karšu un mapju caurspīdības efektus, nodrošinot izcilu vizuālo pieredzi. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Iestatījumi > Sākuma ekrāns un stils > Sākuma ekrāna iestatījumi > Caurspīdīguma režīms</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• Piekļuves karšu funkcija atbalsta nešifrētu piekļuves karšu simulāciju</feature>
			<feature>• Lietotnē Honor maks ir pieejama tukšas kartes funkcija. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Iestatījumi > Honor maks > Piekļuves karte</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Piezīmes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Šī atjauninājuma instalēšana neietekmēs jūsu personas datus, taču joprojām ir ieteicams pirms atjaunināšanas dublēt datus
2. Lietotnē Padomi atklājiet vairāk par produkta funkcijām
3. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, varat saņemt mūsu palīdzību, zvanot uz Honor klientu apkalpošanas dienesta tālruni vai apmeklējot Honor klientu pakalpojumu centru.</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="mai-IN">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, ई अपडेट मुख्य रूप सँ सिस्टमक कार्य-क्षमता केँ वर्धित करैत अछि। सुधार सभक आनंद लेबाक लेल अपडेट करू</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="होम स्क्रीन">
            <feature>• पारदर्शी मोड कार्ड आ फोल्डर सभ सन तत्व सभक पारदर्शी प्रभाव सभ केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि, जाहि सँ असाधारण दृश्य अनुभव प्रदान कयल जा सकए। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: सेटिंग्स > होम स्क्रीन आ शैली > होम स्क्रीनक सेटिंग्स > पारदर्शी मोड</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor वॉलेट">
            <feature>• एक्सेस कार्ड विशेषता एन्क्रिप्ट नहि कयल एक्सेस कार्ड केर सिमुलेशन केर सपोर्ट करैत अछि</feature>
			<feature>• Honor वॉलेट मे रिक्त कार्ड विशेषता सम्मिलित अछि। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: सेटिंग्स > Honor वॉलेट > एक्सेस कार्ड</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="नोट्स" type="end">
             <feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा प्रभावित नहि होयत, मुदा तैयो अपडेट करए सँ पहिने अहाँ केँ डेटाक बैकअप लेबाक सुझाव देल जाइत अछि
2. टिप्स मे उत्पाद विशेषता सभ पर आओर जानकारी डिस्‍कवर करू
3. यदि अपडेट केर दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' अहाँ Honor सेवा हॉटलाइन केँ कॉल कए वा Honor सर्विस सेंटर जा कए हमरासभक मदति प्राप्त कए सकैत छी</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1153" name="mi-NZ">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>E te kaiwhakamahi aroha, ko tēnei whakahoutanga e whakarei ake ana i te mahinga pūnaha. Whakahōu ki te oaoa i te whakapai ake</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Mata kāinga">
            <feature>• Ka arotau e te Aratau te mārama ngā pānga te mārama o ngā wāhanga pēnei i ngā kāri me ngā kōpaki, hei whakarato wheako tirohanga tino pai. Whakamātauria mā te haere ki: Ngā Tautuhinga > Mata kāinga &amp; kāhua > Ngā tautuhinga mata kāinga > Aratau te mārama</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Wāreti Honor">
            <feature>• E āhuahira tautoko ana te Kāri urunga i te āhei ki te whakakāhore i ngā kāri urunga kāore i whakamunatia</feature>
			<feature>• Kei roto i te Wāreti Honor te āhuahira Kāri pātea. Whakamātauhia mā te haere ki: Ngā Tautuhinga > Wāreti Honor > Kāri urunga</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Ngā Tuhipoka" type="end">
             <feature>1. Mā te tāuta i tēnei whakahōutanga e kore tō raraunga whaiaro e pāngia, engari e taunaki ana kia tāruatia ō raraunga i mua i te whakahōutanga
2. Tūhura mōhiohio ētahi anō mō ngā āhuahira o te hua i Ngā Aki
3. Mēnā ka pāngia koe e ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōutanga, ka taea e koe te tiki āwhina mā te waea atu ki te waeawera ratonga Honor, mā te toro atu rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki a Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1071" name="mk-mk">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Почитуван кориснику, ова ажурирање главно ги подобрува перформансите на системот. Ажурирајте за да уживате во подобрувањата</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Почетен екран">
            <feature>• Режимот на проѕирност ги оптимизира ефектите на проѕирност на елементи како картички и папки, овозможувајќи исклучително визуелно искуство. Пробајте го така што ќе одите во: Нагодување > Почетен екран и стил > Поставки за почетниот екран > Режим на проѕирност</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Паричник од Honor">
            <feature>• Карактеристиката Картичка за пристап го поддржува симулирањето нешифрирани картички за пристап</feature>
			<feature>• Паричник од Honor ја вклучува карактеристиката за празна картичка. Пробајте го така што ќе одите во: Нагодување > Паричник од Honor > Картичка за пристап</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Белешки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да влијае врз вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува да направите резервна копија од податоците пред да ажурирате
2. Откријте повеќе информации за карактеристиките на производот во Совети
3. Ако наидете на какви било проблеми при ажурирањето, може да ја добиете нашата помош со повикување на телефонскиот број на службата на Honor или посета на сервисниот центар за корисници на Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1100" name="ml-IN">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് പ്രധാനമായും സിസ്റ്റം പ്രകടനം മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു. മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തലുകൾ ആസ്വദിക്കാൻ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുക</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ">
            <feature>• ഒരു സവിശേഷമായ ദൃശ്യാനുഭവം നൽകുന്നതിനായി, സുതാര്യതാ മോഡ് കാർഡുകളും ഫോൾഡറുകളും പോലുള്ള ഘടകങ്ങളുടെ സുതാര്യതാ ഇഫക്റ്റുകൾ ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുന്നു. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്രമീകരണം > ഹോം സ്ക്രീനും ശൈലിയും > ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ക്രമീകരണം > സുതാര്യതാ മോഡ്</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor വാലറ്റ്">
            <feature>• എൻക്രിപ്‌റ്റ് ചെയ്യാത്ത ആക്‌സസ് കാർഡുകളുടെ സിമുലേഷൻ ആക്‌സസ് കാർഡ് സവിശേഷത പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കുന്നു</feature>
			<feature>• Honor വാലറ്റിൽ 'ശൂന്യമായ കാർഡ്' സവിശേഷത ഉൾപ്പെടുന്നു. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ക്രമീകരണം > Honor വാലറ്റ് > ആക്‌സസ് കാർഡ്</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ ബാധിക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിന് മുമ്പായി നിങ്ങളുടെ ഡാറ്റ ബാക്കപ്പ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു
2. 'നുറുങ്ങുകൾ' എന്നതിൽ ഉൽപ്പന്ന സവിശേഷതകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾ കണ്ടെത്തുക
3. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ നിങ്ങൾക്ക് എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, Honor സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ Honor ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്‌ത് ഞങ്ങളുടെ സഹായം കരസ്ഥമാക്കാവുന്നതാണ്</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1104" name="mn-MN">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэ шинэчлэлтээр голчлон системийн гүйцэтгэлийг сайжрууллаа. Шинэчлээд, сайжруулсан хэрэглээг мэдрээрэй</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Үндсэн дэлгэц">
            <feature>• Тунгалаг горим карт, хавтас гэх мэт элементийн тунгалагших эффектийг оновчилж, онцгой үзэмжтэй болгоно. Тохиргоо > Үндсэн дэлгэц, хэв маяг > Үндсэн дэлгэцийн тохиргоо > Тунгалаг горим руу очиж туршиж үзнэ үү</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Түрийвч">
            <feature>• Нэвтрэх карт онцлог шифрлээгүй нэвтрэх картыг дуурайхыг дэмжинэ</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Түрийвчид Хоосон картын онцлог бий. Тохиргоо > Honor Түрийвч > Нэвтрэх карт рүү очиж туршиж үзнэ үү</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Тэмдэглэл" type="end">
             <feature>1. Энэхүү шинэчлэлтийг суулгахад таны хувийн мэдээлэлд нөлөөлөхгүй ч шинэчлэхээс өмнө өгөгдлөө нөөцлөхийг зөвлөж байна
2. Зөвлөгөө дотроос бүтээгдэхүүний онцлогийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэлтэй танилцана уу
3. Шинэчлэх үед асуудал гарвал Honor-н үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгах буюу Honor-н хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төвд зочилж болно</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1102" name="mr-in">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, हे अद्यतन प्रामुख्याने सिस्टम कार्यप्रदर्शन वाढवते. सुधारणांचा आनंद घेण्यासाठी अद्यतनित करा</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="मुख्य स्क्रीन">
            <feature>• पारदर्शकता मोड कार्ड आणि फोल्डर्स सारख्या घटकांच्या पारदर्शकता प्रभावांना ऑप्टिमाइझ करतो, एक अपवादात्मक दृश्य अनुभव देतो. येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पहा: सेटिंग्ज > मुख्य स्क्रीन आणि शैली > मुख्य स्क्रीन सेटिंग्ज > पारदर्शकता मोड</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• प्रवेश कार्ड वैशिष्ट्य एन्क्रिप्ट न केलेल्या प्रवेश कार्ड्सच्या सिम्युलेशनला समर्थन करते</feature>
			<feature>• Honor वॉलेटमध्ये रिक्त कार्ड वैशिष्ट्य समाविष्ट आहे. येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पहा: सेटिंग्ज > Honor वॉलेट > प्रवेश कार्ड</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="नोट्स" type="end">
             <feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्‍थापित केल्याने आपल्या वैयक्तिक डेटावर परिणाम होणार नाही, परंतु तरीही अद्यतनित करण्यापूर्वी आपल्या डेटाचा बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते
2. उत्पादन वैशिष्ट्यांबद्दल अधिक माहिती Tips मध्ये शोधा
3. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, आपण Honor सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करून किंवा Honor ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जाऊन आमची मदत घेऊ शकता</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1086" name="ms-my">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini ini meningkatkan prestasi sistem terutamanya. Kemas kini untuk menikmati penambahbaikan tersebut</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Skrin utama">
            <feature>• Mod lut sinar mengoptimumkan kesan lut sinar elemen seperti kad dan folder, memberikan pengalaman visual yang luar biasa. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Skrin utama &amp; gaya > Tetapan skrin utama > Mod lut sinar</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• Ciri kad akses menyokong simulasi kad akses yang tidak disulitkan</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Wallet menyertakan ciri Kad kosong. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Honor Wallet > Kad akses</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Nota" type="end">
             <feature>1. Memasang kemas kini ini tidak akan menjejaskan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda masih disyorkan agar menyandarkan data sebelum melakukan kemas kini
2. Temui maklumat lanjut tentang ciri produk dalam Tip
3. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, anda boleh mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi talian penting perkhidmatan Honor atau melawati pusat khidmat pelanggan Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1109" name="my-mm">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် စနစ် စွမ်းဆောင်ရည်ကို အဓိက မြှင့်တင်ပေးသည်။ တိုးတက်ကောင်းမွန်အောင်လုပ်ထားသည်များကို သုံးစွဲခံစားရန် အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်">
            <feature>• ကြည်လင်ပြတ်သားမှု မုဒ်သည် ကတ်များနှင့် ဖိုင်တွဲများကဲ့သို့ ပစ္စည်းများ၏ ကြည်လင်ပြတ်သားမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်များကို အကောင်းဆုံး မြှင့်တင်ပေးပြီး ထူးခြားသော ကြည့်ရှုမှုအတွေ့အကြုံကို ပေးအပ်သည်။ ဖော်ပြပါအတိုင်းသွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ဆက်တင် > ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်နှင့် ပုံစံ > ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင် ဆက်တင် > ကြည်လင်ပြတ်သားမှု မုဒ်</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• ဝင်ရောက်ခွင့်ကတ် လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်သည် ကုဒ်ပြောင်းဝှက်မထားသော ဝင်ရောက်ခွင့်ကတ်များကို တုပနိုင်သည်</feature>
			<feature>• Honor ပိုက်ဆံအိတ်တွင် ကတ်အလွတ် လုပ်ဆောင်ချက် ပါဝင်သည်။ ဖော်ပြပါအတိုင်း သွား၍ စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ဆက်တင် > Honor ပိုက်ဆံအိတ် > ဝင်ရောက်ခွင့်ကတ်</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="မှတ်ချက်" type="end">
             <feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းက သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာကို ထိခိုက်စေမည်မဟုတ်သော်လည်း အပ်ဒိတ်မလုပ်မီ သင့်ဒေတာကို ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ထားရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်
2. Tips တွင် ကုန်ပစ္စည်း လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို လေ့လာပါ
3. အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်နေစဉ် ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခုနှင့် ကြုံရပါက Honor ဝန်ဆောင်မှု ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ဖုန်းခေါ်၍ သို့မဟုတ် Honor ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားရောက်၍ အကူအညီရယူနိုင်သည်</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1109" name="my-zg">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ စနစ္ စြမ္းေဆာင္ရည္ကို အဓိက ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးသည္။ တိုးတက္ေကာင္းမြန္ေအာင္လုပ္ထားသည္မ်ားကို သုံးစြဲခံစားရန္ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ပါ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္">
            <feature>• ၾကည္လင္ျပတ္သားမႈ မုဒ္သည္ ကတ္မ်ားႏွင့္ ဖိုင္တြဲမ်ားကဲ့သို႔ ပစၥည္းမ်ား၏ ၾကည္လင္ျပတ္သားမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္မ်ားကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးၿပီး ထူးျခားေသာ ၾကည့္ရႈမႈအေတြ႕အႀကဳံကို ေပးအပ္သည္။ ေဖာ္ျပပါအတိုင္းသြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ဆက္တင္ > ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ႏွင့္ ပုံစံ > ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ ဆက္တင္ > ၾကည္လင္ျပတ္သားမႈ မုဒ္</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• ဝင္ေရာက္ခြင့္ကတ္ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္သည္ ကုဒ္ေျပာင္းဝွက္မထားေသာ ဝင္ေရာက္ခြင့္ကတ္မ်ားကို တုပႏိုင္သည္</feature>
			<feature>• Honor ပိုက္ဆံအိတ္တြင္ ကတ္အလြတ္ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္ ပါဝင္သည္။ ေဖာ္ျပပါအတိုင္း သြား၍ စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ဆက္တင္ > Honor ပိုက္ဆံအိတ္ > ဝင္ေရာက္ခြင့္ကတ္</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="မွတ္ခ်က္" type="end">
             <feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းက သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာကို ထိခိုက္ေစမည္မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း အပ္ဒိတ္မလုပ္မီ သင့္ေဒတာကို ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ထားရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္
2. Tips တြင္ ကုန္ပစၥည္း လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို ေလ့လာပါ
3. အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ေနစဥ္ ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခုႏွင့္ ႀကဳံရပါက Honor ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈ ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ဖုန္းေခၚ၍ သို႔မဟုတ္ Honor ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားေရာက္၍ အကူအညီရယူႏိုင္သည္</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1044" name="nb-no">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Kjære bruker. Denne oppdateringen forbedrer hovedsakelig systemytelsen. Oppdater for å få forbedringene</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Startskjerm">
            <feature>• Gjennomsiktighetsmodus optimaliserer gjennomsiktighetseffektene til elementer som kort og mapper, og gir en eksepsjonell visuell opplevelse. Prøv funksjonen ved å gå til Innstillinger > Startskjerm og stil > Innstillinger for startskjerm > Gjennomsiktighetsmodus</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Lommebok">
            <feature>• Adgangskort-funksjonen støtter simulering av ukrypterte adgangskort</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Lommebok inkluderer funksjonen Blankt kort. Prøv funksjonen ved å gå til Innstillinger > Honor Lommebok > Tilgangskort</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Merknader" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installeringen av denne oppdateringen påvirker ikke personopplysningene dine, men det anbefales likevel å sikkerhetskopiere dataene dine før du oppdaterer
2. Finn mer informasjon om produktfunksjoner i Tips
3. Hvis det oppstår problemer under oppdateringen, kan du få hjelp ved å ringe Honors kundeservice eller gå til Honors kundeservicesenter</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1121" name="ne-np">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, यो अपडेटले मुख्य गरी प्रणालीको कार्यसम्पादन परिष्कार गर्छ । सुधार गरिएका सुविधाहरूको आनन्द लिन अपडेट गर्नुहोस्</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="गृह स्क्रिन">
            <feature>• पारदर्शिता मोडले कार्ड र फोल्डरहरू जस्ता एलिमेन्टहरूको पारदर्शिता प्रभावहरू अप्टिमाइज गर्छ र अद्भुत भिजुअल अनुभव प्रदान गर्छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > गृह स्क्रिन र शैली > गृह स्क्रिन सेटिङहरू > पारदर्शिता मोड</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor वालेट">
            <feature>• पहुँच कार्डमा इन्क्रिप्ट नगरिएका पहुँच कार्डहरू सिमुलेसन गर्ने सुविधा उपलब्ध भएको छ</feature>
			<feature>• Honor वालेटमा खाली कार्डको सुविधा समावेश गरिएको छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > Honor वालेट > पहुँच कार्ड</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="नोटहरू" type="end">
             <feature>1. तपाईंले यो एप स्थापना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटामा कुनै प्रभाव नपर्ने भए पनि तपाईंलाई अपडेट गर्नुअघि आफ्नो डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ
2. सुझावहरूमा गई उत्पादनका सुविधाहरूका बारेमा थप जानकारी हेर्नुहोस्
3. अपडेटको क्रममा तपाईंले कुनै समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईं Honor सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गरेर वा Honor ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा गएर हाम्रो मद्दत प्राप्त गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ ।</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1043" name="nl-nl">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Beste gebruiker, deze update verbetert vooral de systeemprestaties. Werk bij om van de verbeteringen te genieten</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Startscherm">
            <feature>• De Transparantiemodus optimaliseert de transparantie-effecten van elementen zoals kaarten en mappen en levert een uitzonderlijke visuele ervaring. Probeer het uit via: Instellingen > Startscherm en stijl > Startscherminstellingen > Transparantiemodus</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• De functie Toegangskaart ondersteunt de simulatie van niet-versleutelde toegangskaarten</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Wallet bevat de functie Blanco kaart. Probeer het uit via: Instellingen > Honor Wallet > Toegangskaart</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notities" type="end">
             <feature>1. Het installeren van deze update heeft geen invloed op uw persoonlijke gegevens, maar het wordt nog steeds aanbevolen om een back-up van uw gegevens te maken voordat u deze update uitvoert
2. Ontdek meer informatie over productfuncties in Tips
3. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, kunt u onze hulp krijgen door de Honor-servicehotline te bellen of naar het Honor-klantenservicecentrum te gaan</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1096" name="or-IN">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ମୁଖ୍ୟତଃ ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ର କାର୍ଯ୍ୟଦକ୍ଷତାକୁ ବଢାଏ। ଉନ୍ନତିଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଉପଭୋଗ କରିବାକୁ ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରନ୍ତୁ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌">
            <feature>• ପାରଦର୍ଶିତା ମୋଡ୍ କାର୍ଡ ଏବଂ ଫୋଲ୍ଡର ଭଳି ଉପାଦାନଗୁଡ଼ିକର ସ୍ୱଚ୍ଛତା ପ୍ରଭାବକୁ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍ କରେ, ଏକ ଅସାଧାରଣ ଦୃଶ୍ୟ ଅନୁଭୂତି ପ୍ରଦାନ କରେ। ଏଠାକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାକୁ ବ୍ୟବହାର କରି ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ଓ ଷ୍ଟାଇଲ୍ > ହୋମ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ପାରଦର୍ଶିତା ମୋଡ୍</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor ୱାଲେଟ୍">
            <feature>• ଆକସେସ୍ କାର୍ଡ୍ ବିଶେଷତା ଏନକ୍ରିପ୍ଟ କରାଯାଇଥିବା ଆକସେସ୍ କାର୍ଡ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକର ସିମୁଲେସନ୍ ସମର୍ଥନ କରେ</feature>
			<feature>• Honor ୱାଲେଟ୍‌ ଶୂନ୍ୟ କାର୍ଡ୍‌ ବିଶେଷତା ମଧ୍ୟ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରେ। ନିମ୍ନଲିଖିତକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାକୁ ବ୍ୟବହାର କରି ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > Honor ୱାଲେଟ୍‌ > ଆକସେସ୍ କାର୍ଡ୍‌</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ପ୍ରଭାବିତ ହେବ ନାହିଁ, ତଥାପି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରିବା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡାଟାର ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି
2. ଟିପ୍ସରେ ଉତ୍ପାଦ ବିଶେଷତାଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଉପରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ଆବିଷ୍କାର କରନ୍ତୁ
3. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରିବା ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଆପଣ Honor ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌କୁ କଲ୍‌ କରି କିମ୍ବା Honor ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଇ, ଆମ ସହାୟତା ପାଇପାରିବେ</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1094" name="pa-IN">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਮੁੱਖ ਤੌਰ 'ਤੇ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੀ ਕਾਰਗੁਜ਼ਾਰੀ ਨੂੰ ਬਿਹਤਰ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਸੁਧਾਰਾਂ ਦਾ ਅਨੰਦ ਲੈਣ ਲਈ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰੋ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ">
            <feature>• ਪਾਰਦਰਸ਼ਤਾ ਮੋਡ ਕਾਰਡਾਂ ਅਤੇ ਫੋਲਡਰਾਂ ਵਰਗੇ ਐਲੀਮੈਂਟਾਂ ਦੇ ਪਾਰਦਰਸ਼ਤਾ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਉਂਦਾ ਹੈ, ਇੱਕ ਸ਼ਾਨਦਾਰ ਵਿਜ਼ੂਅਲ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਪ੍ਰਦਾਨ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਅਤੇ ਸ਼ੈਲੀ > ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਪਾਰਦਰਸ਼ਤਾ ਮੋਡ</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor ਵਾਲੇਟ">
            <feature>• ਐਕਸੈਸ ਕਾਰਡ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾ ਏਨਕ੍ਰਿਪਟ ਨਾ ਕੀਤੇ ਐਕਸੈਸ ਕਾਰਡਾਂ ਦੀ ਨਕਲ ਦਾ ਸਮਰਥਨ ਕਰਦੀ ਹੈ</feature>
			<feature>• Honor ਵਾਲੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਖਾਲੀ ਕਾਰਡ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > Honor ਵਾਲੇਟ > ਐਕਸੈਸ ਕਾਰਡ</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="ਨੋਟਸ" type="end">
             <feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ 'ਤੇ ਕੋਈ ਅਸਰ ਨਹੀਂ ਪਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਹਾਲੇ ਵੀ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਦਾ ਬੈਕ ਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ
2. ਸੁਝਾਅ ਐਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਉਤਪਾਦ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾਵਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਦੀ ਖੋਜ ਕਰੋ
3. ਜੇਕਰ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਤੁਸੀਂ Honor ਸੇਵਾ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰ ਕੇ ਜਾਂ Honor ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਮਦਦ ਲੈ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1045" name="pl-pl">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Szanowny użytkowniku, ta aktualizacja w głównej mierze podnosi wydajność systemu. Zainstaluj ją, aby korzystać z ulepszeń</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ekran główny">
            <feature>• Tryb przezroczystości optymalizuje efekty przezroczystości elementów takich jak karty i foldery, zapewniając wyjątkowe wrażenia wizualne. Wypróbuj go, wybierając Ustawienia > Ekran główny i styl > Ustawienia ekranu głównego > Tryb przezroczystości</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Portfel Honor">
            <feature>• Funkcja karty dostępu umożliwia symulację niezaszyfrowanych kart dostępu</feature>
			<feature>• Portfel Honor ma funkcję Pusta karta. Wypróbuj ją, wybierając: Ustawienia > Portfel Honor > Karta dostępu</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notatki" type="end">
             <feature>1. Ta aktualizacja nie ma wpływu na Twoje dane osobowe, jednak przed jej zainstalowaniem zaleca się wykonanie kopii zapasowej danych
2. Więcej informacji o funkcjach produktu znajdziesz w Poradach
3. Jeśli podczas aktualizacji napotkasz jakiekolwiek problemy, możesz uzyskać pomoc, dzwoniąc na infolinię serwisu Honor lub odwiedzając punkt serwisowy Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1046" name="pt-br">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Prezado(a) usuário(a), essa atualização aprimora principalmente o desempenho do sistema. Atualize para aproveitar as melhorias</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Tela inicial">
            <feature>• O Modo Transparência otimiza os efeitos de transparência dos elementos como cartões e pastas, proporcionando uma experiência visual excepcional. Experimente acessando: Configurações > Tela inicial e estilo > Configurações da tela inicial > Modo Transparência</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Carteira Honor">
            <feature>• O recurso de Cartão de acesso suporta a simulação de cartões de acesso não criptografados</feature>
			<feature>• A Carteira Honor inclui o recurso de Cartão em branco. Experimente acessando: Configurações > Carteira Honor > Cartão de acesso</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. A instalação desta atualização não afetará os dados pessoais, mas ainda é recomendável fazer backup dos dados antes de atualizar
2. Descubra mais informações sobre os recursos do produto em Dicas
3. Se você encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, poderá obter nossa ajuda ligando para a Linha de atendimento de serviço da Honor ou acessando a Central de serviços ao cliente da Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2070" name="pt-pt">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Caro utilizador, esta atualização melhora principalmente o desempenho do sistema. Atualize para aproveitar as melhorias</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ecrã Inicial">
            <feature>• O Modo de transparência otimiza os efeitos de transparência de elementos como cartões e pastas, proporcionando uma experiência visual excecional. Experimente, acedendo a: Definições > Ecrã inicial e estilo > Definições do ecrã inicial > Modo de transparência</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• A funcionalidade de cartão de acesso suporta a simulação de cartões de acesso não encriptados</feature>
			<feature>• A Carteira Honor inclui a funcionalidade Cartão em branco. Experimente-a, acedendo a: Definições > Carteira Honor > Cartão de acesso</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não afetará os seus dados pessoais, mas ainda assim é recomendável efetuar uma cópia de segurança dos seus dados antes de atualizar
2. Descobrir mais informações sobre as funcionalidades do produto em Sugestões
3. Se encontrar quaisquer problemas durante a atualização, pode obter ajuda ligando para a linha direta de assistência da Honor ou visitando o centro de apoio ao cliente da Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1048" name="ro-ro">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Stimate utilizator, această actualizare îmbunătățește în principal performanța sistemului. Actualizați pentru a beneficia de îmbunătățiri</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Ecran de pornire">
            <feature>• Modul transparență optimizează efectele de transparență ale elementelor precum cardurile și folderele, oferind o experiență vizuală excepțională. Încercați-l accesând: Setări > Ecran de pornire și stil > Setări ecran de pornire > Mod transparență</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• Funcția Card de acces acceptă simularea cardurilor de acces necriptate</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Wallet include funcția Card gol. Încercați-o mergând la: Setări > Honor Wallet > Card de acces</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notițe" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instalarea acestei actualizări nu va afecta datele dvs. cu caracter personal, dar este totuși recomandat să faceți o copie de rezervă a datelor înainte de actualizare
2. Descoperiți mai multe informații despre caracteristicile produsului în Sugestii
3. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, puteți solicita ajutorul nostru apelând linia de asistență Honor sau vizitând Centrul de service pentru clienți Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1049" name="ru-ru">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Мы выпустили это обновление, чтобы улучшить производительность системы. Установите его, чтобы оценить изменения</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Рабочий экран">
            <feature>• «Прозрачный режим» оптимизирует эффекты прозрачности таких элементов, как карты и папки, создавая профессиональное визуальное оформление. Чтобы опробовать эту функцию, выберите «Настройки > Рабочий экран и стиль > Настройки экрана > Прозрачный режим»</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Кошелек Honor">
            <feature>• Функция «Карта доступа» поддерживает симуляцию незашифрованных карт доступа</feature>
			<feature>• Приложение «Кошелек Honor» включает функцию «Пустая карта». Чтобы опробовать эту функцию, выберите: Настройки > Кошелек Honor > Карта доступа</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Заметки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Установка этого обновления не приведет к удалению ваших персональных данных, но мы все равно рекомендуем вам создать резервную копию своих данных перед обновлением
2. Изучите дополнительную информацию о функциях продукта в «Советах»
3. Если во время обновления у вас возникнут проблемы, обратитесь за помощью на горячую линию службы поддержки Honor или в сервисный центр для клиентов Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1115" name="si-lk">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, මෙම යාවත්කාලීන කිරීම ප්‍රධාන වශයෙන් පද්ධතියේ කාර්යසාධනය උසස් කරයි. වැඩිදියුණු කිරීම් අත්විඳීමට යාවත්කාල කරන්න</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="මුල් තිරය">
            <feature>• සුවිශේෂී දෘශ්‍ය අත්දැකීමක් ලබා දෙමින් විනිවිදභාවය ප්‍රකාරය කාඩ්පත් සහ ෆෝල්ඩර් වැනි සංරචකවල විනිවිදභාවය ප්‍රයෝග ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: සැකසුම් > මුල් තිරය සහ විලාසය > මුල් තිර සැකසුම් > විනිවිදභාවය ප්‍රකාරය</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• ප්‍රවේශ කාඩ්පත් විශේෂාංගය සංකේතනය නොකළ ප්‍රවේශ කාඩ්පත් අනුකරණයට සහය දක්වයි</feature>
			<feature>• Honor පසුම්බිය තුළ හිස් කාඩ්පත විශේෂාංගය ඇතුළත් වේ. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: සැකසුම් > Honor පසුම්බිය > ප්‍රවේශ කාඩ්පත</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="සටහන්" type="end">
             <feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්තවලට බල නොපානු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් යාවත්කාල කිරීමට පෙර ඔබගේ දත්ත උපස්ථ කිරීමට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ
2. ඉඟි තුළ නිෂ්පාදන විශේෂාංග පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සොයා ගන්න
3. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේදී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, ඔබට Honor සේවා හොට්ලයින් ඇමතීමෙන් හෝ Honor පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට පිවිසීමෙන් අපගේ උපකාර ලබා ගත හැකි වේ</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1051" name="sk-sk">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Vážený používateľ, táto aktualizácia hlavne zvyšuje výkon systému. Aktualizujte, aby ste si užili zlepšenia</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Domovská obrazovka">
            <feature>• Režim priehľadnosti optimalizuje efekty priehľadnosti prvkov, ako sú karty a priečinky, čím poskytuje výnimočný vizuálny zážitok. Vyskúšajte to v časti: Nastavenia > Domovská obrazovka a štýl > Nastavenia domovskej obrazovky > Režim priehľadnosti</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Peňaženka">
            <feature>• Funkcia prístupovej karty podporuje simuláciu nešifrovaných prístupových kariet</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Peňaženka obsahuje funkciu Prázdna karta. Vyskúšajte to v časti: Nastavenia > Honor Peňaženka > Prístupová karta</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Poznámky" type="end">
             <feature>1. Inštalácia tejto aktualizácie neovplyvní vaše osobné údaje, ale aj tak sa odporúča pred aktualizáciou si ich zálohovať
2. Ďalšie informácie o funkciách produktu si pozrite v aplikácii Tipy
3. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytne problém, pomoc môžete získať na zákazníckej linke Honor alebo navštívením Centra služieb zákazníkom Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1060" name="sl-si">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, ta posodobitev izboljša predvsem delovanje sistema. Posodobite, da boste lahko izkoristili izboljšave</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Začetni zaslon">
            <feature>Način prosojnosti optimizira učinke prosojnosti elementov, kot so kartice in mape, ter zagotavlja vrhunsko vizualno izkušnjo. Preizkusite ga tako, da odprete: Nastavitve > Začetni zaslon in slog > Nastavitve začetnega zaslona > Način prosojnosti</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Denarnica Honor">
            <feature>• Funkcija dostopne kartice podpira simulacijo nešifriranih dostopnih kartic</feature>
			<feature>• V aplikaciji Denarnica Honor je na voljo funkcija praznih kartic. Preizkusite jo tako, da odprete razdelek: Nastavitve > Denarnica Honor > Pristopna kartica</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Zapiski" type="end">
             <feature>1. Namestitev te posodobitve ne vpliva na vaše osebne podatke, vendar je kljub temu priporočljivo, da podatke pred posodobitvijo varnostno kopirate
2. Več informacij o funkcijah izdelka je na voljo v razdelku Nasveti
3. Če med posodabljanjem pride do težav, lahko pokličete odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom družbe Honor ali obiščete servisni center družbe Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1053" name="sv-se">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Bästa användare, den här uppdateringen förbättrar främst systemets prestanda. Uppdatera för att ta del av förbättringarna</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Startsida">
            <feature>• Transparensläge optimerar transparenseffekterna för element som kort och mappar, och ger en exceptionell visuell upplevelse. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Startsida och stil > Inställningar för startsidan > Transparensläge</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Plånbok">
            <feature>•Funktionen Passerkort stöder simulering av passerkort som inte är krypterade</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Plånbok omfattar funktionen Tomt kort. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Honor Plånbok > Passerkort</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Noteringar" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installation av den här uppdateringen påverkar inte dina personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du säkerhetskopierar alla data innan du uppdaterar
2. Upptäck mer information om produktfunktioner i Tips
3. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa Honors hotline för service eller besöka Honors kundtjänstcenter för att få hjälp</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1089" name="sw-TZ">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, sasisho hili kwa kiasi kikubwa linaboresha utendaji wa mfumo. Sasisha ili ufurahie maboresho</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Skrini ya mwanzo">
            <feature>• Hali ya uwazi huboresha athari za uwazi za elementi kama vile kadi na folda, hivyo basi kuwasilisha hali ya kipekee ya mwonekano. Ijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Skrini ya mwanzo na mtindo > Mipangilio ya skrini ya mwanzo > Hali ya uwazi</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Pochi la Honor">
            <feature>• Kipengele cha Kadi ya ufikiaji kinaruhusu uigaji wa kadi za ufikiaji ambazo hazijasimbwa</feature>
			<feature>• Pochi la Honor linajumuisha kipengele cha Kadi tupu. Lijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Pochi la Honor > Kadi ya ufikiaji</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Madokezo" type="end">
             <feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutaathiri data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado inapendekezwa ili kuweka hifadhi rudufu ya data yako kabla ya kusasisha
2. Gundua maelezo zaidi kwenye vipengele vya bidhaa kwenye Vidokezo
3. Ikiwa utakumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, unaweza kupata msaada wetu kwa kupiga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya Honor au tembelea kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1097" name="ta-IN">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு முதன்மையாக சிஸ்டம் செயல்திறனை மேம்படுத்துகிறது. மேம்பாடுகளைப் பெற, புதுப்பிக்கவும்</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="முகப்புத் திரை">
            <feature>• அட்டைகள் மற்றும் கோப்புறைகள் போன்ற கூறுகளின் ஒளிபுகு விளைவுகளை ஒளிபுகு முறை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது, இது ஒரு விதிவிலக்கான விஷுவல் அனுபவத்தை வழங்குகிறது. இங்குச் சென்று அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: அமைப்புகள் > முகப்புத் திரை &amp; ஸ்டைல் > முகப்புத் திரை அமைப்புகள் > ஒளிபுகு முறை</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor வாலட்">
            <feature>• அணுகல் அட்டை அம்சம் குறியாக்கப்படாத அணுகல் அட்டைகளின் உருவகப்படுத்துதலை ஆதரிக்கிறது</feature>
			<feature>• Honor வாலட்டில் வெற்று அட்டை அம்சமும் உள்ளது. இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: அமைப்புகள் > Honor வாலட் > அணுகல் அட்டை</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="குறிப்புகள்" type="end">
             <feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவைப் பாதிக்காது, எனினும் புதுப்பிப்பதற்கு முன்பு உங்கள் தரவைக் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுப்பது இன்னும் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது
2. உதவிக்குறிப்புகளில் தயாரிப்பு அம்சங்களைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களைக் கண்டறிக
3. புதுப்பிக்கும்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், Honor சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைப்பதன் மூலமோ அல்லது Honor வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்தைப் பார்வையிடுவதன் மூலமோ எங்கள் உதவியைப் பெறலாம்</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1098" name="te-IN">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారుకు, ఈ అప్‌డేట్ ప్రధానంగా సిస్టమ్ పనితీరును మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది. మెరుగుదలలను ఆనందించడానికి అప్‌డేట్ చేయండి</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="హోమ్ స్క్రీన్">
            <feature>• పారదర్శకత మోడ్ అనేది అద్భుతమైన విజువల్ అనుభవాన్ని అందిస్తూ, కార్డ్‌లు మరియు ఫోల్డర్‌లు వంటి ఎలిమెంట్‌ల పారదర్శక ప్రభావాలను ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది. ఇక్కడికి వెళ్ళి దానిని ప్రయత్నించండి: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ &amp; శైలి > హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ సెట్టింగ్‌లు > పారదర్శకత మోడ్</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor వాలెట్">
            <feature>• యాక్సెస్ కార్డ్ ఫీచర్ అన్ఎన్‌క్రిప్ట్ చేసిన యాక్సెస్ కార్డ్‌ల సిమ్యులేషన్‌కు మద్దతు ఇస్తుంది</feature>
			<feature>• Honor వాలెట్‌లో ఖాళీ కార్డ్ ఫీచర్ ఉంది. ఇక్కడికి వెళ్ళి సెట్టింగ్‌లు > Honor వాలెట్ > యాక్సెస్ కార్డ్ దానిని ప్రయత్నించండి:</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="గమనికలు" type="end">
             <feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్ ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వలన మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటా ప్రభావితం కాదు, కాని అప్‌డేట్ చేయడానికి ముందు మీ డేటాను బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని ఇంకా సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది
2. చిట్కాల్లో ఉత్పత్తి ఫీచర్లపై మరింత సమాచారాన్ని తెలుసుకోండి
3. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో ఏవైనా సమస్యలను ఎదుర్కొంటే, మీరు Honor సర్వీస్ హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేసి లేదా Honor కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రాన్ని సందర్శించి మా సహాయం పొందవచ్చు</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1054" name="th-th">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตครั้งนี้เน้นปรับปรุงประสิทธิภาพระบบเป็นหลัก โปรดอัปเดตเพื่อใช้การปรับปรุง</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="หน้าจอหลัก">
            <feature>• โหมดความโปร่งใสจะปรับปรุงเอฟเฟ็กต์ความโปร่งใสขององค์ประกอบต่างๆ เช่น การ์ดและโฟลเดอร์ เพื่อมอบประสบการณ์การรับชมภาพที่ยอดเยี่ยม ลองใช้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > หน้าจอหลักและสไตล์ > การตั้งค่าหน้าจอหลัก > โหมดความโปร่งใส</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• ฟีเจอร์บัตรเข้าใช้งานรองรับการจำลองบัตรเข้าใช้งานที่ไม่ได้เข้ารหัส</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Wallet ประกอบไปด้วยฟีเจอร์บัตรเปล่า ลองใช้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > Honor Wallet > บัตรเข้าใช้งาน</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="โน้ต" type="end">
             <feature>1. การติดตั้งการอัปเดตนี้จะไม่ส่งผลต่อข้อมูลส่วนตัว แต่เราขอแนะนำให้คุณสำรองข้อมูลก่อนอัปเดต
2. ค้นพบข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับฟีเจอร์ผลิตภัณฑ์ในเคล็ดลับ
3. หากคุณพบปัญหาใดๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต คุณสามารถรับความช่วยเหลือได้โดยการโทรติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการลูกค้าของ Honor หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1124" name="tl-ph">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Minamahal na user, pangunahing pinapahusay ng update na ito ang performance ng system. I-update para i-enjoy ang mga pagpapahusay</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Home screen">
            <feature>• Ino-optimize ang Transparency mode ang mga effect sa transparency ng mga element gaya ng mga card at folder, at naghahatid ng pinakamagandang visual na karanasan. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Home screen at estilo > Mga setting ng home screen > Transparency mode</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• Sinusuportahan ng feature na access card ang simulation ng mga hindi naka-encrypt na access card</feature>
			<feature>• Kasama sa Honor Wallet ang feature na Blangkong card. Subukan ang mga ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Honor Wallet > Access card</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Mga Tala" type="end">
             <feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto ang pag-install sa update na ito sa iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update
2. Tuklasin ang higit pang impormasyon sa mga feature ng produkto sa Mga Tip
3. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, makukuha mo ang tulong namin sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng Honor o pagbisita sa customer service center ng Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1055" name="tr-tr">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Değerli kullanıcımız, bu güncelleme ile çoğunlukla sistem performansı artırılmıştır. İyileştirmelerin tadını çıkarmak için güncelleyin</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Başlangıç ekranı">
            <feature>• Saydamlık modu, kartlar ve klasörler gibi öğelerin saydamlık efektlerini optimize ederek olağanüstü bir görsel deneyim sunar. Şu adımları takip ederek deneyebilirsiniz: Ayarlar > Başlangıç ekranı ve stil > Başlangıç ekranı ayarları > Saydamlık modu</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Cüzdan">
            <feature>• Giriş kartı özelliğine şifrelenmemiş giriş kartlarını simüle etme desteği eklendi</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Cüzdan'a boş kart özelliği eklenmiştir. Şu adımları takip ederek deneyebilirsiniz: Ayarlar > Honor Cüzdan > Giriş kartı</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notlar" type="end">
             <feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi etkilemeyecektir ancak yine de güncellemeden önce verilerinizi yedeklemeniz önerilir
2. İpuçları bölümünden ürün özellikleri hakkında daha fazla bilgiyi keşfedin
3. Güncelleme sırasında sorunla karşılaşırsanız Honor yardım hattını arayarak veya Honor müşteri hizmetleri merkezini ziyaret ederek yardım alabilirsiniz</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1058" name="uk-ua">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Шановний користувачу! Це оновлення насамперед підвищує продуктивність системи. Установіть його, щоб відчути покращення</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Головний екран">
            <feature>• Режим прозорості оптимізує ефекти прозорості елементів, як-от карток і папок, створюючи особливе візуальне подання. Щоб спробувати, виберіть "Налаштування" > "Головний екран і стиль" > "Налаштування головного екрана" > "Режим прозорості"</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Гаманець Honor">
            <feature>• Функція картки доступу підтримує моделювання незашифрованих карток доступу</feature>
			<feature>• Гаманець Honor містить функцію банківської картки. Виберіть Налаштування > Гаманець Honor > Картка доступу, щоб спробувати</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Нотатки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Установлення цього оновлення не вплине на ваші особисті дані, однак рекомендовано спочатку створити їхні резервні копії
2. Дізнайтеся більше про функції продукту в розділі "Підказки"
3. Якщо під час оновлення у вас виникнуть будь-які проблеми, ви можете отримати нашу допомогу, зателефонувавши на гарячу лінію Honor або відвідавши центр послуг Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1056" name="ur-pk">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>محترم صارف، یہ اپ ڈیٹ بنیادی طور پر سسٹم کی کارکردگی کو بڑھاتی ہے۔ بہتریوں سے لطف اندوز ہونے کے لیے اپ ڈیٹ کریں</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="ہوم اسکرین">
            <feature>‏• شفافیت موڈ ایک غیر معمولی بصری تجربہ فراہم کر کے، کارڈز اور فولڈرز جیسے عناصر کی شفافیت کے اثرات کو بہتر بناتا ہے۔ یہاں جا کر اسے آزمائیں: ترتیبات > ہوم اسکرین اور طرز > ہوم اسکرین کی ترتیبات > شفافیت موڈ</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="‏Honor والیٹ">
            <feature>‏‏• رسائی کا کارڈ کی خصوصیت غیر مرموز کردہ رسائی کے کارڈز کی نقل سازی میں تعاون کرتی ہے</feature>
			<feature>‏• Honor والیٹ میں خالی کارڈ کی خصوصیت شامل ہے۔ یہاں جا کر اسے آزمائیں: ترتیبات > ‏‏Honor والیٹ > رسائی کا کارڈ</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="نوٹس" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا متاثر نہیں ہو گا، لیکن اپ ڈیٹ کرنے سے پہلے اب بھی اپنے ڈیٹا کا بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے
‏2. تجاویز میں پروڈکٹس کی خصوصیات کے بارے میں مزید معلومات دریافت کریں
‏3. اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کوئی مسئلہ درپیش ہوتا ہے، تو آپ Honor سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کر کے یا Honor کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جا کر ہماری مدد حاصل کر سکتے ہیں</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2115" name="uz-uz">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu yangilanish asosan tizim unumdorligini oshiradi. Takomillashtirishlardan foydalanish uchun yangilang</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Bosh ekran">
            <feature>• Shaffoflik rejimi kartochkalar va jildlar kabi elementlarning shaffoflik effektlarini optimallaydi hamda ajoyib vizual taassurotni taqdim etadi. Bu yerda sinang: Sozlamalar > Bosh ekran va uslub > Bosh ekran sozlamalari > Shaffoflik rejimi</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• Kirish kartasi funksiyasi shifrlanmagan kirish kartalarini simulyatsiyalashni dastaklaydi</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Wallet Toza karta funksiyasini oʻz ichiga oladi. Bu yerda sinang: Sozlamalar > Honor Wallet > Kirish kartasi</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Eslatmalar" type="end">
             <feature>1. Bu yangilanishni oʻrnatish shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringizga taʼsir qilmaydi, lekin yangilashdan oldin maʼlumotlaringizni zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi
2. Maslahatlar ilovasida mahsulot xususiyatlari bilan batafsilroq tanishing
3. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, Honor xizmatining tezkor raqamiga telefon qilish yoki Honor mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyurish orqali yordam olishingiz mumkin</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1066" name="vi-vn">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật này chủ yếu nâng cao hiệu suất hệ thống. Hãy cập nhật để tận hưởng các cải tiến</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Màn hình chính">
            <feature>• Chế độ trong suốt tối ưu hóa các hiệu ứng trong suốt của các thành phần như thẻ và thư mục, mang đến trải nghiệm hình ảnh đặc biệt. Hãy dùng thử bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Phong cách và màn hình chính > Cài đặt màn hình chính > Chế độ trong suốt</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Ví">
            <feature>• Tính năng Thẻ truy cập hỗ trợ mô phỏng thẻ truy cập không được mã hóa</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Ví bao gồm tính năng Thẻ trống. Hãy dùng thử bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Honor Ví > Thẻ truy cập</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Ghi chú" type="end">
             <feature>1. Việc cài đặt bản cập nhật này sẽ không ảnh hưởng đến dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn, nhưng bạn vẫn nên sao lưu dữ liệu trước khi cập nhật
2. Khám phá thêm thông tin về các tính năng sản phẩm trong ứng dụng Mẹo
3. Nếu gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, bạn có thể nhận trợ giúp của chúng tôi bằng cách gọi đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ của Honor hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="3076" name="zh-hk">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新主要針對系統進行了優化，建議您進行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="主屏幕">
            <feature>• 新增通透模式，提升卡片、資料夾等元素的通透效果，帶來極致通透體驗。體驗路徑：設定 > 主屏幕和個人化 > 主屏幕設定 > 通透模式</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="榮耀錢包">
            <feature>• 新增門卡功能，支援模擬未經加密過的門卡</feature>
			<feature>• 新增空白卡功能。體驗路徑：設定 > 榮耀錢包 > 門卡</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="更新注意事項" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份
2. 更多精彩功能介紹，請瀏覽「玩機技巧」應用程式
3. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線或至榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1028" name="zh-tw">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新主要針對系統進行了最佳化，建議您進行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="桌面">
            <feature>•  新增通透模式，提升卡片、資料夾等元素的通透效果，帶來極致通透體驗。體驗路徑：設定 > 桌面和個人化 > 桌面設定 > 通透模式</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="榮耀錢包">
            <feature>• 新增門禁卡功能，支援模擬未經加密的門禁卡</feature>
			<feature>• 新增空白卡功能。體驗路徑：設定 > 榮耀錢包 > 門禁卡</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="更新注意事項" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份
2. 如需更多精彩功能介紹，請查看「玩機技巧」應用程式
3. 在更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1152" name="ug-cn">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا ئاساسلىقى سىستېمىغا قارىتا ئەلالاشتۇرۇش ئېلىپ بېرىلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="‏ئۈستەليۈزى">
            <feature>‏•  سۈزۈك ھالەت يېڭىدىن قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، كارتا، ھۆججەت قاتارلىق ئېلېمېنتلارنىڭ سۈزۈكلۈك ئۈنۈمى يۇقىرى كۆتۈرۈلدى، ئېسىل سۈزۈك تەسىراتى ئېلىپ كېلىدۇ. ئىشلىتىش يولى: تەڭشەك > ئۈستەليۈزى ۋە خاسلاشتۇرۇش > ئۈستەليۈزى تەڭشىكى > ‏سۈزۈك ھالەت</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="‏روڭياۋ ھەميانى">
            <feature>‏• ئاچقۇچ كارتا ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، مەخپىيلەشتۈرۈلمىگەن ئاچقۇچ كارتىنى تەقلىد قىلىشنى قوللايدۇ</feature>
			<feature>‏• قۇرۇق كارتا ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى. ئىشلىتىش يولى: تەڭشەك > روڭياۋ ھەميانى > ئاچقۇچ كارتا</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="‏يېڭىلاش بىلدۈرگۈسى" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، لېكىن يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتنى زاپاسلاشنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز
‏2. تېخىمۇ كۆپ سەرخىل ئىقتىدارلارنى «ئىشلىتىش كۆرسەتمىسى» ئەپىنى زىيارەت قىلىپ كۆرۈڭ
‏3. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركىسى مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1031" name="de-at">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung verbessert hauptsächlich die Systemleistung. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Startbildschirm">
            <feature>• Der Transparenzmodus optimiert die Transparenzeffekte von Elementen wie Karten und Ordnern und sorgt so für ein außergewöhnliches Anzeigeerlebnis. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Startbildschirm und Stil > Startbildschirmeinstellungen > Transparenzmodus</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• Die Funktion Zugangskarte unterstützt die Simulation unverschlüsselter Zugangskarten</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Wallet enthält die Funktion Blankokarte. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Honor Wallet > Zugangskarte</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notizen" type="end">
             <feature>1. Die Installation dieses Updates hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, es wird jedoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen
2. Entdecken Sie weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen in Tipps
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Honor-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein Honor-Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1031" name="de-ch">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Sehr geehrter Nutzer, diese Aktualisierung verbessert hauptsächlich die Systemleistung. Nehmen Sie die Aktualisierung vor, um in den Genuss der Verbesserungen zu kommen</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Startbildschirm">
            <feature>• Der Transparenzmodus optimiert die Transparenzeffekte von Elementen wie Karten und Ordnern und sorgt so für ein außergewöhnliches Anzeigeerlebnis. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Startbildschirm und Stil > Startbildschirmeinstellungen > Transparenzmodus</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• Die Funktion Zugangskarte unterstützt die Simulation unverschlüsselter Zugangskarten</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Wallet enthält die Funktion Blankokarte. Probieren Sie es aus, gehen Sie zu: Einstellungen > Honor Wallet > Zugangskarte</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notizen" type="end">
             <feature>1. Die Installation dieses Updates hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, es wird jedoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen
2. Entdecken Sie weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen in Tipps
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Honor-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein Honor-Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1036" name="fr-ch">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour améliore principalement les performances du système. Effectuez la mise à jour pour profiter des améliorations</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Écran d'accueil">
            <feature>• Le mode transparence optimise les effets de transparence d'éléments tels que les cartes et les dossiers, procurant une expérience visuelle exceptionnelle. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Écran d'accueil et style > Paramètres de l'écran d'accueil > Mode transparence</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• La fonction Carte d'accès prend en charge la simulation de cartes d'accès non cryptées</feature>
			<feature>• Portefeuille Honor comprend la fonctionnalité Carte vierge. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Portefeuille Honor > Carte d'accès</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour
2. Découvrez plus d'informations sur les fonctionnalités du produit dans Astuces
3. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes pendant la mise à jour, vous pouvez obtenir de l'aide en contactant la hotline de service Honor ou en vous rendant dans un centre de services clients Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1040" name="it-ch">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento migliora principalmente le prestazioni del sistema. Esegui l'aggiornamento per usufruire dei miglioramenti</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Schermata Home">
            <feature>• La modalità trasparenza ottimizza gli effetti di trasparenza di elementi quali schede e cartelle, offrendo un'esperienza visiva eccezionale. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Schermata Home e stile > Impostazioni schermata Home > Modalità trasparenza</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• La funzione delle carte di accesso supporta la simulazione delle carte di accesso non crittografate</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Wallet include la funzione Carta vuota. Per provarla, vai in: Impostazioni > Honor Wallet > Carta di accesso</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Note" type="end">
             <feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup dei dati prima di procedere
2. Scopri ulteriori informazioni sulle funzioni del prodotto in Suggerimenti
3. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center Honor o visitando un centro servizio clienti Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2074" name="sr-ba">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se unapređuju performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u unapređenjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Početni ekran">
            <feature>• Režim providnosti optimizuje efekte providnosti elemenata kao što su kartice i fascikle, pružajući izuzetno vizuelno iskustvo. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Početni ekran i stil > Podešavanja početnog ekrana > Režim providnosti</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Novčanik">
            <feature>• Funkcija Kartica za pristup podržava simulaciju nešifriranih kartica za pristup</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Novčanik obuhvata funkciju Prazna kartica. Isprobajte je tako što ćete otići na sledeću lokaciju: Podešavanja > Honor Novčanik > Kartica za pristup</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Zabeleške" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka pre ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o karakteristikama proizvoda u odeljku Saveti
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete dobiti našu pomoć pozivom dežurne linije kompanije Honor ili posetom centru za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2074" name="sr-me">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim ažuriranjem se unapređuju performanse sistema. Ažurirajte da biste uživali u unapređenjima</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Početni ekran">
            <feature>• Režim providnosti optimizuje efekte providnosti elemenata kao što su kartice i fascikle, pružajući izuzetno vizuelno iskustvo. Isprobajte to tako što ćete otići u: Podešavanja > Početni ekran i stil > Podešavanja početnog ekrana > Režim providnosti</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Novčanik">
            <feature>• Funkcija Kartica za pristup podržava simulaciju nešifriranih kartica za pristup</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Novčanik obuhvata funkciju Prazna kartica. Isprobajte je tako što ćete otići na sledeću lokaciju: Podešavanja > Honor Novčanik > Kartica za pristup</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Zabeleške" type="end">
             <feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka pre ažuriranja
2. Otkrijte više informacija o karakteristikama proizvoda u odeljku Saveti
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tokom ažuriranja, možete dobiti našu pomoć pozivom dežurne linije kompanije Honor ili posetom centru za korisničku podršku kompanije Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1057" name="id-">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini utamanya meningkatkan kinerja sistem. Instal pembaruan untuk menikmati berbagai peningkatan</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Layar beranda">
            <feature>• Mode transparansi mengoptimalkan efek tembus pandang pada elemen seperti kartu dan folder sehingga menghadirkan pengalaman visual yang menakjubkan. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Gaya &amp; layar beranda > Pengaturan layar beranda > Mode transparansi</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Dompet">
            <feature>• Fitur Kartu akses mendukung simulasi kartu akses tanpa enkripsi</feature>
			<feature>• Honor Dompet menyertakan fitur Kartu kosong. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Honor Dompet > Kartu akses</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Catatan" type="end">
             <feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan untuk mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui
2. Pelajari informasi selengkapnya terkait fitur produk di Kiat
3. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan Honor atau mengunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1037" name="he-">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון זה משפר בעיקר את ביצועי המערכת. עדכן כדי ליהנות מהשיפורים</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="מסך הבית">
            <feature>‏• מצב 'שקיפות' ממטב את אפקטי השקיפות של אלמנטים כמו כרטיסים ותיקיות, לחוויה חזותית יוצאת מן הכלל. כדי לנסות אותו, אפשר לעבור אל: הגדרות > מסך הבית וסגנון > הגדרות מסך הבית > מצב 'שקיפות'</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="‏‏Honor Wallet">
            <feature>‏‏• תכונת כרטיסי הגישה תומכת בהדמיה של כרטיסי גישה לא מוצפנים</feature>
			<feature>‏• Honor Wallet כולל את התכונה 'כרטיס ריק'. כדי לנסות, אפשר לעבור אל: הגדרות > ‏‏Honor Wallet > כרטיס גישה</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="הערות" type="end">
             <feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון
‏2. גלה מידע נוסף על תכונות המוצר ב'טיפים'
‏3. אם תיתקל בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, ניתן לקבל עזרה מאיתנו באמצעות התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של Honor או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1124" name="fil-ph">
        <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Minamahal na user, pangunahing pinapahusay ng update na ito ang performance ng system. I-update para i-enjoy ang mga pagpapahusay</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Home screen">
            <feature>• Ino-optimize ang Transparency mode ang mga effect sa transparency ng mga element gaya ng mga card at folder, at naghahatid ng pinakamagandang visual na karanasan. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Home screen at estilo > Mga setting ng home screen > Transparency mode</feature>
	    </features>
		<features module="Honor Wallet">
            <feature>• Sinusuportahan ng feature na access card ang simulation ng mga hindi naka-encrypt na access card</feature>
			<feature>• Kasama sa Honor Wallet ang feature na Blangkong card. Subukan ang mga ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Honor Wallet > Access card</feature>
	    </features>
        <features module="Mga Tala" type="end">
             <feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto ang pag-install sa update na ito sa iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update
2. Tuklasin ang higit pang impormasyon sa mga feature ng produkto sa Mga Tip
3. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, makukuha mo ang tulong namin sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng Honor o pagbisita sa customer service center ng Honor</feature>
        </features>
    </language>
            <imgs>
            </imgs>
</root>