<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version=""/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language code="2052" name="zh-cn">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature/>
</features>
<features module="系统">
<feature>•  系统优化，推荐您进行更新</feature>
</features>

<features module="UX 焕新">
             <feature>•  UX 视觉升级焕新，打造全新 OS 视觉体验</feature>
             <feature img="1">•  控制中心风格焕新，深色背景强化视觉层级，多彩图标让界面更生动，支持个性化调整，操作更合心意</feature>
             <feature img="2">•  新增通透模式，提升卡片、文件夹等元素的通透效果，带来极致通透体验。体验路径：设置 &gt; 桌面和个性化 &gt; 桌面设置 &gt; 通透模式开关</feature>
             <feature>•  新增最近任务堆叠布局，多任务切换更直观，操作更高效。体验路径：设置 &gt; 桌面和个性化 &gt; 最近任务样式</feature>
             <feature>•  新增桌面底部常驻栏背景板。体验路径：双指捏合进入桌面编辑 &gt; 桌面设置 &gt; 显示桌面底部常驻栏背景板</feature>
             <feature>•  新增时钟/图库卡片和日程/笔记应用一镜到底动效，实现跨页面转场的丝滑过渡</feature>
             <feature>•  新增桌面卡片、控制中心按压位置响应效果</feature>
             <feature>•  新增多种锁屏时钟样式，基于壁纸智能推荐布局，支持调节时钟字体、字重、颜色以及位置。体验路径：锁屏双指捏合 &gt; 自定义 &gt; 点击时钟即可编辑</feature>
             <feature>•  新增密码解锁、控制中心等按压通透光感效果</feature>
             <feature>•  新增溯光等系列动态主题。体验路径：联网后，设置 &gt; 桌面和个性化 &gt; 主题 &gt; 选择对应主题</feature>
             <feature img="3">•  新增锁屏长时钟。体验路径：设置 &gt; 桌面和个性化 &gt; 锁屏自定义 &gt; 点击时钟即可编辑</feature>
             <feature>•  新增通透图标。体验路径：设置 &gt; 桌面和个性化 &gt; 图标 &gt; 通透图标</feature>
             <feature img="4">•  新增通知中心/控制中心背景动态模糊效果</feature>
             <feature>•  优化卡片集翻转效果</feature>
             <feature>•  相机应用界面焕新，操作更便捷。影像菜单支持双排显示和滑动翻页。体验路径：相机 &gt; 上滑底部箭头调出影像菜单</feature>
             <feature>•  相机新增状态栏自定义功能，可自定义编辑状态栏功能显示</feature>
        </features><features module="丝滑流畅">
             <feature img="5">•  新增 Turbo X 性能引擎平台界面，性能优化效果看得见</feature>
             <feature>•  新增抢购功能，抢票快人一步</feature>
             <feature>•  优化存储体验，采用荣耀最新的存储优化技术，实现对存储空间的无损压缩和整理，为您增加更多可用空间</feature>
             <feature>•  优化刷视频、看直播、图文浏览流畅体验</feature>
             <feature>•  优化应用安装速度，应用安装更快速</feature>
             <feature>•  优化输入法打字体验，打字更流畅</feature>
        </features><features module="荣耀 AI &amp; YOYO">
             <feature>•  优化 YOYO 记忆收藏体验，知乎、小红书等高频应用 (需将应用升级到最新版本) 收藏可智能提取原文，并支持一键跳转原应用</feature>
             <feature>•  新增 YOYO 记忆双重隐私保护机制，使用更安心</feature>
        </features><features module="荣耀互联">
             <feature img="6">•  开启 NFC，可与 iPhone 一碰传，实现文件高速传输，好玩又快捷。iOS 上需安装荣耀互联 App (1.1.18312 及以上版本)</feature>
             <feature>•  新增支持荣耀手机之间的一碰传，实现文件高速传输，好玩又快捷。体验路径：设置 &gt; 更多连接 &gt; 一碰传</feature>
             <feature>•  新增与 macOS、Windows 互传功能，在电脑安装“荣耀超级工作台”即可互传图片、视频与文件</feature>
             <feature>•  新增支持与 iOS 设备的 OTG 有线克隆，可支持更多数据项</feature>
             <feature>•  新增支持与鸿蒙 NEXT 的联系人、图片、视频的换机克隆</feature>
             <feature img="7">•  新增支持荣耀手机与 iPhone 互相共享通知消息。体验路径：iPhone 下载最新版“荣耀互联”应用，打开获取互联二维码；荣耀手机打开设置 &gt; 智慧互联 &gt; 与 iPhone 互联，点击“扫码添加”，连接后即可体验</feature>
             <feature>•  新增一句话投屏功能，您可以对 YOYO 说："把手机投屏到电视上"等类似指令，即可体验 (YOYO 智能体需要在应用市场升级到 90.10.22.031 版本及以上)</feature>
             <feature>•  分享动态照片时，在荣耀分享界面新增动态照片角标，方便识别分享的照片类型</feature>
        </features><features module="安全守护">
             <feature img="8">•  新增 AI 通话防诈功能，通话中可检测对方声音是否为 AI 合成或诈骗电话</feature>
        </features><features module="便捷易用">
             <feature>•  充电、YOYO 打电话、YOYO 记忆等接入灵动胶囊，便于查看实时状态、快捷触达</feature>
             <feature img="9">•  新增人脸解锁接入胶囊。体验路径：设置 &gt; 通知和状态栏 &gt; 灵动胶囊 &gt; 人脸识别</feature>
             <feature>•  新增 AI 截屏功能，智能学习使用场景和习惯，自动推荐所需服务，让操作更随心</feature>
             <feature>•  新增悬浮窗截屏，截屏后可一步选择悬浮窗区域</feature>
             <feature>•  新增截屏编辑后保存，覆盖原图选项</feature>
             <feature>•  新增部分银行进行应用分身</feature>
             <feature>•  新增媒体播控卡片进度条调节功能，可随意调整进度</feature>
             <feature>•  新增 ICCE 协议适配车型，支持比亚迪、极氪、奔腾、小鹏等车型的连接</feature>
             <feature img="10">•  新增个性化动效图标，提升缓解效果，为您带来舒适的旅途用机体验。体验路径：设置 &gt; 辅助功能 &gt; 晕动舒缓显示 &gt; 显示内容 &gt; 图形 (YOYO 建议需升级到最新版本，升级路径：设置 &gt; 荣耀 AI &amp; YOYO &gt; YOYO 建议 &gt; 右上角三个点 &gt; 设置 &gt; 检查更新)</feature>
             <feature>•  新增支持更多横屏应用进入横屏悬浮窗</feature>
             <feature>•  新增支持响铃/取消响铃设置快捷入口。体验路径：设置 &gt; 辅助功能 &gt; 快捷启动及手势 &gt; 双击电源键/熄屏下双击音量下键 &gt; 响铃/取消响铃</feature>
             <feature>•  新增 WLAN 断开连接、密码显示功能。体验路径：设置 &gt; WLAN &gt; 点击已连接的 WLAN，可断开 WLAN 或者查看密码</feature>
             <feature>•  支持来电场景配置为横幅通知或全屏显示</feature>
             <feature>•  支持图库视频播放帧预览，快速浏览锁定指定帧</feature>
             <feature>•  优化状态栏三方应用通知图标显示效果，提升显示一致性</feature>
             <feature>•  优化部分应用导航条沉浸式体验</feature>
             <feature>•  控制中心新增任意位置横划切换至通知中心，操作更方便</feature>
             <feature>•  控制中心新增关机按钮，关机重启更便捷</feature>
             <feature>•  户外模式界面焕新，全新的桌面卡片，带来更直观、顺畅的交互体验</feature>
             <feature>•  户外模式支持胶囊提示，包括亮度、网络增强胶囊以及温度和天气提醒胶囊，帮您随时掌握环境与设备变化</feature>
             <feature>•  户外模式界面和卡片新增屏幕增强、网络优化以及通话增强次数显示，让关键优化一目了然</feature>
        </features><features module="稳定可靠">
             <feature>•  优化系统稳定性，提高用户整机使用体验</feature>
             <feature>•  优化三方头部应用长时间使用的卡顿、卡死问题，提升稳定流畅体验</feature>
             <feature>•  优化部分场景续航体验</feature>
        </features><features module="荣耀分享">
             <feature>•  新增与 macOS、Windows 互传功能，在电脑安装“荣耀超级工作台”即可互传图片、视频与文件</feature>
        </features><features module="YOYO 助理">
             <feature>•  新增一句话开启省电模式、设置字体大小、设置应用分身、查看电话骚扰拦截等功能</feature>
        </features><features module="状态栏">
             <feature>•  新增状态栏图标自定义功能，可自由选择需要显示的状态栏图标。体验路径：设置 &gt; 通知和状态栏 &gt; 状态栏</feature>
        </features><features module="桌面">
             <feature>•  新增长按桌面空白区域进入编辑模式功能</feature>
        </features><features module="通话">
             <feature>•  来电场景支持配置为横幅通知或全屏显示。体验路径：设置 &gt; 应用 &gt; 拨号服务 &gt; 解锁后来电通知</feature>
        </features><features module="截屏">
             <feature>•  截屏编辑后保存支持覆盖原图选项</feature>
        </features><features module="控制中心">
             <feature>•  控制中心任意位置支持横划切换至通知中心，操作更方便</feature>
             <feature>•  控制中心新增关机按钮，关机重启更便捷</feature>
        </features><features module="通知中心">
             <feature>•  媒体播控卡片新增进度条调节，可随意调整进度</feature>
        </features><features module="荣耀车联">
             <feature>•  新增荣耀车联连接 HiCar 车机功能，手机智能服务结合车机大屏和音响效果，带来更安全、更便捷、更智能的驾车服务新体验
体验路径 1：通过荣耀车联图标进入
体验路径 2：设置 &gt; 更多连接 &gt; 荣耀车联 &gt; 连接车辆 &gt; 通用连接方式</feature>
        </features><features module="设置">
             <feature>•  支持双击电源键/熄屏状态下双击音量下键打开指定应用</feature>
             <feature>•  定时开关机功能可独立设置</feature>
        </features><features module="性能">
             <feature>•  优化系统性能</feature>
        </features><features module="稳定性">
             <feature>•  提升系统稳定性</feature>
        </features><features module="安全补丁">
             <feature>•  合入安卓 2025 年 11 月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features><features module="更新注意事项" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份
2. 更多精彩功能介绍，请访问“玩机技巧”应用
3. 如果您在使用过程中遇到任何问题，请访问“我的荣耀”应用或访问荣耀官方服务网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us 寻求支持</feature>
</features></language>
<language code="1033" name="en-us">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature/>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>• Update to enjoy the system optimizations</feature>
</features>

<features module="New interaction">
             <feature>• The upgraded interface design delivers a new look for the OS</feature>
             <feature img="1">• The refreshed Control Center includes a dark background to improve visual hierarchy and colorful icons for a more vibrant interface. It also supports personalized adjustments for a better user experience</feature>
             <feature img="2">• Transparency mode optimizes the transparency effects of elements such as cards and folders, delivering an exceptional visual experience. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; Home screen &amp; style &gt; Home screen settings &gt; Enable Transparency mode</feature>
             <feature>• Recent tasks now feature a new card-stack layout, making it easier and more efficient to switch between tasks. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; Home screen &amp; style &gt; Recent task style</feature>
             <feature>• The home screen now enables a dock background. Try it out by going to: Pinch with two fingers to access home screen editing &gt; Home screen settings &gt; Show dock background</feature>
             <feature>• Long take animation enables smooth transitions across pages for Clock and Gallery cards, as well as Calendar and Notes apps</feature>
             <feature>• When pressing home screen cards or the Control Center, you can experience responsive effects</feature>
             <feature>• The lock screen offers more clock styles, with intelligent layout recommendations based on wallpaper. You can also customize the clock's font, font weight, color, and position. Pinch with two fingers on the lock screen, tap Custom, then tap the clock to edit</feature>
             <feature>• A tactile light effect responds to your tap on the password unlock and Control Center screens</feature>
             <feature>• Themes includes new dynamic themes, such as Luminous. After connecting to the internet, go to Settings &gt; Home screen &amp; style &gt; Themes, and select your desired theme</feature>
             <feature img="3">• The lock screen offers a bigger and stretched clock style. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; Home screen &amp; style &gt; Custom &gt; Tap the clock to edit</feature>
			 <feature>• The icons now have a transparent appearance. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; Home screen &amp; style &gt; Icons &gt; Transparent icons</feature>
			 <feature img="4">• The Notification center and Control Center include background motion blur effects</feature>	             			 
			 <feature>• Optimizes the card set flipping effect</feature>
             <feature>• The Camera interface has been refreshed for easier use. Imaging menu allows you to view items in two rows and swipe to turn pages. To access the imaging menu, go to Camera and swipe up the bottom arrow</feature>
             <feature>• You can now customize the functions displayed in the Camera's status bar</feature>
        </features><features module="Smoothness">
             <feature img="5">• The new Turbo X performance engine interface makes optimization visible</feature>
             <feature>• Purchase acceleration helps you get tickets faster than others</feature>
             <feature>• Honor's storage optimization technology achieves lossless data compression and organization of storage space, providing you with more available space</feature>
             <feature>• Enhances the smoothness of video playback, live streaming, and browsing images and text</feature>
             <feature>• Speeds up app installation</feature>
             <feature>• Improves the typing experience with a more responsive keyboard</feature>
        </features><features module="Honor AI &amp; YOYO">
             <feature>• YOYO Memories can intelligently extract text from the content you saved in popular apps like Zhihu and Xiaohongshu (ensure the apps are upgraded to the latest version). It also allows for one-tap navigation back to the original app</feature>
             <feature>• Dual privacy protection makes YOYO Memories more secure to use</feature>
        </features><features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature img="6">• Enable NFC to transfer files by tapping against an iPhone, achieving high-speed file transfer that is both fun and convenient. Honor Connect app (version 1.1.18312 or above) needs to be installed on iOS</feature>
             <feature>• OneTap enables seamless file transfer between Honor devices, combining speed with ease and fun. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; More connections &gt; OneTap</feature>
             <feature>• Install HONOR WorkStation on your macOS or Windows computer to easily transfer images, videos, and files between your Honor device and the computer</feature>
             <feature>• OTG wired cloning with iOS devices allows more data items to be transferred</feature>
             <feature>• Device Clone supports the migration of contacts, images, and videos with HarmonyOS NEXT</feature>
		     <feature img="7">• Honor phones and iPhones can now share notification messages with each other. To try it out, download the latest Honor Connect app on the iPhone, open it and get the QR code. On the Honor device, go to Settings &gt; Honor Connect &gt; Connect with iPhone &gt; Scan to add, then scan the QR code on the iPhone to establish the connection</feature>
             <feature>• To easily mirror your phone screen to the TV, just say a command like "Cast my phone screen to the TV." (Make sure YOYO Agent is updated to version 90.10.22.031 or above from the App Market)</feature>
             <feature>• When sharing moving photos, you can see a moving photo badge on the Honor Share interface, making it easier to identify the type of photo being shared</feature>        							 
        </features><features module="Security Guard">
             <feature img="8">• AI Call fraud prevention can detect whether the caller's voice is AI-generated or a scam during the call</feature>
        </features><features module="Convenience">
             <feature>• Charging, YOYO calls, YOYO Memories, and other features are integrated into Magic Capsule for viewing real-time status and quick access</feature>
			 <feature img="9">• Face recognition is integrated into Magic Capsule. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; Notifications &amp; status bar &gt; Magic Capsule &gt; Face recognition</feature>
             <feature>• AI screenshot can intelligently learn from your usage scenarios and habits to automatically recommend the services you need, making operations simpler</feature>
             <feature>• You can take a screenshot that includes a floating window and easily select the floating window area in one step</feature>
             <feature>• After editing a screenshot, you can save it to replace the original image</feature>
             <feature>• Some bank apps now support App Twin</feature>
             <feature>• The media control card features a progress bar, allowing you to easily adjust the playback</feature>
             <feature>• ICCE protocol supports new car models, enabling connection with vehicles from brands such as BYD, Zeekr, Bestune, XPeng, and more</feature>
             <feature img="10">• Icons with dynamic effects can enhance the motion sickness relief effect, allowing you to use your device more comfortably while traveling. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; Accessibility features &gt; Motion Sickness Relief &gt; Appearance &gt; Shapes (Ensure that YOYO Suggestions is upgraded to the latest version. To update, go to Settings &gt; Honor AI &amp; YOYO &gt; YOYO Suggestions &gt; Three dots in the upper right corner &gt; Settings &gt; Check for updates)</feature>
			 <feature>• More landscape-oriented apps can now be switched to floating windows while in use</feature>
			 <feature>• Use shortcuts to quickly turn the ringtone on or off. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; Accessibility features &gt; Shortcuts &amp; gestures &gt; Double press power button/Double press volume down button with the screen off &gt; Turn on/off ringtone</feature>
             <feature>• Supports disconnecting from WLAN and viewing the password. Go to Settings &gt; WLAN, tap the connected WLAN, then you can disconnect it or view the password</feature>             
			 <feature>• You can set incoming calls to show as either a banner notification or a full-screen display</feature>
             <feature>• You can quickly browse videos and easily locate specific frames in Gallery</feature>
             <feature>• Improves the display of third-party app notification icons in the status bar for a more unified look</feature>
             <feature>• Optimizes the immersive experience of the navigation bar in some apps</feature>
             <feature>• You can swipe horizontally from anywhere in the Control Center to quickly switch to the Notification Center</feature>
             <feature>• Control Center now includes a Power off button, making it easier to power off and restart your device</feature>
			 <feature>• Outdoor mode enables brand-new home screen cards, delivering a more seamless interactive experience</feature>
             <feature>• Outdoor mode supports Magic Capsule notifications, including brightness, network enhancement, as well as temperature and weather reminders, keeping you stay informed of environment and device status at any time</feature>
             <feature>• Outdoor mode interface and cards now display Enhanced screen, Network optimization, and the count of Enhanced calling activations, making key improvements easy to track at a glance</feature>				 
        </features><features module="Stability and reliability">
             <feature>• Improves the system stability to optimize the user experience</feature>
             <feature>• Fixes lag and crash issues for popular third-party apps, ensuring a stable and smooth experience</feature>
             <feature>• Optimizes the user experience with battery life in some scenarios</feature>
        </features><features module="Honor Share">
             <feature>• Install HONOR WorkStation on your macOS or Windows computer to easily transfer images, videos, and files between your Honor device and the computer</feature>
        </features><features module="YOYO Assistant">
             <feature>• With a single command, you can turn on Power saving mode, adjust font size, create a twin app, check spam call blocking, and more</feature>
        </features><features module="Status bar">
             <feature>• Status bar enables icon customization, allowing you to choose which status bar icons to display. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; Notifications &amp; status bar &gt; Status bar</feature>
        </features><features module="Home screen">
             <feature>• Long press the blank area of the home screen to start editing</feature>
        </features><features module="Call">
             <feature>• You can set incoming calls to show as either a banner notification or a full-screen display. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; Apps &gt; Phone Services &gt; Call notification after unlocking</feature>
        </features><features module="Screenshot">
             <feature>• After editing a screenshot, you can save it to replace the original image</feature>
        </features><features module="Control Center">
             <feature>• You can swipe horizontally from anywhere in the Control Center to quickly switch to the Notification Center</feature>
             <feature>• Control Center now includes a Power off button, making it easier to power off and restart your device</feature>
        </features><features module="Notification center">
             <feature>• The media control card features a progress bar, allowing you to easily adjust the playback</feature>
        </features><features module="Honor CarConnect">
             <feature>• Honor CarConnect can now link with HiCar, integrating smart services on the phone with the car's large screen and audio system. This brings a safer, more convenient, and smarter driving experience
Access method 1: Access via the Honor CarConnect icon
Access method 2: Settings &gt; More connections &gt; Honor CarConnect &gt; Connect cars &gt; General connection method</feature>
        </features><features module="Settings">
             <feature>• Double-press the Power button or, when the screen is off, double-press the Volume down button to open a specified app</feature>
             <feature>• Scheduled power on/off feature allows you to set Power on and Power off times separately</feature>
        </features><features module="Performance">
             <feature>• Improves the system performance</feature>
        </features><features module="Stability">
             <feature>• Improves the system stability</feature>
        </features><features module="Security patch">
             <feature>• Android security patch (Nov 2025) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about Honor Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features><features module="Notes" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating
2. Discover more information on product features in Tips
3. If you encounter any issue during use, please get support by going to My Honor or visiting our website: https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us</feature>
</features></language>
</root>