<root>
    <component name="TCPU" version="请自行修改"></component>
    <default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
    <language code="2052" name="zh-cn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新主要针对系统进行了优化，推荐您进行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="丝滑流畅">
             <feature>•  新增 Turbo X 性能引擎平台界面，性能优化效果看得见</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="便捷易用">
             <feature>•  充电和录屏接入灵动胶囊，便于查看实时状态、快捷触达</feature>
             <feature>•  新增支持悬浮窗截屏，截屏后可一步选择悬浮窗区域</feature>
			 <feature>•  晕动舒缓显示开启后支持圆点颜色自定义、乘车自动开启。体验路径：设置 > 辅助功能 > 晕动舒缓显示</feature>
             <feature>•  支持更多应用横屏使用</feature>
             <feature>•  支持图库视频播放帧预览，快速浏览锁定指定帧</feature>
             <feature>•  优化状态栏三方应用通知图标显示效果，提升显示一致性</feature>
             <feature>•  优化部分应用导航条沉浸式体验</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="UX 焕新">
             <feature>•  UX 视觉升级焕新，打造全新 OS 视觉体验</feature>
             <feature>•  控制中心风格焕新，深色背景强化视觉层级，多彩图标让界面更生动，支持个性化调整，操作更合心意</feature>
             <feature>•  新增桌面卡片、控制中心按压位置响应效果</feature>
             <feature>•  新增溯光等系列主题。体验路径：联网后，设置 > 桌面和个性化 > 主题 > 选择对应主题</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="玩转桌面">
             <feature>•  媒体播控卡片新增进度条调节，可随意调整进度</feature>
             <feature>•  控制中心下任意位置支持横划切换至通知中心，操作更方便</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="媒体创作">
			 <feature>•  相机新增状态栏自定义功能，可自定义编辑状态栏功能显示，体验路径：相机 > 设置 > 状态栏自定义</feature>
             <feature>•  图库视频播放支持帧预览，快速浏览锁定指定帧</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="荣耀互联">
             <feature>•  新增与 macOS、Windows 互传功能，在电脑安装“荣耀超级工作台”即可互传图片、视频与文件</feature>
             <feature>•  新增全新 Cast+ 投屏，为您带来高质量、低时延的投屏体验</feature>
             <feature>•  投屏状态下可同时分享热点</feature>
             <feature>•  新增支持与 iOS 设备的 OTG 有线克隆，可支持更多数据项</feature>
             <feature>•  新增支持与鸿蒙 NEXT 的联系人、图片、视频的换机克隆</feature>
             <feature>•  新增支持荣耀平板和手机之间的一碰传，实现文件高速传输，好玩又快捷。体验路径：设置 > 更多连接 > 一碰传</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="更新注意事项" type="end">
             <feature>1. 新版本下载及安装过程会消耗部分电量及轻微发热，属于正常现象
2. 版本安装后重启期间会做部分系统优化，预计花费 1~3 分钟，请耐心等待
3. 升级完成后部分系统优化会在后台自动进行，系统会在后台自动优化，出现少量耗电，轻微发热是正常现象，1 天内即可恢复
4. 因部分第三方应用与 Android 16 不兼容，更新后可能会出现第三方应用无法正常使用的情况 (如闪退、卡顿、耗电等)。建议您在应用市场尝试将该应用更新至最新版本，若仍无法解决问题，请您耐心等待应用更新信息，并及时更新
5. 请务必确保设备有 10 GB 以上的内部存储空间，否则会有升级失败的风险 (查看存储空间方法：设置 > 存储)
6. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份
7. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1033" name="en-us">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Dear user, this update mainly enhances the system performance. Update to enjoy the improvements</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Smoothness">
             <feature>• The new Turbo X performance engine interface makes optimization visible</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Convenience">
             <feature>• Charging and screen recording are integrated into Magic Capsule for viewing real-time status and quick access</feature>
             <feature>• You can take a screenshot that includes a floating window and easily select the floating window area in one step</feature>
			 <feature>• Motion Sickness Relief now includes an auto-enable feature during driving, and you can customize the dot color. Try it out by going to: Settings > Accessibility features > Motion Sickness Relief</feature>
             <feature>• More apps support landscape orientation</feature>
             <feature>• You can quickly browse videos and easily locate specific frames in Gallery</feature>
             <feature>• Improves the display of third-party app notification icons in the status bar for a more unified look</feature>
             <feature>• Optimizes the immersive experience of the navigation bar in some apps</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="New interaction">
             <feature>• The upgraded interface design delivers a new look for the OS</feature>
             <feature>• The refreshed Control Center includes a dark background to improve visual hierarchy and colorful icons for a more vibrant interface. It also supports personalized adjustments for a better user experience</feature>
             <feature>• When pressing home screen cards or the Control Center, you can experience responsive effects</feature>
             <feature>• Themes now includes new styles, such as Luminous. After connecting to the internet, go to Settings > Home screen &amp; style > Themes, then select the desired theme</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Explore the home screen">
             <feature>• The media control card features a progress bar, allowing you to easily adjust the playback</feature>
             <feature>• You can swipe horizontally from anywhere in the Control Center to quickly switch to the Notification center</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Media creation">
			 <feature>• You can customize the functions displayed in the Camera's status bar. Enable this feature by going to: Camera > Settings > Customize status bar</feature>
             <feature>• You can now quickly browse videos and easily locate specific frames in Gallery</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Install HONOR WorkStation on your macOS or Windows computer to easily transfer images, videos, and files between your Honor device and the computer</feature>
             <feature>• The new Cast+ projection offers a high-quality, low-latency casting experience</feature>
             <feature>• You can share your hotspot while your device is in screen mirroring mode</feature>
             <feature>• OTG wired cloning with iOS devices allows more data items to be transferred</feature>
             <feature>• Device Clone supports the migration of contacts, images, and videos with HarmonyOS NEXT</feature>
             <feature>• OneTap enables seamless file transfer between Honor tablets and Honor phones, combining speed with ease and fun. Try it out by going to: Settings > More connections > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. The download and installation process of the new version will consume some battery power and cause slight heating, which is normal
2. During the restart after the installation, some system optimizations will be performed, expected to take 1~3 minutes. Please be patient
3. After the upgrade is completed, some system optimizations will automatically proceed in the background. During this period, the device may experience increased power consumption and slight heating, which is a normal phenomenon. It will return to its usual state within one day
4. Some third-party apps may not be compatible with Android 16 and may malfunction after the update (such as crash, lag, abnormal power consumption). Please update your apps to the latest version in App Market. If the problems persist, please wait for the upcoming app updates and update in a timely manner
5. Make sure your device has more than 10 GB of free storage space. Otherwise, the update may fail (To check your storage space, go to Settings > Storage)
6. This update will not affect your personal data, but it is recommended to back up your data before updating
7. If you encounter any issues during the update, please call the Honor service hotline or go to the Honor customer service center for support</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="3073" name="ar-eg">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، يحسّن هذا التحديث أداء النظام بشكل أساسي. للاستمتاع بالتحسينات، ما عليك سوى التحديث</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="السلاسة">
             <feature>• واجهة محرك الأداء Turbo X الجديدة تجعل التحسين مرئيًا</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="الملاءمة">
             <feature>• تم دمج الشحن وتسجيل الشاشة في Magic Capsule لعرض الحالة في الوقت الفعلي والوصول السريع</feature>
             <feature>• يمكنك أخذ لقطة شاشة تتضمن نافذة عائمة وتحديد منطقة النافذة العائمة بسهولة في خطوة واحدة</feature>
			 <feature>• تتضمن الآن ميزة تخفيف دوار الحركة ميزة التمكين التلقائي أثناء القيادة، ويمكنك تخصيص لون النقطة. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > ميزات إمكانية الوصول > تخفيف دوار الحركة</feature>
             <feature>• يدعم عدد أكبر من التطبيقات الاتجاه الأفقي</feature>
             <feature>• يمكنك تصفح مقاطع الفيديو بسرعة وتحديد الإطارات المحددة بسهولة في المعرض</feature>
             <feature>• يحسّن عرض أيقونات إشعارات تطبيقات الطرف الثالث في شريط الحالة للحصول على مظهر أكثر تناسقًا</feature>
             <feature>• يحسّن التجربة الغامرة لشريط التنقل في بعض التطبيقات</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="تفاعل جديد">
             <feature>• يوفر تصميم الواجهة المحسّن مظهرًا جديدًا لنظام التشغيل</feature>
             <feature>• يتضمن مركز التحكم المحدّث خلفية داكنة لتحسين التسلسل الهرمي المرئي، وأيقونات ملونة لإضفاء المزيد من الحيوية على الواجهة. وهو يدعم أيضًا إجراء تعديلات مخصصة لتحسين تجربة المستخدم</feature>
             <feature>• عند الضغط على بطاقات الشاشة الرئيسية أو مركز التحكم، يمكنك تجربة تأثيرات سريعة الاستجابة</feature>
             <feature>• تتضمن السمات الآن أنماطًا جديدة، مثل النمط المضيء. بعد الاتصال بالإنترنت، انتقل إلى الإعدادات > الشاشة الرئيسية والنمط > السمات، ثم حدد السمة المطلوبة</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="استكشاف الشاشة الرئيسية">
             <feature>• تتميز بطاقة التحكم في الوسائط بشريط تقدم، مما يسمح لك بضبط التشغيل بسهولة</feature>
             <feature>• يمكنك السحب أفقيًا من أي مكان في مركز التحكم للتبديل بسرعة إلى مركز الإشعارات</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="إنشاء الوسائط">
			 <feature>• يمكنك تخصيص الوظائف المعروضة في شريط حالة الكاميرا. مكّن هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الكاميرا > الإعدادات > تخصيص شريط الحالة</feature>
             <feature>• يمكنك الآن تصفح مقاطع الفيديو بسرعة وتحديد موقع إطارات محددة بسهولة في المعرض</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="الاتصال من Honor">
             <feature>• ثبّت محطة العمل من HONOR على الكمبيوتر الذي يعمل بنظام macOS أو Windows لنقل الصور ومقاطع الفيديو والملفات بسهولة بين جهاز Honor والكمبيوتر</feature>
             <feature>• توفّر تقنية العرض الجديدة Cast+ تجربة بث عالية الجودة وبزمن تأخير منخفض.</feature>
             <feature>• يمكنك مشاركة نقطة الاتصال الخاصة بك أثناء وجود جهازك في وضع مطابقة الشاشة</feature>
             <feature>• يتيح الاستنساخ السلكي OTG مع أجهزة iOS نقل عدد أكبر من عناصر البيانات</feature>
             <feature>• يدعم استنساخ الجهاز نقل جهات الاتصال والصور ومقاطع الفيديو باستخدام HarmonyOS NEXT</feature>
             <feature>• تسمح ميزة OneTap بنقل الملفات بسلاسة بين الأجهزة اللوحية من Honor وهواتف Honor، مما يجمع بين السرعة والسهولة والمتعة. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > طرق توصيل أخرى > ‏OneTap</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="ملاحظات" type="end">
             <feature>1. ستستهلك عملية تنزيل الإصدار الجديد وتثبيته قدرًا من طاقة البطارية، وستتسبب في حدوث ارتفاع طفيف في درجة الحرارة، وهذا أمر طبيعي
2. أثناء إعادة التشغيل بعد التثبيت، سيتم تنفيذ بعض تحسينات النظام، ومن المتوقع أن تستغرق هذه العملية من دقيقة إلى 3 دقائق. يُرجى التحلي بالصبر
3. بعد اكتمال عملية الترقية، سيتم تنفيذ بعض تحسينات النظام تلقائيًا في الخلفية. خلال هذه الفترة، قد يواجه الجهاز زيادة في استهلاك الطاقة وارتفاع طفيف في درجة الحرارة، وهذا أمر طبيعي. وسيعود إلى حالته الطبيعية خلال يوم واحد
4. قد لا تكون بعض تطبيقات طرف ثالث متوافقة مع أندرويد 16، وقد تحدث فيها حالات خلل بعد التحديث (كالتعطل والتأخير واستهلاك الطاقة بصورة غير طبيعية). يُرجى تحديث تطبيقاتك إلى أحدث إصدار في متجر التطبيقات. إذا استمرت المشاكل، فيرجى انتظار تحديثات التطبيقات القادمة والتحديث في الوقت المناسب
5. تأكد من توفر مساحة تخزين فارغة تزيد عن 10 غيغابايت في جهازك. وإلا، فقد يفشل التحديث (للتحقق من مساحة التخزين، انتقل إلى الإعدادات > التخزين)
6. لن يؤثر هذا التحديث على بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية لبياناتك قبل التحديث
7. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيُرجى الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة Honor أو الانتقال إلى أحد مراكز خدمة عملاء Honor لطلب الدعم</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="2057" name="en-GB">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Dear user, this update mainly enhances the system performance. Update to enjoy the improvements</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Smoothness">
             <feature>• The new Turbo X performance engine interface makes optimisation visible</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Convenience">
             <feature>• Charging and screen recording are integrated into Magic Capsule for viewing real-time status and quick access</feature>
             <feature>• You can take a screenshot that includes a floating window and easily select the floating window area in one step</feature>
			 <feature>• Motion Sickness Relief now includes an auto-enable feature during driving, and you can customise the dot colour. Try it out by going to: Settings > Accessibility features > Motion Sickness Relief</feature>
             <feature>• More apps support landscape orientation</feature>
             <feature>• You can quickly browse videos and easily locate specific frames in Gallery</feature>
             <feature>• Improves the display of third-party app notification icons in the status bar for a more unified look</feature>
             <feature>• Optimises the immersive experience of the navigation bar in some apps</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="New interaction">
             <feature>• The upgraded interface design delivers a new look for the OS</feature>
             <feature>• The refreshed Control Centre includes a dark background to improve visual hierarchy and colourful icons for a more vibrant interface. It also supports personalised adjustments for a better user experience</feature>
             <feature>• When pressing home screen cards or the Control Centre, you can experience responsive effects</feature>
             <feature>• Themes now includes new styles, such as Luminous. After connecting to the internet, go to Settings > Home screen &amp; style > Themes, then select the desired theme</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Explore the home screen">
             <feature>• The media control card features a progress bar, allowing you to easily adjust the playback</feature>
             <feature>• You can swipe horizontally from anywhere in the Control Centre to quickly switch to the Notification centre</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Media creation">
			 <feature>• You can customise the functions displayed in the Camera's status bar. Enable this feature by going to: Camera > Settings > Customise status bar</feature>
             <feature>• You can now quickly browse videos and easily locate specific frames in Gallery</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Install HONOR WorkStation on your macOS or Windows computer to easily transfer images, videos, and files between your Honor device and the computer</feature>
             <feature>• The new Cast+ projection offers a high-quality, low-latency casting experience</feature>
             <feature>• You can share your hotspot while your device is in screen mirroring mode</feature>
             <feature>• OTG wired cloning with iOS devices allows more data items to be transferred</feature>
             <feature>• Device Clone supports the migration of contacts, images, and videos with HarmonyOS NEXT</feature>
             <feature>• OneTap enables seamless file transfer between Honor tablets and Honor phones, combining speed with ease and fun. Try it out by going to: Settings > More connections > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. The download and installation process of the new version will consume some battery power and cause slight heating, which is normal
2. During the restart after the installation, some system optimisations will be performed, expected to take 1~3 minutes. Please be patient
3. After the upgrade is completed, some system optimisations will automatically proceed in the background. During this period, the device may experience increased power consumption and slight heating, which is a normal phenomenon. It will return to its usual state within one day
4. Some third-party apps may not be compatible with Android 16 and may malfunction after the update (such as crash, lag, abnormal power consumption). Please update your apps to the latest version in App Market. If the problems persist, please wait for the upcoming app updates and update in a timely manner
5. Make sure your device has more than 10 GB of free storage space. Otherwise, the update may fail (To check your storage space, go to Settings > Storage)
6. This update will not affect your personal data, but it is recommended to back up your data before updating
7. If you encounter any issues during the update, please call the Honor service hotline or go to the Honor customer service centre for support</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1034" name="es-es">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado/a usuario/a, esta actualización mejora principalmente el rendimiento del sistema. Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Suavidad">
             <feature>• La nueva interfaz del motor de rendimiento Turbo X hace visible la optimización</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Comodidad">
             <feature>• La carga y la grabación de pantalla están integradas en Cápsula mágica para ver el estado en tiempo real y acceder rápidamente</feature>
             <feature>• Puede sacar una captura que incluya una ventana flotante y seleccionar fácilmente el área de la ventana flotante en un solo paso</feature>
			 <feature>• Alivio del mareo por movimiento ahora incluye una función de activación automática durante la conducción y puede personalizar el color de puntos. Pruébela en: Ajustes > Funciones de accesibilidad > Alivio del mareo por movimiento</feature>
             <feature>• Más aplicaciones admiten orientación horizontal</feature>
             <feature>• Puede explorar vídeos rápidamente y localizar fácilmente fotogramas específicos en Galería</feature>
             <feature>• Mejora la visualización de los iconos de notificación de aplicaciones de terceros en la barra de estado para una apariencia más unificada</feature>
             <feature>• Optimiza la experiencia inmersiva de la barra de navegación en algunas aplicaciones</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Nueva interacción">
             <feature>• El diseño de interfaz mejorado ofrece una nueva apariencia del sistema operativo</feature>
             <feature>• El Centro de control renovado incluye un fondo oscuro para mejorar la jerarquía visual e iconos coloridos para una interfaz más vibrante. También admite ajustes personalizados para una mejor experiencia de usuario</feature>
             <feature>• Al pulsar las tarjetas de la pantalla principal o el Centro de control, puede experimentar efectos de respuesta</feature>
             <feature>• Ahora, los temas incluyen nuevos estilos, como Luminous. Tras conectarse a internet, vaya a Ajustes > Pantalla principal y estilo > Temas y seleccione el tema deseado</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Explorar la pantalla principal">
             <feature>• La tarjeta de control de medios cuenta con una barra de progreso, lo que le permite ajustar fácilmente la reproducción</feature>
             <feature>• Puede deslizar horizontalmente desde cualquier parte del Centro de control para cambiar rápidamente al Centro de notificaciones</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Creación de elementos multimedia">
			 <feature>• Puede personalizar las funciones que se muestran en la barra de estado de la Cámara. Habilite esta función en: Cámara > Ajustes > Personalizar barra superior</feature>
             <feature>• Ahora puede explorar vídeos rápidamente y localizar fácilmente fotogramas específicos en Galería</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Instale HONOR WorkStation en su ordenador macOS o Windows para transferir fácilmente imágenes, vídeos y archivos entre su dispositivo Honor y el ordenador</feature>
             <feature>• La nueva proyección Cast+ ofrece una experiencia de transmisión de alta calidad y baja latencia</feature>
             <feature>• Puede compartir su zona Wi-Fi mientras su dispositivo está en modo de duplicación de pantalla</feature>
             <feature>• La clonación por cable OTG con dispositivos iOS permite transferir más elementos de datos</feature>
             <feature>• La función Clonación de dispositivo permite migrar contactos, imágenes y vídeos con HarmonyOS NEXT</feature>
             <feature>• OneTap permite la transferencia de archivos fluida entre tabletas y teléfonos Honor, combinando velocidad con facilidad y diversión. Pruébelo en: Ajustes > Más conexiones > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. El proceso de descarga e instalación de la nueva versión consumirá algo de energía de la batería y provocará un ligero calentamiento, lo cual es normal
2. Durante el reinicio después de la instalación, se realizarán algunas optimizaciones del sistema, que se espera que tarden entre 1 y 3 minutos. Tenga paciencia
3. Una vez completada la actualización, algunas optimizaciones del sistema se realizarán automáticamente en segundo plano. Durante este periodo, el dispositivo puede experimentar un mayor consumo de energía y un ligero calentamiento, que es un fenómeno normal. Volverá a su estado habitual en un día
4. Algunas aplicaciones de terceros pueden no ser compatibles con Android 16 y pueden funcionar mal después de la actualización (como generación de errores, retrasos, consumo de energía anormal). Actualice sus aplicaciones a la última versión en la Tienda de aplicaciones. Si los problemas persisten, espere las próximas actualizaciones de la aplicación y actualícela de manera oportuna
5. Asegúrese de que su dispositivo tenga más de 10 GB de espacio de almacenamiento libre. De lo contrario, la actualización puede fallar (vaya a Ajustes > Almacenamiento para comprobar el espacio de almacenamiento)
6. Esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar
7. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de Honor o diríjase al centro de servicios al cliente de Honor para obtener ayuda</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="21514" name="es-us">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización mejora principalmente el rendimiento del sistema. Actualice para disfrutar de las mejoras</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fluidez">
             <feature>• La nueva interfaz del motor de rendimiento Turbo X hace visible la optimización</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Comodidad">
             <feature>• La carga y la grabación de pantalla se integran en Magic Capsule para ver el estado en tiempo real y acceder rápidamente</feature>
             <feature>• Permite tomar una captura de pantalla que incluya una ventana flotante y seleccionar su área en un solo paso</feature>
			 <feature>• La función de alivio de mareo por movimiento ahora incluye activación automática durante la conducción y permite personalizar el color del punto. Puede probar esta función en: Ajustes > Funciones de accesibilidad > Alivio del mareo por movimiento</feature>
             <feature>• Más aplicaciones admiten orientación horizontal</feature>
             <feature>• Permite explorar videos rápidamente y ubicar fotogramas específicos en Galería</feature>
             <feature>• Mejora la visualización de íconos de notificación de apps de terceros en la barra de estado para un aspecto más uniforme</feature>
             <feature>• Optimiza la experiencia inmersiva de la barra de navegación en ciertas aplicaciones</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Nueva interacción">
             <feature>• El diseño de interfaz actualizado ofrece una apariencia renovada del sistema</feature>
             <feature>• El Centro de control renovado incluye fondo oscuro para mejorar la jerarquía visual e íconos coloridos para una interfaz más vibrante. También admite ajustes personalizados para mejorar la experiencia de uso</feature>
             <feature>• Al presionar tarjetas de la pantalla principal o el Centro de control, se activan efectos de respuesta</feature>
             <feature>• Temas ahora incluye nuevos estilos como Luminous Después de conectarse a internet, vaya a Ajustes > Pantalla principal y estilo > Temas y seleccione el tema</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Explore la pantalla de inicio">
             <feature>• La tarjeta de control multimedia incluye una barra de progreso para ajustar la reproducción fácilmente</feature>
             <feature>• Se puede deslizar horizontalmente desde cualquier parte del Centro de control para cambiar rápidamente al Centro de notificaciones</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Creación de elementos multimedia">
			 <feature>• Puede personalizar las funciones que se muestran en la barra de estado de la Cámara. Habilite esta función desde: Cámara > Ajustes > Personalizar barra de estado</feature>
             <feature>• Ahora es posible explorar videos rápidamente y localizar fotogramas específicos en la Galería</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Conecta con Honor">
             <feature>• Instale HONOR WorkStation en su computadora macOS o Windows para transferir fácilmente imágenes, videos y archivos entre su dispositivo Honor y la computadora</feature>
             <feature>• La nueva proyección Cast+ ofrece transmisión de alta calidad y baja latencia</feature>
             <feature>• Puede compartir su zona Wi-Fi mientras el dispositivo está en modo duplicación de pantalla</feature>
             <feature>• La clonación por cable OTG con dispositivos iOS permite transferir más datos</feature>
             <feature>• Clonación de dispositivo admite migrar contactos, imágenes y videos con HarmonyOS NEXT</feature>
             <feature>• OneTap permite transferir archivos sin interrupciones entre tabletas y teléfonos Honor, combinando velocidad y facilidad Puede probar esta función en: Ajustes > Más conexiones > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notas" type="end">
             <feature>1. La descarga e instalación de la nueva versión consumirá batería y puede causar ligero calentamiento, lo que es un fenómeno normal.
2. Durante el reinicio posterior a la instalación, se realizarán optimizaciones que tardarán entre 1 y 3 minutos. Espere
3. Tras completar la actualización, se ejecutarán optimizaciones del sistema en segundo plano. Durante este periodo, el dispositivo puede consumir más energía y calentarse ligeramente, lo que es un fenómeno normal. Volverá a su estado habitual en un día.
4. Algunas aplicaciones de terceros no son compatibles con Android 16 y podrían presentar problemas tras la actualización (por ejemplo, cierres inesperados, lentitud o consumo anómalo de batería). Actualice sus aplicaciones a la versión más reciente en la Tienda de apps. Si los problemas persisten, espere las próximas actualizaciones y actualice oportunamente
5. Asegúrese de que el dispositivo tenga más de 10 GB de espacio libre De lo contrario, la actualización podría fallar (Para verificar el espacio, vaya a Ajustes > Almacenamiento)
6. Esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero igualmente se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad antes de la actualización
7. Si presenta problemas durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención de Honor o acuda al centro de servicio</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1036" name="fr-fr">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour améliore principalement les performances du système. Effectuez la mise à jour pour profiter des améliorations</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fluidité">
             <feature>• La nouvelle interface du moteur de performance Turbo X rend l'optimisation visible</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Commodité">
             <feature>• La charge et la capture vidéo d'écran sont intégrées à Magic Capsule pour la visualisation du statut en temps réel et un accès rapide</feature>
             <feature>• Vous pouvez faire une capture d'écran qui inclut une fenêtre flottante et sélectionner facilement la zone de la fenêtre flottante en une seule étape</feature>
			 <feature>• Soulagement du mal des transports comprend désormais une fonctionnalité d'activation automatique pendant la conduite, et vous pouvez personnaliser la couleur des points. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Fonctionnalités d'accessibilité > Soulagement du mal des transports</feature>
             <feature>• Plus d'applications prennent en charge l'orientation paysage</feature>
             <feature>• Vous pouvez parcourir rapidement les vidéos et localiser facilement des images spécifiques dans Galerie</feature>
             <feature>• Améliore l'affichage des icônes de notification des applications tierces dans la barre d'état pour un aspect plus unifié</feature>
             <feature>• Optimise l'expérience immersive de la barre de navigation dans certaines applications</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Nouvelle interaction">
             <feature>• La mise à niveau du design de l'interface offre un nouvel aspect au système d'exploitation</feature>
             <feature>• Le Centre de contrôle actualisé comprend un arrière-plan sombre pour améliorer la hiérarchie visuelle et des icônes colorées pour une interface plus dynamique. Il prend également en charge les ajustements personnalisés pour une meilleure expérience utilisateur</feature>
             <feature>• Lorsque vous appuyez sur les cartes de l'écran d'accueil ou le Centre de contrôle, vous pouvez constater des effets réactifs</feature>
             <feature>• Thèmes comprend désormais de nouveaux styles, tels que Lumineux. Après vous être connecté à Internet, accédez à Paramètres > Écran d'accueil et style > Thèmes, puis sélectionnez le thème souhaité</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Découvrez l'écran d'accueil">
             <feature>• La carte de contrôle multimédia comprend une barre de progression, vous permettant d'ajuster facilement la lecture</feature>
             <feature>• Vous pouvez faire glisser horizontalement depuis n'importe où dans le Centre de contrôle pour basculer rapidement sur le Centre de notifications</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Création de médias">
			 <feature>• Vous pouvez personnaliser les fonctions affichées dans la barre d'état d'Appareil photo. Activez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Appareil photo > Paramètres > Personnaliser la barre d'état</feature>
             <feature>• Vous pouvez désormais parcourir rapidement les vidéos et localiser facilement des images spécifiques dans Galerie</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Installez HONOR WorkStation sur votre ordinateur macOS ou Windows pour transférer facilement des images, des vidéos et des fichiers entre votre appareil Honor et l'ordinateur</feature>
             <feature>• La nouvelle projection Cast+ offre une expérience de projection de haute qualité et à faible latence</feature>
             <feature>• Vous pouvez partager votre point d'accès pendant que votre appareil est en mode miroir d'écran</feature>
             <feature>• Le clonage filaire OTG avec les appareils iOS permet de transférer plus d'éléments de données</feature>
             <feature>• Device Clone prend en charge la migration des contacts, des images et des vidéos avec HarmonyOS NEXT</feature>
             <feature>• OneTap permet des transferts de fichiers transparents entre les tablettes Honor et les téléphones Honor, associant vitesse, facilité et plaisir. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Plus de paramètres de connectivité > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Le processus de téléchargement et d'installation de la nouvelle version consommera de l'énergie de la batterie et entraînera un léger échauffement, ce qui est normal
2. Pendant le redémarrage après l'installation, certaines optimisations du système seront effectuées, ce qui devrait durer entre 1 et 3 minutes. Veuillez patienter
3. Une fois la mise à niveau terminée, certaines optimisations du système seront automatiquement effectuées en arrière-plan. Pendant cette période, l'appareil peut présenter une consommation d'énergie accrue et un léger échauffement, ce qui est un phénomène normal. Il retournera à la normale dans un délai d'un jour
4. Certaines applications tierces peuvent ne pas être compatibles avec Android 16 et peuvent présenter un dysfonctionnement après la mise à jour (tel qu'un plantage, un décalage, une consommation d'énergie anormale). Veuillez mettre à jour vos applications à la dernière version dans App Market. Si les problèmes persistent, veuillez attendre les prochaines mises à jour des applications et effectuer les mises à jour en temps opportun
5. Assurez-vous que votre appareil dispose de plus de 10 Go d'espace de stockage libre. Dans le cas contraire, la mise à jour peut échouer (Pour vérifier votre espace de stockage, accédez à Paramètres > Stockage)
6. Cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour
7. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la hotline de service Honor ou accéder au centre de service clients Honor pour obtenir une assistance</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1049" name="ru-ru">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Мы выпустили это обновление, чтобы улучшить производительность системы. Установите его, чтобы оценить изменения</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Плавность">
             <feature>• Новый интерфейс движка производительности Turbo X делает оптимизацию более наглядной</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Удобство">
             <feature>• Зарядка и запись экрана интегрированы в функцию Magic Capsule для просмотра статуса в режиме реального времени и быстрого доступа</feature>
             <feature>• Вы можете сделать скриншот, который включает плавающее окно, и легко выбрать область плавающего окна за один шаг</feature>
			 <feature>• Функция «Уменьшение симптомов укачивания» теперь автоматически включается во время вождения, и вы можете настроить цвет точки. Чтобы опробовать эту функцию, перейдите в раздел Настройки > Специальные возможности > Уменьшение симптомов укачивания</feature>
             <feature>• Большее количество приложений поддерживает горизонтальную ориентацию</feature>
             <feature>• Вы можете быстро просматривать видео и с легкостью находить нужные кадры в приложении «Галерея»</feature>
             <feature>• Улучшает отображение значков уведомлений сторонних приложений в строке состояния для более унифицированного вида</feature>
             <feature>• Оптимизирует эффект погружения для панели навигации в некоторых приложениях</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Новое взаимодействие">
             <feature>• Обновленный дизайн интерфейса придает операционной системе новый вид</feature>
             <feature>• Обновленный «Центр управления» включает темный фон для улучшения визуальной иерархии и красочные иконки для более яркого интерфейса. Он также поддерживает персонализированные настройки для лучшего взаимодействия</feature>
             <feature>• Эффекты появятся при нажатии на карты рабочего экрана или «Центр управления»</feature>
             <feature>• «Темы» теперь включают новые стили, такие как «Свечение». Подключитесь к Интернету, нажмите «Настройки > Рабочий экран и стиль > Темы», а затем выберите нужную тему</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Новые функции рабочего экрана">
             <feature>• Карта управления медиа включает в себя индикатор выполнения, позволяющий легко настроить воспроизведение</feature>
             <feature>• Вы можете провести пальцем в горизонтальном направлении в любом месте «Центра управления», чтобы быстро перейти в «Центр уведомлений»</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Создание медиаконтента">
			 <feature>• Вы можете настроить функции, отображаемые в строке состояния камеры. Включите эту функцию в разделе: Камера > Настройки > Настройка строки состояния</feature>
             <feature>• Теперь вы можете быстро просматривать видео и легко находить конкретные кадры в «Галерее»</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Установите функцию HONOR WorkStation на ваш компьютер с macOS или Windows, чтобы легко передавать изображения, видео и файлы между вашим устройством Honor и компьютером</feature>
             <feature>• Новая проекция Cast+ поддерживает высококачественные трансляции с низкой задержкой</feature>
             <feature>• Вы можете делиться своей точкой доступа, когда ваше устройство находится в режиме зеркала экрана</feature>
             <feature>• Проводное клонирование OTG с устройствами на базе iOS поддерживает передачу большего объема данных</feature>
             <feature>• Device Clone поддерживает перенос контактов, изображений и видео на HarmonyOS NEXT</feature>
             <feature>• OneTap обеспечивает быструю и удобную передачу файлов между планшетами Honor и телефонами Honor. Чтобы опробовать эту возможность, выберите «Настройки > Другие соединения > OneTap»</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Заметки" type="end">
             <feature>1. Загрузка и установка новой версии затратит определенное количество заряда, а само устройство может немного нагреваться. Это не является неисправностью
2. Во время перезапуска после установки будут выполняться процессы оптимизации системы, которые могут занять примерно 1–3 минуты. Подождите
3. После завершения обновления будут автоматически выполнены некоторые оптимизации системы в фоновом режиме. В этот период энергопотребление и температура устройства могут немного увеличиться. Это не является неисправностью. Устройство вернется к обычному состоянию в течение одного дня
4. Некоторые сторонние приложения могут быть несовместимы с Android 16 и после обновления могут иметь неисправности при работе (например, сбои, задержки или увеличенное энергопотребление). Обновите приложения до последней версии в «Магазине приложений». Если проблемы сохраняются, дождитесь выхода следующего обновления приложения и своевременно обновите его
5. Убедитесь, что на вашем устройстве есть более 10 ГБ свободного пространства. В противном случае может произойти сбой обновления. Чтобы узнать свободный объем, выберите «Настройки > Память»
6. Это обновление не приведет к удалению ваших персональных данных, но мы все равно рекомендуем вам создать резервную копию своих данных перед обновлением
7. Если во время обновления произойдет ошибка, позвоните по телефону горячей линии службы поддержки клиентов Honor или обратитесь в авторизованный сервисный центр Honor</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <language code="1036" name="fr-ch">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour améliore principalement les performances du système. Effectuez la mise à jour pour profiter des améliorations</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Fluidité">
             <feature>• La nouvelle interface du moteur de performance Turbo X rend l'optimisation visible</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Commodité">
             <feature>• La charge et la capture vidéo d'écran sont intégrées à Magic Capsule pour la visualisation du statut en temps réel et un accès rapide</feature>
             <feature>• Vous pouvez faire une capture d'écran qui inclut une fenêtre flottante et sélectionner facilement la zone de la fenêtre flottante en une seule étape</feature>
			 <feature>• Soulagement du mal des transports comprend désormais une fonctionnalité d'activation automatique pendant la conduite, et vous pouvez personnaliser la couleur des points. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Fonctionnalités d'accessibilité > Soulagement du mal des transports</feature>
             <feature>• Plus d'applications prennent en charge l'orientation paysage</feature>
             <feature>• Vous pouvez parcourir rapidement les vidéos et localiser facilement des images spécifiques dans Galerie</feature>
             <feature>• Améliore l'affichage des icônes de notification des applications tierces dans la barre d'état pour un aspect plus unifié</feature>
             <feature>• Optimise l'expérience immersive de la barre de navigation dans certaines applications</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Nouvelle interaction">
             <feature>• La mise à niveau du design de l'interface offre un nouvel aspect au système d'exploitation</feature>
             <feature>• Le Centre de contrôle actualisé comprend un arrière-plan sombre pour améliorer la hiérarchie visuelle et des icônes colorées pour une interface plus dynamique. Il prend également en charge les ajustements personnalisés pour une meilleure expérience utilisateur</feature>
             <feature>• Lorsque vous appuyez sur les cartes de l'écran d'accueil ou le Centre de contrôle, vous pouvez constater des effets réactifs</feature>
             <feature>• Thèmes comprend désormais de nouveaux styles, tels que Lumineux. Après vous être connecté à Internet, accédez à Paramètres > Écran d'accueil et style > Thèmes, puis sélectionnez le thème souhaité</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Découvrez l'écran d'accueil">
             <feature>• La carte de contrôle multimédia comprend une barre de progression, vous permettant d'ajuster facilement la lecture</feature>
             <feature>• Vous pouvez faire glisser horizontalement depuis n'importe où dans le Centre de contrôle pour basculer rapidement sur le Centre de notifications</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Création de médias">
			 <feature>• Vous pouvez personnaliser les fonctions affichées dans la barre d'état d'Appareil photo. Activez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Appareil photo > Paramètres > Personnaliser la barre d'état</feature>
             <feature>• Vous pouvez désormais parcourir rapidement les vidéos et localiser facilement des images spécifiques dans Galerie</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature>• Installez HONOR WorkStation sur votre ordinateur macOS ou Windows pour transférer facilement des images, des vidéos et des fichiers entre votre appareil Honor et l'ordinateur</feature>
             <feature>• La nouvelle projection Cast+ offre une expérience de projection de haute qualité et à faible latence</feature>
             <feature>• Vous pouvez partager votre point d'accès pendant que votre appareil est en mode miroir d'écran</feature>
             <feature>• Le clonage filaire OTG avec les appareils iOS permet de transférer plus d'éléments de données</feature>
             <feature>• Device Clone prend en charge la migration des contacts, des images et des vidéos avec HarmonyOS NEXT</feature>
             <feature>• OneTap permet des transferts de fichiers transparents entre les tablettes Honor et les téléphones Honor, associant vitesse, facilité et plaisir. Essayez cette fonctionnalité en accédant à : Paramètres > Plus de paramètres de connectivité > OneTap</feature>
        </features>
         <features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Le processus de téléchargement et d'installation de la nouvelle version consommera de l'énergie de la batterie et entraînera un léger échauffement, ce qui est normal
2. Pendant le redémarrage après l'installation, certaines optimisations du système seront effectuées, ce qui devrait durer entre 1 et 3 minutes. Veuillez patienter
3. Une fois la mise à niveau terminée, certaines optimisations du système seront automatiquement effectuées en arrière-plan. Pendant cette période, l'appareil peut présenter une consommation d'énergie accrue et un léger échauffement, ce qui est un phénomène normal. Il retournera à la normale dans un délai d'un jour
4. Certaines applications tierces peuvent ne pas être compatibles avec Android 16 et peuvent présenter un dysfonctionnement après la mise à jour (tel qu'un plantage, un décalage, une consommation d'énergie anormale). Veuillez mettre à jour vos applications à la dernière version dans App Market. Si les problèmes persistent, veuillez attendre les prochaines mises à jour des applications et effectuer les mises à jour en temps opportun
5. Assurez-vous que votre appareil dispose de plus de 10 Go d'espace de stockage libre. Dans le cas contraire, la mise à jour peut échouer (Pour vérifier votre espace de stockage, accédez à Paramètres > Stockage)
6. Cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour
7. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la hotline de service Honor ou accéder au centre de service clients Honor pour obtenir une assistance</feature>
         </features>
    </language>
            <imgs>
            </imgs>
</root>