<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
    <component name="TCPU" version="请自行修改"/>
    <default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
    <language code="2052" name="zh-cn">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新主要针对系统进行了优化，推荐您进行更新</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="荣耀分享">
             <feature>•  新增与 macOS、Windows 互传功能，在电脑安装“荣耀超级工作台”即可互传图片、视频与文件</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="YOYO 助理">
             <feature>•  新增一句话开启省电模式、设置字体大小、设置应用分身、查看电话骚扰拦截等功能</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="状态栏">
             <feature>•  新增状态栏图标自定义功能，可自由选择需要显示的状态栏图标。体验路径：设置 &gt; 通知和状态栏 &gt; 状态栏</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="桌面">
		     <feature>•  新增支持动态照片设置为锁屏壁纸。体验路径：设置 &gt; 桌面和个性化 &gt; 锁屏样式 &gt; 图库 &gt; 选择动态照片</feature>
		     <feature>•  新增视频壁纸，支持最长 10 秒动态效果。体验路径：设置 &gt; 桌面和个性化 &gt; 锁屏样式 &gt; 选择照片 &gt; 视频</feature>
             <feature>•  新增长按桌面空白区域进入编辑模式功能</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="通话">
             <feature>•  来电场景支持配置为横幅通知或全屏显示。体验路径：设置 &gt; 应用 &gt; 拨号服务 &gt; 解锁后来电通知</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="截屏">
             <feature>•  截屏编辑后保存支持覆盖原图选项</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="控制中心">
             <feature>•  控制中心任意位置支持横划切换至通知中心，操作更方便</feature>
             <feature>•  控制中心新增关机按钮，关机重启更便捷</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="通知中心">
             <feature>•  媒体播控卡片新增进度条调节，可随意调整进度</feature>	 
        </features>
        <features module="应用">
             <feature>•  浏览器换新，全面提升 AI 智能体、搜索、网页浏览、交互视觉等体验</feature>
        </features>		
        <features module="设置">
             <feature>•  定时开关机功能可独立设置</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="性能">
             <feature>•  优化系统性能</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="稳定性">
             <feature>•  提升系统稳定性</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="安全补丁">
             <feature>•  合入安卓 2025 年 11 月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         
    <features id="1" module="系统">
             <feature title="">•  优化系统，提升使用体验。</feature>
         </features><features module="更新注意事项" type="end">
             <feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份
2. 更多精彩功能介绍，请访问“玩机技巧”应用
3. 如果您在使用过程中遇到任何问题，请访问“我的荣耀”应用或访问荣耀官方服务网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us 寻求支持</feature>
         </features></language>
            <language code="1033" name="en-us">
                <features module="" type="header">
            <feature>Dear user, this update mainly enhances the system performance. Update to enjoy the improvements</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Honor Share">
             <feature>• Install HONOR WorkStation on your macOS or Windows computer to easily transfer images, videos, and files between your Honor device and the computer</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="YOYO Assistant">
             <feature>• With a single command, you can turn on Power saving mode, adjust font size, create a twin app, check spam call blocking, and more</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Status bar">
             <feature>• Status bar enables icon customization, allowing you to choose which status bar icons to display. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; Notifications &amp; status bar &gt; Status bar</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Home screen">
	         <feature>• You can now set a moving photo as the lock screen wallpaper. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; Home screen &amp; style &gt; Lock screen style &gt; Gallery &gt; Select a moving photo</feature>
	         <feature>• You can now use videos as the wallpaper, with dynamic effects that play for up to 10 seconds. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; Home screen &amp; style &gt; Lock screen style &gt; Select photo &gt; Videos</feature>
             <feature>• Long press the blank area of the home screen to start editing</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Call">
             <feature>• You can set incoming calls to show as either a banner notification or a full-screen display. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; Apps &gt; Phone Services &gt; Call notification after unlocking</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Screenshot">
             <feature>• After editing a screenshot, you can save it to replace the original image</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Control Center">
             <feature>• You can swipe horizontally from anywhere in the Control Center to quickly switch to the Notification Center</feature>
             <feature>• Control Center now includes a Power off button, making it easier to power off and restart your device</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Notification center">
             <feature>• The media control card features a progress bar, allowing you to easily adjust the playback</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Apps">
             <feature>• The refreshed Browser greatly improves the user experience of AI agent, search, web browsing, and interactive visuals</feature>
        </features>
		<features module="Settings">
             <feature>• Scheduled power on/off feature allows you to set Power on and Power off times separately</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Performance">
             <feature>• Improves the system performance</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Stability">
             <feature>• Improves the system stability</feature>
        </features>
        <features module="Security patch">
             <feature>• Android security patch (Nov 2025) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about Honor Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/11</feature>
        </features>
         
    <features id="1" module="System">
             <feature title="">•  Enhances the system to optimize the user experience.</feature>
         </features><features module="Notes" type="end">
             <feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating
2. Discover more information on product features in Tips
3. If you encounter any issue during use, please get support by going to My Honor or visiting our website: https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us</feature>
         </features></language>
            <imgs>
            </imgs>
</root>