<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version=""/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature/>
</features>
<features module="系统">
<feature>•  系统优化，推荐您进行更新</feature>
<feature>•  新增支持响铃/取消响铃设置快捷入口。体验路径：设置 &gt; 辅助功能 &gt; 快捷启动及手势 &gt; 双击电源键/熄屏下双击音量下键 &gt; 响铃/取消响铃</feature><feature>•  新增 WLAN 断开连接、密码显示功能。体验路径：设置 &gt; WLAN &gt; 点击已连接的 WLAN，可断开 WLAN 或者查看密码</feature><feature>•  支持蓝牙 LHDC 5.0 高清音频编码</feature><feature>•  优化部分游戏触控体验</feature></features>

<features module="桌面">
             <feature img="1">•  新增通透图标。体验路径：设置 &gt; 桌面和个性化 &gt; 图标 &gt; 通透图标</feature>
        </features><features module="通控中心">
             <feature img="2">•  新增通知中心/控制中心背景动态模糊效果</feature>
        </features><features module="荣耀互联">
             <feature img="3">•  新增支持荣耀手机与 iPhone 互相共享通知消息。体验路径：iPhone 下载最新版“荣耀互联”应用，打开获取互联二维码；荣耀手机打开设置 &gt; 智慧互联 &gt; 与 iPhone 互联，点击“扫码添加”，连接后即可体验</feature>
             <feature>•  新增一句话投屏功能，您可以对 YOYO 说："把手机投屏到电视上"等类似指令，即可体验 (YOYO 智能体需要在应用市场升级到 90.10.22.031 版本及以上)</feature>
             <feature>•  分享动态照片时，在荣耀分享界面新增动态照片角标，方便识别分享的照片类型</feature>
        </features><features module="智慧多窗">
             <feature>•  新增支持更多横屏应用进入横屏悬浮窗</feature>
        </features><features module="性能">
             <feature>•  优化部分场景使用卡顿问题，提升整机流畅性</feature>
        </features><features module="稳定性">
             <feature>•  修复部分场景下三方应用闪退问题</feature>
             <feature>•  提升系统稳定性，让您的手机运行更稳定</feature>
        </features><features module="更新注意事项" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份
2. 更多精彩功能介绍，请访问“玩机技巧”应用
3. 如果您在使用过程中遇到任何问题，请访问“我的荣耀”应用或访问荣耀官方服务网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us 寻求支持</feature>
</features></language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature/>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>• Update to enjoy the system optimizations</feature>
<feature>• Use shortcuts to quickly turn the ringtone on or off. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; Accessibility features &gt; Shortcuts &amp; gestures &gt; Double press power button/Double press volume down button with the screen off &gt; Turn on/off ringtone</feature><feature>• Supports disconnecting from WLAN and viewing the password. Go to Settings &gt; WLAN, tap the connected WLAN, then you can disconnect it or view the password</feature><feature>• Supports Bluetooth LHDC 5.0 high-definition audio codec</feature><feature>• Optimizes the touchscreen experience in some games</feature></features>

<features module="Home screen">
             <feature img="1">• The icons now have a transparent appearance. Try it out by going to: Settings &gt; Home screen &amp; style &gt; Icons &gt; Transparent icons</feature>
        </features><features module="Notification center &amp; Control Center">
             <feature img="2">• The Notification center and Control Center include background motion blur effects</feature>
        </features><features module="Honor Connect">
             <feature img="3">• Honor phones and iPhones can now share notification messages with each other. To try it out, download the latest Honor Connect app on the iPhone, open it and get the QR code. On the Honor device, go to Settings &gt; Honor Connect &gt; Connect with iPhone &gt; Scan to add, then scan the QR code on the iPhone to establish the connection</feature>
             <feature>• To easily mirror your phone screen to the TV, just say a command like "Cast my phone screen to the TV." (Make sure YOYO Agent is updated to version 90.10.22.031 or above from the App Market)</feature>
             <feature>• When sharing moving photos, you can see a moving photo badge on the Honor Share interface, making it easier to identify the type of photo being shared</feature>
        </features><features module="Multi-Window">
             <feature>• More landscape-oriented apps can now be switched to floating windows while in use</feature>
        </features><features module="Performance">
             <feature>• Resolves the occasional stuttering issues to enhance the overall smoothness of the device</feature>
        </features><features module="Stability">
             <feature>• Fixes the issues causing third-party apps to crash in some scenarios</feature>
             <feature>• Improves the system stability</feature>
        </features><features module="Notes" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating
2. Discover more information on product features in Tips
3. If you encounter any issues during use, you can get our support by going to My Honor or visiting our website at https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us</feature>
</features></language>

</root>